<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Florida State Seminoles &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/college/florida-state-seminoles/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:08:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Florida State Seminoles &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Hubb scores 22 as Notre Dame beats No. 11 Florida State</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hubb-scores-22-as-notre-dame-beats-no-11-florida-state/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877594</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — This time, Notre Dame made enough plays to knock off a ranked team. It had been a while. Prentiss Hubb...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — This time, Notre Dame made enough plays to knock off a ranked team.</p>
<p>It had been a while.</p>
<p>Prentiss Hubb scored 22 points, Dane Goodwin had 15 and Notre Dame beat No. 11 Florida State 83-73 on Saturday.</p>
<p>The Seminoles s (15-5, 11-4 squandered a chance for a second straight Atlantic Coast Conference title, losing out on the title when No. 21 Virginia beat Louisville later Saturday to win the regular-season championship.</p>
<p>The Fighting Irish (10-14, 7-11) had five players score in double figures in the program&#8217;s first win against a ranked team since a 67-66 victory over Wichita State in November 2017. They had dropped 28 such games in a row.</p>
<p>“I thought we had some edge about us to get loose balls and stick our nose in there and take charges, and that helped us,” coach Mike Brey said. “You’re not gonna really run anything pretty against an athletic, switching defense, (but) I thought we did a good job the last two days of practice talking about just opening the floor up and cutting more.”</p>
<p>Cormac Ryan, Nikola Djogo and Nate Laszewski had 11 points apiece for Notre Dame, which had dropped four in a row. Juwan Durham had nine points and nine rebounds.</p>
<p>The Fighting Irish went 28 for 34 at the free-throw line, compared to 15 for 20 for the Seminoles.</p>
<p>“I thought Notre Dame did a better job of being extremely aggressive and hitting the open shots and challenging our defensive discipline by making the extra pass,” Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton said. “Then at the end, they hit their free throws.”</p>
<p>Scottie Barnes led Florida State with 17 points. RaiQuan Gray added 15 points and 10 rebounds. M.J. Walker had 12 points on 4-for-16 shooting.</p>
<p>Notre Dame led by as many as 20 on its way to a 47-31 halftime lead. Florida State closed to 74-70 on Anthony Polite&#8217;s 3-pointer with 2:34 left. But Laszewski hit four foul shots down the stretch to help the Irish close it out.</p>
<p>WORTH NOTING</p>
<p>Hubb passed 1,000 career points, becoming the 65th player in program history to reach the milestone.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles are comfortably in the NCAA Tournament and only fighting for seeding position as they head into the ACC Tournament.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish got Brey a sorely needed victory near the end of a challenging season.</p>
<p>TITLE TALK</p>
<p>Florida State got its first ACC regular-season title last year during its 29th year in the league. A repeat seemed likely entering Saturday.</p>
<p>“Part of the journey of our team is being in a position mentally and emotionally to handle this moment, the pressure to want to play well and win a championship,” Hamilton said. “The will of Notre Dame wanting to be successful against a Top 25 opponent, their will was a little stronger than ours today.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles enter the ACC tourney as either the No. 1 or No. 2 seed, pending the outcome of Virginia’s game. Either way, FSU will have a double bye into Thursday’s quarterfinals.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish, as the ACC’s No. 11 seed, face 14th-seeded Wake Forest on Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877594</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kessler, Tar Heels rally from 16 down to upset No. 11 FSU</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kessler-tar-heels-rally-from-16-down-to-upset-no-11-fsu/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 05:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHAPEL HILL, N.C. (AP) — It took Walker Kessler one afternoon to go from promising reserve to having North Carolina fans — the first allowed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHAPEL HILL, N.C. (AP) — It took Walker Kessler one afternoon to go from promising reserve to having North Carolina fans — the first allowed to attend games all year — chanting his name.</p>
<p>He earned it, too, after sparking a turnaround that helped the Tar Heels upset the Atlantic Coast Conference&#8217;s top team, boost their NCAA Tournament resume and give their Hall of Fame coach a milestone victory.</p>
<p>The 7-foot-1 freshman scored a season-high 20 points to help North Carolina beat No. 11 Florida State 78-70 on Saturday, a game that saw the Tar Heels rally from 16 down on the way to giving Roy Williams his 900th career win.</p>
<p>Kessler had scored 10 points in each of his last three games, then surpassed that by going 9 for 10 from the field with 14 points after halftime. He also had season highs of eight rebounds and four blocks for the Tar Heels (15-8, 9-5).</p>
<p>“A lot of my points were just: I was in the right place at the right time,&#8221; Kessler said. “Had guards and everyone, bigs, just throwing the ball when I was two feet away from the basket, so props to them too.”</p>
<p>Trailing 41-29 at halftime, the Tar Heels shot 50% after the break. But more importantly, they rode Kessler&#8217;s production to better production in the paint while cutting down on the turnovers that undercut any offensive flow in the opening half.</p>
<p>“I do think we showed some immaturity in the first half and showed some maturity in the second half,” Williams said.</p>
<p>By the end, the Tar Heels were knocking down clinching free throws and denying comeback bids from the ACC-leading Seminoles (14-4, 10-3) just days after a clunker of a performance in a home loss to Marquette.</p>
<p>Kerwin Walton added 13 points for North Carolina, which made all 10 of its free throws in the final 2:15 to stay in control.</p>
<p>RaiQuan Gray scored 17 points for Florida State, which went from being in firm control to watching it slip away amid a mistake-filled second half. As North Carolina built confidence, Florida State shot just 32% after the break and committed more turnovers (12) than field goals (11).</p>
<p>“They did to us what normally what we’ve been doing to other people,” Seminoles coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#8220;They had an excellent gameplan defensively, they were extremely aggressive. They were so aggressive that I thought it creates indecision on some of our parts.</p>
<p>“And sometimes you just got to give teams credit — it’s not as much about what you didn’t do, it’s what they did.&#8221;</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles had climbed to the top of the ACC standings by winning nine of 10 since the start of 2021, including a 21-point win against then-No. 7 Virginia. They were also chasing their first win at North Carolina since 2010. But they mirrored the Tar Heels&#8217; turnover troubles after halftime, an unexpectedly shaky performance from a team that has been surging.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re just learning, we live and we learn,” said Scottie Barnes, who had 12 points and seven rebounds. “We&#8217;ve got more games to play. We&#8217;re still getting better.”</p>
<p>North Carolina: The Tar Heels had been trending in the right direction by winning nine of 12 after last weekend&#8217;s blowout of Louisville. The Marquette loss squandered some of that momentum. But they responded by rallying from a 39-23 deficit on the way helping Williams become just the fourth Division I men’s coach to hit 900 wins. It marked North Carolina&#8217;s largest halftime deficit overcome at home in win since February 2006 against Georgia Tech (13).</p>
<p>FAN SUPPORT</p>
<p>It marked North Carolina’s first home game with fans in attendance, which came after Gov. Roy Cooper eased public-gathering restrictions earlier this week to permit indoor arenas with a capacity of at least 5,000 to bring up to 15% of that total.</p>
<p>That meant North Carolina could bring around 3,200 mask-wearing fans in the Smith Center seating more than 21,000. Two fans even stuck around afterward to take a selfie with Kessler, who stood on the court below while they posed from a row of seats above the tunnel.</p>
<p>KEY AREAS</p>
<p>The Tar Heels were shooting a league-low 65% from the line, but they defied that by hitting 27 of 30 Saturday. They also had just seven second-half turnovers after committing 14 before the break, while finishing with 20 offensive boards.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: Host Boston College on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>North Carolina: At Syracuse on Monday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872683</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raiquan Gray scores 16 as Florida State tops Pitt 79-72</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/raiquan-gray-scores-16-as-florida-state-tops-pitt-79-72/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 23:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PITTSBURGH (AP) — Raiquan Gray had 16 points and eight rebounds, and No. 16 Florida State beat Pittsburgh 79-72 on Saturday for its third straight...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PITTSBURGH (AP) — Raiquan Gray had 16 points and eight rebounds, and No. 16 Florida State beat Pittsburgh 79-72 on Saturday for its third straight win.</p>
<p>The Seminoles (13-3, 9-2 ACC) led for over 35 minutes of the game, but never by more than 11 points. Malik Osborne had 12 points and a team-high nine rebounds. RayQuan Evans also scored 12 points, and Scottie Barnes had 11.</p>
<p>Pitt (9-9, 5-8) was able to shut down M.J. Walker, who finished 0 for 5 with no points, but Florida State used its size advantage and reserves to wear down the Panthers. Nine Florida State players scored four points or more. Walker remains seven points away from 1,000 for his career.</p>
<p>ACC leading scorer and rebounder Justin Champagnie had 21 points and 10 boards for the Panthers in his 11th double-double of the season. Xavier Johnson added 15 points.</p>
<p>Starting Florida State guard Wyatt Wilkes was limited by injury and scored six points in 13 minutes.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State appears to be rounding into form at the right time. It has won eight of nine overall, including an 81-60 victory over No. 7 Virginia on Monday</p>
<p>Pitt junior Au’Diese Toney missed the game with an undisclosed injury. Toney is Pitt’s second-leading scorer and rebounder and one of Pitt&#8217;s best defenders. Senior Nike Sibande started in his place and scored a season-high 12 points.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State continues its three-game road swing at Miami on Wednesday night. The Seminoles beat the Hurricanes 81-59 at home in January.</p>
<p>Pitt’s next scheduled game is Feb. 28 at North Carolina State. The Panthers had been scheduled to host Clemson on Sunday, but that game was postponed after a positive COVID-19 test in the Tigers’ program.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868438</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gray, Barnes lift No. 17 Florida State past Wake in OT</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/gray-barnes-lift-no-17-florida-state-past-wake-in-ot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 05:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=864789</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State had the depth and made the clutch plays yet again, pulling off an overtime win. RaiQuan Gray had career...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State had the depth and made the clutch plays yet again, pulling off an overtime win.</p>
<p>RaiQuan Gray had career highs in points (24) and rebounds (12) as No. 17 Florida State defeated Wake Forest 92-85 in overtime on Saturday.</p>
<p>The Seminoles tied it at 80 with under a second to go in regulation when Scottie Barnes drove the length of the floor and made a reverse layup. That set up Florida State in the extra period; the Seminoles have tied a national record by winning 11 straight overtime games.</p>
<p>Gray made all 10 of his free-throw attempts and scored the Seminoles’ first four points in overtime. The redshirt junior forward scored in double figures for the sixth straight game and had his second double-double in a month for the Seminoles (11-3, 7-2 Atlantic Coast Conference), who were playing their first game in two weeks due to coronavirus issues.</p>
<p>Playing without starting center Balsa Koprivica, the 6-foot-8 Gray was often the Seminoles’ tallest player on the court and did a little bit of everything — even adding four assists and three steals.</p>
<p>“He got some tough rebounds,” coach Leonard Hamilton said. “He was our big guy. He stepped up tonight and gave us a major contribution.”</p>
<p>Jonah Antonio scored a career-high 23 points, drilling 7 of 8 shots from 3-point range, for Wake Forest (6-9, 3-9). Antonio had the best 3-point shooting game in Wake history with a minimum of eight attempts from long range. He was 23 of 62 (37.1 percent) from deep coming into Saturday’s game.</p>
<p>Ian DuBose, one of three Wake players who fouled out, added 18 points on 6 of 9 shooting. Guard Carter Whitt’s nine assists were the most by a Wake Forest freshman since Bryant Crawford dished out nine against Coastal Carolina on Dec. 18, 2015.</p>
<p>Wake coach Steve Forbes lamented two missed free-throw attempts by DuBose in the final 13 seconds as well as Barnes’ final play of regulation as the road upset slipped away.</p>
<p>“At the end of the day we got nobody to blame but ourselves for this loss,” Forbes said. “We had ourselves in position to win and we didn’t make the play or the plays that we needed to make.”</p>
<p>Florida State has won 23 straight home ACC games, a streak that dates to a 77-68 win over Clemson on Jan. 22, 2019.</p>
<p>Barnes had 11 of his 13 points for Florida State in second half or overtime. M.J. Walker scored 14 points, giving him 976 for his career.</p>
<p>Malik Osborne also added eight rebounds. Despite being without Koprivica, Florida State still outrebounded Wake 39-32.</p>
<p>COMFORT OF HOME</p>
<p>Florida State has not lost a home ACC game in more than two years. The 23-game league win streak is second in ACC history, shy of Duke’s 26-game string from January 1997-February 2000.</p>
<p>The Seminoles also tied the national record for consecutive overtime wins, matching the totals by Louisville (1968-75), UMass (1991-96) and Virginia (1991-96).</p>
<p>INJURY REPORT</p>
<p>Hamilton said Koprivica turned his ankle in pregame warmups. The Seminoles did welcome back Anthony Polite, who missed four games with a shoulder injury. A junior guard, Polite scored 12 points and pulled down five rebounds.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State could move up a few spots with its return to the court. But the Seminoles are poised to make a bigger move if they defeat No. 19 Virginia and No. 18 Virginia Tech in home games next week.</p>
<p>TAKEAWAYS</p>
<p>Wake has struggled on the road but battled Florida State to the finish. Aside from the cold finish to end the first half, the Demon Deacons played the Seminoles evenly and nearly pulled off the upset.</p>
<p>Florida State played without Koprivica and gave up too many baskets on easy drives. But the Seminoles made timely plays and had too much depth as Wake battled foul trouble.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Wake Forest plays host to Duke on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Florida State plays host to Virginia on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">864789</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wright, Alvarado lead Ga Tech past No. 16 Florida State 76-65</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/wright-alvarado-lead-ga-tech-past-no-16-florida-state-76-65/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=851346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — Florida State&#8217;s winning streak ended when its usually reliable scoring fell flat. Moses Wright scored 23 points and Georgia Tech beat No....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — Florida State&#8217;s winning streak ended when its usually reliable scoring fell flat.</p>
<p>Moses Wright scored 23 points and Georgia Tech beat No. 16 Florida State 76-65 on Saturday, ending the Seminoles&#8217; five-game winning string.</p>
<p>Florida State (10-3, 6-2 Atlantic Coast Conference) had 19 points from RaiQuan Gray but too little offensive help for the junior. The Seminoles lead the ACC with their average of 79.25 points. Hurt by 20 turnovers, they were held to their fewest points of the season.</p>
<p>“I think we shot ourselves in the foot,” Gray said. “&#8230; We’re definitely a better offensive team than what we showed. We kind of let the turnovers affect our aggression.”</p>
<p>Added Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton: “Today our offensive execution was probably as poor as it’s been all year.”</p>
<p>The Seminoles couldn&#8217;t overcome Wright and the Yellow Jackets&#8217; backcourt duo of Jose Alvarado, who had 21 points, and Michael Devoe, who had 19.</p>
<p>Wright had six steals and one block. Alvarado added five.</p>
<p>“It shows how good we are and how good we can be,” Alvarado said.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech (8-5, 4-3) never trailed in the second half and snapped a two-game losing streak.</p>
<p>“We played well,” Georgia Tech coach Josh Pastner said. “It was ugly well but we did enough to scrap and win.”</p>
<p>Gray was the Seminoles&#8217; only scorer in double figures. Scottie Barnes had nine points.</p>
<p>Florida State was denied its attempt to go undefeated in January for the first time the the 1988-89 season.</p>
<p>Florida State and Georgia Tech lead the ACC in 3-point shooting in conference games and field-goal percentage for all games. Both teams struggled, especially on long-distance attempts.</p>
<p>The Yellow Jackets made only 2 of 12 3-point shots in the first half and 7 of 24 overall. The Seminoles finished 3 of 14 on 3s.</p>
<p>The Yellow Jackets missed three more 3s to open the second half before Devoe ended a scoring drought with a 3-pointer, extending the lead to 36-26.</p>
<p>The Seminoles answered with a 9-2 run, including seven points by Gray, to trim Georgia Tech&#8217;s lead to 38-35.</p>
<p>The Yellow Jackets quickly pushed the advantage back to a big lead of 12 points, the last time at 54-42. The Seminoles closed to within 63-56 on two free throws by Gray. Devoe answered with a free throw and a 3-pointer.</p>
<p>Junior Khalid Moore scored two points in his first start of the season for Georgia Tech.</p>
<p>TAKEAWAYS</p>
<p>Florida State fell to 1-2 on the road. The Seminoles&#8217; five-game winning streak included four home games. The Seminoles lost at Clemson on Dec. 29 and won at Louisville on Jan. 18. Hamilton wouldn&#8217;t blame the loss on the lack of road games in the pandemic-affected season. “When you lose a game you can overanalyze this and say it’s being on the road,” Hamilton said. “&#8230; The bottom line is we just got outplayed.”</p>
<p>Georgia Tech&#8217;s big advantage was the solid backcourt play from Alvarado and Devoe. The veterans combined for 10 assists and only four turnovers. Alvarado had six assists and only two turnovers.</p>
<p>WINNING FOR BUBBA</p>
<p>Georgia Tech senior guard Bubba Parham, who averages 8.1 points and had started the last nine games, was away while attending his cousin’s funeral, Pastner said. Pastner said Parham is not expected to miss any additional games.</p>
<p>“This one was for Bubba,” Alvarado said.</p>
<p>DECISIVE FINISH</p>
<p>The Seminoles led 25-22 before Georgia Tech closed the first half with an 11-1 run for a 33-26 lead at the break. White scored the first six points of the run.</p>
<p>“We want into the locker room feeling very good about ourselves and we came out the same way,” Alvarado said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: At Boston College on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech: At Louisville on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">851346</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walker has 20, Gray 19; FSU wins 20th straight ACC home game</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/walker-has-20-gray-19-fsu-wins-20th-straight-acc-home-game/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=833428</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — M.J. Walker scored 20 points, Raiquan Gray added a career-high 19 and Florida State beat North Carolina 82-75 on Saturday for...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — M.J. Walker scored 20 points, Raiquan Gray added a career-high 19 and Florida State beat North Carolina 82-75 on Saturday for the Seminoles&#8217; 20th consecutive home conference victory.</p>
<p>Walker, who made 4 of 5 shots from the arc, missed three minutes of the second half after turning an ankle but returned to hit his final 3-pointer with 11 1/2 minutes left to give the Seminoles (7-2, 3-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) a 10-point lead.</p>
<p>The Tar Heels (8-5, 3-3) were within a point with just over two minutes remaining but missed their next three shots and had a turnover while Gray converted a three-point play and two free throws and the Seminoles went up seven with 16 seconds remaining.</p>
<p>RayQuan Evans, Balsa Koprivica and Malik Osborne added 10 points each for the Seminoles, who were 8 of 16 on 3-point attempts and made 26 of 27 free throws. The Seminoles were without third-leading scorer Scottie Barnes, who turned his ankle in Wednesday&#8217;s win over North Carolina State.</p>
<p>RJ Davis scored 16 points, Kerwin Walton 14, Garrison Brooks 12 and Caleb Love 11 for North Carolina, which made 10 of 24 from the arc but only got to the line 14 times, making 11. Guard Anthony Harris, out since December 2019 while recovering from a knee injury, played nine minutes in the second half and scored five points with three assists.</p>
<p>The Tar Heels had a three-game win streak snapped.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">833428</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 20 FSU tops Florida 83-71 after Johnson collapses early</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-20-fsu-tops-florida-83-71-after-johnson-collapses-early/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 21:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=797505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton told assistants and administrators that Florida could decide whether to continue after standout forward Keyontae Johnson...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton told assistants and administrators that Florida could decide whether to continue after standout forward Keyontae Johnson collapsed and was rushed to a nearby hospital.</p>
<p>Coach Mike White let his players make the call — not once, but twice. With tears in their eyes and their teammate&#8217;s condition uncertain, the Gators wanted to play.</p>
<p>They were obviously and understandably distracted the rest of the way.</p>
<p>Highly touted freshman Scottie Barnes scored 17 points and No. 20 Florida State extended its dominance against the Gators with an 83-71 victory Saturday that came after Florida suddenly lost its best player.</p>
<p>Johnson, the Southeastern Conference’s preseason player of the year, was taken off the floor on a stretcher in the opening minutes and transported to Tallahassee Memorial for evaluation. Florida officials said he was in critical but stable condition and would remain there overnight.</p>
<p>White canceled postgame interviews to join Johnson at the hospital as his players boarded a bus for the two-hour trip back to Gainesville. Johnson&#8217;s parents were flying in from Virginia to be with their son.</p>
<p>Whether the game should have resumed surely will be debated. White let his players chose both times — moments after Johnson left the court and then again at halftime.</p>
<p>“Whatever they thought was in the best interest of their team, then I would accept it,” Hamilton said. &#8220;My administration asked me and I told them we would be OK with whatever they decided. It was my understanding that they wanted to play.”</p>
<p>Johnson, a junior from Norfolk, Virginia, had just dunked in transition a couple of minutes before he crumpled to the hardwood as the team broke its huddle. The Gators were emotional wrecks as they watch the situation unfold, and a couple of them buried their faces in towels as White gathered his team in prayer.</p>
<p>Several Seminoles were in tears as well and took a knee to do the same.</p>
<p>“Those types of things can affect you in some adverse ways,” Hamilton said. &#8220;We’re just all hopeful and praying that he’s OK. If it affected our players in an emotional way, I can imagine what the situation was with his teammates.”</p>
<p>Officials gave both teams extra time to regroup before restarting. The Gators weren’t the same afterward.</p>
<p>Florida (3-1) was ahead 11-3 following Johnson’s dunk. The Seminoles (3-0) scored the next seven points and pulled away from there. They outscored the Gators 42-24 in the first half after Johnson was stricken.</p>
<p>The Seminoles led by as many as 18 in the second half. They ended up extending their winning streak against Florida to seven games, tying the longest by either team in the series. They also stretched their winning streak against nonconference opponents at home to 41 and won their 26th straight at home.</p>
<p>Barnes, Anthony Polite and M.J. Walker made this one look easy most of the day. Barnes, the top-rated recruit of Hamilton’s tenure in Tallahassee, had two thunderous dunks and was 7-of-10 shooting. It was a breakout game for the 6-foot-9 point guard many expect to be an NBA lottery pick.</p>
<p>“There’s no doubt that he showed potential,&#8221; Hamilton said. “He’s showing that he has the ability that we always knew he had. He made pretty good decisions with the ball and he did some athletic things. But as a team we have to get a little better all on the same page so that we could all be a little bit better in sync than we were.”</p>
<p>Polite hit three 3-pointers and finished with 14 points. Walker was perfect from the free-throw line, draining all 12 attempts, and ended up with 17 points.</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Scottie Lewis, who was clearly affected by Johnson’s ordeal, tied a career high with 19 points. Tre Mann added 17 points, eight rebounds and seven assists.</p>
<p>The Gators got little from anyone else. Johnson surely would have been a factor. He averaged a team-high 14 points last season to go along with 7.1 rebounds. He also led the Gators with 38 steals. He had five points in four minutes Saturday.</p>
<p>Like many of his teammates, Johnson tested positive for COVID-19 during the summer. The coronavirus can lead to myocarditis, a viral infection of the heart muscle, and it is common for athletes. At its most severe, myocarditis can lead to sudden cardiac arrest and has been a documented cause of death for young, otherwise healthy athletes.</p>
<p>The Southeastern Conference mandates strict protocols, including rigorous heart testing, before players can be cleared to return to play following positive COVID tests.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: It’s impossible to know how the Gators would have played with Johnson on the floor more than just a few minutes.</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles, who were ranked No. 4 in the country when the coronavirus pandemic ended the 2019-20 postseason, should be a factor in the Atlantic Coast Conference again this year. They have the fourth-biggest team in the country, a dynamic point guard in Barnes and an experienced leader in Walker.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: Hosts North Florida on Wednesday night. The Gators have won all nine meetings between the teams.</p>
<p>Florida State: Begins Atlantic Coast Conference play against Georgia Tech on Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">797505</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>2nd straight postponement for FSU; Ohio State on pause</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/2nd-straight-postponement-for-fsu-ohio-state-on-pause/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 17:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=787197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) — Florida State had a home football game postponed on the day it was to be played for the second straight week, and Ohio...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) — Florida State had a home football game postponed on the day it was to be played for the second straight week, and Ohio State officials said it was impossible to say when the third-ranked Buckeyes could get back on the field as they deal with a COVID-19 outbreak.</p>
<p>The Atlantic Coast Conference announced Saturday the Seminoles&#8217; game against Virginia would not be played because of COVID-19 issues within Florida State’s program. The game was to have started at 8 p.m. EST.</p>
<p>Florida State athletic director David Coburn said after one positive test on Friday night, contact tracing — along with previous opt-outs and injuries — left the team with only 44 scholarship players and some position groups “almost entirely depleted.”</p>
<p>“We deeply regret that many Florida State and Virginia fans have already traveled to the game as well as Virginia&#8217;s team,” Coburn said. “We simply had no way of knowing we would not be playing until this morning. We made every effort to play, but we could not do so in a way that was safe for the players.”</p>
<p>Ohio State postponed its Saturday game at Illinois on Friday night after an increase in COVID-19 cases in the program.</p>
<p>The Big Ten has two thresholds that could trigger a team to pause activities related to the percentage of positive tests and the percentage of people within the program who are positive.</p>
<p>Ohio State team doctor Jim Borchers said only one of those thresholds was met. The percentage of people who are currently positive in the Buckeyes’ program is more than 7.5%. The total number of people a school can designate as being a Tier 1 member of the program is 170.</p>
<p>“Could we have played? Sure,&#8221; Ohio State athletic director Gene Smith said Saturday. &#8220;Was it the right thing to play? No.”</p>
<p>Smith said there was no way to predict when Ohio State could return to practice for its game next Saturday at Michigan State.</p>
<p>The Buckeyes (4-0) are in danger of not playing the minimum number of games required to be eligible for the Big Ten championship game.</p>
<p>In the Mountain West, San Jose State at Boise State was also canceled Saturday morning as was UTEP at Rice shortly before the scheduled kickoff between the Conference USA teams.</p>
<p>Last week, Florida State’s game against Clemson was called off a few hours before a noon start because medical personnel from each school could not agree on whether it was safe to proceed.</p>
<p>Clemson wanted to play after a player who traveled with the team to Tallahassee, Florida, tested positive, but Florida State officials did not want to go ahead with the game.</p>
<p>The decision infuriated Clemson coach Dabo Swinney, who insisted his program had followed protocols and said Florida State used COVID-19 as an excuse to call off a game in which the Tigers were a five-touchdown favorite.</p>
<p>The ACC&#8217;s testing protocol requires the final test of players to be done within 24 hours of kickoff.</p>
<p>Florida State&#8217;s game against Clemson has not yet been rescheduled, though Dec. 12 would be the logical date, with Clemson on the road to playing in the conference title game on Dec. 19.</p>
<p>The Seminoles are scheduled to play next week at Duke.</p>
<p>Across major college football, 17 of 58 games scheduled for this weekend have been postponed or canceled.</p>
<p>Elsewhere Saturday, the start of the Rice-UTEP football game in Houston was delayed because of a second round of virus testing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">787197</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pickett returns to help Pitt snap skid, defeat Florida St.</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/pickett-returns-to-help-pitt-snap-skid-defeat-florida-st/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 02:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=775051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Kenny Pickett knew he would miss some games with an ankle injury. But he also had a recovery plan and intended...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Kenny Pickett knew he would miss some games with an ankle injury. But he also had a recovery plan and intended to be back in time to face Florida State.</p>
<p>His return was just the spark Pittsburgh needed.</p>
<p>Nick Patti had two touchdown runs, Pickett added a 10-yard TD run and the Panthers capitalized on short fields to defeat Florida State 41-17 on Saturday night, snapping a four-game losing streak.</p>
<p>Pickett returned to the starting lineup after missing two games, losses to top-15 teams Miami and Notre Dame. The senior completed 21 of 27 passes for 210 yards, connecting with freshman Jordan Addison a season-high 11 times for 127 yards.</p>
<p>“I’m just not at 100 percent yet,” Pickett said. “I had this game circled after it happened, I kind of knew this was the game where it would come back or at least plan to come back. A credit to our training staff and doctors. I was pretty much living with those guys to this moment. A lot of hard work went into it and it’s just great to be back.”</p>
<p>Pickett said he was watching Florida State film, preparing for this game during the bye last week. With Pitt on the goal line twice in the first half, he yielded to Patti for touchdown runs from 1 and 2 yards for Pittsburgh (4-4, 3-4 Atlantic Coast Conference). But Pickett was efficient and showed little effects from the ankle injury.</p>
<p>“Kenny Pickett is a tough, tough son of a gun,” Pitt coach Pat Narduzzi said. “I didn’t even know if he was going to go or not. He did go and he played hard. Obviously, he had a heavily taped up, braced ankle, but he’s my MVP. Our offense ticks when he’s out there.”</p>
<p>Florida State’s offense stopped ticking and was scoreless in the second half for a third straight game. Jordan Travis had an 88-yard TD run, but Florida State (2-5, 1-5) couldn’t generate much of a rushing attack otherwise, accumulating just 58 yards on their other 34 carries.</p>
<p>Travis left the game at halftime with an undisclosed injury. Freshman Chubba Purdy came off the bench and completed 12 of 21 passes for 38 yards, including an interception.</p>
<p>The Panthers scored four touchdowns with the benefit of short fields, completing drives of 32, 41, 47 and 20 yards. Two interceptions as well as a pair of fourth-down stops helped Pitt’s offense.</p>
<p>“That’s all the difference in the world when you give your offense a short field to work with,” Narduzzi said. “The offense did a heck of a job, the run game, the pass game, we put it all together.”</p>
<p>Brandon Hill also had a 50-yard interception return for a touchdown in the fourth quarter, the Panthers’ third pick of the game.</p>
<p>SirVocea Dennis had two of Pitt’s seven sacks, which matched a season-best for the Panthers. Pitt also had seven sacks against Syracuse and Louisville.</p>
<p>Pitt’s defensive pressure coupled with the turnovers forced Florida State coach Mike Norvell to go for it on fourth down, with the Seminoles converting just 1 of 3 chances.</p>
<p>“We put the defense in some really bad situations tonight with field position and some turnovers,” Norvell said. “Right now we’re not at that place within our program where we’re able to overcome the negatives that are showing up there offensively.”</p>
<p>ADDING UP FOR ADDISON</p>
<p>Addison came into the day tied for second in the ACC in receptions. He now has 52 catches for 611 yards, which extends his team lead in both categories. It was the most catches by a Pitt freshman since Tyler Boyd in 2013 against Georgia Tech.</p>
<p>SHORTHANDED DEFENSE</p>
<p>Florida State was playing shorthanded on defense without preseason All-American tackle Marvin Wilson. The Seminoles were also without defensive backs Hamsah Nasirildeen, Renardo Green and Travis Jay.</p>
<p>TAKEAWAYS</p>
<p>Pittsburgh had struggled on the ground this season but was balanced on offense and had 148 yards rushing on 37 carries.</p>
<p>Florida State had been averaging 197 yards rushing per game but couldn’t get a ground game going against one of the nation’s top-5 rush defenses.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Pittsburgh will play at Georgia Tech on Saturday.</p>
<p>Florida State will play at NC State on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">775051</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hawkins fuels Louisville in 48-16 rout of Florida St.</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hawkins-fuels-louisville-in-48-16-rout-of-florida-st/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 01:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=766667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — Javian Hawkins ran for a season-best 174 yards and a career-high three touchdowns for Louisville, which snapped a four-game losing streak...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — Javian Hawkins ran for a season-best 174 yards and a career-high three touchdowns for Louisville, which snapped a four-game losing streak Saturday by beating Florida State 48-16.</p>
<p>The Cardinals (2-4, 1-4 Atlantic Coast Conference) took advantage of a yielding Seminoles defense to amass 410 yards of its 569 total yards in the first half. Five plays went for at least 35 yards in the half, helping the Cardinals take a 31-14 halftime lead.</p>
<p>Louisville coach Scott Satterfield said his team’s attitude hadn’t waned despite the rough start to conference play. He said he’s told the players that hard work in practice doesn’t guarantee them a victory, but it gives them a chance. During the skid, the Cardinals held second-half leads in two of the games.</p>
<p>“Then today, when it all clicks, you get a big win,” he said.</p>
<p>Jordan Travis, who transferred from Louisville two seasons ago, recovered his fumble after a botched handoff and ran it in 15 yards to give the Seminoles (2-4, 1-4) a 7-0 lead just 2:30 into the game. But Louisville responded quickly, needing just 2:01 to tie it on a 9-yard run by Hawkins, one of his 16 carries on the day.</p>
<p>That was the start of 28 straight points for Louisville, which never looked back. After the Cardinals defense forced a three-and-out on Florida State’s ensuing drive, Hawkins gave Louisville the lead for good on a 70-yard scoring run on the Cardinals next play.</p>
<p>Louisville hopes that run can be a metaphor for its season. Initially, it appeared that Hawkins would be stuffed for a loss as he went to the right, but he reversed field and found daylight down the left sideline. A key downfield block from quarterback Malik Cunningham sprung the sophomore, who entered Saturday as the fifth-leading rusher in FBS.</p>
<p>“We just got to keep our foot on the gas,” Hawkins said. “Ain’t no looking back. This is us. We got to be consistent now.”</p>
<p>Cunningham completed 16 of 24 passes for 278 yards and two scores in the victory. Tutu Atwell caught three passes for 129 yards, including a 66-yard scoring strike from Cunningham, and added a 2-yard rushing touchdown.</p>
<p>“That was a talented, explosive offense that we faced today, and we couldn’t slow them down,” Florida State coach Mike Norvell said. “That was not the performance reflected of what I expected, and we’ve got a lot of work to do.”</p>
<p>Despite racking up a season-best 265 yards rushing, the Seminoles offense could not match the Cardinals. Travis finished completing just 14-of-32 passes for 141 yards with a touchdown and an interception before being pulled midway through the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>LOUISVILLE DEFENSE STINGY</p>
<p>Thanks to two second-half stands inside its 10-yard-line, Louisville held a Power 5 foe to less than 20 points for the second consecutive week. The last time that happened was Nov. 18-25, 2017, when the Cardinals held Syracuse and Kentucky to 10 and 17 points, respectively.</p>
<p>ROUGH DEBUT FOR PURDY</p>
<p>Travis wasn’t the only FSU quarterback with a Louisville connection to see action Saturday. Late in the game, he was replaced by freshman Chubba Purdy, who was a verbal commit to the Cardinals before the four-star recruit flipped late in the process to sign with the Seminoles last fall.</p>
<p>The crowd of 11,465 booed the true freshman throughout his time on the field in the final period. In his collegiate debut, Purdy failed to complete a pass in nine tries and ran twice for eight yards.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Florida State: A week after notching a top-10 upset against North Carolina, the Seminoles defensive issues prevented them from building off that momentum. It marks the third time this season, FSU has given up at least 40 points. The offense did the defense no favors as it punted on three-straight possessions in the first quarter, allowing the Cardinals to build an insurmountable lead.</p>
<p>“We made a lot of mistakes today, and we have two weeks to correct them,” Travis said.</p>
<p>Louisville: The last team to notch a victory in ACC play, the Cardinals built off last week’s close loss at Notre Dame and put together their best game of the season Saturday. With a more favorable schedule looming, Louisville could see this win become a turning point in the season. After the Cardinals host Virginia Tech next weekend, their final four opponents have a combined five conference wins heading into this week.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Florida State has a bye next week and will next host Pittsburgh on Nov. 7.</p>
<p>Louisville will host Virginia Tech next Saturday afternoon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">766667</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Williams, Crawford lead No. 5 Notre Dame past Florida State</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/williams-crawford-lead-no-5-notre-dame-past-florida-state/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 04:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=758488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Kyren Williams ran for 185 yards and two touchdowns and safety Shaun Crawford helped thwart a potential Florida State rally...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Kyren Williams ran for 185 yards and two touchdowns and safety Shaun Crawford helped thwart a potential Florida State rally with a goal-line interception in No. 5 Notre Dame’s 42-26 victory Saturday night.</p>
<p>Williams fumbled at his own 32 on the second play from scrimmage, then riddled Florida State the rest of the way, picking up 130 yards and both his TDs by halftime as the Fighting Irish (3-0, 2-0 Atlantic Coast Conference) took a 35-20 lead.</p>
<p>Ian Book completed 16 of 25 passes for 201 yards and two touchdowns and ran for 58 yards and another score for ND.</p>
<p>With Notre Dame leading 42-26, the Seminoles (1-3, 0-3) drove 73 yards to the Irish 5, but Crawford picked off Jordan Travis’ pass with 8:21 left.</p>
<p>“First and foremost, winning is hard,” said Notre Dame coach Brian Kelly, whose team was playing after two idle weeks, one of them due to a COVID-19 outbreak within the team.</p>
<p>“Just to be here talking about a victory is really satisfying given the fact that just about 10 days ago we had 36 guys that were unavailable to us,” Kelly said. “In short order, to prepare our team and have our guys be selfless and take care of themselves and put themselves in position to win a football game today, I couldn’t be more proud of our group.”</p>
<p>The Irish were too powerful despite a solid performance by Travis for the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Making his first start after shining in relief last week against Jacksonville State, Travis hit 13 of 24 passes for 204 yards and led Florida State in rushing with 96 yards on 19 keepers, even with a pair of sacks. He threw a TD pass and ran for a score.</p>
<p>“We’re all disappointed,” Florida State coach Mike Norvell said. “You invest so much time and effort into a game to win that contest. We didn’t do that and we didn’t do (things) consistently enough, even with some bright spots throughout the course.”</p>
<p>Florida State’s Tamorrion Terry caught seven passes for 121 yards and a touchdown.</p>
<p>Irish wideout Javon McKinley had five receptions for 107 yards, while freshman Chris Tyree joined Williams in surpassing 100 on the ground, closing at 103 on 11 carries with a TD.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles, who gave up 52 points two weeks ago at Miami, looked overwhelmed at times on defense. Not only did the Irish offensive line have no trouble knocking Florida State off the ball — little surprise given Notre Dame’s ranking as the nation’s best unit — but Seminoles linebackers other than Amari Gainer often were unable to step up and close gaps. Notre Dame had 240 rushing yards by halftime on 20 attempts.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish offense was often lethal, especially once it stopped hurting its own cause. Norte Dame had five touchdowns and 365 yards in the first half and finished with 554 yards. The damage could’ve been worse if not for Williams’ fumble and a special teams turnover, those leading to 10 Seminoles points in the first quarter for a 17-14 FSU lead.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>The Irish, given No. 4 Florida’s loss at No. 21 Texas A&amp;M earlier in the day, stand poised to move up to that fourth slot, although they are also the lone club in the current top five yet to face a ranked opponent.</p>
<p>GAME BALLS</p>
<p>Kelly presented the game balls to athletic trainer Rob Hunt and team physician Matt Leiszler.</p>
<p>“We couldn’t have been out here today without their extraordinary efforts to get our football team safe and healthy,” Kelly said.</p>
<p>After Notre Dame had 25 players in isolation with positive tests and 14 others in quarantine due to contact tracing on Sept. 28, just two players of note — starting defensive tackle Myron Tagovailoa-Amosa and linebacker Jack Kiser — were missing Saturday.</p>
<p>It was not confirmed that they were necessarily out due to the coronavirus.</p>
<p>ASSAILING ASANTE</p>
<p>Standout cornerback Asante Samuels’ first-quarter fumble recovery for the Seminoles was his fifth takeaway of the season, giving him at least one in each of Florida State&#8217;s first four games.</p>
<p>That count includes three interceptions, which led the nation entering the day.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State faces its second straight Top 10 opponent when No. 8 North Carolina visits Doak Campbell Stadium on Oct. 17.</p>
<p>Notre Dame is home for the fourth straight game to start the season when Louisville visits Oct. 17.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">758488</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Travis comes off bench to guide Florida State rally</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/travis-comes-off-bench-to-guide-florida-state-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=753929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Jordan Travis came off the bench to lead Florida State to touchdowns on five straight drives as the Seminoles rallied to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Jordan Travis came off the bench to lead Florida State to touchdowns on five straight drives as the Seminoles rallied to knock off FCS program Jacksonville State 41-24 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Travis completed 13 of 18 passes for 215 yards, including a 41-yard touchdown pass to Keyshawn Helton. The redshirt sophomore also added a touchdown run, one of four TD runs from the Seminoles .</p>
<p>Florida State (1-2) trailed 14-0 in the first quarter and went scoreless on four opening drives under the direction of true freshman quarterback Tate Rodemaker.</p>
<p>Zerrick Cooper completed 22 of 30 passes for 232 yards and had a rushing touchdown. Cooper, who threw for back-to-back 3,000-yard seasons at JSU, was efficient but a fourth-quarter interception snagged by Florida State&#8217;s Asante Samuel Jr. all but ended the Gamecocks&#8217; upset bid.</p>
<p>JSU&#8217;s Kolbi Fuqua also had a 13-yard interception return for a touchdown in the first quarter.</p>
<p>Lawrance Toafili ran for 99 yards and a touchdown for Florida State, which finished with 256 rushing yards on 53 carries. The Seminoles were held to just 38 first-half rushing yards.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Jacksonville State plays host to Mercer next Saturday.</p>
<p>Florida State plays at Notre Dame next Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">753929</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FSU coach Norvell tests positive for virus before Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/college/fsu-coach-norvell-tests-positive-for-virus-before-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=740821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; Florida State coach Mike Norvell has tested positive for COVID-19 and will not coach the Seminoles in-person this week as they prepare for...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; Florida State coach Mike Norvell has tested positive for COVID-19 and will not coach the Seminoles in-person this week as they prepare for Miami.</p>
<p>Norvell released a statement Saturday saying he tested positive a day earlier but is feeling fine. He said his wife and daughter tested negative Saturday.</p>
<p>Florida State athletic director David Coburn said Norvell is isolating, which lasts a minimum of 10 days.</p>
<p>“We will continue to test staff and student-athletes as we have been,” Coburn said in a statement. “We have communicated with Commissioner John Swofford and Miami athletic director Blake James. At this point, based on our testing this week, we have no reason to believe that the Miami game is in jeopardy.&#8221;</p>
<p>While that game is still on, COVID-19 complications caused more schedule rearrangement Saturday.</p>
<p>Memphis announced that it needed another week off to get through its issues and canceled its nonconference game against Texas-San Antonio that was scheduled for Friday. The Tigers were supposed to play Houston this weekend but that game was postponed after a COVID-19 outbreak among Memphis&#8217; players.</p>
<p>Memphis announced it added FCS Stephen F. Austin on Nov. 21 and UTSA said instead of the Tigers it will play Middle Tennessee on Friday.</p>
<p>In Tallahassee, Florida, deputy head coach Chris Thomsen is taking over Norvell&#8217;s duties, but the first-year Florida State head coach said he still intends to contribute.</p>
<p>“I will remain involved remotely as much as possible to help our team continue to prepare,&#8221; Norvell said. “I’m grateful to the administration, players and staff for their commitment to the protocols we have in place, which have helped us limit contact with others and allowed us to continue moving forward.”</p>
<p>Thomsen has 24 years of college coaching experience and was head coach at Division II Abilene Christian from 2005-11, where he went 51-21.</p>
<p>Florida State lost its season opener at home to Georgia Tech last week and was off Saturday. The Seminoles play at the rival Hurricanes next Saturday.</p>
<p>Norvell, who came to Florida State from Memphis after last regular season, is the first major college football coach known to have tested positive for the coronavirus in season.</p>
<p>Toledo coach Jason Candle and UCLA coach Chip Kelly tested positive earlier this year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">740821</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 7 Florida State tops Boston College to clinch ACC title</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-7-florida-state-tops-boston-college-to-clinch-acc-title/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 03:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=604531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — The banner was ready. So was the ladder. Balsa Koprivica scored 15 points, and No. 7 Florida State won its first...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — The banner was ready. So was the ladder.</p>
<p>Balsa Koprivica scored 15 points, and No. 7 Florida State won its first Atlantic Coast Conference regular-season title in school history with an 80-62 victory over Boston College on Saturday.</p>
<p>Dominik Olejniczak added a season-high 14 points as the Seminoles (26-5, 16-4) had everything prepared to celebrate their accomplishment, which was secured with Virginia’s victory over No. 10 Louisville. FSU will be the No. 1 seed in next week’s ACC Tournament and looks to claim its first championship since 2012.</p>
<p>“We’ve coined our own phrase: we’re new bloods,” FSU coach Leonard Hamilton said. “We’re not going to catch up with the 80 years that were before us. We’re fighting for our spot and our position, the hierarchy of the most respected programs in the history of college basketball.</p>
<p>“It’s important for us because we get a notch on our belt. And we have to enjoy this. But we think we’re just getting started.”</p>
<p>The Seminoles’ first NCAA Tournament appearance under Hamilton came during his seventh season in 2008-09. He now has FSU among the nation&#8217;s top 10 teams and poised to earn a high seeding in the NCAA Tournament, its fourth consecutive appearance.</p>
<p>Koprivicia matched his season high in points as both of FSU’s 7-footers scored in double figures for the first time in ACC play. Patrick Williams had 10 points and six rebounds.</p>
<p>Derryck Thornton scored 13 points for Boston College (13-18, 7-13), which has lost five consecutive games. The Eagles shot just 9 of 33 (27%) from 3-point range and had 19 turnovers.</p>
<p>&#8220;We don’t have a post player left,” BC coach Jim Christian said. “We’re playing without three of our top five scorers. They put so much pressure on you. Obviously wore some guys down. There were careless turnovers.”</p>
<p>HONORING FORREST</p>
<p>Trent Forrest was selected winner of the ACC’s Skip Prosser Award, presented to the league’s top men’s basketball student-athlete. Forrest, who has a 3.43 grade-point average, earned his bachelor’s degree in December and is working towards his master’s degree. Forrest has 1,139 points and is third in career steals with 224, fifth in assists (454) and 10th in made free throws with 334.</p>
<p>CLOSING STRONG</p>
<p>BC’s Steffon Mitchell was coming off double-doubles against Notre Dame and Syracuse. He went scoreless in the first half but had 12 in the second and finished with nine rebounds.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State could climb higher in the rankings after closing the regular season with its sixth win in seven games.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State recognized its seniors and was able to rest several starters on a memorable day.</p>
<p>Boston College shot just 8 of 30 (27%) from the floor in the first half and couldn’t keep up with the Seminoles’ depth.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Boston College will play Notre Dame on Wednesday in the ACC Tournament.</p>
<p>Florida State awaits the Clemson-Miami winner in Thursday&#8217;s quarterfinals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">604531</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dawes&#8217; dash lifts Clemson to 70-69 win over No. 6 Seminoles</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dawes-dash-lifts-clemson-to-70-69-win-over-no-6-seminoles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 23:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=598003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CLEMSON, S.C. (AP) — Clemson coach Brad Brownell had one thought when he watched young Al-Amir Dawes take the inbounds pass with only a few...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CLEMSON, S.C. (AP) — Clemson coach Brad Brownell had one thought when he watched young Al-Amir Dawes take the inbounds pass with only a few seconds left.</p>
<p>“Go,” Brownell said. “Get to the basket.”</p>
<p>Dawes followed instructions perfectly on a three-quarter court-length drive that finished with a left-handed flip with a second to go as Clemson toppled another highly ranked team, rallying past No. 6 Florida State 70-69 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Dawes, a freshman, put the ball behind his back to start the run, then stutter-stepped to get free in the lane before driving around Florida State&#8217;s Trent Forrest for the game-winning bucket.</p>
<p>“I knew how much time I had left and I was just ready to make a play,” said Dawes, who finished with 18 points.</p>
<p>Clemson seemingly made almost all the plays it had to down the stretch after falling behind 42-32 on Forrest&#8217;s 3-pointer to start the second half.</p>
<p>The Tigers (15-13, 9-9 Atlantic Coast Conference) used a 17-5 run over the next eight minutes to get back in it.</p>
<p>When Florida State (24-5, 14-4) built back a 56-51 lead, Khavon Moore had two baskets and Clyde Trapp a foul shot to tie things once more.</p>
<p>After M.J. Walker&#8217;s basket with 2:29 left put the Seminoles up 63-60, John Newman III hit a jumper and Tevin Mack nailed a 3-pointer to send Clemson in front.</p>
<p>And when Forrest hit a short jumper with 8.4 seconds left for Florida State&#8217;s last lead, Dawes&#8217; dash gave the Tigers another highlight moment in a puzzling season that includes victories over then-No. 3 Duke and No. 5 Louisville.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s the first time Clemson has beaten three Top Seven AP-ranked opponents in the same season since 1979-80. Oh, and don&#8217;t forget the Tigers&#8217; first-ever win at North Carolina last month, ending their 0-for-59 lifetime in Chapel Hill.</p>
<p>And just like after beating Duke and Louisville, fans flooded the court in celebration.</p>
<p>“I think we&#8217;ve had several wins through the season, wins where we fought back,” Newman said. “I&#8217;m thankful for the experiences like that because in life, if you&#8217;re resilient, anything&#8217;s possible.”</p>
<p>Florida State&#8217;s desperation heave after Dawes&#8217; basket last-chance heave was way off the mark</p>
<p>Trapp had a chance to extend Clemson&#8217;s 68-67 lead, but missed a pair of foul shots. Teammate Aamir Simms got the rebound and threw the ball into the open court as he approached the sideline, leading to what looked like a Florida State breakaway for Forrest.</p>
<p>But a referee&#8217;s whistle stopped play. After a lengthy review and discussion, Florida State was awarded possession to set up Forrest&#8217;s go-ahead basket.</p>
<p>Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton chuckled when asked about the whistle. He made it clear the delay and confusion didn&#8217;t cost the Seminoles.</p>
<p>“What hurt us again was having the courage to let them go the length of the floor for the winning basket,” he said.</p>
<p>Clemson also sent the ACC title race back into a three-way chase.</p>
<p>Florida State had hoped to take another step toward its first ACC regular-season crown. Instead, the Seminoles joined No. 7 Duke and No. 11 Louisville with four league losses with just over a week left.</p>
<p>Devin Vessell had 14 points to lead the Seminoles, who saw their four-game win streak snapped.</p>
<p>THE BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles, like Duke and Louisville, lost a chance to take control of the ACC against the scrappy Tigers. Shots that fell early for Florida State did not down the stretch in losing for just the second time in nine games this month.</p>
<p>Clemson: What to make of the Tigers? They&#8217;ve beaten the three ACC leaders, yet have losses to Virginia Tech, Miami and Wake Forest. Clemson has been a developmental program and is clearly playing better in January and February than it did in November and December.</p>
<p>NOT LOOKING AHEAD</p>
<p>Florida State&#8217;s Hamilton said his team was not overlooking the Tigers after his team&#8217;s impressive showing over Louisville a few days earlier. “We haven&#8217;t earned the right to overlook anyone,” he said.</p>
<p>CHARGE IT</p>
<p>Clemson forced six charges against Florida State, tied for fourth most in a game in program history. Brad Brownell said since the Tigers don&#8217;t have tall players to protect the rim — their only regular over 6-foot-8 is 7-foot backup Trey Jemison — they must lock in on other ways to slow down opponents. “I&#8217;m not sure I&#8217;ve ever been in a game” where there have been that many, Florida State&#8217;s Hamilton said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State plays its final regular-season road game at Notre Dame on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Clemson plays for the final time on the road, going to Virginia Tech on Wednesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598003</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walker, Williams help No. 8 Seminoles beat Wolfpack 67-61</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/college/florida-state-seminoles/walker-williams-help-no-8-seminoles-beat-wolfpack-67-61/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 23:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=593768</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) &#8212; M.J. Walker scored all 12 of his points after halftime to help eighth-ranked Florida State take control in the second half...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) &#x2014; M.J. Walker scored all 12 of his points after halftime to help eighth-ranked Florida State take control in the second half and beat North Carolina State 67-61 on Saturday.<p>Patrick Williams also scored 12 points for the Seminoles, who have won six of seven to stay near the top of the Atlantic Coast Conference standings. FSU spent much of the second half shooting better than 50% and repeatedly got into the interior of the Wolfpack defense while controlling the glass in the final 20 minutes.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/FSUHoops/status/1231353813774278668?s=20</embed></div><p>The Seminoles (23-4, 13-3) also threw out some zone looks to get the Wolfpack off stride early in the second half, helping them quickly erase the 32-27 deficit and go ahead for good with about 13 1/2 minutes left.</p><p>Devon Daniels scored 18 points to lead N.C. State (17-10, 8-8), which was trying to follow its lopsided home win against No. 6 Duke on Wednesday with another big one to bolster its NCAA Tournament resume. But the Wolfpack shot 40% after halftime and couldn&#x2019;t get to the line with the same first-half frequency, a combination that turned scoring into a tougher test as FSU asserted control.</p><p>The frustration built for the Wolfpack, so much that coach Kevin Keatts picked up a technical foul with 9:21 left after Markell Johnson couldn&#x2019;t draw a whistle on a drive.</p><p>Johnson, who had a career-high 28 points against Duke, finished with seven points on 3-for-10 shooting.</p><p>BIG PICTURE</p><p>FSU: The Seminoles handled the halftime deficit with composure. They shot 44% after the break, though they made 10 of their first 17 shots to take a 57-48 lead on Trent Forrest&#x2019;s basket in the lane. They were up big on the boards for much of the second half before finishing the half with a 23-17 advantage. Walker helped, too, by scoring 10 points in the first 5 minutes of the second half. He was limited to 6 first-half minutes after picking up two fouls.</p><p>N.C. State: This week has been all about improving the tournament resume, with Keatts describing the doubleheader with Duke and FSU as a big opportunity for his Wolfpack. N.C. State helped itself immensely with Wednesday&#x2019;s 22-point rout of the Blue Devils, pushing them to No. 51 in the NET rankings as of Saturday with five Quadrant 1 wins. But with only one more Quadrant 1 game left on the schedule, N.C. State could have helped itself by getting this one, too.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>FSU: The Seminoles host No. 11 Louisville on Monday with a chance to sweep the Cardinals after winning on the road on Jan. 4.</p><p>N.C. State: North Carolina hosts the Wolfpack on Tuesday, with N.C. State looking to avenge a home loss to the rival Tar Heels on Jan. 27.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">593768</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Williams, Walker carry load as Florida State survives Orange</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/williams-walker-carry-load-as-florida-state-survives-orange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 01:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=590313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — MJ Walker took an elbow to his lip and missed a large chunk of the game. But 12 stitches later, numb...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — MJ Walker took an elbow to his lip and missed a large chunk of the game. But 12 stitches later, numb around his mouth, Walker’s shooting spoke volumes.</p>
<p>Walker scored 16 points, including five 3-pointers, as No. 8 Florida State played without star guard Devin Vassell and held off Syracuse 80-77 on Saturday.</p>
<p>“We were floundering a little bit,” FSU coach Leonard Hamilton said. “The game was somewhat in doubt and he put us on his shoulders. He made plays down the stretch. That says an awful lot about him.”</p>
<p>Florida State needed Walker, especially late. The junior guard drilled a 3-pointer with 4:19 left and then another 3-pointer with 2:36 to go — as he was fouled — and made the free throw to complete a four-point play. In a tight game, Walker’s shooting and defense helped the Seminoles win their 20th straight home game.</p>
<p>“It wasn&#8217;t going to stop me from playing,” Walker said. “I felt good. I was still energized. I just picked up where I left off.”</p>
<p>Vassell was on the bench but did not play. The sophomore guard averages 13.4 points per game and Hamilton declined to discuss the reason why Vassell did not play.</p>
<p>Florida State won because of its trademark depth and defense. Freshman Patrick Williams came off the bench to play a season-high 32 minutes, scoring 17 points on 7-of- 14 shooting and pulling down seven rebounds for the Seminoles (21-4, 11-3 Atlantic Coast Conference).</p>
<p>Syracuse had a last-second shot, but Elijah Hughes missed a 25-footer that went off the rim and would have tied the game. Hughes scored 25 points on 10-of-20 shooting and added four rebounds, playing just over 39 minutes as he returned from a groin injury that limited him to 3 minutes in Tuesday’s home loss against N.C. State.</p>
<p>Freshman point guard Joe Girard scored 22 points on 7-of-22 shooting and grabbed seven rebounds for Syracuse (14-11, 7-7), which has lost four of its last five games.</p>
<p>“Our defense hasn&#8217;t been good down the stretch,” Syracuse coach Jim Boeheim said. “We got to get stops, we got to rebound to win games like this.”</p>
<p>Trent Forrest scored 13 points, making two free-throw attempts with 8.5 seconds to go for FSU. RaiQuan Gray also had 10 rebounds as the Seminoles had a 47-29 edge on the boards.</p>
<p>Led by Williams’ 17 points, Florida State’s bench outscored Syracuse’s reserves 41-13. Wyatt Wilkes (eight points), RayQuan Evans (six points, four assists) and Dominik Olejniczak (six points, four rebounds) were also critical in securing the win.</p>
<p>“The quality of our depth really stood out,” Hamilton said.</p>
<p>BACK ON TRACK</p>
<p>Florida State has only lost four times this year but each time has bounced back to win its next game. One of the main reasons on Saturday was the Seminoles’ 11-of-25 shooting (44%) from 3-point range.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State is coming off a road loss to Duke in a top-10 showdown and a close win at home vs. Syracuse. The Seminoles will likely remain in the top 10.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Syracuse: Buddy Boeheim, who averages 16.3 points per game, was held without a point on 0-of-7 shooting, five of the shots coming from beyond the 3-point arc. The Orange shot just 7 of 25 (28%) from 3-point range.</p>
<p>Florida State: Won despite playing without Vassell, its leading scorer at 13.4 points. Still, 10 players scored, the Seminoles had seven steals, and they were able to shut down Buddy Boeheim, who is shooting 39.1% from behind the arc.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Syracuse: Plays at No. 5 Louisville on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Florida State: Will host Pittsburgh on Tuesday. The Panthers defeated the visiting Seminoles in the season opener on Nov. 6.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">590313</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jones, Goldwire help No. 7 Duke beat No. 8 FSU 70-65</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/jones-goldwire-help-no-7-duke-beat-no-8-fsu-70-65/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=587844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DURHAM, N.C. (AP) — Seventh-ranked Duke had just followed a wild overtime win against its fiercest rival by battling through the final minutes of a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DURHAM, N.C. (AP) — Seventh-ranked Duke had just followed a wild overtime win against its fiercest rival by battling through the final minutes of a close game to beat eighth-ranked Florida State when coach Mike Krzyzewski paused on his way off the court.</p>
<p>The Hall of Famer turned back in the direction of the “Cameron Crazies” and motioned for them to make even more noise, seeking even more of a tribute for his young team after Monday&#8217;s 70-65 win.</p>
<p>“This has been an incredible 48 hours for our team,” Krzyzewski said. “I&#8217;ve got good guys, man. I&#8217;ve got really good kids.”</p>
<p>It was only two days earlier that the Blue Devils (21-3, 11-2 Atlantic Coast Conference) had rallied from 13 down late in regulation and earned an emotionally draining road win at North Carolina, a game that saw them rally from 13 down late in regulation and get buzzer-beating shots to force overtime and later to win.</p>
<p>They returned home to face a team tied with them for second in the ACC, one game back in the loss column of fifth-ranked Louisville. And despite a turnover-heavy performance, the Blue Devils did enough down the stretch — a key rebound here, a defensive stop there — to beat the Seminoles (20-4, 10-3).</p>
<p>“Not many teams would&#8217;ve won tonight after Saturday,” Krzyzewski said. “I’m so damn proud of them, man. I wish you could feel what I feel.”</p>
<p>Tre Jones had 13 points for the Blue Devils, who shot 45% and hit 7 of 17 3-pointers to overcome 21 turnovers. Their defense also gave FSU tough looks and forced Trent Forrest to carry the offensive burden for much of the night for the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Forrest finished with 18 points, nine rebounds and eight steals to lead the Seminoles (20-4, 10-3), who shot just 38% and misfired from both the arc and the foul line.</p>
<p>“You&#8217;re going to have games like this,” FSU coach Leonard Hamilton said, adding: “We don’t always hit on all cylinders. This is part of the journey and part of the process. You learn from it and you move on.”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles helped themselves in this one by scoring 15 points off turnovers, but their poor outside shooting (3 of 18 from behind the arc) proved troublesome. FSU also made just 12 of 20 free throws, which loomed larger as the Seminoles found themselves in a tight game coming down the stretch.</p>
<p>“Free throws and a couple of 3s, and the game is totally different,” Forrest said. “Usually we’re hitting those shots. It’s really just a learning stage for all of us and I feel like we’re going to definitely learn from it.”</p>
<p>Duke: It wouldn’t have been a surprise to see Duke look a bit flat considering how much energy and emotion the Blue Devils spent in the comeback win in Chapel Hill — complete with Jones&#8217; shot to force OT and freshman Wendell Moore Jr.&#8217;s putback to win. The Blue Devils played well enough to overcome the turnovers and win their fifth straight meeting against the Seminoles, including last year’s ACC Tournament championship game.</p>
<p>“We were tough throughout the entire game, even when we got down there in the second half,” Jones said. “We stayed tough, got the lead back and just made winning plays down the stretch.”</p>
<p>HELP ALL AROUND</p>
<p>Contributions came from throughout the Duke lineup on a quiet night for big man Vernon Carey Jr. Junior guard Jordan Goldwire matched his career high with 13 points on 5-for-5 shooting &#8212; including three 3s &#8212; after coming in averaging 4.0 points.</p>
<p>Alex O&#8217;Connell had five straight points during a key second-half sequence after FSU had gone up 52-50, then freshman Matthew Hurt went 4 for 4 at the line in the final 11.7 seconds as a clincher.</p>
<p>“Good teams win that game on Saturday, and lose on Monday,” said Javin DeLaurier, who hit two big free throws of his own with 52 seconds left. “Great teams win them both. As our group continues to grow and develop, this was a game that we really wanted.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles host Syracuse on Saturday.</p>
<p>Duke: The Blue Devils host Notre Dame on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">587844</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walker, Williams lead Florida State&#8217;s 99-81 rout of Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/walker-williams-lead-florida-states-99-81-rout-of-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 01:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=586924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Florida State picked up win No. 20 on Sunday, finishing a season sweep of Miami. But the Seminoles also picked up...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Florida State picked up win No. 20 on Sunday, finishing a season sweep of Miami. But the Seminoles also picked up some needed rest for a short turnaround against No. 7 Duke.</p>
<p>M.J. Walker and Patrick Williams scored 14 points apiece as No. 8 Florida State beat Miami 99-81 to win its fifth straight against the rivals.<br />
Devin Vassell had 13 points and Wyatt Wilkes scored 11, knocking down three 3-pointers, for the Seminoles (20-3, 10-2 ACC). Florida State connected on 13 of 26 3-point attempts.</p>
<p>Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton made an effort to rest two starting guards, Trent Forrest and Vassell, with the top-10 showdown at Duke coming up Monday. Still, both were effective: Forrest had 10 points, six rebounds and six assists in just under 24 minutes, while Vassell shot 5 of 9 from the floor and had five rebounds on 24 minutes.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s one of the things that if I could change anything in college basketball, I wouldn&#8217;t want to play three games a week and I would not ever want to play a game with a one-day turnaround,&#8221; Hamilton said. &#8220;I think that&#8217;s tremendously taxing on these young men, and we have three of them (Saturday-Monday games). One was North Carolina, Duke and the other was Louisville. By coincidence. Sometimes that&#8217;s part of the luck of the draw. &#8230; I do think it&#8217;s extremely tough on our guys.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coming off a Saturday-Monday turnaround in which the Seminoles won at Virginia Tech and then knocked off North Carolina at home, Hamilton opted to rest two of his stars against Miami. Forrest had played 30 or more minutes in each ACC game while Vassell had played 31 or more minutes in his last nine ACC games.</p>
<p>Florida State&#8217;s reserves more than picked up the slack. Williams, Wilkes, Dominik Olejniczak (eight points) and RayQuan Evans (eight points, four rebounds) led a Seminoles&#8217; bench that outscored Miami&#8217;s reserves 54-11.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s big,&#8221; Vassell said. &#8220;Our bodies are going through it when you have a few back-to-backs. People are hurting. It&#8217;s huge for people to come in and step up.&#8221;</p>
<p>Isaiah Wong had a career-high 23 points on 8 of 12 shooting for Miami (11-12, 3-10). Sam Waardenburg added 15 points, Harlond Beverly had 14 and Dejan Vasiljevic scored 12 on 5-of-13 shooting.</p>
<p>Wong became a starter in January and is averaging 13.3 points, but on Saturday he was a consistent scorer by driving the lane. The freshman also made both of his 3-point attempts.</p>
<p>&#8220;I thought Isaiah had a great first half,&#8221; Miami coach Jim Larranaga said. &#8220;He was really on the attack. He made some tough layups. He was able to get to the rim. He was able to get to the foul line as well.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Miami couldn&#8217;t keep the Seminoles from winning the lopsided rebounding battle. Anthony Polite had eight rebounds for Florida State, which outrebounded Miami 46-24.</p>
<p>Florida State won 83-79 in overtime at Miami on Jan. 18.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes got a career day from Wong, and Chris Lykes returned after missing four games due to injury to score eight points. But the &#8216;Canes used just eight players and ran out of gas in the second half as they shot 10 of 33 (30.3%).</p>
<p>Florida State: Five players scored in double figures and 13 players scored, including walk-ons Travis Light and Harrison Prieto. The Seminoles also had a 22-rebound edge over an ACC opponent, by far the largest margin for Florida State this season.</p>
<p>STRING OF 20-WIN SEASONS</p>
<p>Florida State has won 20 games for a fifth straight season, which is a school record. The Seminoles have won 118 games since the 2015-16 season.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State has made an argument to move up in the polls on the strength of three straight wins: at Virginia Tech, vs. North Carolina and vs. Miami.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami plays host to Boston College on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Florida State is at No. 7 Duke on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">586924</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vassell&#8217;s 3-pointers send Florida State over Virginia Tech</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/vassells-3-pointers-send-florida-state-over-virginia-tech/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=584091</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BLACKSBURG, Va. (AP) &#8212; Devin Vassell tied an ACC record by shooting 7 for 7 from 3-point range and scored 27 points to lift No....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BLACKSBURG, Va. (AP) &#8212; Devin Vassell tied an ACC record by shooting 7 for 7 from 3-point range and scored 27 points to lift No. 5 Florida State to a 74-63 victory over Virginia Tech on Saturday.</p>
<p>Vassell helped the Seminoles (18-3, 8-2) rebound from Tuesday night&#8217;s loss at Virginia that snapped a 10-game winning streak. Florida State remained a game out of first place in the ACC standings.</p>
<p>The Seminoles led for much of the first half, were ahead 34-29 at the break and held the lead the rest of the way. Florida State grabbed a 60-44 advantage on a free throw by Trent Forrest with 9:25 remaining before the Hokies scored the next nine points. They cut the lead to 60-53 on a dunk by Nahiem Alleyne with 6:23 left, but got no closer.</p>
<p>Tyrece Radford paced the Hokies (14-8, 5-6) with 18 points. Virginia Tech lost its third consecutive game.</p>
<p>Vassell connected on his first six shots from the floor &#8212; five 3-pointers &#8212; and made 8 of 10 for the game.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles have all the traits needed to make a deep NCAA Tournament run. They feature a deep roster (10 players scored), have forced more turnovers than any team in the ACC, and possess on underrated star in Vassell, who has scored in double figures in eight consecutive games. He is averaging 17.6 points per game in that span.</p>
<p>Virginia Tech: When the Hokies don&#8217;t hit 3-pointers, they struggle, and that happened again Saturday. Virginia Tech made just 7 of 30 from beyond the arc against the Seminoles. In their three-game losing streak, the Hokies are shooting just 30.1% (22 of 73) from 3-point range.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles play at home against North Carolina on Monday.</p>
<p>Virginia Tech: The Hokies take on Georgia Tech in Atlanta on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">584091</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wilkes scores 19 points, No. 5 Florida State beats Notre Dame</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/wilkes-scores-19-points-no-5-florida-state-beats-notre-dame/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=581088</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State hit on 12 of 18 3-point shots and the Seminoles needed each of them to hold off Notre Dame’s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State hit on 12 of 18 3-point shots and the Seminoles needed each of them to hold off Notre Dame’s late charge.</p>
<p>Wyatt Wilkes came off the bench to score a career-high 19 points as Florida State held on for an 85-84 win over Notre Dame on Saturday night, the Seminoles’ 10th straight victory.</p>
<p>The redshirt sophomore hit 5 of 6 shots from 3-point range and easily surpassed his previous career high of 14 points. Wilkes played nearly 19 minutes, seeing more playing time because forward Patrick Williams (toe) missed the game.</p>
<p>“That’s kind of the strength of our team,” guard Trent Forrest said. “You never know who can come in and give us that spark. Tonight, it was Wyatt. They were leaving him open. And he’s a shooter. That’s target practice for him. He was shooting with confidence.”</p>
<p>Wilkes’ hard work in practice translated into a pressure-packed game. His 3-pointers, as well as those from Anthony Polite (3 of 5) and M.J. Walker (2 of 3) helped put the Seminoles in front by double figures for much of the second half.</p>
<p>“Wyatt Wilkes gave us a tremendous lift,” Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton said. “He&#8217;s showing his potential.”</p>
<p>But Florida State quickly saw its considerable lead dwindle. The Seminoles missed their last nine shots from the floor, leaving the door open just enough for Notre Dame. The Fighting Irish had a few chances in the final moments, including Dane Goodwin’s desperation 3-pointer that was short at the buzzer.</p>
<p>Trent Forrest and RaiQuan Gray each scored 13 points for Florida State (17-2, 7-1 Atlantic Coast Conference), which has also won 10 consecutive home games in 2019-20 and 19 straight victories at the Donald L. Tucker Center dating to last season.</p>
<p>Prentiss Hubb scored 24 points, knocking down 5 of 11 3-pointers, and John Mooney scored 16 points for Notre Dame (11-8, 2-6). But Mooney pulled down just five rebounds, halting his streak of double-doubles at 12 games.</p>
<p>Notre Dame was able to get to the free-throw line with frequency, making shot 22 of 27 (81.5%) from the line. But Juwan Durham, Mooney, Hubb and Goodwin all missed shots in the final 16 seconds.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m proud of our group,” Notre Dame coach Mike Brey said. “Disappointed though. We had chances there at the end.”</p>
<p>Balsa Koprivica returned after missing four games due to injury for Florida State. The freshman center had six points and six rebounds.</p>
<p>Notre Dame led by 11 points just minutes into the game, but Florida State went on an 18-0 run — helped by Wilkes’ and Walker’s 3-pointers — to take a 47-37 lead at the half.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State may find it difficult to move up any more now that it&#8217;s in the top 5, but 10 straight wins speaks volumes about the team&#8217;s resume and the Seminoles could pick up a spot in the next poll.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Fighting Irish used just seven players and didn’t have the depth to keep up with the Seminoles, who had a 40-12 bench scoring advantage.</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles had a 23-11 rebounding edge early, including eight offensive boards that led to 10 second-chance points.</p>
<p>BREY&#8217;S CRITICISM</p>
<p>Brey was critical of some of the crew&#8217;s calls, especially late in the game. He questioned a traveling call and a technical on the Notre Dame bench.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re treated by the officials like we haven&#8217;t brought football as a full member, but yet we get a full share of the ACC Network TV,&#8221; Brey said. &#8220;Are you kidding me? &#8230; I&#8217;m frustrated, man. &#8230; You got to be kidding me, man. We&#8217;re in the league, too. C&#8217;mon.&#8221;</p>
<p>Brey walked off the interview podium and continued to criticize the officials, specifically mentioning referee John Gaffney.</p>
<p>FORREST FOR 1,000</p>
<p>Florida State’s Trent Forrest scored his 1,000th point on a dunk in the first half. The senior guard is the 48th player in Seminoles history to surpass the milestone.</p>
<p>“All of my hard work is starting to pay off,” Forrest said. “I’m just glad to say that I accomplished it.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Notre Dame: Hosts Wake Forest on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Florida State: Plays at Virginia on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">581088</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 9 Florida State rallies past Miami in OT, 83-79</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-9-florida-state-rallies-past-miami-in-ot-83-79/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 04:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=577663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton admits he was worried when his team trailed Miami by nine points with five minutes...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton admits he was worried when his team trailed Miami by nine points with five minutes to go Saturday.</p>
<p>His players: not so much.</p>
<p>“We hated to put that stress on coach,” M.J. Walker said. “But it’s the ACC. I love it.”</p>
<p>The No. 9-ranked Seminoles forced 24 turnovers, including three in a row in overtime, and rallied Saturday to earn their ninth consecutive victory by beating Miami 83-79.</p>
<p>“I was very proud of the way our guys maintained their composure.,” Hamilton said. “When Miami went up nine, I was probably the only one who was really concerned. Our players kept saying, ‘We can win this game.’&#8221;</p>
<p>Sophomore Devin Vassell set a career high for the second consecutive game by leading Florida State with 23 points while adding 11 rebounds and five assists. His two free throws with six seconds left sealed the win.</p>
<p>Walker played only 23 minutes because of foul trouble but scored 19 points, all in the second half, Malik Osborne&#8217;s three-point play with 2:25 left in overtime put the Seminoles ahead to stay.</p>
<p>“A four-point victory in my mind is an ACC blowout,” Hamilton said.</p>
<p>Florida State (16-2, 6-1 Atlantic Coast Conference), which began the day tied with No. 3 Duke for the league lead, beat Miami for the fourth time in a row. The Hurricanes (10-7, 2-5 ACC) lost in league play at home for the third time.</p>
<p>“We did everything it took to win the game except win,” Miami coach Jim Larranaga said. “We did a very, very nice job. We weren’t able to close.”</p>
<p>Chris Lykes had 24 points but also six turnovers for the Hurricanes. Their turnover total was a season high.</p>
<p>The Seminoles won despite shooting 42 percent and committing 16 turnovers. They compensated by scoring 21 points off takeaways.</p>
<p>“The last few minutes we got some deflections and steals. That’s who we are,” Hamilton said. “During that stretch we were able to turn it up a notch or two, and that really made a difference in the game.”</p>
<p>Not that Florida State&#8217;s characteristically strong defense wasn&#8217;t stout from the start. The Hurricanes had to call a timeout when they were trapped on the game&#8217;s first possession. They blew a dunk, threw up air balls and had 10 shots blocked.</p>
<p>But Miami stayed in the game early with a strong defensive effort of its own. DJ Vasiljevic sank a 3-pointer and then scored on a breakaway to give the Hurricanes their biggest lead with 5:20 remaining, 65-56.</p>
<p>“We came to the huddle and the fans were screaming and frantic, but we all said, ‘We’ve been in this situation before. We’ll get this win,&#8217;” Vassell said. “We knew we had to turn it up on defense. We started more pressure on them and getting out in transition — playing our way.”</p>
<p>Walker&#8217;s three free throws cut the spread to 65-61, and his 3-pointer with 40 seconds left in regulation tied it at 69.</p>
<p>ANOTHER STREAK</p>
<p>The Seminoles have won nine consecutive overtime games, including two this season. Their last OT loss came against Iowa in December 2016.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: Hamilton said he has heard talk that the league isn&#8217;t as strong as usual — and figures his team&#8217;s place in the standings reinforces that perception.</p>
<p>“People say that because we’re not one of the tradition-rich programs — blue bloods or whatever they call them — the fact we’re in this position, something must be wrong,” Hamilton said. &#8220;If the same traditionally successful programs are not in the position they’ve always been, the conference must be down.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m not going to tell you what I think about that. I might get fined.”</p>
<p>Miami: The addition of freshman Anthony Walker to the rotation gave the Hurricanes more depth. Walker, who sat out the past two games because Larranaga was unhappy with his effort, played 13 minutes and had three rebounds.</p>
<p>Even so, three Hurricanes played more than 40 minutes.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Seminoles: Return home to play Notre Dame on Saturday. They are 2-3 against the Fighting Irish in the past three years.</p>
<p>Hurricanes: Play Tuesday at Duke, which won 95-62 when the teams met Jan. 4. It was Larranaga’s worst home loss in nine years at Miami.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">577663</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walker leads No. 18 FSU to 78-65 win over No. 7 Louisville</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/walker-leads-no-18-fsu-to-78-65-win-over-no-7-louisville/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 05:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=571874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) &#8212; M.J. Walker could have spent this weekend preparing for college football&#8217;s national championship game. Instead, he helped Florida State&#8217;s basketball team...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) &#8212; M.J. Walker could have spent this weekend preparing for college football&#8217;s national championship game. Instead, he helped Florida State&#8217;s basketball team make a statement Saturday on the road.</p>
<p>Walker, a five-star hoops recruit who turned down football scholarships from Michigan, Miami and Clemson, scored 23 points and made 5 of 7 3-pointers for the 18th-ranked Seminoles, who beat No. 7 Louisville 78-65. It was his first action since suffering a bone bruise in a win over North Alabama last Saturday.</p>
<p>&#8220;He hadn&#8217;t practiced probably in about 10 days,&#8221; Seminoles coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#8220;He didn&#8217;t even practice yesterday, but he walked through everything.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Seminoles (13-2, 3-1 Atlantic Coast Conference), who were 6 1/2-point underdogs, endured a big game from Louisville&#8217;s Jordan Nwora to pull the upset. The preseason All-American scored 32 points, matching a career high.</p>
<p>But the Cardinals (11-3, 2-1) could not overcome a 55.2% shooting performance by the Seminoles in losing their second straight. Florida State made a season-best 11 of 23 3-pointers in extending its winning streak to six.</p>
<p>&#8220;I give all the credit to Florida State,&#8221; Louisville coach Chris Mack said. &#8220;I thought for, really, the entire game they were the tougher team. I thought our guards got manhandled. They shot over the top of our guards, especially in the second half.&#8221;</p>
<p>Walker finished one point short of his career high. Trent Forrest added 20 points on 9-of-11 shooting, and Devin Vassell scored 14. Those three guards are all 6-foot-4 or taller. Three of four Louisville guards who played 14 or more minutes were 6-2 or shorter.</p>
<p>Nwora had a hot hand early for Louisville, scoring 21 points in the first half. The junior shot 6 of 9 from the floor, but the Cardinals combined to make just 10 of 37. They went the last 5:04 without a field goal as the Seminoles took 39-32 lead into the break.</p>
<p>Walker helped offset Nwora&#8217;s early barrage. Usually a starter, the 6-5 junior came off the bench to score 15 points in the first half on 6-of-8 shooting, including 3 of 5 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>He said the bruise hasn&#8217;t completely healed. He felt he was at about 90 percent as he continues to get treatment.</p>
<p>&#8220;When your adrenaline&#8217;s rushing and then just who I am, when I&#8217;m out there on the battlefield, I want to sell out for my teammates, so I don&#8217;t think about (the injury) at all,&#8221; Walker said. &#8220;When I was out there, I didn&#8217;t feel anything. It just came natural.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida State led 52-42 with 13:43 remaining. Louisville cut that to 54-51 on Nwora&#8217;s putback, but that was as close as the Cardinals would get.</p>
<p>&#8220;They played better than us today,&#8221; Louisville guard Lamarr Kimble said. &#8220;We&#8217;ll see them again down the road, so I think our group of guards will be ready for that.&#8221;</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Look for the Seminoles, who beat a ranked foe for the third time this season, to move up in Monday&#8217;s poll. The Cardinals, who spent two weeks at the top spot last month, will likely find themselves outside the top 10.</p>
<p>HOMECOMING OF SORTS</p>
<p>The trip to Louisville allowed Hamilton to reconnect with his old boss, former Kentucky coach Joe B. Hall. Hamilton served as an assistant to Hall for 11 of the 12 years he spent in Lexington, including the 1978 championship team. On Friday, Mike Summers, a former assistant football coach at Louisville and Hall&#8217;s son-in-law, brought Hall to the team&#8217;s hotel for a visit.</p>
<p>&#8220;I just want to make sure that every chance that&#8217;s available, I&#8217;m going to try to come up here and enjoy those moments,&#8221; Hamilton said.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles&#8217; perimeter shooting not only helped them beat a top-10 team on the road, it also gave them consecutive wins at Louisville for the first time in a series that dates back to 1968. FSU also won 80-76 at the KFC Yum Center on Feb. 3, 2018.</p>
<p>Louisville: Playing for the third time in 17 days, the Cardinals had their worst shooting half of the season in the first half. They followed that up by committing 11 of their 16 turnovers in the second.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State travels to Wake Forest on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Louisville hosts Miami on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">571874</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arizona St, Florida St meet in Sun Bowl without top RBs</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/arizona-st-florida-st-meet-in-sun-bowl-without-top-rbs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=570051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[EL PASO, Texas (AP) — The top running backs for Arizona State and Florida State won&#8217;t be around for the Sun Bowl. Sun Devils coach...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EL PASO, Texas (AP) — The top running backs for Arizona State and Florida State won&#8217;t be around for the Sun Bowl.</p>
<p>Sun Devils coach Herm Edwards and interim Seminoles coach Odell Haggins can live with those decisions regardless of their effect on Tuesday&#8217;s game.</p>
<p>“Don&#8217;t forget that these players that are sitting out actually helped these teams get to bowl games,” Edwards said. &#8220;Some people get all sideways. ‘Why isn’t he playing?&#8217; It&#8217;s the way of the world. You don&#8217;t disrespect them. You don&#8217;t get mad at them.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m hoping they&#8217;ll show up for the game, stand on the sidelines. As long as you play with 11, you&#8217;re OK.”</p>
<p>Eno Benjamin of Arizona State and Cam Akers of Florida State will miss the game after declaring for the NFL draft. Benjamin is in Arizona State&#8217;s top 10 in career rushing, and Akers is one of three Seminoles with multiple 1,000-yard seasons.</p>
<p>The Sun Devils also won&#8217;t have receiver Brandon Aiyuk because of his pro hopes, same as Seminoles cornerback Stanford Samuels.</p>
<p>“I can’t tell a kid to go or stay,” Haggins said. “I never forget coach Bobby Bowden, I had a kid who as a junior projected to be in the first round, ‘Coach, what I’m supposed to do?’ You give him all the information that he needs. You don’t tell him to stay. You don’t tell him to go.”</p>
<p>RUN GAME RUNDOWN</p>
<p>Without Benjamin and Akers, it&#8217;s hard to know where the teams will turn in the running game.</p>
<p>The Seminoles also are without second-leading rusher Khalan Laborn, leaving the likely duties to walk-ons Deonte Sheffield and Treshaun Ward. Redshirt freshman A.J. Carter has 38 yards for the season for the Sun Devils.</p>
<p>“You don&#8217;t make excuses,” Haggins said. “Go do it.”</p>
<p>INTERIM AGAIN</p>
<p>Haggins is finishing his second stint as interim coach after replacing the fired Willie Taggart. Mike Norvell will take over after the Sun Bowl. Haggins is 4-1 as the interim coach, including an Independence Bowl win in 2017.</p>
<p>“It’s just like being a coach,” said Haggins, who has coached at Florida State since the early 1990s. “I’m going out and doing my job. It’s no different.”</p>
<p>BACK IN EL PASO</p>
<p>Arizona State is appearing in the Sun Bowl for the third time in the past six seasons, but it&#8217;s the first for Edwards. The former NFL player and coach is in his second season after a lengthy stint as an NFL television analyst. The Sun Devils are 14-11 under Edwards, with a loss in the Las Vegas Bowl last year.</p>
<p>UNDER CENTER</p>
<p>Arizona State quarterback Jayden Daniels has easily topped the freshman school record with 2,748 yards and has just two interceptions. The school&#8217;s previous low for interceptions with at least 200 passing attempts was six by Manny Wilkins last season. Seminoles quarterback James Blackman leads an offense that averages 269 yards passing per game.</p>
<p>HELLO, OLD FRIEND</p>
<p>It&#8217;s the fifth overall meeting between the schools, but the first since 1984. The first meeting in the 1971 Fiesta Bowl was Arizona State&#8217;s only win, 45-38. The Seminoles have won the past three, once in Tampa, Florida, and twice at Arizona State.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">570051</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 19 Florida State rallies past South Florida 66-60</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-19-florida-state-rallies-past-south-florida-66-60/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 04:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=566768</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State had trouble making a shot. South Florida had trouble getting a shot. The No. 19-ranked Seminoles used smothering defense...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State had trouble making a shot. South Florida had trouble getting a shot.</p>
<p>The No. 19-ranked Seminoles used smothering defense to overcome a 10-point deficit in the final seven minutes and beat South Florida 66-60 Saturday in the Orange Bowl Classic.</p>
<p>The Seminoles shot only 40 percent but matched a season high by forcing 24 turnovers, including seven as they outscored the Bulls 19-3 down the stretch.</p>
<p>“When we went down 10, I thought we became more aggressive,&#8221; Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#8220;Our aggressiveness generated some easy baskets off turnovers.”</p>
<p>The Seminoles (10-2) deployed double teams along the sidelines and near midcourt to repeatedly force South Florida mistakes down the stretch.</p>
<p>“We had a plan to trap the ball screen,” said guard Anthony Polite, chosen the game&#8217;s most valuable player. &#8220;That led to a few steals that gave us energy, and we were able to get some easy baskets in transition. That gave us momentum.&#8221;</p>
<p>South Florida (6-6) lost to a ranked team for the 27th consecutive time since 2012.</p>
<p>“The guys are ticked off because we lost that game, which is good for me to able to coach them, because they are not going to accept the fact that we just competed and hung in there,” coach Brian Gregory said. “They want to take another step.”</p>
<p>With 13 steals and 21 points off turnovers, the Seminoles won despite a poor shooting effort, including 7 for 27 from 3-point range. They also were outrebounded by 14 by the Bulls.</p>
<p>“They outplayed us for the majority of the game,” Hamilton said. “They brought a lot more than we had asked for.”</p>
<p>RaiQuan Gray had 11 points, seven rebounds and three steals for Florida State. Polite, Trent Forrest and M.J. Walker also scored 11 points apiece.</p>
<p>A flurry of nine points in 39 seconds by the Bulls — including a pair of 3s and two free technical foul free throws — helped them lead 57-47 with 6:32 to go. But they didn&#8217;t score another field goal until garbage time with 3 seconds left, and committed turnovers on four consecutive possessions as the Seminoles pulled ahead.</p>
<p>Devin Vassell&#8217;s jumper with two minutes left put Florida State in front to stay.</p>
<p>Michael Durr had 15 points and seven rebounds for the Bulls, but they shot just 3 for 15 from 3-point range. Four of their turnovers came on shot-clock violations.</p>
<p>EARLY DEFICIT</p>
<p>The Seminoles trailed for more than 33 minutes, and made only one of their first 13 shots as South Florida raced to a 17-4 advantage. Florida State missed its first 10 3-point tries.</p>
<p>Xavier Castaneda&#8217;s driving layup with 3 seconds left in the first half gave the Bulls a 31-28 halftime lead.</p>
<p>Trent Forrest&#8217;s layup with eight minutes to go gave the Seminoles their first lead, 47-46.</p>
<p>OVERHEARD</p>
<p>The technical foul was called on the Florida State bench, but Hamilton pleaded innocent.</p>
<p>“I really don&#8217;t know what happened on the technical,” he said. “The ref was on the other side of the court. He has really good ears, I guess. I didn&#8217;t hear it, and I was right there.”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Winning with defense is nothing new for the Seminoles. Four victories have come when they score 66 points or fewer.</p>
<p>South Florida has a .500 record for the fifth time this season.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State plays host to North Alabama on Dec. 28 before returning to Atlantic Coast Conference play.</p>
<p>South Florida plays host to Florida Atlantic on Dec. 29.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">566768</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State RB Akers to enter draft, won&#8217;t play in bowl</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-rb-akers-to-enter-draft-wont-play-in-bowl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 05:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=564323</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Junior running back Cam Akers of Florida State will enter the 2020 NFL draft and won’t play in the Seminoles’ Sun...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Junior running back Cam Akers of Florida State will enter the 2020 NFL draft and won’t play in the Seminoles’ Sun Bowl game on Dec. 31 against Arizona State.</p>
<p>Akers, who ran for 1,144 yards and 14 touchdowns this season, made the announcement on Twitter on Saturday as the Seminoles began pre-bowl practices.</p>
<p>“These last three years have been incredible, and I am so appreciative that the FSU family welcomed a kid from Mississippi with open arms,” Akers wrote on Twitter.</p>
<p>Akers had 231 carries, a career high for one season along with his yardage and touchdown totals. He finishes his Florida State career with 2,875 rushing yards (sixth on the Seminoles&#8217; career rushing list) and 27 touchdowns. He also had 69 career receptions for 486 yards and seven touchdowns.</p>
<p>Interim head Coach Odell Haggins also said senior quarterback Alex Hornibrook and senior linebacker Dontavious Jackson would not be with the team in preparations for the bowl game and instead are working toward their pro futures.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">564323</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State makes Memphis’ Mike Norvell new head coach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-makes-memphis-mike-norvell-new-head-coach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 15:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=561758</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Mike Norvell is Florida State’s new coach, taking over a Seminoles program that has struggled while he was helping to build...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Mike Norvell is Florida State’s new coach, taking over a Seminoles program that has struggled while he was helping to build Memphis into a Group of Five power.</p>
<p>Florida State made it official Sunday with an announcement and a news conference was scheduled for noon in Tallahassee, Florida.</p>
<p>Norvell will replace Willie Taggart, fired Nov. 3 by Florida State after going 9-12 as head coach. The Seminoles, who won the 2013 national title, finished the season becoming bowl eligible at 6-6 under interim coach Odell Haggins.</p>
<p>“I’m humbled and honored for the opportunity to be the head coach at Florida State University, one of the iconic brands in college football,” Norvell said in a statement released by the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Norvell will leave Memphis having posted the highest winning percentage in Tigers’ history. He built on the foundation left by Justin Fuente when he left the Tigers for Virginia Tech and he led the Tigers to the first 12-win season in school history. Named Memphis’ head Dec. 4, 2015, Norvell won at least eight games in each of his four years here and reached double digits twice, including this year.</p>
<p>Memphis wrapped up its program-record 12th victory at the Liberty Bowl Memorial Stadium on Saturday in the American Athletic Conference championship win over Cincinnati. Fans stood and cheered as the confetti flew, including one Memphis fan who kept repeating to himself that he hoped Norvell would announce he was staying.</p>
<p>That never came. Even when asked later about Florida State’s news conference coming up the following day, Norvell deflected.</p>
<p>“All our focus tonight is about this football team,” said Norvell, who appeared emotional while his Tigers talked earlier beside him. “It&#8217;s not about me. It&#8217;s not about anything. It’s about this team and winning an American conference championship. I&#8217;m grateful for these guys and what they put in today, and we’re excited obviously about what we were able to do tonight.”</p>
<p>Asked if he would coach the Tigers in the Cotton Bowl berth Memphis expects representing the Group of Five, Norvell said simply, “Obviously, that’s the plan.”</p>
<p>Norvell served as deputy head coach, offensive coordinator and quarterbacks coach at Arizona State before taking the Memphis post. His high-octane offense with the Sun Devils resulted in 299 yards passing per game in his final season, and an overall offense of 473.8 yards a game.</p>
<p>He brought that same creative approach to Memphis, where he called the bulk of the team’s plays even as he had a different coordinator each season.</p>
<p>His offense became known for its explosiveness, leading to big plays. This season, the Tigers are 10th in the nation averaging 483.5 yards a game – 196.4 on the ground and 287.1 through the air — before Saturday’s championship game. His teams scored at least 2,147 points in less than four seasons — more than seven individual decades of Memphis football.</p>
<p>That offensive punch has led to several Memphis playmakers moving to the NFL.</p>
<p>Wide receiver Anthony Miller caught 32 touchdown passes in Norvell’s first two seasons before being drafted in the second round in 2018 by the Chicago Bears. Darrell Henderson was a consensus All-American who rushed for 1,909 yards and led the nation in all-purpose yards last year before being drafted by the Rams in the third round in April.</p>
<p>Tony Pollard, who was at Saturday’s title game, returned seven kickoffs for touchdowns for Memphis before being drafted in the fourth round by Dallas in April.</p>
<p>Before being hired by Memphis, Norvell was offensive coordinator at Arizona State for three seasons. He started his coaching career in 2006 as a graduate assistant at his alma mater Central Arkansas. He moved to Tulsa where he worked with receivers in 2007 and 2008 before being promoted to passing game coordinator for 2009 and 2010.</p>
<p>Pittsburgh hired him as co-offensive coordinator and receivers coach in 2011, and Arizona State hired him in 2012 as offensive coordinator and quarterbacks coach. He was named deputy head coach in 2014.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">561758</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State introduces Mike Norvell as Seminoles’ coach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-introduces-mike-norvell-as-seminoles-coach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 02:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=561686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Mike Norvell was the first coach Florida State interviewed for its football vacancy and though the search took school administrators around...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Mike Norvell was the first coach Florida State interviewed for its football vacancy and though the search took school administrators around the country, they kept coming back to the man running Memphis’ program.</p>
<p>“We really liked him,” Florida State athletics director David Coburn said Sunday during a news conference to introduce Norvell. “The whole way. This guy wanted to be here. Of all the ones we talked to it was crystal clear with Mike that he wanted this job. And he had other opportunities.”</p>
<p>Norvell said he has idolized the Seminoles program since he was a youngster. He said as a 12-year-old growing up in Dallas, the first piece of college memorabilia on his wall was a 1993 Florida State national championship license plate.</p>
<p>“This is an incredible opportunity,” Norvell said. “There is a tradition of excellence here. There is a standard. Success is coming. There are great days ahead.”</p>
<p>Just a day after Norvell guided Memphis to the American Athletic Conference title, he was on a plane to Tallahassee and being introduced as the Seminoles’ 11th full-time coach, replacing Willie Taggart. The 38-year-old Norvell has agreed to a six-year deal and takes over a Seminoles program that has struggled while he was helping build Memphis into a Group of Five power with what annually was a top-10 offense.</p>
<p>Florida State is six years removed from a national championship and is in need of an overhaul. The program struggled late in the Jimbo Fisher’s era years and went 9-12 under Taggart — including a combined 0-3 mark vs. Florida and Miami before he was fired on Nov. 3.</p>
<p>“I want to be the coach that gets us back,” said Norvell, who after the news conference was introduced to Seminoles fans, along with wife Maria and 5-year-old daughter Mila, during the first half of Sunday’s Florida State-Clemson basketball game.</p>
<p>Though Florida State administrators reach out to other coaches during the search, university President John Thrasher said Norvell was the only person who was offered the job.</p>
<p>Norvell leaves Memphis having posted the highest winning percentage in Tigers’ history. He built on the foundation left by Justin Fuente when he left the Tigers for Virginia Tech and he led the Tigers to the first 12-win season in school history. Named Memphis’ head Dec. 4, 2015, Norvell won at least eight games in each of his four years here and reached double digits twice, including this year.</p>
<p>Memphis wrapped up its program-record 12th victory at the Liberty Bowl Memorial Stadium on Saturday in the American Athletic Conference championship win over Cincinnati.</p>
<p>He brought a creative approach to Memphis, where he called the bulk of the team’s plays even as he had a different coordinator each season.</p>
<p>Norvell’s offense became known for its explosiveness, leading to big plays. This season, the Tigers are 10th in the nation averaging 483.5 yards a game — 196.4 on the ground and 287.1 through the air — before Saturday’s championship game. His teams scored at least 2,147 points in less than four seasons — more than seven individual decades of Memphis football.</p>
<p>While Norvell lacks head coaching experience at the Power Five level, he has been the offensive coordinator at Arizona State and the co-offensive coordinator-receivers coach at Pittsburgh.</p>
<p>Thrasher said that Norvell’s name came up two years ago when Florida State was looking to replace Fisher, who departed for Texas A&amp;M. The search in 2017 took less than a week. This time, Thrasher said officials wanted to “take our time.”</p>
<p>Taggart had just one year of experience at a Power Five school, at Oregon, in 2017. Norvell has just four years of experience at a Group of Five school. And Norvell’s resume is similar to Taggart’s in that he’s an innovative offensive mind, a parallel to what Taggart had shown in his career.</p>
<p>Florida State president said there is one distinct difference between Norvell and Taggart.</p>
<p>Norvell “is a winner,” Thrasher said. “I think the guy has proven he’s a winner. He’s proven he can recruit. I think he’s proven he can bring a program that’s down up. I think he has the passion that I look for in every single person. I believe he’ll bring that to Florida State.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">561686</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FSU upsets No. 6 Florida 63-51, extends streak in series</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/fsu-upsets-no-6-florida-63-51-extends-streak-in-series/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 22:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=551504</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Revamped rosters, familiar result. Devin Vassell scored 13 points, M.J. Walker added 12 and Florida State upset No. 6 Florida 63-51...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Revamped rosters, familiar result.<p>Devin Vassell scored 13 points, M.J. Walker added 12 and Florida State upset No. 6 Florida 63-51 on Sunday, extending its series winning streak to six.</p><p>The Seminoles (1-1) avoided their first 0-2 start since 2000 thanks to suffocating defense that forced the rival Gators (1-1) into 16 turnovers and a woeful shooting performance. Florida was 14 of 50 from the field, including 4 of 22 from 3-point range.</p><p>&#x201C;We&#x2019;re both playing with a lot of inexperienced players, a lot of first-year guys,&#x201D; FSU coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#x201C;I&#x2019;m sure they&#x2019;re trying to find themselves and we&#x2019;re trying to find ourselves as well.&#x201D;</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/FSUHoops/status/1193644029008916481?s=20</embed></div><p>Florida&#x2019;s football team scored more points (56) than its basketball squad did this weekend.</p><p>&#x201C;It can be a big wake-up call and it can show how this team can band together rather than splinter,&#x201D; Gators forward Kerry Blackshear Jr. said.</p><p>A six-point favorite at home, Florida expected some growing pains from a team that features graduate transfer Blackshear, three sophomores and five freshmen. The Gators clearly weren&#x2019;t ready to match Florida State&#x2019;s defensive intensity.</p><p>A sellout crowd witnessed FSU take over late in the first half and really seize control after the break. The Gators went 10 minutes with just one field goal &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; a dunk on an inbound play &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; as Florida State pulled ahead 38-25 in the opening minutes of the second half. The &#x2018;Noles went up by 14 on Anthony Polite&#x2019;s 3-pointer with 9:31 to play.</p><p>The Seminoles made 11 of their first 20 shots in the second half. They also finished with five blocked shots and eight steals.</p><p>&#x201C;It&#x2019;s hard to run offense against them,&#x201D; Florida coach Mike White said. &#x201C;They extend as much as anyone in the country. They deny everything. They swarm to the ball. They put a lot of ball pressure on you. It&#x2019;s hard to run a bunch of sets.&#x201D;</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/GatorsMBK/status/1193616231141560320?s=20</embed></div><p>Keyontae Johnson led the Gators with 19 points on 8-of-12 shooting. Blackshear had 10 points and 13 rebounds, his second double-double in as many games this season.</p><p>Malik Osborne chipped in 10 points for FSU.</p><p>Florida State had little to worry about down the stretch, a common occurrence against Florida in recent years. The Gators lost to FSU by 17 points in 2017 and by 21 in the season opener last year.</p><p>&#x201C;We had a lot of hype behind our name, so it probably got to like some of the players,&#x201D; Johnson said. &#x201C;Me as well, saying that we were a top-ranked team. This game can show us that we&#x2019;re really not that good. We&#x2019;ve got room to improve.&#x201D;</p><p>DISPLACED SEMINOLES</p><p>Florida State players spent the last two weeks living in hotel rooms after a broken sprinkler system dumped 9,000 gallons of water into their on-campus apartments and forced them to evacuate. Hamilton used it as a bonding experience, saying &#x201C;adversity has a way of making you grow.&#x201D;</p><p>The Seminoles certainly showed progress between their first and second games of the season.</p><p>Hamilton credited his team&#x2019;s performance in Gainesville to its lackluster opener in Pittsburgh, a two-point loss that came while players were still dealing with the aftereffects of getting flooded out.</p><p>&#x201C;That wasn&#x2019;t very pretty,&#x201D; Hamilton said. &#x201C;We&#x2019;ve had a lot of moving parts with our team. &#x2026; Going on the road and losing to Pittsburgh probably had a lot to do with why we played so well today. It definitely got our attention.&#x201D;</p><p>BIG PICTURE</p><p>Florida State: The Seminoles are the only Power 5 team to open the season with two true road games, losing by two points at Pittsburgh and then bouncing back against Florida, so coach Leonard Hamilton&#x2019;s team might be better than many expected.</p><p>Florida: The Gators probably were overrated to begin the season because of the addition of Blackshear, the country&#x2019;s most high-profile transfer. They expect their revamped roster to be considerably better and more in sync by the time Southeastern Conference play begins in January.</p><p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p><p>Florida surely will fall out of the top 10 in the&#xC2;&#xA0;AP College Basketball&#xC2;&#xA0;Poll.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Florida State: Hosts Western Carolina on Friday. The Seminoles have won 18 consecutive home openers.</p><p>Florida: Hosts Towson on Thursday. The teams last played in 1988.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">551504</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State loses DT Marvin Wilson to season-ending injury</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-loses-dt-marvin-wilson-to-season-ending-injury/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 13:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=550811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State defensive tackle Marvin Wilson will miss the rest of the season due to a hand injury. Interim head coach...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State defensive tackle Marvin Wilson will miss the rest of the season due to a hand injury.</p>
<p>Interim head coach Odell Haggins Thursday announced that Wilson had surgery earlier this week. Wilson had 44 tackles and five sacks as a junior.</p>
<p>Haggins says that Wilson &#8220;will remain involved as a captain and respected leader for our team.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Seminoles (4-5, 3-4 Atlantic Coast Conference) are looking to become bowl eligible in the final three games of the season after coach Willie Taggart was dismissed. The Seminoles must win two of those contests to after missing the postseason in 2018. Florida State finishes the season with a home game against FCS Alabama State and a road game vs. No. 10 Florida</p>
<p>Florida State plays Boston College (5-4, 3-3) on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">550811</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State moving quickly to find new football coach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-moving-quickly-to-find-new-football-coach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 13:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=549432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State athletic director David Coburn would like the Seminoles to have a new head football coach by the end of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State athletic director David Coburn would like the Seminoles to have a new head football coach by the end of the regular season.</p>
<p>The AD doesn&#8217;t seem to be wasting anytime; he doesn&#8217;t like the direction the football program is going and wants things to change.</p>
<p>The AD candidly said Monday — 24 hours after Willie Taggart was fired — he didn&#8217;t need to wait to see how the last three games of the season went before deciding to replace Taggart because no matter how it played out, a 6-6 season wouldn&#8217;t be acceptable.</p>
<p>Coburn and school President John Thrasher felt they needed to move quickly.</p>
<p>&#8220;We looked at the pluses and minuses, and we didn&#8217;t really see any upside to waiting,&#8221; Coburn said. &#8220;We wanted to go ahead and get started with a search, see if we could get somebody in here ready to go as quickly as possible. Frankly, 6-6 isn&#8217;t good enough, and we didn&#8217;t see an advantage to waiting until the end.&#8221;</p>
<p>While it was clear Taggart was struggling — he was 9-12 in less than two seasons and 0-5 against Florida, Clemson and Miami, including the 27-10 loss to the Hurricanes at Doak Campbell Stadium on Saturday — Coburn said the moment was emotional as he sat down and informed Taggart of the decision.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a rough weekend,&#8221; Coburn said. &#8220;I had to fire a friend&#8221; on Sunday.</p>
<p>No matter the cost.</p>
<p>Coburn estimates it will cost Florida State about $18 million to buyout Taggart, although the details have not been finalized.</p>
<p>Declining season ticket sales and booster contributions were factors in the decision, Coburn said. A season-high 63,995 attended Saturday&#8217;s game and prior games attracted considerably less.</p>
<p>&#8220;We looked at it pretty thoroughly,&#8221; Coburn said.</p>
<p>The administrators and boosters will hire a national search firm to help compile a list of names, and Coburn indicated he would like to have a hire made by the end of the regular season. Among the potential candidates: former Oklahoma coach Bob Stoops, Kentucky coach Mark Stoops, Minnesota coach P.J. Fleck and UCF coach Josh Heupel.</p>
<p>Mark Stoops, who was Florida State&#8217;s defensive coordinator from 2010-12 before going to Kentucky, addressed reports that his name is under consideration.</p>
<p>&#8220;Sitting around here, this is 6 1/2 years and you listen to coach (John Calipari) and every year he is going to the NBA, right?&#8221; Stoops said Monday during a break in Kentucky&#8217;s preparations for its game Saturday against Tennessee. &#8220;You just dismiss it and concentrate on the things that you can control. I am not going to get into speculation. I am going to talk about the University of Kentucky and Tennessee.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coburn did not indicate any criteria that Florida State administrators and boosters are looking for in the next coach, albeit the ultimate goal of adding a fourth national title to the Seminoles&#8217; trophy case.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re looking for somebody that can win national championships,&#8221; Coburn said. &#8220;We&#8217;re going to get back to the standard of Florida State University football. That&#8217;s what&#8217;s going to happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>While the school looks for that person, Coburn has appointed Odell Haggins as interim head coach. Haggins, who has been a Florida State assistant coach since 1994, has worked for Bobby Bowden, Jimbo Fisher and Taggart.</p>
<p>This is also familiar territory for Haggins: He went 2-0 as Florida State&#8217;s interim head coach after Fisher left to take the Texas A&amp;M job in 2017. Haggins was also an All-American defensive tackle in the mid-1980s in Tallahassee and is frequently referred to as &#8220;Mr. FSU.&#8221;</p>
<p>Haggins is tasked with helping right the course as Florida State looks for two more wins to become bowl-eligible. The Seminoles play at Boston College on Saturday and then face FCS Alabama State before finishing the regular season at Florida.</p>
<p>&#8220;Coming up again, second time around,&#8221; Haggins said. &#8220;I think this is a blessing. God put me in this situation for a reason, because God knows in my heart what I think about are our players and Florida State University. Both feet in, both hands. All gas, no brakes. Let&#8217;s go.&#8221;</p>
<p>That currently seems to be standard operating procedure these days at Florida State.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">549432</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State fires coach Willie Taggart after 21 games</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-fires-coach-willie-taggart-after-21-games/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 22:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=548725</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State fired second-year football coach Willie Taggart on Sunday, less than 24 hours after the Seminoles lost to rival Miami...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Florida State fired second-year football coach Willie Taggart on Sunday, less than 24 hours after the Seminoles lost to rival Miami and with the team in danger of missing a bowl game for the second consecutive season.<p>Taggart was 9-12 at Florida State, which won the national title in 2013 and has been in a freefall for the last three seasons. The Seminoles have not been ranked this season, are 0-5 against rivals Miami, Florida and Clemson under Taggart and attendance for games at Doak Campbell Stadium has plummeted.</p><p>&#x201C;We had no choice but to make a change,&#x201D; Florida State President John Thrasher said.</p><p>The school said longtime Florida State assistant Odell Haggins has been asked to take over as interim coach for the remainder of the season. Haggins was 2-0 as the interim in 2017, after Jimbo Fisher left Florida State for Texas A&amp;M in December.</p><p>&#x201C;We still have a lot of faith,&#x201D; Florida State linebacker Emmett Rice said Saturday. &#x201C;We have a lot to play for. It&#x2019;s not over just because we lost to Miami.&#x201D;</p><p>For Taggart, it is over. He will receive a large payday as Florida State owes him a $17 million buyout as part of the letter of agreement he signed in Dec. 2017.</p><p>&#x201C;Obviously, I am disappointed in the decision today as I believe our future is bright and Florida State,&#x201D; Taggart said&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://twitter.com/CoachTaggart/status/1191111509860143105?s=20">in a statement</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;posted on Twitter. &#x201C;Building a program and a culture takes time and I regret that we will not have the opportunity to continue to coach these incredible young men.&#x201D;</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/CoachTaggart/status/1191111509860143105?s=20</embed></div><p>Florida State (4-5) plays at Boston College (5-4) on Saturday, and needs to win two of its final three to become bowl eligible. The Seminoles finish the regular season against FCS foe Alabama State and then play at No. 10 Florida.</p><p>Florida State&#x2019;s 5-7 record last season was the program&#x2019;s first losing campaign since 1976 and it snapped a streak of 36 consecutive seasons in which the Seminoles played in a bowl game.</p><p>&#x201C;I spoke to Coach Taggart this afternoon to let him know of our decision,&#x201D; Florida State athletic director David Coburn said Sunday. &#x201C;I met with the team and coaches immediately after that conversation to let them know of the change. It was very important to us that the student-athletes know right away.&#x201D;</p><p>Only 63,995 fans were at Doak Campbell Stadium on Saturday for the Miami-Florida State game, the smallest attendance for any Hurricanes-Seminoles matchup in Tallahassee since 1991. That was the largest crowd to attend a Florida State game this season, with fans clearly showing their unhappiness with the on-field product.</p><p>&#x201C;I think very highly of Coach Taggart and wish him well,&#x201D; Thrasher said.</p><p>Taggart&#x2019;s future has been the subject of speculation for weeks as the team was unable to sustain success. The &#x2018;Noles followed a two-game winning streak in late September with consecutive losses to Clemson and Wake Forest. A victory against Syracuse provided some hope but then Florida State was routed 27-10 by a Miami team that has had its own struggles.</p><p>Taggart, a 43-year-old Florida native who grew up rooting for the Seminoles, thanked the players, coaches and staff and Florida State in his tweet.</p><p>&#x201C;On behalf of my family and I, we wish Florida State nothing but the best and will be cheering on the Seminoles the rest of the way,&#x201D; he wrote.</p><p>Taggart is 56-62 as a head coach. He went 16-20 at Western Kentucky, 24-25 at South Florida and 7-5 in his lone season at Oregon.</p><p>The team Taggart inherited from Fisher had talent deficiencies, especially along the offensive line, and academic issues, but it also showed little improvement on the field over the course of 21 games. Florida State ranks 126th in the nation in penalties per game at 8.9 and has played sloppily and undisciplined throughout Taggart&#x2019;s tenure.</p><p>&#x201C;We will support our student-athletes in every way and do all we can to return to the winning tradition that is Seminole football,&#x201D; Thrasher said.</p><p>Haggins has been a Florida State assistant coach since 1994, coaching alongside Bobby Bowden, Fisher and Taggart. The 52-year-old Haggins spoke in August of &#x201C;the standard at Florida State, it&#x2019;s the standard. There&#x2019;s one way to do it. Do it the right way, do it full speed and be dominant.&#x201D;</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">548725</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Akers&#8217; 4 TDs leads Florida State rout of Syracuse, 35-17</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/akers-4-tds-leads-florida-state-rout-of-syracuse-35-17/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 23:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=545774</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Cam Akers ran for 144 yards and tied a school record with four touchdown runs as Florida State routed Syracuse 35-17...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#x2014; Cam Akers ran for 144 yards and tied a school record with four touchdown runs as Florida State routed Syracuse 35-17 on homecoming on Saturday.<p>The junior tailback had his fifth 100-yard rushing game of the season and now has 12 rushing touchdowns in 2019. Akers also took some snaps out of the wildcat formation and completed two passes for 26 yards.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/FSUFootball/status/1188228053408858113?s=20</embed></div><p>Wisconsin graduate transfer Alex Hornibrook made his second start for FSU (4-4, 3-3 Atlantic Coast Conference). Hornibrook completed 15 of 26 passes for 196 yards for the Seminoles, who led 35-3 going into the third quarter.</p><p>Tommy DeVito completed 20 of 33 passes for 151 yards for Syracuse (3-5, 0-4). Abdul Adams and Moe Neal had touchdown runs in the fourth quarter for the Orange, who have yet to earn a win over a Power 5 team.</p><p>Marvin Wilson had two of Florida State&#x2019;s season-high seven sacks.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Syracuse plays host to Boston College on Saturday.</p><p>Florida State plays host to Miami on Saturday.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">545774</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>QB Blackman to start for Florida State, Hornibrook will play</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/qb-blackman-to-start-for-florida-state-hornibrook-will-play/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 12:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=537606</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Coach Willie Taggart says James Blackman will start for Florida State against Clemson. But Taggart also said Monday that there is...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Coach Willie Taggart says James Blackman will start for Florida State against Clemson.</p>
<p>But Taggart also said Monday that there is a game plan for using Alex Hornibrook, who guided the Seminoles to wins over Louisville and North Carolina State after Blackman suffered an injury.</p>
<p>Taggart says both quarterbacks understand the offense. The coach says his staff really likes &#8220;what they both have done for us, and hoping they continue to do a great job for us.&#8221;</p>
<p>Taggart says that Blackman has practiced consistently during the bye week. He suffered a knee injury in the third quarter of Florida State&#8217;s win over Louisville on Sept. 21.</p>
<p>Blackman has completed 86 of 124 (69.4 of his passes for 970 yards, nine touchdowns and two interceptions.</p>
<p>Hornibrook, a graduate transfer from Wisconsin, has completed 44 of 60 (73.3 of his passes for 571 yards, five touchdowns and no interceptions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">537606</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NC State, Florida State meet seeking consistency, QB answers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nc-state-florida-state-meet-seeking-consistency-qb-answers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 16:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=533122</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State and North Carolina State are searching for consistency on offense, which starts with their quarterbacks. The Seminoles (2-2, 1-1...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State and North Carolina State are searching for consistency on offense, which starts with their quarterbacks.</p>
<p>The Seminoles (2-2, 1-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) have had red-hot starts, scoring 21 points in the first quarter against both Boise State and Louisville.</p>
<p>&#8220;If they play the first quarter for four quarters, they&#8217;re killing people,&#8221; North Carolina State coach Dave Doeren said.</p>
<p>Florida State is outscoring opponents 56-9 in the first quarter. The problem for the Seminoles is they haven&#8217;t been able to do much after halftime and are being outscored 31-3 in the third quarter.</p>
<p>That kind of inconsistency, as well as a knee injury to James Blackman, has led Florida State coach Willie Taggart to evaluate who starts at quarterback against the Wolfpack (3-1, 0-0) on Saturday. Blackman, a 69% passer, has practiced this week for the Seminoles but they could also go with Wisconsin graduate transfer Alex Hornibrook, who led the team to a comeback win over Louisville last week.</p>
<p>&#8220;If James is healthy, James will start,&#8221; Taggart said without declaring a starter on Thursday.</p>
<p>North Carolina State is also taking stock of an offense that Doeren said has been &#8220;pretty stale&#8221; in the first quarter of games, adding that the Wolfpack often &#8220;feel people out and make adjustments.&#8221; They sputtered in last weekend&#8217;s win against Ball State, managing 104 yards and five first downs with just two completed passes after halftime. The Wolfpack had a big punt return from Thayer Thomas and a blocked punt to offset the offensive troubles.</p>
<p>Starting quarterback Matthew McKay has had some good moments but has struggled to consistently connect downfield. North Carolina State gave his backup Bailey Hockman — who started his career at Florida State — a series in the Ball State game. Doeren said they had planned ahead of time to give him more than mop-up duty at the end of the game.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s possible Hockman could get more playing time against Florida State if McKay struggles.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ll just have to see how much he&#8217;s out there,&#8221; Doeren said.</p>
<p>Regardless of who plays at quarterback for the Seminoles or Wolfpack, both teams are looking to piece together four good quarters on offense and build some momentum with a bye week ahead after Saturday&#8217;s game.</p>
<p>For the first time In the 29-game history between the schools, North Carolina State has chance for a three straight win against the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Some other things to watch in Saturday&#8217;s game:</p>
<p>STRENGTH VS. STRENGTH</p>
<p>Florida State junior tailback Cam Akers has 499 rushing yards, leading the ACC with a 124.8-yard per game average. His eight touchdowns (six rushing and two receiving) in four games matches his total from 12 games in 2018.</p>
<p>&#8220;Will and determination, trying to get every crumb,&#8221; Akers said. &#8220;Every play trying to get every crumb.&#8221;</p>
<p>Akers and the Seminoles now face a Wolfpack defense that is 14th in the FBS against the run, allowing just 2.89 yards per carry and 76.5 yards per game.</p>
<p>COHESION</p>
<p>North Carolina State has had a tough time building defensive cohesion due to injuries.</p>
<p>Defensive end James Smith-Williams hasn&#8217;t played since he was injured in Week 2, though Doeren sounded optimistic about his chances to return Saturday. Fellow end Joseph Boletepeli missed the West Virginia game but returned last week against Ball State. And cornerback Nick McCloud hasn&#8217;t played since the opener against East Carolina.</p>
<p>ROAD LESSONS</p>
<p>North Carolina State didn&#8217;t play well in its first road game at West Virginia. Doeren is hoping that prepares them to play better this time around.</p>
<p>The Wolfpack had allowed a combined six points with no touchdowns through its first two games before visiting West Virginia on Sept. 14. But the Mountaineers — who had struggled offensively — posted 44 points and 445 yards in the win. Doeren said he thought his team &#8220;played slow&#8221; defensively in that game, and said the team lacked &#8220;great sideline energy&#8221; that day.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a great experience in a bad way for our guys,&#8221; Doeren said. &#8220;They learned a lot from that trip.&#8221;</p>
<p>FAMILIAR FACE</p>
<p>Hockman never played for Florida State but did show a glimpse of his talent in April 2018 inside Doak Campbell Stadium. The left-hander threw for 208 yards and a touchdown in the Seminoles&#8217; spring game. After falling short in an Aug. 2018 quarterback battle with Deondre Francois and Blackman, Hockman transferred to Hutchinson Community College before enrolling at NC State in January 2019.</p>
<p>RED-HOT IN RED ZONE</p>
<p>North Carolina State is 19 of 19 on its red-zone trips this season, including 13 touchdowns. Florida State is 14 of 16 inside the opponents&#8217; 20-yard line, which includes 12 touchdowns.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">533122</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>All-America Watch: FSU&#8217;s Akers rebounds; USC&#8217;s Pittman pops</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/all-america-watch-fsus-akers-rebounds-uscs-pittman-pops/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 12:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=532077</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Associated Press has been honoring college football&#8217;s best with an All-America team since 1925. The midseason All-Americans will be released Oct. 15. The full...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Associated Press has been honoring college football&#8217;s best with an All-America team since 1925. The midseason All-Americans will be released Oct. 15. The full three-team AP All-America team presented by Regions Bank will be unveiled in December. The weekly All-America watch features a Florida State running back rebounding from a sophomore slump, Southern California&#8217;s top target and a big-time matchup of big men in the SEC.</p>
<p>SPOTLIGHT</p>
<p>Cam Akers, RB, Florida State</p>
<p>Akers is flashing his freshman form again as a junior. Last year, running behind one of the worst offensive lines in the Power Five, Akers rarely was able to get free. Getting a little more help this year, Akers is again a weapon for the Seminoles. He has 17 runs of at least 10 yards through four games compared to 16 all last season. He&#8217;s coming off a grinding 112 yards and three touchdowns in a victory against Louisville. Florida State will need another big day from Akers to make it two straight victories. North Carolina State visits Saturday with one of the best run defenses in the ACC.</p>
<p>WHO&#8217;S HOT?</p>
<p>Michael Pittman Jr., WR, Southern California</p>
<p>The senior went off against Utah, with <a href="https://apnews.com/6078ccee266e47769ed923aebe6af0ca">one of the best individual recei</a>v<a href="https://apnews.com/6078ccee266e47769ed923aebe6af0ca">ing games in USC history</a> pushing him to 11th in the country in yards receiving per game at 109.3. At 6-foot-4 and 220 pounds, Pittman is a security blanket for whoever is playing quarterback for the Trojans. USC is already on its third after injuries to J.T Daniels (knee) and Kedon Slovis, who was knocked out of the Utah game early. No word on whether Matt Fink will have to start this week at No. 17 Washington, but his former roommate, Pittman, is here to help pull him through.</p>
<p>WHO&#8217;S NOT?</p>
<p>Michigan&#8217;s defense.</p>
<p>The Wolverines&#8217; malfunctioning offense has gotten a bunch of attention, but the defense hasn&#8217;t been great either and it was pretty much run over by Wisconsin. Michigan is replacing stars Devin Bush, Rashan Gary and Chase Winovich, but expectations were still plenty high for CB Lavert Hill, LB Khaleke Hudson, S Josh Metellus and DE Kwity Paye. Hudson is the only one playing at a high level, but when the team struggles the chances for individual recognition go way down. Michigan has only the nation&#8217;s No. 47 overall defense and, after last week, is just 68th in scoring defense, allowing 25.7 points per game.</p>
<p>GROUP OF FIVE STAR</p>
<p>Alex Highsmith, DE, Charlotte</p>
<p>Highsmith is following up a breakout 2017 when he had 17.5 tackles for loss with an even better senior season. The former walk-on has five sacks among his 6 ½ tackles for loss in four games for the 49ers.</p>
<p>ON THE LINE</p>
<p>(ESPN and SEC Network analyst Cole Cubelic, who played guard at Auburn, breaks down an offensive lineman playing at an All-America level).</p>
<p>Tyler Biadasz, C, Wisconsin.</p>
<p>The junior and preseason All-American helped paved the way for 359 yards rushing against Michigan on Saturday.</p>
<p>&#8220;He put on a clinic,&#8221; Cubelic said. &#8220;Played through the whistle, finishing his blocks. Not only does he direct traffic at the line of scrimmage, but he is one of the more physical players on that team. He went a long way toward proving he is the best center in college football.&#8221;</p>
<p>ALL-AMERICA MATCHUP</p>
<p>Javon Kinlaw, DT, South Carolina vs. Logan Stenberg, OG, Kentucky</p>
<p>Gamecocks-Wildcats does not qualify as a marquee matchup, but it features two of the best interior lineman in the country. Hopefully, the two seniors, each 300 pounds plus, will get some one-on-one opportunities against each other. Kinlaw has four sacks. Stenberg has been as steady as any offensive lineman in the country. According to Pro Football Focus College, no guard in FBS has had more pass blocking opportunities (138) without allowing a quarterback pressure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">532077</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State loses LB for season, QB Blackman day-to-day</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-loses-lb-for-season-qb-blackman-day-to-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 12:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=531581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Willie Taggart announced Monday that starting linebacker Jaiden Lars-Woodbey is out for the season with a leg injury....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Willie Taggart announced Monday that starting linebacker Jaiden Lars-Woodbey is out for the season with a leg injury.</p>
<p>The coach also said Seminoles quarterback James Blackman and left tackle Jauan Williams are listed day-to-day as they recover from injuries.</p>
<p>Lars-Woodbey, a sophomore who has played inside and outside linebacker, was injured in the second half of Saturday&#8217;s 35-24 win over Louisville. He had 19 tackles, 1 tackle for loss and .5 sacks in four games.</p>
<p>&#8220;Everything happens for a reason,&#8221; Lars-Woodbey posted on Twitter. &#8220;Just know that when one door closes for me, another one opens as well. I know my teammates are going to hold it down for me for the rest of this year and I can&#8217;t wait to be back with them soon!&#8221;</p>
<p>Blackman is 86 of 124 (69.4 for 970 yards, nine touchdowns and two interceptions in 2019. The redshirt sophomore was injured on Florida State&#8217;s first drive of the third quarter and was later seen on the sideline icing his left knee.</p>
<p>If Blackman is not available, to start Saturday against North Carolina State (3-1), the Seminoles (2-2, 1-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) will turn to Alex Hornibrook. A graduate transfer from Wisconsin, Hornibrook completed 15 of 20 passes for 255 yards, two touchdowns and no interceptions in his Florida State debut against the Cardinals on Saturday.</p>
<p>&#8220;What we saw is what we had been seeing since training camp,&#8221; Taggart said. &#8220;He comes to practice, he comes to meetings like a pro, like he&#8217;s done it before. He has put the work in to be confident in what he&#8217;s doing. Putting him out on the field, I don&#8217;t think anyone on our staff or our players felt like we had to worry about anything.</p>
<p>&#8220;We know that Alex was going to be prepared. And he showed it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida State has lost two players for the season in Lars-Woodbey and defensive end/outside linebacker Joshua Kaindoh. With Lars-Woodbey sidelined, expect Emmett Rice and Jaleel McRae to see more playing time at inside linebacker.</p>
<p>Williams missed games against Virginia and Louisville. Senior Abdul Bello has started in his place.</p>
<p>&#8220;Hopefully he can get back in the swing of things and be able to try to help our football team this week,&#8221; Taggart said. &#8220;Bello is doing a good job for us.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">531581</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Penalty trouble puts FSU, Miami, Syracuse in early ACC hole</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/penalty-trouble-puts-fsu-miami-syracuse-in-early-acc-hole/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 12:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=529558</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — The mistakes — a false start here, a facemask penalty there — keep piling up for some Atlantic Coast Conference teams...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — The mistakes — a false start here, a facemask penalty there — keep piling up for some Atlantic Coast Conference teams expected to contend for division titles.</p>
<p>Syracuse and Florida State were picked to finish behind reigning national champion Clemson in the Atlantic Division, while Miami was picked second in the Coastal. Yet they&#8217;re off to shaky starts and rank among the most penalized teams in the nation. Their inability to get out of their own way at the start of league play has put them in an early hole.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think it&#8217;s very telling of who you are as a team,&#8221; said ACC Network analyst Eric Mac Lain, a former Clemson offensive lineman who played on the Tigers&#8217; national runner-up team in 2015. &#8220;At the end of the day, you&#8217;re not going to win a lot of ballgames if you keep that behavior up. You&#8217;re playing now (against) a second team within yourself, and you can&#8217;t even do the little things right. So it&#8217;s really tough.&#8221;</p>
<p>Football coaches constantly talk about avoiding mistakes, even while acknowledging it&#8217;s hard to avoid every penalty. But nothing seems to anger a coach more or can kill a team&#8217;s momentum than mental mistakes or lack of focus — when an offensive lineman jumps for a false start or a team can&#8217;t get lined up in time for a delay-of-game penalty.</p>
<p>Worse than those 5-yarders, there are the 15-yard personal fouls like hitting a ballcarrier out of bounds by failing to pull up at the sideline.</p>
<p>All become magnified in games — whether a matchup between teams of similar talent or an underdog trying to pull off the upset. It becomes a game within the game, which team is more disciplined.</p>
<p>The Seminoles, Hurricanes and Orange have had too many missteps.</p>
<p>Florida State and Miami each have committed 26 penalties, tied with the Big Ten&#8217;s Michigan State and the Pac-12&#8217;s Arizona for the most of any power-conference program. Syracuse is in the next group with 25.</p>
<p>The troubles are particularly concerning for Seminoles coach Willie Taggart, whose team escaped with a win against Louisiana-Monroe that was sandwiched between a season-opening loss to Boise State and last weekend&#8217;s loss at No. 21 Virginia. Florida State ranks tied for 116th in the 130-team Bowl Subdivision, committing 8.67 penalties per game, and 119th in average penalty yards at 78.33.</p>
<p>The penalty flags against Florida State have come flying from all directions.</p>
<p>Four came on false-starts. Four more came when the Seminoles lined up offsides. Another five came on offensive or defensive holding calls. And there have been seven personal fouls, including three fourth-quarter ones against Virginia — prompting Taggart to lament &#8220;selfish penalties&#8221; and talk about doing more in practice to deter players from them because &#8220;it&#8217;s killing this football team.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;We have things that we do internally to try to persuade our guys not to do that,&#8221; Taggart said this week. &#8220;In the fourth quarter, fatigue did play a factor, and you can&#8217;t do that, and that&#8217;s part of winning football. You can&#8217;t make those mistakes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Things started badly for the Hurricanes and first-year coach Manny Diaz with 14 penalties for 118 yards in the season-opening loss to No. 9 Florida, though they had fewer in the loss at North Carolina (7 for 57) before beating overmatched Bethune-Cookman.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think that&#8217;s a habit,&#8221; Miami coach Manny Diaz said. &#8220;I think that&#8217;s a way that you practice. I think that&#8217;s a way that you run your offseason program. That&#8217;s not to say in a heated environment, guys won&#8217;t make a mistake for the rest of the year. When we came in with our accountability structure, we said the mistake of one affects others.&#8221;</p>
<p>There are exceptions, such as the celebration after special-teamer Jimmy Murphy&#8217;s first career touchdown rush last weekend in the 63-0 win over Bethune-Cookman. Murphy&#8217;s exorbitant reaction drew a 15-yard flag, which Diaz understood — but didn&#8217;t necessarily like.</p>
<p>&#8220;Even as funny as Jimmy Murphy&#8217;s penalty was, we had to kick off from the 20-yard line,&#8221; Diaz said. &#8220;So they all understand that anything they do on their own has an impact on the collective.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for Syracuse, Dino Babers&#8217; Orange had an easy season-opening win against Liberty that overshadowed 10 penalties for 88 yards. The problem resurfaced with nine flags for 85 yards against top-ranked Clemson last weekend, including two 15-yarders in the opening quarter while falling behind 14-0.</p>
<p>Figuring out how to fix it isn&#8217;t easy, either.</p>
<p>&#8220;Honestly, I couldn&#8217;t even tell you (why) because I don&#8217;t know myself,&#8221; Syracuse defensive back Trill Williams said when asked about the penalties. &#8220;But it&#8217;s tied in with discipline. We&#8217;ve got to get more disciplined.&#8221;</p>
<p>It is a trademark for good teams and one reason Clemson, Virginia and Wake Forest are unbeaten.</p>
<p>The Demon Deacons are second nationally in fewest penalty yards per game (22.67) and third in average penalties (2.67), flagged just eight times in three games. The Cavaliers rank in the top 25 in fewest penalties per game (5.0), while Clemson is in the top third of the FBS ranks in both categories (5.67, 47.67).</p>
<p>Mac Lean said finding ways to avoid those mistakes have been an emphasis in Clemson&#8217;s practices, down to having defensive backs wear boxing gloves that make them defend without the ability to grab a receiver.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s about building habits that avoid mistakes, then being disciplined enough to stick with them.</p>
<p>Clemson defensive coordinator Brent Venables &#8220;just brings an intensity and a sense of urgency and a standard every single day that you have to match or you&#8217;re not getting out there,&#8221; Tigers linebacker James Skalski said, adding: &#8220;And like coach (Dabo) Swinney says too: &#8216;It&#8217;s all the little things, it&#8217;s all the little things.&#8217; When you continue to do it every single day, under the lights on the big stage, it&#8217;s just second nature to you.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">529558</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taggart: Florida State DE Joshua Kaindoh out for season</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/taggart-florida-state-de-joshua-kaindoh-out-for-season/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=528499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Willie Taggart says junior defensive end/outside linebacker Joshua Kaindoh will miss the rest of the season with a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Willie Taggart says junior defensive end/outside linebacker Joshua Kaindoh will miss the rest of the season with a lower-leg injury.</p>
<p>Kaindoh had nine tackles and one sack in three games this season. He was carted off the field during Saturday&#8217;s 31-24 loss at Virginia.</p>
<p>The injury means that junior Janarius Robinson will likely start for the Seminoles (1-2, 0-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) when they play host to Louisville (2-1, 0-0) on Saturday. Robinson has eight tackles and a fumble recovery in three games this year.</p>
<p>Florida State is still developing depth at the defensive end/linebacker spot, so it&#8217;s unclear who will back up Robinson. Among the veteran options are seniors Adonis Thomas and Josh Brown.</p>
<p>Taggart also said Monday that left tackle Jauan Williams (ankle) remains week to week. Williams missed Saturday&#8217;s game at Virginia.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">528499</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hurricane Dorian prompts move of Boise State-FSU game</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hurricane-dorian-prompts-move-of-boise-state-fsu-game/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 15:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=520310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — The season opener between Boise State and Florida State will be played in Tallahassee because of the threat of Hurricane Dorian....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — The season opener between Boise State and Florida State will be played in Tallahassee because of the threat of Hurricane Dorian.</p>
<p>Officials moved the game out of Jacksonville on Thursday, two days before the 7 p.m. kickoff. The teams will play Saturday at noon at Doak Campbell Stadium, hoping to keep fans away from the coastal region ahead of landfall.</p>
<p>Jacksonville officials, along with those from Florida State and Boise State, collaborated on the decision. Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis declared a state of emergency Wednesday, urging residents and visitors to take precaution before the storm hits.</p>
<p>Dorian is expected to become a Category 3 hurricane and could hit Florida&#8217;s east coast during Labor Day weekend. It is currently projected to make landfall in Brevard County, well south of Jacksonville, but Jacksonville is among the areas within the cone of uncertainty.</p>
<p>The hurricane has slowed over the past 24 hours, but there is concern it could speed up or change direction.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">520310</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5854d60b-819a-494d-9239-70b8a909319a/c615f742-a614-4545-8965-ff19fc8fc1a2/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219447~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5854d60b-819a-494d-9239-70b8a909319a/c615f742-a614-4545-8965-ff19fc8fc1a2/main.mp4*~hmac=75389a0c9f11e3f58e3676bc80f63ac9adc25a28af76130992fcf939dc8e3765' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blackman gets another chance as Florida State&#8217;s starting QB</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/blackman-gets-another-chance-as-florida-states-starting-qb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Franco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 10:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=518852</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — James Blackman had to deal with the pain of not winning a quarterback competition in 2018. But in the last few...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — James Blackman had to deal with the pain of not winning a quarterback competition in 2018.</p>
<p>But in the last few days, it&#8217;s been a complete reversal.</p>
<p>Florida State coach Willie Taggart said he and offensive coordinator Kendal Briles told Blackman on Sunday that he was the starter. And the response was as anyone would expect.</p>
<p>&#8220;He&#8217;s excited about leading this football team,&#8221; Taggart said on Monday. &#8220;He&#8217;s fired up and ready to go.&#8221;</p>
<p>Blackman is emblematic of the Seminoles&#8217; 2019 mantra. Last year, which was a lackluster 5-7 season, is in the rear-view mirror. The focus is on the road ahead, which begins against Boise State in Jacksonville on Saturday.</p>
<p>Taggart also expressed confidence in Wisconsin graduate transfer Alex Hornibrook, who is No. 2 on Florida State&#8217;s depth chart. The coach their performances this preseason were &#8220;almost identical.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;We feel good about the quarterback position,&#8221; Taggart said. &#8220;We feel like we have two guys there that can start a football game for us.&#8221;</p>
<p>Blackman has started 13 games, including 12 as a true freshman in 2017. The redshirt sophomore has thrown for 2,740 yards, 24 touchdowns and 12 interceptions at FSU.</p>
<p>In his only 2018 start, Blackman threw for 421 yards, four touchdowns and an interception in a road loss to NC State. Blackman became the immediate odds-on early favorite this winter when Taggart dismissed Deondre Francois, who started 11 games last fall.</p>
<p>&#8220;Sitting out last year wasn&#8217;t necessarily easy for him,&#8221; Taggart said. &#8220;He&#8217;s what a big-time college quarterback is supposed be like. He&#8217;s a young man that&#8217;s loyal to this program and more importantly he&#8217;s loyal to his teammates.&#8221;</p>
<p>Blackman is charismatic and a natural leader. He took on more responsibility in the offseason, acting as if he were the No. 1 quarterback all along. Earlier in the preseason, Blackman was asked if he felt like it was his offense to lead.</p>
<p>&#8220;When I bleed, I bleed garnet and gold,&#8221; Blackman said. &#8220;I feel like I put in a lot of work to be here.&#8221;</p>
<p>Blackman has added weight, more than 30 pounds since arriving at FSU two summers ago. The 6-foot-5 Blackman now weighs 195 pounds.</p>
<p>Teammates raved about him this spring and August.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s my brother,&#8221; said junior receiver D.J. Matthews, who is Blackman&#8217;s roommate. &#8220;It doesn&#8217;t go no further than that. That&#8217;s my brother. Ride for him all the time.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a crucial early decision by Taggart and Briles, who will tailor his fast-paced offense to Blackman. While Blackman isn&#8217;t a dual-threat quarterback like those Briles has had in the past, it&#8217;s expected that Blackman will be able to execute the run-pass option that the Seminoles have implemented.</p>
<p>&#8220;The way he plays the game, it&#8217;s a little different from everybody else,&#8221; Briles said on FSU&#8217;s media day on Aug. 18. &#8220;He does have that passion and is a great leader. His arm talent is really good, his accuracy getting better, and he&#8217;s a great decision maker.&#8221;</p>
<p>With the race being close and coming down to the final days of camp, Taggart said the coaches are undecided about playing two quarterbacks on Saturday.</p>
<p>&#8220;We just figured out who are No. 1 quarterback is,&#8221; Taggart said. &#8220;. We feel good knowing that Alex can go in there and execute our offense.&#8221;</p>
<p>Notes: Taggart said that defensive tackle Marvin Wilson is moving well and is &#8220;ready to go&#8221; after missing more than a week due to a knee injury. Tamorrion Terry (knee) is also running and cutting, although Taggart said the coaches haven&#8217;t pushed the team&#8217;s top receiver hard in practices.</p>
<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — James Blackman was the front-runner all along and now the quarterback has won Florida State&#8217;s starting job.</p>
<p>Coach Willie Taggart made the announcement on Sunday night in a statement posted on the school&#8217;s website. Blackman beat out Wisconsin graduate transfer Alex Hornibrook and Louisville transfer Jordan Travis. The redshirt sophomore will start for the Seminoles when they open the season against Boise State on Saturday in Jacksonville.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not clear if Hornibrook or Travis will be FSU&#8217;s backup. Taggart&#8217;s next opportunity to meet with the media is on Monday.</p>
<p>Blackman has started 13 games, including 12 as a true freshman in 2017. He has thrown for 2,740 yards, 24 touchdowns and 12 interceptions at FSU.</p>
<p>In his only 2018 start, Blackman threw for 421 yards, four touchdowns and an interception in a road loss to NC State. Blackman became the immediate odds-on favorite this winter when Taggart dismissed Deondre Francois, who started 11 games last fall.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">518852</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mendoza lifts Florida St. past LSU 5-4 in 12th for CWS berth</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mendoza-lifts-florida-st-past-lsu-5-4-in-12th-for-cws-berth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 05:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=491205</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — Florida State&#8217;s 75-year-old head coach, Mike Martin, was in pain and enjoying every moment of it. A celebratory bear hug...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — Florida State&#8217;s 75-year-old head coach, Mike Martin, was in pain and enjoying every moment of it.</p>
<p>A celebratory bear hug from trainer Brandon Stone felt like it &#8220;had broken five of my ribs,&#8221; said Martin, who&#8217;ll finish his 40th and likely final season at the College World Series in Omaha, Nebraska.</p>
<p>Drew Mendoza&#8217;s two-out hit to right center drove home Mike Salvatore from second base in the bottom of the 12th inning, lifting Florida State to a 5-4 victory over LSU that gave the Seminoles a sweep of the best-of-three Baton Rouge NCAA super regional on Sunday night.</p>
<p>&#8220;I ain&#8217;t going to get all teary eyed, but I wanted this so bad for our young men,&#8221; said Martin, who has insisted he&#8217;ll retire after this season. If so, he&#8217;ll conclude his career with his 17th trip to the College World Series as a head coach.</p>
<p>LSU (40-26) had rallied from a 4-1 deficit in the sixth to tie it in the eighth. Tigers reliever Devin Fontenot (5-4) pitched six no-hit innings and struck out 10 before Salvatore broke through for Florida State&#8217;s first hit since the fourth inning. Salvatore advanced to second on a passed ball and, after Fontenot recorded his 11th strikeout against Reese Albert, LSU elected to pitch to Mendoza — one of the Seminoles&#8217; most productive hitters — with first base open.</p>
<p>LSU coach Paul Mainieri said he preferred to pitch to Mendoza over the following batter, Robby Martin, who came in with a team-leading .338 batting average.</p>
<p>But Mendoza delivered with his second hit of the game, the Seminoles (41-21) spilled onto the field and Stone exuberantly wrapped his arms around Martin.</p>
<p>&#8220;He hugged me and I&#8217;m saying, &#8216;That&#8217;s what this is all about,'&#8221; Martin said. &#8220;Those are things you just will never forget. This night will be etched in stone with me for the rest of my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>SHUT-DOWN RELIEF</p>
<p>Florida State reliever Antonio Velez (5-2) pitched 4 2/3 shutout innings in relief and struck out six to pick up his second win of the best-of-three Baton Rouge super regional after his inning of relief earned him the Game 1 win a day earlier.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a huge, huge situation for him to show what he&#8217;s all about,&#8221; Martin said. &#8220;He has proven that no situation is too big for him. He doesn&#8217;t care if you put him in thee bases loaded on a 2-0 count.&#8221;</p>
<p>Martin also praised Fontenot, calling him &#8220;a warrior.&#8221;</p>
<p>BASE-RUNNING BLUNDERS</p>
<p>The Tigers ran themselves out of potential run-scoring chances twice in the game. Giovanni DiGiacomo was picked off of third by catcher Matheu Nelson with one out and the tying runners in scoring position in a 4-2 game in the sixth. After Zach Watson delivered a game-tying, one-out single in the eighth, he was cut down trying to take second on the throw back to the infield, and LSU wound up stranding a runner at third.</p>
<p>&#8220;Major leaguers are not perfect; certainly college kids are not perfect,&#8221; Mainieri said. &#8220;You can analyze the game however you want and say this play factored in or this play factored in. That is what happens in sports.&#8221;</p>
<p>LEADING HITTERS</p>
<p>Salvatore produced three hits and drove in a run before scoring the game-winner.</p>
<p>Antoine Duplantis, who last week became LSU&#8217;s all-time hits leader, had four hits in his final college game and drove in three runs, including a home run down the right field line that cut LSU&#8217;s deficit to 3-1 in the fourth.</p>
<p>MOMENTUM SHIFTS</p>
<p>Florida State scored the game&#8217;s first run on a disputed play in which the ball squirted out of LSU catcher Saul Garza&#8217;s glove as he swung his arm upward after appearing to tag Martin out at the plate. Umpire Tony Norris initially called Martin out, but the call was reversed after he consulted the rest of the umpiring crew and reviewed video replay.</p>
<p>The Seminoles capitalized further by scoring twice more in the frame on singles by Nelson and Salvatore.</p>
<p>Florida State made it 4-1 in the fourth when Tim Becker&#8217;s double over third base drove in Nelson, who&#8217;d advanced to second on a wild pitch.</p>
<p>Duplantis singled in a run in the sixth and LSU tied it in the eighth with a rally that opened with Josh Smith&#8217;s double, followed by Duplantis&#8217; double that scored Smith and drove starter CJ Van Eyk from the game. Watson drove in Duplantis to make it 4-4.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t think this team ever quit,&#8221; Duplantis said. &#8220;I don&#8217;t think any of us should have any regrets.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">491205</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Carolina beats Florida State 72-64 to reach Sweet 16</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/south-carolina-beats-florida-state-72-64-to-reach-sweet-16/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 20:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=467217</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) &#8212; Mikiah Herbert Harrigan scored 20 points, Alexis Jennings added 16 and fourth-seeded South Carolina beat No. 5 seed Florida State 72-64...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) &#8212; Mikiah Herbert Harrigan scored 20 points, Alexis Jennings added 16 and fourth-seeded South Carolina beat No. 5 seed Florida State 72-64 on Sunday to advance to the women&#8217;s NCAA Tournament Sweet 16 for the sixth straight season.</p>
<p>Te&#8217;a Cooper added 13 points and Tyasha Harris had 11 for South Carolina, which won despite being outrebounded 50-33 and allowing Florida State to grab 27 offensive rebounds.<br />
It&#8217;s the third time in the past five seasons the Gamecocks have eliminated the Seminoles from the NCAA Tournament, beating them in the Elite Eight in 2015 and 2017.</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="fr" dir="ltr">Final in Charlotte. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FSUWBB?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FSUWBB</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ncaaW?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ncaaW</a> <a href="https://t.co/Rg9XFDjoFY">pic.twitter.com/Rg9XFDjoFY</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FSU Women&#39;s Hoops (@fsuwbb) <a href="https://twitter.com/fsuwbb/status/1109908334986055685?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 24, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>Nicki Ekhomu scored 19 points and Kiah Gilespie had 15 points and 18 rebounds for Florida State (24-9).</p>
<p>South Carolina (23-9) took the lead for good with 2:14 left when Cooper drove the lane and dished to Jennings, who scored and drew a foul for a three-point play for a 63-60 lead.</p>
<p>Ekhomu answered with a mid-range jumper to cut the lead to one. South Carolina&#8217;s Victaria Saxton made two free throws to push the lead back to three with 1:22 left.</p>
<p>But Gillespie grabbed the Seminoles 26th rebound of the game and scored to trim the lead back to one with 46 seconds left.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s when Harris came up with the play of the game, driving the right side of the lane, scoring off the glass and drawing a foul for a three-point play to make it a two-possession game with 27.2 seconds left.</p>
<p>For the first time all game, Florida State didn&#8217;t have an answer as Ekhomu missed a 3-pointer and then fouled. Cooper made 1 of 2 free throws to push the lead to five.</p>
<p>Gillespie then missed a 3-pointer when Florida State was called for a foul with 9.8 seconds left. She slammed the ball down to the court twice in frustration drawing a technical foul.</p>
<p>After falling behind by eight early on, the Gamecocks got a big second quarter from Herbert Harrigan, who helped build 37-30 halftime lead behind a steady stream of mid-range jumpers. But the Seminoles would battle back in the third to close to the gap to 52-51 behind strong offensive rebounding.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles don&#8217;t have a senior on the roster and they have nine freshman and sophomores, so they have a bright future ahead and this year&#8217;s tournament experience will only help them moving forward.<br />
South Carolina: The Gamecocks appear to have regained some of their swagger but it will need to work on boxing out if it hopes to advance in the NCAA Tournament.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Gamecocks move on to face the winner of the No. 1 seed Baylor and No. 8 California in the Sweet 16 in Greensboro, North Carolina.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">467217</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Williamson, No. 5 Duke beat No. 12 FSU 73-63 for ACC title</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/williamson-no-5-duke-beat-no-12-fsu-73-63-for-acc-title/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 05:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=465065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — Zion Williamson remembers crying in his mother&#8217;s arms after suffering a knee sprain that would sideline him for nearly six full...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — Zion Williamson remembers crying in his mother&#8217;s arms after suffering a knee sprain that would sideline him for nearly six full games and threaten fifth-ranked Duke&#8217;s title potential.</p>
<p>Less than a month later, Williamson was standing amid fallen confetti, raising an Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament championship trophy and cutting down a strand of net while sporting the widest of smiles.</p>
<p>This was a moment that Williamson fought so hard to make it back for.</p>
<p>Williamson had 21 points in Duke&#8217;s 73-63 victory over No. 12 Florida State on Saturday night in the championship game to complete his dominating three-game show. And with Williamson back and healthy, the Blue Devils are charging into the NCAA Tournament.</p>
<p>&#8220;For people who said I shouldn&#8217;t return,&#8221; Williamson said during the trophy presentation, &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t abandon my brothers and coaches like that.&#8221;</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Fought til the end.  Final from the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ACCTourney?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#ACCTourney</a> <a href="https://t.co/DOPEFch49i">pic.twitter.com/DOPEFch49i</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FSU Hoops (@FSUHoops) <a href="https://twitter.com/FSUHoops/status/1107109295940947968?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 17, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>The Blue Devils (29-5) won their 21st tournament title for yet another trophy in an already-record haul. Williamson became only the sixth freshman in the event&#8217;s 66-year history to win MVP honors and the first in a dozen years after averaging 27 points and 10 rebounds while making 33 of 43 shots in the three games.</p>
<p>&#8220;My teammates and my coaches, they never rushed me back,&#8221; Williamson said. &#8220;I could&#8217;ve come back a few games ago, but I wouldn&#8217;t have been myself. So they sat me down and said &#8216;Get in better condition.&#8217; That&#8217;s what I did. &#8230; I feel like I&#8217;m back to normal.&#8221;</p>
<p>He certainly looked back to highlight-making form. There of course were the high-flying dunks, the unstoppable attacks to the paint and the defensive pressure that made him a factor at both ends since his return in Thursday&#8217;s quarterfinals against Syracuse.</p>
<p>Yet Williamson might have made his most dazzling play with an open-court pass: a perfect baseball-style bounce pass he threw to fellow freshman Tre Jones nearly a half-a-court ahead in transition for a second-half score.</p>
<p>Williamson even stopped to look at his hand almost in surprise at his own latest jaw dropper.</p>
<p>&#8220;When I made that pass, I even looked at my arm,&#8221; Williamson said. &#8220;It was like, &#8216;Thank you for getting that pass through.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Everything started with a quarterfinal win over Syracuse, with Williamson going for 29 points on 13-for-13 shooting in his first game back. Then came an even bigger performance in the semifinals: 31 points, 11 rebounds and the final-minute tip-in that ultimately helped Duke hold off third-ranked North Carolina in a rivalry classic.</p>
<p>This time, Williamson didn&#8217;t need as big of a performance with all four of Duke&#8217;s top-tier freshmen hitting double figures. RJ Barrett added 17 points and nine rebounds, while Jones had his own strong outing with 18 points and six assists. Duke shot 58 percent after halftime to turn a 36-all score into a 14-point lead by midway through the half.</p>
<p>It was all part of Duke&#8217;s closing act that showed the Blue Devils are ready for what&#8217;s ahead. And it gave Hall of Fame coach Mike Krzyzewski his record 15th ACC Tournament championship.</p>
<p>&#8220;I told them last night: &#8216;We&#8217;ve won a lot of championships but I haven&#8217;t won one with you,'&#8221; Krzyzewski said during the trophy presentation. &#8220;So to be in their moment is the very best thing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mfiondu Kabengele scored 14 points for the Seminoles (27-7). They upset No. 2 Virginia in Friday&#8217;s semifinals but couldn&#8217;t recover after falling behind big, getting no closer than five again.</p>
<p>Florida State shot just 32 percent, including 8 for 32 after halftime (25 percent).</p>
<p>&#8220;The main thing with us is that we beat ourselves,&#8221; Florida State forward Phil Cofer said. &#8220;Duke&#8217;s still a great team. But we can&#8217;t shoot that bad. And we missed some easy shots that we usually make.&#8221;</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>FSU: The Seminoles had been rolling since a 1-4 ACC start in January, winning 14 of 15 games with the only loss coming at third-ranked North Carolina. And they controlled most of the game against the Cavaliers, shooting nearly 57 percent to tear through Virginia&#8217;s stout defense. But by Saturday, they managed to stay right with Duke for a half only to fade as the Blue Devils made their title-clinching move.</p>
<p>Duke: This tournament was all about the 6-foot-7, 285-pound Williamson, whose Feb. 20 knee sprain — that included the image of his left foot tearing through the side of his shoe as he fell to the court — loomed over a team that had spent a national-best seven weeks at No. 1 in the AP Top 25. But Williamson&#8217;s return restored that confident edge that reaches throughout Duke&#8217;s lineup at both ends of the court.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think there&#8217;s a verve when he&#8217;s in there,&#8221; associate head coach Jon Scheyer said, adding: &#8220;I think his personality and the connection that he has with the rest of our guys, that&#8217;s real, and there&#8217;s something to be said for that.&#8221;</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>FSU: The Seminoles are headed to the NCAA Tournament, where they hope for another deep run like last year&#8217;s push to within a game of the Final Four. &#8220;We know that we&#8217;re national championship contenders,&#8221; senior Terance Mann said. &#8220;We&#8217;ve got to keep that in mind and keep fighting.&#8221;</p>
<p>Duke: The Blue Devils have claimed the league&#8217;s automatic bid to the NCAA Tournament, possibly as the No. 1 overall seed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">465065</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 14 Florida State surges past Wake Forest 65-57</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-14-florida-state-surges-past-wake-forest-65-57/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 07:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=462928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WINSTON-SALEM, N.C. (AP) &#8212; Florida State made no excuses for its sluggish first half. The No. 14 Seminoles fell behind 14-2 to Wake Forest, a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINSTON-SALEM, N.C. (AP) &#8212; Florida State made no excuses for its sluggish first half.</p>
<p>The No. 14 Seminoles fell behind 14-2 to Wake Forest, a team near the bottom of the Atlantic Coast Conference standings. Then came a second-half surge &#8212; 18 straight points &#8212; and a 65-57 victory. Florida State won for the 12th time in 13 games to finish fourth in conference.</p>
<p>&#8220;They kept us out of sorts,&#8221; FSU coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#8220;We couldn&#8217;t find our rhythm. I just felt Wake Forest did a very good job defensively of not letting us do what we need to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Seminoles (25-6, 13-5 ACC) never led until grabbing the lead at 47-45 on Trent Forrest&#8217;s basket with 7:28 left. Phil Cofer followed with an easy basket, then M.J. Walker supplied the knockout with a 3-pointer.</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Noles finish the regular season with another  road victory <a href="https://t.co/5gKnMAn05W">https://t.co/5gKnMAn05W</a> <a href="https://t.co/LNwlSW6ujQ">pic.twitter.com/LNwlSW6ujQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FSU Hoops (@FSUHoops) <a href="https://twitter.com/FSUHoops/status/1104527343304015872?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 9, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>The Deacons (11-19, 4-14 ACC) frequently switched defenses, making it hard for the Seminoles to get the ball inside to 7-foot-4 Christ Koumadje and 6-10 Mfiondu Kabengele.</p>
<p>Forrest led a balanced FSU attack &#8212; 11 players scored &#8212; with 11 points. Koumadje had 8 points and 10 rebounds. After a cold-shooting first half by both teams, FSU shot 54 percent in the second half.</p>
<p>Brandon Childress, who scored three baskets to spark the Deacons to their early 12-point lead, finished with 13 points and Chaundee Brown added 11 &#8212; all in the first half.</p>
<p>The Deacons, who shot just 26 percent, went scoreless for nearly six minutes as the Seminoles erased a 45-40 deficit with their 18-0 run.</p>
<p>Wake Forest was 16 of 16 from the foul line en route to a 31-24 halftime lead as both teams struggled from the field. But the Deacons made only 6 of 13 from the line in the second half.</p>
<p>&#8220;We came out low energy, but we didn&#8217;t take them lightly,&#8221; Koumadje said. &#8220;Their defense was kind of tricky. But at the end of the day, we did what we had to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>PJ Savoy&#8217;s 3-pointer with 9:28 left pulled FSU into a tie at 45 &#8212; the first time the Seminoles hadn&#8217;t trailed since Wake Forest scored the opening basket.</p>
<p>&#8220;I thought we executed a lot better (in the second half),&#8221; Hamilton said. &#8220;We got some tremendous help from our non-starters in the first half.&#8221;</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles capped their first 25-game regular season and maintained their momentum heading into the ACC Tournament.</p>
<p>Wake Forest: The Deacons gave a strong performance for 30 minutes against a ranked team &#8212; they blew a big lead earlier in the week in a one-point loss to Duke &#8212; for the second straight home game. They&#8217;ll need to continue their improved play in the tournament in Charlotte to extend their season.</p>
<p>STAT PACK</p>
<p>Florida State rallied to finish 12-5 in the ACC after a 1-4 start that included losses at Pitt and Boston College, which finished back in the standings. But the Seminoles played only single games (all losses) against Virginia, North Carolina and Duke.</p>
<p>SENIOR NIGHT</p>
<p>Wake Forest senior Anthony Bilas, a seldom-used reserve was in the starting lineup for the first time in his last home game. Bilas&#8217; father, Jay, a college basketball analyst for ESPN, was in attendance before going to Chapel Hill for the broadcast of the Duke-North Carolina game. Bilas re-entered the game in the final seconds and made an open 3-pointer for the game&#8217;s final points.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: Plays Virginia Tech or the Wake Forest/Miami winner in the third round of the ACC tournament in Charlotte on March 14.</p>
<p>Wake Forest: Plays Miami in the first round of the ACC tournament on March 12.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">462928</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 18 Florida State, behind Kabengele, tops NC State 78-73</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-18-florida-state-behind-kabengele-tops-nc-state-78-73/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=460725</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Trent Forrest has been in pain with a toe injury throughout the season. The Florida State guard hasn&#8217;t missed a game...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Trent Forrest has been in pain with a toe injury throughout the season. The Florida State guard hasn&#8217;t missed a game yet, though, and he pushed through to provide a second-half spark Saturday.</p>
<p>Mfiondu Kabengele came off the bench to score 16 points, Forrest added 11 of his 13 points in the second half and the No. 18 Seminoles held off North Carolina State 78-73.</p>
<p>Forrest was quiet early but drove to the basket with ease in the second half, helping Florida State (23-6, 11-5 Atlantic Coast Conference) hold on. He shot 5 of 10 from the floor with a team-leading six rebounds, three assists and two steals.</p>
<p>&#8220;He&#8217;s a competitor,&#8221; Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#8220;He&#8217;s not 100 percent, but he gives you what he has every time he walks on the court. That&#8217;s the true measure of a person&#8217;s character is how do they respond under adversity.&#8221;</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Great atmosphere, Great game, Great opponent &amp; Great <a href="https://twitter.com/FSUHoops?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FSUHoops</a> win. See you Tuesday night! It’s the last one <a href="https://twitter.com/FSUTuckerCenter?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FSUTuckerCenter</a> until next season! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/1f362.png" alt="🍢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Go Noles<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/1f362.png" alt="🍢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/Ug2DCkeTQZ">pic.twitter.com/Ug2DCkeTQZ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dennis Gates (@coachdgates) <a href="https://twitter.com/coachdgates/status/1101938410590257157?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 2, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>The Wolfpack gave the Seminoles some adversity to deal with Saturday. While it never trailed, NC State kept clawing back and had a chance to win in the final minute.</p>
<p>Devon Daniels blocked Kabengele and Torin Dorn grabbed it with 24 seconds left and the Seminoles leading 76-73. After a timeout, Braxton Beverly dribbled the ball beyond the 3-point arc but was fouled.</p>
<p>He missed the front end of a 1-and-1, and Kabengele rebounded. He was quickly fouled, making two free-throw attempts to seal it.</p>
<p>&#8220;I thought we had our chances, especially late in the second half,&#8221; NC State coach Kevin Keatts said. &#8220;It seemed like every time we cut the lead they did a great job making a big play, whether it was an offensive rebound or getting a steal.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida State made enough plays down the stretch, holding on to win 11 ACC games for the second time in three seasons. Florida State has won 12 ACC games three times since joining the league in 1991-92. With two games remaining, it has a chance to match it or tie the mark.</p>
<p>DJ Funderburk fouled out with 1:09 left, tying a season high with 18 points and pulling down nine rebounds for NC State (20-9, 8-8). Dorn, who leads the Wolfpack in scoring at 13.9 points, was 0 for 4 from the floor in the first half but finished with 12 points.</p>
<p>M.J. Walker scored 11 of his 15 points in the first half, putting him in double figures for the first time since Feb. 9.</p>
<p>Kabengele shot 7 of 8 from the free-throw line while adding five rebounds and four of the Seminoles&#8217; season-high nine blocks. It was the 19th time in 29 games he has scored in double figures, with all of them coming as a reserve.</p>
<p>The Wolfpack shot just 26.7 percent (8 of 30) in the first half but hit 55.2 percent (16 of 29) in the second half. NC State stayed in the game behind consistent 3-point shooting, making 47.4 percent (9 of 19).</p>
<p>LATE-SEASON RUN</p>
<p>Florida State is 8-1 in February and March. The Seminoles opened ACC play at 1-4, including a buzzer-beating loss at home to No. 1 Duke. Since a Jan. 22 win over Clemson, the Seminoles have reeled off 10 victories in their last 11 games.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think it&#8217;s just the maturity,&#8221; Walker said. &#8220;We obviously understand what we need to be doing on and off the court. We know what&#8217;s at stake for us. We know how good we can be, the potential we have on this team.&#8221;</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State is in position to move up, possibly into the top 15, on the heels of consecutive wins over Notre Dame and NC State.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>NC State: The Wolfpack scored 34 bench points but lost for a third straight time at Florida State.</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles are 14-1 at home this season and 48-3 in their last 51 games in Tallahassee.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>NC State plays host to Georgia Tech on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Florida State plays host to Virginia Tech on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">460725</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Johnson, Maye lead No. 8 UNC past No. 16 FSU, 77-59</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/johnson-maye-lead-no-8-unc-past-no-16-fsu-77-59/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 04:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=458540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHAPEL HILL, N.C. (AP) — No. 8 North Carolina convincingly beat both of the Atlantic Coast Conference&#8217;s hottest teams over a four-day span. In the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHAPEL HILL, N.C. (AP) — No. 8 North Carolina convincingly beat both of the Atlantic Coast Conference&#8217;s hottest teams over a four-day span.</p>
<p>In the process, the Tar Heels laid claim to that honor for themselves.</p>
<p>Cameron Johnson had 18 points and 10 rebounds, and North Carolina routed No. 16 Florida State 77-59 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Luke Maye added 15 points and 11 rebounds, while freshman Nassir Little scored 18 points and Coby White finished with 10. The Tar Heels (22-5, 12-2) have won 10 of 11 to remain in a first-place tie.</p>
<p>They beat No. 1 Duke by 16 points on Wednesday night to snap the Blue Devils&#8217; nine-game winning streak. That was the longest such string in the ACC at the time, and Duke&#8217;s loss left Florida State and its eight-game streak as the best in the league.</p>
<p>That one&#8217;s over, too, thanks to the Tar Heels — who shot 48 percent in the second half while holding Florida State to 25 percent shooting after halftime.</p>
<p>&#8220;When we got back here Wednesday night, I talked to them. We did some good things. We got a win,&#8221; coach Roy Williams said. &#8220;You&#8217;ve got to keep playing or you&#8217;re going to give it back. We&#8217;ve had a couple of Ls in the Smith Center, so you&#8217;ve got to protect your home court.&#8221;</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Not our day.  Final from Chapel Hill. <a href="https://t.co/oyuNA69nRI">pic.twitter.com/oyuNA69nRI</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FSU Hoops (@FSUHoops) <a href="https://twitter.com/FSUHoops/status/1099440275804614657?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 23, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>David Nichols scored 16 points and Terance Mann added 10 for the Seminoles (21-6, 9-5), who had won eight straight but were held to a season-worst 31 percent shooting in their first loss in more than a month.</p>
<p>&#8220;A lot of it is their defensive schemes that took us out of some of the stuff we normally get around the basket,&#8221; coach Leonard Hamilton said. &#8220;We&#8217;ve got to have a quick recovery.&#8221;</p>
<p>RaiQuan Gray pulled Florida State to 56-52 with a 3-pointer with 10½ minutes remaining. Maye followed that by sandwiching a pair of 3s — including one he banked in from about 25 feet — around a contested jumper by Little to give the Tar Heels all the breathing room they needed.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles were trying for their first five-game winning streak in ACC road games since 2014, but the Smith Center wasn&#8217;t exactly the ideal venue for that pursuit. Florida State fell to 4-18 here, with only one victory since 2000.</p>
<p>North Carolina: The Tar Heels haven&#8217;t exactly ducked anyone during their surge, either. This was their 10th game of the season against an opponent ranked in the top 19 of the AP Top 25, and they improved to 7-3 against them, with wins in five of six and the loss coming to a third-ranked Virginia team with which they share the ACC lead.</p>
<p>TRENDING</p>
<p>So much for the idea of a Duke hangover. The Tar Heels improved to 30-3 under Williams in their games immediately following their matchups with the Blue Devils, who were without star Zion Williamson for virtually the entire game on Wednesday. All three losses have come in ACC Tournament openers over the years after facing Duke in regular-season finales.</p>
<p>STAR WATCH</p>
<p>Johnson reached double figures for the eighth straight game and is averaging 21.8 points during his last four games, with three Top 25 opponents — No. 3 Virginia, the Blue Devils and the Seminoles — in that stretch.</p>
<p>&#8220;Just as the season gets on, gaining more experience and kind of getting more comfortable with everything, it&#8217;s always big at this time of year,&#8221; Johnson said. &#8220;Just staying in the gym has been helpful.&#8221;</p>
<p>KEY STAT</p>
<p>The Tar Heels have spent the week simply dominating the lanes. North Carolina outscored Florida State 28-12 in the paint three nights after outscoring Duke 62-28 there. UNC also held a 47-32 rebounding advantage over the Seminoles. &#8220;That&#8217;s something that we emphasize all the time,&#8221; Williams said of the rebounding edge, &#8220;so you should do things better if it&#8217;s what you emphasize the most.&#8221;</p>
<p>KEY MATCHUP</p>
<p>Christ Koumadje, who&#8217;s 7-foot-4, entered averaging 13.3 points and 10.3 rebounds during his last three games and had two double-doubles in that stretch. He finished this one with six points and four rebounds in 14 minutes. After shooting 76 percent in his previous three games, he was 2 of 5.</p>
<p>HE SAID IT</p>
<p>&#8220;You haven&#8217;t heard the last of the Seminoles&#8221; — Hamilton, with a smile.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: visits Notre Dame on Monday night.</p>
<p>North Carolina: plays host to Syracuse on Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">458540</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Koumadje leads No. 17 Florida State past Georgia Tech 69-47</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/koumadje-leads-no-17-florida-state-past-georgia-tech-69-47/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 06:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=456403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — Christ Koumadje and No. 17 Florida State featured a balanced scoring approach. Georgia Tech could barely score — again. Koumadje had 10...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — Christ Koumadje and No. 17 Florida State featured a balanced scoring approach. Georgia Tech could barely score — again.</p>
<p>Koumadje had 10 points and 12 rebounds as the Seminoles tied a school record with their seventh straight ACC win, 69-47 Saturday.</p>
<p>Freshman Devin Vassell came off the bench to score a team-high 11 while playing in his hometown for the Seminoles (20-5, 8-4). Seven Florida State players scored between seven and 11 points.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech (11-15, 3-10) lost its seventh straight ACC game with another offensive struggle.</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/270c-1f3ff.png" alt="✌🏿" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/1f590-1f3ff.png" alt="🖐🏿" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> in a row!  <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NolesWin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NolesWin</a> <a href="https://t.co/fYshBWL68l">pic.twitter.com/fYshBWL68l</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FSU Hoops (@FSUHoops) <a href="https://twitter.com/FSUHoops/status/1096876499930628096?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 16, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>Jose Alvarado broke out of a lengthy slump with 17 points, but the Yellow Jackets made just 8 of 36 shots from inside the 3-point arc. They&#8217;re averaging 53.1 points in their skid after their seventh and eighth halves scoring 25 or fewer points.</p>
<p>The 7-foot-4 Koumadje took just seven shots, making five. He was even more of a factor on the defensive end as he blocked three shots as Tech made just 6 of 28 in the paint. The Jackets&#8217; big men, James Banks III (two points) and Abdoulaye Gueye (five) made a combined 3 of 16.</p>
<p>Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton said the Jackets play, &#8220;probably the best match-up zone scheme that I&#8217;ve seen in my coaching career.&#8221; While the Seminoles shot 39.1 percent, the Jackets&#8217; imbalance on the offensive end saw them fall behind by as many as 27 in the second half.</p>
<p>The teams were tied at 10 early before the Jackets fell into the first of multiple shooting freezes, and Florida State stretched the lead to 31-15 on a layup by Terance Mann with 4:27 left.</p>
<p>Phil Cofer, David Nichols and Vassell each a pair of 3-pointers in the first half for FSU before Banks finally got loose for a dunk shortly before halftime to pull Tech within 34-23.</p>
<p>Hamilton said his team &#8220;crowded&#8221; Gueye with frequent double teams on most of his possessions. When Tech stationed Banks at the high post, the Seminoles sagged off him and let him shooter jumpers.</p>
<p>Banks missed every one of those and hit just 1 of 9 overall. All Jackets other than Alvarado — who made 6 of 11 to snap out of a six-game streak in which he made 10 of 59 — connected on just 10 of 48 shots, or 20.8 percent.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our guys give everything they have on the defensive end &#8230; we give ourselves a chance,&#8221; Tech coach Josh Pastner said. &#8220;We have just had a real issue with scoring.&#8221;</p>
<p>SPREADING IT AROUND</p>
<p>Tech often doubled Florida State leading scorer Mfiondu Kabengele, who had eight points on 2 of 5 shooting, but Mann wasn&#8217;t surprised by his team&#8217;s offensive balance, nor that Vassell became the ninth player this season to lead Florida State in scoring.</p>
<p>&#8220;Christ is coming into his own,&#8221; Mann said after having seven points and eight rebounds in a game where the Seminoles had a 50-38 rebounding edge. &#8220;That&#8217;s just what we do. We&#8217;re 18 strong. Every night it&#8217;s different.&#8221;</p>
<p>SICK AND TIRED</p>
<p>Tech played without sophomore forward Evan Cole, an occasional starter, and assistant Julian Schwartz was not at the game because they&#8217;re both fighting flu-like symptoms. Pastner said, &#8220;I didn&#8217;t know until this morning if (Alvarado and starting guard Michael Devoe) were going to play. They weren&#8217;t able to practice the last couple days.&#8221;</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The first time the Seminoles put together a seven-game ACC winning streak, in the 2011-&#8217;12 season, they went on to win the ACC Tournament. This also cemented a fourth consecutive season with 20 or more wins overall, matching a run from 2009-&#8217;12 that also was under Hamilton.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech: The Jackets keep churning their lineup, as freshman forward Kristian Sjolund made his first start and sophomore Moses Wright started for the first time in more than a month. Sjolund scored 19 points in Tech&#8217;s previous two games after scoring just nine combined all season before that, and he can shoot. They were replaced to start the second half by Gueye and Brandon Alston. Sjolund had 11 points, including 3 of 7 3-pointers, and Wright scored two.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: Will play Tuesday at Clemson.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech: Will be at home Wednesday against Pitt.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">456403</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida State trio combines for no-hitter in opener</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-state-trio-combines-for-no-hitter-in-opener/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Junette Reyes]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 15:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=456277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Drew Parrish and relievers Conor Grady and Chase Haney combined for Florida State&#8217;s 10th no-hitter in the Seminoles&#8217; 11-0 season-opening victory...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Drew Parrish and relievers Conor Grady and Chase Haney combined for Florida State&#8217;s 10th no-hitter in the Seminoles&#8217; 11-0 season-opening victory over Maine on Friday.</p>
<p>Parrish went five innings, striking out five and walking one. Grady struck out four and walked one in three innings, and Haney had a strikeout and a walk in the ninth.</p>
<p>&#8220;This was so much fun,&#8221; said coach Mike Martin, beginning his final season with the Seminoles. &#8220;It&#8217;s very special. The closest that I think we&#8217;ve come to a no-hitter on opening day was us getting one-hit.&#8221;</p>
<p>Freshman designated hitter Robby Martin was 3 for 4 with RBIs, and Reese Albert and J.C. Flowers homered.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">456277</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ogunbowale, Shepard lead No. 4 Irish to rout of No. 24 FSU</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ogunbowale-shepard-lead-no-4-irish-to-rout-of-no-24-fsu/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 05:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=454412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Muffet McGraw got the effort she wanted from No. 4 Notre Dame right from the start Sunday, especially from Arike...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Muffet McGraw got the effort she wanted from No. 4 Notre Dame right from the start Sunday, especially from Arike Ogunbowale, in a 97-70 rout of No. 24 Florida State.</p>
<p>&#8220;She looked like she was enjoying herself out there,&#8221; McGraw said after Ogunbowale, who has been struggling of late, scored 27 points. Jessica Shepard added 26 as the Fighting Irish, who had two rare Atlantic Coast Conference losses in their last four games, rebounded from Thursday&#8217;s 72-65 defeat at No. 25 Miami.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve got to be aggressive from the start — I&#8217;ve been kind of laid back,&#8221; said Ogunbowale, who had 13 points on 4-of-15 shooting against the Hurricanes but hit her first four shots against the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Ogunbowale had made just 20 of 61 shots in her previous four games, which began with then-No. 1 Notre Dame&#8217;s 78-73 loss at North Carolina on Jan. 27.</p>
<div class="embed-twitter">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Noles?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Noles</a> fall to 8-3 in the ACC.</p>
<p>We&#39;ve got another big one at Clemson on Thursday. <a href="https://t.co/Lddut4MLdF">pic.twitter.com/Lddut4MLdF</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FSU Women&#39;s Hoops (@fsuwbb) <a href="https://twitter.com/fsuwbb/status/1094668987353481216?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 10, 2019</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div>
<p>Her 27 points, on 9-of-16 shooting including 5 of 7 from beyond the 3-point line, left Ogunbowale with 2,301 career points, 21 behind current Irish assistant coach Beth (Morgan) Cunningham. Skylar Diggins-Smith is the all-time leader at 2,357. Ogunbowale also had nine rebounds, five assists, two steals and had zero turnovers for Notre Dame (21-3, 9-2 ACC), which turned the ball over just 10 times.</p>
<p>&#8220;I was happy with the offense,&#8221; McGraw said as the Irish shot 52.9 percent (36 of 68) and had a 43-36 edge on the boards after shooting a season-low 37.3 percent and being outrebounded 46-37 at Miami. &#8220;We were able to get the break going because we rebounded better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Shepard had eight rebounds with two assists, including one from her knees when she fed Ogunbowale for a corner 3-pointer that gave Notre Dame a 45-33 lead in the second quarter.</p>
<p>&#8220;Arike made a great pass to me and I probably blew it,&#8221; Shepard said. &#8220;I remember seeing her out there and found a way to tip her the ball. Coming off a loss, it was important to come out strong.&#8221;</p>
<p>Brianna Turner had 13 points, five blocks and four assists, and Jackie Young had 10 points and five assists for the Irish, who had 25 assists, led by Marina Mabrey&#8217;s six.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think they are the best transition team in the country,&#8221; Florida State coach Sue Semrau said. &#8220;We knew with our young pups coming in here that it was going to be a huge challenge and it was.&#8221;</p>
<p>Nicki Ekhomu scored 26 points, Kiah Gillespie added 17 and Nausia Woolfolk had 15 before fouling out as the Seminoles (20-4, 8-3) lost for the first time on the road this season.</p>
<p>The game was tied 2-2 before the Irish opened up a 22-12 first-quarter lead at 4:02 on a 3-pointer by Ogunbowale. Notre Dame led 28-22 after a turnover-less first quarter.</p>
<p>The Seminoles made just 5 of 15 shots in the second quarter and Notre Dame opened a 52-38 halftime lead with the help of a 9-0 run.</p>
<p>The Irish used a 15-0 run to start the third quarter for a 67-40 lead with 3:34 to go as Florida State, after making its first shot, missed its next 10 in a 6-minute scoring drought. It was 74-50 after three quarters.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles came into the game with an ACC-leading plus-4.8 turnover margin but made 10 in the first half. It also didn&#8217;t help that Florida State missed its first six shots of the second quarter. Notre Dame never trailed and had 16-point leads at several occasions in the first half before pulling away in the third quarter when the Seminoles hit just 4 of 20 shots. They finished at 34.3 percent (24 of 70).</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Fighting Irish, who were averaging almost 15 turnovers a game, made just four in the first half. The Irish&#8217;s transition game, lacking in the loss at Miami, also got going and Notre Dame had 13 assists on its 20 first-half field goals. They finished with 25 assists on 36 field goals. But defense still concerns McGraw.</p>
<p>&#8220;We could have put them away really early,&#8221; she said. &#8220;We kept giving them 3s. They average three 3s a game and they had nine. We&#8217;ve got to do better.&#8221;</p>
<p>FROM THE BENCH</p>
<p>Freshman Abby Prohaska had nearly 23 minutes on the floor and scored six points with five rebounds, two assists and two steals. But McGraw believes her 5-foot-10 guard can do more when she gives Ogunbowale, Young and Marina Mabrey rest.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think she can bring more, I do,&#8221; McGraw said after also giving freshman point guard Jordan Nixon extended minutes early in the game.</p>
<p>Sophomore Mikayla Vaughn, who hyperextended the knee on which she had ACL surgery last season in a 90-50 victory over Georgia Tech on Feb. 3, left the game with 2:57 to go in the first half after going down hard battling for a rebound. McGraw said she suffered a concussion and probably would miss the next game.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State plays at Clemson on Thursday.</p>
<p>Notre Dame plays at Boston College on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">454412</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
