<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Hope and Healing &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 22:27:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Hope and Healing &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Chemo Kits</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-chemo-kits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanah Faroke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 22:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=408691</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One South Florida woman turned her battle with cancer into a business that is inspiring other cancer patients around the world. 7&#8217;s Gina Benitez has...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One South Florida woman turned her battle with cancer into a business that is inspiring other cancer patients around the world. 7&#8217;s Gina Benitez has this report of &#8220;Hope and Healing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Like most 28-year-olds, Jessica didn&#8217;t have a worry in the world.</p>
<p>Jessica DeCristofaro, cancer survivor: &#8220;I was 28. I was used to going out every weekend, dating, just doing things that a normal 28-year-old would do. And all of a sudden, I was diagnosed with cancer, and I&#8217;m not sure what&#8217;s going to happen next.&#8221;</p>
<p>In 2016, she was rushed to the hospital in respiratory failure. The diagnosis was cancer, Stage 4 Hodgkin&#8217;s lymphoma.</p>
<p>The cancer spread to every organ in her body. Her doctors immediately started chemotherapy.</p>
<p>Jessica DeCristofaro: &#8220;I think I went crazy when my hair was falling out in clumps. It was the most mortifying thing I have ever dealt with in my whole life. You just don&#8217;t feel good about yourself. It&#8217;s depressing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Friends say, no matter how hard it got, Jessica kept a smile on her face and stayed motivated.</p>
<p>Noelle Pellar, Jessica&#8217;s friend: &#8220;She kept doing her facials and kept her skin routine. She got dressed, she made herself look good. She didn&#8217;t give up.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now cancer free, Jessica wants to help other patients stay motivated and feel better.</p>
<p>She created care packages she calls Chemo Kits. Each box is put together by Jessica and her friends in her Miami apartment, then shipped out around the world.</p>
<p>Jessica DeCristofaro: &#8220;They write me messages all the time saying how much they love them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Noelle Pellar: &#8220;Going through it first-hand, she knows what people need when they&#8217;re going through this.&#8221;</p>
<p>Every item in the box is personal to Jessica and her cancer experience. Items like lip balm, because chemo made her lips dry.</p>
<p>The boxes also have popsicle makers. Jessica says she used popsicles to get rid of the weird taste chemo left in her mouth.</p>
<p>There is also a head wrap, like the one she used when she lost her hair.</p>
<p>Noelle Pellar: &#8220;Jessica put so much thought into what she would want when she was going through chemo and what would have helped her.&#8221;</p>
<p>The most important thing in the box? A card with a special note from Jessica.</p>
<p>Jessica DeCristofaro: &#8220;&#8216;Everyone has a journey to take, and I believe this one will make you stronger than you already are.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Jessica says these Chemo Kits are more than a business; they are a part of her healing process.</p>
<p>She hopes they will bring others hope and healing, too.</p>
<p>Jessica DeCristofaro: &#8220;It just helps remind me of what I&#8217;ve been through and helps me keep my feet on the ground.&#8221;</p>
<p>Each Chemo Kit costs $29.99. If you would like to learn more about Jessica&#8217;s story or Chemo Kits go to the links below.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p>Chemo Kits:<br />
<a href="https://chemo-kits.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://chemo-kits.com/</a></p>
<p>Jessica on Instagram:<br />
<a href="https://www.instagram.com/jessdecris/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.instagram.com/jessdecris/?hl=en</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">408691</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180827_chemo_kits.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/98d36f72-0761-4247-bebb-e775f523e7e4/mid.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216681~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/98d36f72-0761-4247-bebb-e775f523e7e4/mid.mp4*~hmac=0a4f33206d4a947fe38a1b0dc79f77e9bbe297542a1afa64f5efb8cba66eaa04' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180827_chemo_kits.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180827_chemo_kits.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180827_chemo_kits</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Deputy&#8217;s act of kindness saves homeless man</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-deputys-act-of-kindness-saves-homeless-man/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=336508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Law enforcement is there to protect and serve, but one local deputy has taken his calling well beyond that. 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens shows us how...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Law enforcement is there to protect and serve, but one local deputy has taken his calling well beyond that. 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens shows us how he has dramatically changed one man&#8217;s life in tonight&#8217;s Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie patrols the streets of Deerfield Beach.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie, Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office: &#8220;I&#8217;m just a regular deputy on road patrol, working street crimes at night.&#8221;</p>
<p>He has experienced a lot in his years with the Broward County Sheriff&#8217;s Office, but a call he received one night in 2008 changed his life forever.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;A homeless person in the middle of the roadway at Dixie and Hillsboro Boulevard, and that was my first encounter with Steve.&#8221;</p>
<p>Steve, who had been homeless for some time at that point, appeared to be at the end of his rope.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;Not good. He was erratic. He had a lot of medical issues, and that scared people. That&#8217;s why they called.&#8221;</p>
<p>That call stayed with Deputy Barrie, and he kept tabs on Steve.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;I would come in contact with him. I would hear other deputies come in contact with him on the radio.&#8221;</p>
<p>Then one day, Deputy Barrie decided he wanted to know more about this homeless man, so he took him for lunch at McDonald&#8217;s, and over a simple fish sandwich, he heard an unexpected life story.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;I learned that he&#8217;s a graduate of UCF with a degree in accounting, that he grew up right here in Boca Raton. He once had a family that thrived here in the area.&#8221;</p>
<p>Steve says he was once a successful accountant, but when his mom died, he became depressed.</p>
<p>First he lost his job, and then his home.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;Some people, if they don&#8217;t have the resources around them or the network of family and friends, once that network disappears, you have nothing. So, he needed a friend.&#8221;</p>
<p>And that&#8217;s when this patrolman decided to become the patron for a man who had nothing.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;Actually took my own money and put him in a hotel, got him in there, and I said, &#8216;Here&#8217;s our plan.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The deputy started reaching out to agencies to get Steve his social security and disability benefits.</p>
<p>He even found out the homeless man had a pension he wasn&#8217;t collecting.</p>
<p>Steve Wend, formerly homeless: &#8220;He was very helpful to me, he&#8217;s understanding towards me.&#8221;</p>
<p>And now he&#8217;s making sure Steve has a solid future.</p>
<p>Steve Wend: &#8220;I got a place to live. He owns free and clear, a one-bedroom, one-bath condo.&#8221;</p>
<p>Steve bought his own place with the money he was owed from the government and lives independently &#8212; with Mark checking in on him once a week.</p>
<p>Now Steve dreams about once again taking up a favorite hobby.</p>
<p>Steve Wend: &#8220;I used to like to go fishing. I like to fish.&#8221;</p>
<p>Deputy Barrie hopes sharing Steve&#8217;s story will inspire others to also reach out.</p>
<p>Deputy Mark Barrie: &#8220;Steve&#8217;s a good guy, and everybody should reach out. There&#8217;s a lot of Steves out there.&#8221;</p>
<p>Deputy Barrie tells us Broward County has homeless outreach specialists at each district office.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong><br />
Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office<br />
<a href="http://www.sheriff.org/Pages/Home.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.sheriff.org/Pages/Home.aspx</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">336508</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180303-hope-healing1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5744243320001_5744238503001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5744238503001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180303-hope-healing1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180303-hope-healing1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180303 hope healing</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Haiti Mentor</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-haiti-mentor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanah Faroke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=311327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Haitian immigrant has a bright future thanks to a South Florida businessman. In tonight&#8217;s Hope And Healing report, 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens shows us how...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Haitian immigrant has a bright future thanks to a South Florida businessman. In tonight&#8217;s Hope And Healing report, 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens shows us how these two very different people are making a huge impact on one another&#8217;s lives.</p>
<p>All smiles and surrounded by friends, Garsendy may look like any other teen.</p>
<p>But dig a little deeper, and you&#8217;ll find out his life hasn&#8217;t always been this happy.</p>
<p>Garsendy St. Fleur, high school senior: &#8220;I&#8217;m from Haiti. I was born in Port-au-Prince. The people get mad at the government and there&#8217;s always fighting.&#8221;</p>
<p>Garsendy always dreamed of being the first in his family to get a college degree.</p>
<p>Garsendy St. Fleur: &#8220;I want to go to college and study business.&#8221;</p>
<p>But for a teen in Haiti, just getting a job out of high school can be a challenge.</p>
<p>Garsendy St. Fleur: &#8220;There&#8217;s not a lot of opportunities. You need to have a friend or family so they can try to get you a connection to get the job.&#8221;</p>
<p>So when the family moved to the U.S., Garsendy swore he would make his college dream come true.</p>
<p>But he quickly learned it was going to be an uphill battle.</p>
<p>Garsendy St. Fleur: &#8220;My English wasn&#8217;t that good, but I still understood what someone was saying to me &#8212; but I didn&#8217;t know how to respond back.&#8221;</p>
<p>He studied hard and enrolled in an after-school program called Propel.</p>
<p>Gregg Francis, CEO of Propel: &#8220;He came on board a shy individual, but I never met somebody who worked so hard.&#8221;</p>
<p>The program helps with tutoring for high school classes and college entrance exams. Garsendy excelled.</p>
<p>Gregg Francis: &#8220;Not only does he carry a 3.7 GPA, but his character is above and beyond that.&#8221;</p>
<p>He did so well, in fact, that he caught the attention of Richard Weissman.</p>
<p>The CEO of a nationwide preschool program called The Learning Experience wanted to become Garsendy&#8217;s mentor.</p>
<p>Richard Weissman, CEO, The Learning Experience: &#8220;He respected himself so much that not once in communication that I had with him did he ever complain about everynything. He asked for guidance.&#8221;</p>
<p>Richard gave Garsendy a summer job, and after two years, their relationship grew.</p>
<p>Richard Weissman: &#8220;He understands that he can talk to me, and he understands that I&#8217;m here to support him, but that&#8217;s a two-way street.&#8221;</p>
<p>Richard now sees Garsendy as a part of his family. He is even offering to pay for part of his college.</p>
<p>Richard Weissman: &#8220;I put him in the same caliber as my kids.&#8221;</p>
<p>Garsendy St. Fleur: &#8220;I never expected somebody to help me that much. I would love to follow in his steps.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Richard says he gets just as much inspiration from the relationship.</p>
<p>Richard Weissman: &#8220;I don&#8217;t think I&#8217;m as much of a man as he is.&#8221;</p>
<p>And this young man hopes to make his mentor proud when he heads off to college next year.</p>
<p>Garsendy hopes to get accepted to Florida Atlantic University and enroll in the fall.</p>
<p>To learn more about Propel and the programs they offer, go to the links below.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p>Propel:<br />
<a href="https://www.propelyourfuture.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.propelyourfuture.org/</a></p>
<p>The Learning Experience:<br />
<a href="https://www.thelearningexperience.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.thelearningexperience.com/</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">311327</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/01/180119_garsendy_st_fleur.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/01/180119_garsendy_st_fleur.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/01/180119_garsendy_st_fleur.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180119_Garsendy_St_Fleur</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: South Floridians help less fortunate during holidays</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/south-floridians-help-less-fortunate-during-holidays/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanah Faroke]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 04:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=303766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s the season of giving, and that means helping those less fortunate. 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens is here now to show us how some South Floridians...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s the season of giving, and that means helping those less fortunate. 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens is here now to show us how some South Floridians are making a difference.</p>
<p>Sleeping on the streets is a grim reality for the homeless in South Florida.</p>
<p>Thomas Foley knows how easily life can take a turn for the worse.</p>
<p>Thomas Foley, helping homeless: &#8220;A couple of years back, I was not as fortunate as I am today to have a place to live. I was sleeping on a family member&#8217;s couch. Homeless? No. Out in the streets? No, but just about as close as you can possibly get to it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Life is good now, and from his home in Davie, he is working to help those in need.</p>
<p>Thomas Foley: &#8220;This is all for one person.&#8221;</p>
<p>Thomas and his girlfriend Sonia are busy putting together special care packages for homeless people in Broward.</p>
<p>Sonia Millet, helping homeless: &#8220;It&#8217;s a blessing that we can share with others.&#8221;</p>
<p>Each bag has about $100 worth of non-perishable food, toiletries, a rain poncho, a blanket, even a gift card to Dunkin&#8217; Donuts!</p>
<p>Thomas Foley: &#8220;We have the ability to help these people, so why not? There&#8217;s no reason why we can&#8217;t take what we have and share.&#8221;</p>
<p>Eighteen-year-old Erika Castroman feels the same way.</p>
<p>Erika Castroman, helping homeless: &#8220;We decided to do everyday necessities because they&#8217;re pretty much out there with nothing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Last year, a chance encounter with a homeless man inspired her to create a Facebook page called Stockings Filled with Love, drumming up support and donations.</p>
<p>Erika Castroman: &#8220;We ask people for donations like everyday necessities, food, water, soap, tissues.&#8221;</p>
<p>She and her family gave out 50 backpacks last year. This year they&#8217;ll double that number. Their home in Hialeah is a staging area, getting everything ready to be delivered in Downtown Miami on Christmas morning.</p>
<p>Ivette Castroman, helping homeless: &#8220;I am very proud of her, we both are. I love that she came up with this idea, because it is something that we can do to give back to the community.&#8221;</p>
<p>For this American High School senior, it has been a life-changing experience.</p>
<p>Erika Castroman: &#8220;I&#8217;ve learned that I shouldn&#8217;t take what I have for granted. There&#8217;s so many people out there who don&#8217;t have the same opportunities as me, so this makes me feel really great, giving them and showing them love.&#8221;</p>
<p>Giving during the holidays is rewarding, and these families say it will be an ongoing tradition for them.</p>
<p>Thomas Foley: &#8220;If you see someone out there that needs a helping hand and you have the ability, whether it&#8217;s a Monday, a year from now or today, just help. That&#8217;s what we&#8217;re all about.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bringing the spirit of Christmas, hope and healing, to those who need it most.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">303766</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/12/171222_hope_and_healing.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5691205371001_5691128997001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5691128997001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/12/171222_hope_and_healing.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/12/171222_hope_and_healing.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">171222_hope_and_healing</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Norland Senior High teacher inspires students to become authors</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-norland-senior-high-teacher-inspires-students-to-become-authors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Erica Santiago]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=236696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When 16 students were told, &#8220;No, you can&#8217;t&#8221; one teacher told them, &#8220;Yes, you can.&#8221; And now those students, who go to one of the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When 16 students were told, &#8220;No, you can&#8217;t&#8221; one teacher told them, &#8220;Yes, you can.&#8221; And now those students, who go to one of the roughest schools in Miami-Dade County, are book authors! 7&#8217;s Robbin Simmons has their story of Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>Inspiration comes to us in different ways. For these Miami Norland Senior High School students, inspiration comes from hardship &#8212; a hardship they learned to embrace.</p>
<p>Glenda Moton, Miami Norland Senior High: &#8220;Good afternoon, everybody.&#8221;</p>
<p>Students: &#8220;Good afternoon.&#8221;</p>
<p>Glenda Moton has been a teacher for 18 years.</p>
<p>She has a kind and encouraging voice, and a mutual respect with her students.</p>
<p>Ms. Moton was reading a book in class about three African-American teenage boys who made a pact to beat the streets and become successful doctors. That&#8217;s when she realized&#8230;</p>
<p>Glenda Moton: &#8220;My students were experiencing some of the same challenges that they experienced when they were growing up.&#8221;</p>
<p>So she had an idea. She would encourage her students to write their own book.</p>
<p>Glenda Moton: &#8220;I said, &#8216;How would you all like to write your own personal narratives in the form of a poem or a short story?'&#8221;</p>
<p>Trachell, student author: &#8220;I was really excited when she proposed the idea to write a book.&#8221;</p>
<p>But it wasn&#8217;t easy.</p>
<p>Sunsurray Wyn, concerned parent: &#8220;They need to find a better solution to keep the guns out of school.&#8221;</p>
<p>These students have faced gun scares at the school. They&#8217;ve also had classmates gunned down in some of the roughest neighborhoods in Miami-Dade County.</p>
<p>In addition to all that, Rodney lost his father last year to a deadly disease.</p>
<p>Rodney Vaughn, student author: &#8220;I really thought this was a great way for me to open up and show others how I felt.&#8221;</p>
<p>Other students struggle with how others treat them.</p>
<p>Shanice, student author: &#8220;Being told you&#8217;re a failure.&#8221;</p>
<p>Alisha, student author: &#8220;I am constantly reminded that I could be a failure.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Ms. Moton encouraged students in this class to turn their failure into success by facing criticism head on.</p>
<p>Breanna, student author (reading): &#8220;She really loved him, and with her happiness came mine as well.&#8221;</p>
<p>She told them to dig deeper into their troubles, put it on paper.</p>
<p>Allasia, student author (reading): &#8220;But things must die before they turn beautiful to the max.&#8221;</p>
<p>And what they made was beautiful.</p>
<p>Asayah, student author (reading): &#8220;Live life and be proud of who you are, and not who people want you to be.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ms. Moton was so proud of what her students created, she got a grant and threw in some of her own money to publish their work. The book is called &#8220;iRead, iThink, iWrite.&#8221;</p>
<p>Glenda Moton: &#8220;I always tell my students, even though we&#8217;re in Miami Gardens, that they don&#8217;t have to become a victim of your community, but that they can become a success.&#8221;</p>
<p>Proceeds from the book will be used for other writing projects and for scholarships for the students. If you would like to find out how to purchase one, click on the link below.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong><br />
iRead, iThink, iWrite<br />
<a href="https://www.lulu.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.lulu.com/</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">236696</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/06/170906hopehealing.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5466586857001_5466567913001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5466567913001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/06/170906hopehealing.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/06/170906hopehealing.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170906HopeHealing</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope And Healing: Buzz Boxx</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-buzz-boxx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=218332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Can something as simple as a haircut change your life? One South Florida organization thinks so. 7&#8217;s Katrina Bush shows us how some local entrepreneurs...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Can something as simple as a haircut change your life? One South Florida organization thinks so. 7&#8217;s Katrina Bush shows us how some local entrepreneurs are creating quite the &#8220;buzz&#8221; in tonight&#8217;s edition of &#8220;Hope and Healing.&#8221;</p>
<p>You&#8217;d never guess it from the smile on Michael&#8217;s face, but he has faced some tough times.</p>
<p>Michael Caraballo, founder of Talent 4 Change: &#8220;My parents were drug addicts. I was born in Puerto Rico. Coming to the U.S. was my introduction to hell, because the first community I moved into was the projects.&#8221;</p>
<p>He remembers being picked on in school because he couldn&#8217;t afford nice things.</p>
<figure id="attachment_218333" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-218333" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-218333" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_michael_caraballo.jpg?w=300" alt="" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_michael_caraballo.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_michael_caraballo.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-218333" class="wp-caption-text">Michael Caraballo</figcaption></figure>
<p>Michael Caraballo: &#8220;People tend to frown and look down on you when you don&#8217;t look right, don&#8217;t look cleaned up.&#8221;</p>
<p>So he&#8217;s helping South Florida kids clean up, one haircut at a time.</p>
<p>Michael Caraballo: &#8220;Well we&#8217;ve had plenty of kids that would tell us how important a haircut is to them. Maybe they didn&#8217;t want to go to school because they&#8217;re embarrassed.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Michael doesn&#8217;t run a traditional barber shop. This is a mini mobile shop inside a shipping crate called Buzz Boxx. And it is creating quite the buzz!</p>
<p>Kids earn a free haircut by doing good in school or helping their community.</p>
<p>Tina Brown, Overtown Youth Center: &#8220;We will use this concept as another way to tie in incentives.&#8221;</p>
<p>This box is headed to the Overtown Youth Center, but the goal is to have a Buzz Boxx at organizations across South Florida.</p>
<p>And these kids aren&#8217;t just getting a haircut. The barbers double as mentors.</p>
<p>Ladon Quivette, Barber Love Barbershop: &#8220;I go from being a barber to Auntie to Mama, so those are the types of reactions I get because I give them that. I&#8217;m genuine.&#8221;</p>
<p>Felecia Hatcher, co-founder of Code Fever: &#8220;You never know, just a random conversation or a haircut can turn into so many things.&#8221;</p>
<p>Today is Clifton&#8217;s turn in the barber chair. The 15-year-old lost his dad when he was 2. He says it&#8217;s been hard not having a father figure in his life.</p>
<p>Clifton Ross, 15-years-old: &#8220;When I was younger, I didn&#8217;t have really good common sense because I always liked to play around, get in trouble.&#8221;</p>
<p>For him, sitting in this chair, talking to someone he trusts helps him see how much support he has around him. And Clifton and Michael believe, if you feel good, you do good, and they hope these boxes continue to create a positive buzz.</p>
<p>Clifton Ross: &#8220;Everybody in my community loves me and helps me out. I guess that&#8217;s what really motivates me, too.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Buzz Boxx team recently took first place in a Philanthropy Miami competition! Congrats to them! And Buzz Boxx is just one of the mentoring programs offered by the Talent 4 Change organization.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.talent4change.org/" target="_blank">Talent 4 Change</a></p>
<p><a href="http://buzzitforward.com/" target="_blank">Buzz It Forward</a></p>
<p><a href="http://overtownyouth.org/" target="_blank">Overtown Youth Center</a></p>
<p><a href="http://barberlove.com/" target="_blank">Barber Love Barbershop</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">218332</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_buzz_boxx_haircut.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5377154703001_5377148805001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5377148805001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_buzz_boxx_haircut.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_buzz_boxx_haircut.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170328_Buzz_Boxx_haircut</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170328_michael_caraballo.jpg?w=300" medium="image" />
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bikes Up Gunz Down</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/bikes-up-gunz-down/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Riggin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 03:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=212883</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Life in the inner city can be violent, and as young kids grow into teens, life-changing choices are made. As 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens tells us,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Life in the inner city can be violent, and as young kids grow into teens, life-changing choices are made. As 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens tells us, one man in Liberty City is working to make sure those choices are good ones, by encouraging kids to pick their bikes up and put guns down for good.</p>
<p>They come to ride. Kids, bonding over bikes, and bad times.</p>
<p>Dwight Wells, Bikes Up Gunz Down: &#8220;When I say King, y&#8217;all say Carter.&#8221;</p>
<p>Chanting the names of those lost to senseless street violence, so their young lives are never forgotten.</p>
<p>Dwight Wells: &#8220;When I say Jada, you say Page.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dwight Wells wants the killing to stop. That&#8217;s why he started &#8220;Bikes Up Gunz Down.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dwight Wells: &#8220;We started off with the kids on the bikes, doing tricks, and I seen that bikes was always a part of our culture. Keeping a gun out of their hands is the main objective, and that&#8217;s what we&#8217;re all about.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dwight knows how violence ruins lives. When he was younger, he spent 10 years in prison for second-degree murder. While he was behind bars, a friend&#8217;s baby was killed in a shootout. He says that changed him forever.</p>
<p>Dwight Wells: &#8220;Eighteen months old and shot directly in the head with a AK-47. And when I was in that institution, behind those walls, I told myself, I said, &#8216;When I get back out I&#8217;m going to change Miami-Dade County.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Now, he makes it his mission to keep kids busy on their bikes, organizing group rides where they learn about black history.</p>
<p>Bikes Up Gunz Down instructor: &#8220;OK, this graveyard where we at right now, Lincoln Memorial Park, it was built in the 1950s.&#8221;</p>
<p>After school, he coaches the serious riders.</p>
<p>Dwight Wells: &#8220;We go up to the roof, go up to the roof and practice. We use the area to &#8216;cat walk.&#8217; They learn various tricks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Teaching tricks like &#8220;cat-walking,&#8221; riding with one wheel up.</p>
<p>Oscar Lopez: &#8220;It makes me feel alive, free.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sixteen-year-old Oscar Lopez has been in the group for four years.</p>
<p>Oscar Lopez: &#8220;Bikes bring bonds. It was hard for me to, like, fit in. But then I just fit in with the pack, and it was just like a good experience for me, and it still is.&#8221;</p>
<p>The teens practice every day, perfecting their tricks.</p>
<p>Jayquan Hill: &#8220;I&#8217;m in my own world, you know. &#8220;It&#8217;s just me and my bike &#8212; nothing else. It&#8217;s like a stress reliever. It&#8217;s like a pill.&#8221;</p>
<p>Under Dwight&#8217;s watchful eye, they work off their daily frustrations and have fun.</p>
<p>Duran Hill: &#8220;My parents, they think it&#8217;s the best thing I ever did &#8217;cause, you know, it&#8217;s a lot of kids my age and younger than me picking up a gun instead of a bike. That&#8217;s the wrong thing to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Every time they get together, they remember why they&#8217;re here.</p>
<p>Dwight Wells: &#8220;What is the motto for Bikes Up Gunz Down?&#8221;</p>
<p>Teenagers: &#8220;Bikes Up Gunz Down, it&#8217;s more than a movement, it&#8217;s a lifestyle. Everybody wants to live. Nobody wants to die.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dwight Wells: &#8220;We just taking it one day at a time. We changing lives one day at a time.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dwight says the group&#8217;s main goal is to see the murder rate for young people in Miami-Dade County decrease in the coming years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">212883</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170306-bikes-up-gunz-down.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5350114364001_5350060489001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5350060489001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170306-bikes-up-gunz-down.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/170306-bikes-up-gunz-down.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170306 bikes up gunz down</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Troubled teens receive help at Urban Promise Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-healing-troubled-teens-receive-help-at-urban-promise-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Riggin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 03:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=207114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After hitting rock bottom at just 15 years old, a South Florida teen is turning her life around and helping other kids work through their...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After hitting rock bottom at just 15 years old, a South Florida teen is turning her life around and helping other kids work through their tough times. 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens has tonight&#8217;s Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>Teenagers often deal with bullying or depression, but for 15-year-old Maygan that was just the beginning of her problems.</p>
<p>Maygan Rivera: &#8220;It came out later that I am bipolar, and I was dealing with some eating problems.&#8221;</p>
<p>Her problems became so overwhelming she had to be hospitalized.</p>
<p>Maygan Rivera: &#8220;I just thought, &#8216;Oh, my life doesn&#8217;t have a purpose to it.'&#8221;</p>
<p>She was ready to give up, but her therapist at the hospital encouraged her to go to Urban Promise Miami, an organization that helps troubled kids.</p>
<p>Ryan Carter, Urban Promise Miami: &#8220;Gang violence, bullying, broken homes, single-parent families. Often the influences that they see are usually negative.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ryan started working at Urban Promise four months ago. He says he had an instant connection with the kids, because of struggles he faced in his own life growing up without a father.</p>
<p>Ryan Carter: &#8220;I was witnessed to, you know, not the best example of a male role model in my father. I can only imagine the benefits that it would have brought to my life when I was younger.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maygan Rivera: &#8220;I was really, really shy and really, really in my shell when I came.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maygan came in with reservations, but with nothing to lose, she gave it a try. To her surprise, the program changed her life.</p>
<p>Maygan Rivera: &#8220;I smile a lot more. If I&#8217;m having a bad day at school, I look forward to coming here and look forward to seeing all of my friends and seeing all the kids, and it just brightens my day.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kids who come to Urban Promise can get tutoring or help with their homework, but what&#8217;s unique about this organization is that it also offers counseling for the entire family.</p>
<p>Ryan Carter: &#8220;We all need some therapy at some point.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maygan and Ryan agree the sense of belonging and family is what matters most.</p>
<p>Ryan Carter: &#8220;Just dealing with the realities of their communities &#8212; it&#8217;s a lot going on, and it&#8217;s a lot to take in, so here is sort of like their sanctuary.&#8221;</p>
<p>Megan Rivera: &#8220;There&#8217;s just people who are willing to be your friend and not judge.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maygan is now mentoring and helping other kids at Urban Promise, and that&#8217;s also helping her heal.</p>
<p>Ryan Carter: &#8220;You can really make an impact on their lives by just being vulnerable, being relatable and really making a genuine connection.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maygan Rivera: &#8220;You&#8217;re not just a role model to the other kids, but you&#8217;re a role model to yourself.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maygan says she can&#8217;t change her past, but she can&#8217;t wait to see what her future holds.</p>
<p>Maygan Rivera: &#8220;I look forward to being alive every day. Even if I can make one kid happy, one kid smile, that&#8217;s my goal.&#8221;</p>
<p>And what better example of Hope and Healing than the smile of a child?</p>
<p>Urban Promise Miami is hosting their first annual &#8220;Drive the Dream&#8221; event on Feb. 22.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.upmiami.org/" target="_blank">Urban Promise Miami</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/upmstreetleaders" target="_blank">Urban Promise GoFundMe page</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">207114</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/02/170210-urban-promise.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5319492826001_5319488747001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5319488747001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/02/170210-urban-promise.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/02/170210-urban-promise.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170210-urban-promise</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Orange Bowl</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-orange-bowl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 04:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=192330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When you hear &#8220;Orange Bowl,&#8221; you think football. But the organization is doing as much off the field as they are on the field. 7&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you hear &#8220;Orange Bowl,&#8221; you think football. But the organization is doing as much off the field as they are on the field. 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens has more in tonight&#8217;s Hope And Healing.</p>
<p>When you walk into this class of sixth-graders, you can feel good things are about to happen.</p>
<p>These students are part of an after-school leadership class at Bair Middle School in Sunrise.</p>
<p>Today, before any books are opened, there&#8217;s an impromptu Mannequin Challenge to break the ice.</p>
<p>Then on to the lesson&#8230;</p>
<p>Salomon Sredni, mentor at Orange Bowl Leadership Academy: &#8220;So what is kindness? How would you describe kindness?&#8221;</p>
<p>Student: &#8220;Respect.&#8221;</p>
<p>Salomon Sredni: &#8220;Respect. I like that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s lesson is about filling people&#8217;s &#8220;buckets&#8221; or hearts with kindness.</p>
<p>Salomon Sredni: &#8220;Do you think even adults have buckets, or just kids have buckets? Everyone has buckets, right?&#8221;</p>
<p>Salomon Sredni is their mentor. He works for a Fortune 500 company during the day, but makes time two afternoons a month to teach the students.</p>
<p>This is just one of the community programs run by the Orange Bowl Committee. The goal is to teach leadership skills to students in lower-income neighborhoods.</p>
<p>Salomon says it&#8217;s important, because these kids are our future.</p>
<p>Salomon Sredni: &#8220;What we&#8217;re doing is giving them tools. We&#8217;re giving them methodology. We&#8217;re giving them insight to what it is to be a leader.&#8221;</p>
<figure id="attachment_192332" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-192332" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-192332" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_salomon_sredni.jpg?w=300" alt="Salomon Sredni" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_salomon_sredni.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_salomon_sredni.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-192332" class="wp-caption-text">Salomon Sredni</figcaption></figure>
<p>The students are chosen to participate in the program because teachers saw their leadership potential.</p>
<p>Students like Julia Benkovic.</p>
<p>Julia Benkovic, Bair Middle School: &#8220;You&#8217;re there to be helpful to others and let them do their own thing, but guide them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tristan Constant was in Salomon&#8217;s first leadership academy class three years ago. He&#8217;s now a student mentor.</p>
<p>Tristan Constant: &#8220;I love the Orange Bowl. It&#8217;s one of the best things that are happening in my life right now.&#8221;</p>
<p>Salomon is sure one day these students and many others like them will make our communities better places to live.</p>
<p>Salomon Sredni: &#8220;We&#8217;re creating the next generation of people that give hope and provide healing.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you would like information on how to become a mentor with the Orange Bowl Leadership Academy, go to <a href="http://community.orangebowl.org/obla/" target="_blank">http://community.orangebowl.org/obla/</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">192330</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_hope_and_healing_orange_bowl.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5248827577001_5248823955001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5248823955001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_hope_and_healing_orange_bowl.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_hope_and_healing_orange_bowl.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">161214_hope_and_healing_orange_bowl</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161214_salomon_sredni.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Salomon Sredni</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miracle Maker</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/miracle-maker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Riggin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 03:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=190905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A South Florida woman is changing the lives of Broward County students. At first, she volunteered to listen to their problems, but what she heard...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Florida woman is changing the lives of Broward County students. At first, she volunteered to listen to their problems, but what she heard prompted her to start a charity that brings Christmas to the kids. 7&#8217;s Robbin Simmons has more in tonight&#8217;s Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe, Make A Miracle: &#8220;They don&#8217;t have Christmas. How do they dream?&#8221;</p>
<p>One simple question&#8230;</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;I asked him what are you gonna do for Christmas and he said, &#8216;I&#8217;ve never had Christmas.'&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8230;Is all it took to spark the desire for Regina Champlin Igoe to change lives.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;I said, &#8216;OK, I&#8217;ll make Christmas for the school.'&#8221;</p>
<p>And for the past 10 years, Regina has been making miracles happen &#8212; bringing love, life, and hope to thousands of under priveleged kids.</p>
<p>Rosemila Pierre, Make a Miracle: &#8220;She helps us with everything. She puts food in our stomachs when we&#8217;re hungry. She helps us with everything.&#8221;</p>
<p>The kids submit a list asking for things like bicycles and mp3 players.</p>
<p>Then, there are these wishes.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;They don&#8217;t always ask for toys, they&#8217;ll ask for food for their mom or eyeglasses, eye exams.&#8221;</p>
<p>Those are ones that force Regina to fight back the tears.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;It just shouldn&#8217;t be that way.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now 10 years later, Make A Miracle has developed into much more.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;It turned from Christmas gifts that I started bringing them here to if they got suspended, I brought them to the house.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s expanded to also celebrating the Easter holiday. It has kids at both Northside Elementary and Martin Luther King Elementary.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;I just want them to succeed. I want them to have the opportunities that my children have.&#8221;</p>
<p>When these kids need a safety zone &#8212; Regina is always it.</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;One night one little girl was there by herself with a baby and her pipes broke and there was three inches of water in their house and I was there helping her turn the water off. There&#8217;s lots of things I do with these kids.&#8221;</p>
<p>While Regina is the Santa Claus of the group, she has plenty of elves. One of them &#8212; the home sharing service Airbnb.</p>
<p>Ben Breit, Airbnb Florida: &#8220;She has a heart of gold, we&#8217;re so proud that our service and the income she earns for renting out the rooms in her home to visitors through Airbnb can help contribute to this incredible foundation.&#8221;</p>
<p>Such partnerships allow Regina to focus on impacting lives.</p>
<p>The result of her work? Rosemila Pierre who credits Regina&#8217;s gift of giving for turning her life around.</p>
<p>Rosemila Pierre: &#8220;I probably would be doing something I shouldn&#8217;t be doing if she didn&#8217;t take me in how she did.&#8221;</p>
<p>Regina Champlin Igoe: &#8220;Just a little bit of love, just a little bit of attention to them, they blossom.&#8221;</p>
<p>Regina is still furiously shopping for this year&#8217;s gifts. And says she could use some extra elves. If you&#8217;d like to help go to: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MakeAMiracleFTL/?fref=ts" rel="nofollow">https://www.facebook.com/MakeAMiracleFTL/?fref=ts</a> or contact Regina at (954) 803-1780.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">190905</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161208-miracle-maker.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5241035161001_5241020183001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5241020183001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161208-miracle-maker.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/12/161208-miracle-maker.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">161208-miracle-maker</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Cops 4 Kids</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-cops-4-kids/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Riggin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 04:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=188652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Some Fort Lauderdale Police Officers are doing very special things for students in Broward County. Craig Stevens has tonight&#8217;s special report: Hope and Healing. Officer...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some Fort Lauderdale Police Officers are doing very special things for students in Broward County. Craig Stevens has tonight&#8217;s special report: Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell: &#8220;Bravo 7-4 can you show me out at Stephen Foster Elementary.&#8221;</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell is not responding to a police call from this school &#8230; he is here to teach third-graders at Stephen Foster Elementary in Fort Lauderdale.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;We&#8217;re talkin&#8217; about teams right, shouldn&#8217;t they be capitalized?&#8221;</p>
<p>Not far away, at Sunland Park Academy, Officer Laurenia Fahie is doing the same thing.</p>
<p>Officer Laurenia Fahie, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;Are we ready for Cops 4 Kids?&#8221;</p>
<p>Both officers are part of the Fort Lauderdale Police Department&#8217;s Cops 4 Kids Program.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;Our main objective is to give them positive light, let them know we can go beyond just the person you see in the badge.&#8221;</p>
<p>The officers spend an hour in the classroom hoping to build bonds with students in high-risk schools.</p>
<p>Officer Laurenia Fahie, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;We wanted not to change the face of policing, but expand the face of policing to include these types of interactions.&#8221;</p>
<p>They help students with whatever subject they&#8217;re learning that day.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;OK, let&#8217;s go on to number three.&#8221;</p>
<p>But they also use the time to talk about issues these kids face every day.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;Remember I said we need to be that leader, not the follower.&#8221;</p>
<p>Today, officers assigned to patrol the area around Sunland Park Academy stopped in to meet the students.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;Officer Etienne, step up and tell them a little something &#8230; everybody knows Officer Paul.&#8221;</p>
<p>Because they want the kids to get to know their local police officers.</p>
<p>And when you see the kids interact with the officers, you can feel the trust and see respect they are building.</p>
<p>Officer McDowell says he jumped at the chance to get involved with the Cops 4 Kids program.</p>
<p>Because he wanted to make sure these kids didn&#8217;t have a childhood like his.</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;I grew up, I didn&#8217;t have a father, I never had a role model in my life. I never had anything like this, so this is big for me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Officer Fahie says she wants to make sure the next generation knows police officers are here to help.</p>
<p>Officer Laurenia Fahie, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;One of our major sticking points is when you see one of our cars, especially in the daytime when we all work, please flag us down because you know inside of that car it&#8217;s your friends.&#8221;</p>
<p>The two officers visit eight elementary schools within the city and say they have made hundreds of new friends.</p>
<p>Officer Laurenia Fahie, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;When you hear a kid calling you, and then calling you by name, you know you absolutely scored a home run.&#8221;</p>
<p>Officer James McDowell, Fort Lauderdale Police: &#8220;We&#8217;re building that relationship. I think that the Cops 4 Kids program, that&#8217;s what it&#8217;s about.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Broward County School District says, in addition to Cops 4 Kids, they have many police departments mentoring students district wide.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">188652</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/11/161129-cops4kids.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5228982709001_5228965578001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5228965578001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/11/161129-cops4kids.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/11/161129-cops4kids.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">161129-cops4kids</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Local church donates Thanksgiving dinners to families in need</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-local-church-donates-thanksgiving-dinners-to-families-in-need/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 15:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=186188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With Thanksgiving right around the corner, a local organization is doing its part to help feed a need. It&#8217;s part of their pledge to bring...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Thanksgiving right around the corner, a local organization is doing its part to help feed a need. It&#8217;s part of their pledge to bring Hope and Healing to families across South Florida.</p>
<p>A South Florida church offered up some hope and healing in time for the holiday season.</p>
<p>The Faith Center hosted its &#8220;Dare to Care&#8221; turkey distribution, at their church in Lauderhill, Saturday.</p>
<p>Pastor Henry Fernandez, The Faith Center: &#8220;We are daring to care, to take care of the needy in our community. So many hurting families, and once a year, we have hundreds of volunteers to come and we give out turkeys to every family and we also give groceries.&#8221;</p>
<p>The giveaway was set up to bring all the delicious Thanksgiving fixings to the table for families in need. The event drew a large turnout, this year &#8212; with people getting in line as early as Friday night. The day came as a sigh of relief for many.</p>
<p>Pastor Henry Fernandez: &#8220;It&#8217;s just an amazing feeling to witness all of them coming together and handing out turkeys to these families, and to give them groceries and just to see the smile &#8212; the expression of gratitude from these people is just amazing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sheriff Scott Israel also showed his support. He brought out a few furry members on the force to back the cause.</p>
<p>Broward Sheriff Scott Israel: &#8220;Our first objective is to help people feed and have a feast on Thanksgiving that might not, ordinarily, be able to enjoy this type of meal and, as importantly, we want to say to the community, we are your friend, we are your teammate&#8221;</p>
<p>Other organizations got involved as well, to spread some much needed holiday cheer.</p>
<p>Volunteer: &#8220;We are coming together to show an example of what we can do as a great country and as a great community.&#8221;</p>
<p>Pastor Henry Fernandez: &#8220;It&#8217;s really about bringing the healing and restoration and hope if you will, to the community that&#8217;s hurting so much from drugs, from crime and from the uprising of the election. I think this is a great expression of love and to change the tone of what&#8217;s happening in our world.&#8221;</p>
<p>This year, the church was able to help more than 3,000 families throughout South Florida.</p>
<p>7News is also a proud sponsor.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186188</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/11/161120-turkey-giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/11/161120-turkey-giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/11/161120-turkey-giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">161120-turkey-giveaway</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overtown coaches lead students by example</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/overtown-coaches-lead-students-by-example/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 02:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=177734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When it comes to teaching kids about life, using your mistakes as an example of what not to do can really hit home. That&#8217;s what...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to teaching kids about life, using your mistakes as an example of what not to do can really hit home. That&#8217;s what two coaches are doing in Miami&#8217;s Overtown neighborhood &#8212; and as 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens reports &#8212; kids are listening.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s little league football &#8230; and Coach Shanton Crummie is getting the Overtown Tornadoes ready for the final games of the season.</p>
<p>Coach Crummie has volunteered in the neighborhood for 18 years teaching football skills and life lessons he learned the hard way.</p>
<p>Shanton Crummie, football coach: &#8220;I went to jail maybe about six or seven times. My mom was a single parent. I growed up in the projects right across the street.&#8221;</p>
<p>He says he started selling crack cocaine to make ends meet.</p>
<p>Shanton Crummie: &#8220;I sold drugs to support my family &#8212; to support me. I went to jail, I never went to prison.&#8221;</p>
<p>David Miller, track coach: &#8220;We got a lot of young kids gang banging.&#8221;</p>
<p>David Miller did go to prison several times &#8230; spending a total of almost 20 years behind bars for a variety of offenses, like armed robbery, drug trafficking and possession.</p>
<p>David Miller, track coach: &#8220;I wish I wouldn&#8217;t of did it because now I have a bad record. Everywhere I go, everybody ask me about a background check and it&#8217;s like &#8230; it&#8217;s not good.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s off season now, but in January he&#8217;ll start his third year as assistant coach with the Overtown Tornadoes track team.</p>
<p>He tells his story whenever he can &#8212; hoping kids will listen.</p>
<p>David Miller: &#8220;I&#8217;ve been five times to prison, not just jail. And it&#8217;s like &#8230; it&#8217;s a wake up call. If it&#8217;s 10 of them pick up what I&#8217;m saying, that would be great. If all of them listen, that would be even better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Single parent homes, police records and hard times are difficult to talk about &#8230; but these men are brutally honest for the good of the kids.</p>
<p>Shanton Crummie: &#8220;My mom had to put up some money for me to get out of jail. When she started crying, I started crying. I don&#8217;t want these guys to go through that.&#8221;</p>
<p>And his words are making an impression.</p>
<p>Akin Liverpool, football player: &#8220;I&#8217;m learning that you shouldn&#8217;t go with the wrong crowds of people.&#8221;</p>
<p>Akin hopes football &#8212; and the lessons learned from Coach Crummie will help him get to college.</p>
<p>Akin Liverpool: &#8220;Growing up in bad neighborhoods like Overtown and Liberty City &#8212; it&#8217;s like your father&#8217;s not around, but you have coaches who&#8217;s your father figure and helps you in life.&#8221;</p>
<p>Leonardo Temple, football player: &#8220;I think most of the time all of us are listening and taking notes in our mind for what to do and what not to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>The message is simple: stay out of trouble and in school.</p>
<p>David Miller: &#8220;It&#8217;s like everywhere you go, the first thing they ask is, &#8216;Do you have a high school diploma?&#8217; And I feel bad &#8217;cause it&#8217;s like, I say no.&#8221;</p>
<p>They hope that by sharing their failures, these kids will be inspired to succeed.</p>
<p>David Miller: &#8220;It&#8217;s not how you start, but how you finish your life.&#8221;</p>
<p>Both coaches say they will continue to talk to kids and volunteer for football and track in the years to come.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">177734</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/10/161020-coach-players.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5179314966001_5179297735001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5179297735001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/10/161020-coach-players.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/10/161020-coach-players.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">161020-coach-players</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Youth program teaches students how to resolve conflict without violence</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/youth-program-teaches-students-how-to-resolve-conflict-without-violence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=175885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He has seen the worst, but a Miami man is turning his tragedy into triumph, one child at a time. He started a mentoring program...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He has seen the worst, but a Miami man is turning his tragedy into triumph, one child at a time. He started a mentoring program that teaches students how to resolve conflict withour resorting to violence. Here&#8217;s 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens with tonight&#8217;s Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes, Affirming Youth: &#8220;Aaand action!&#8221;</p>
<p>Student 1: &#8220;You wanna fight me, you got a problem?&#8221;</p>
<p>Student 2: &#8220;I don&#8217;t know you like that. I don&#8217;t think you wanna fight.&#8221;</p>
<p>These students are not really fighting.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;What was the negative outcome of the fight?&#8221;</p>
<p>But they are learning that a bit of drama can have real-life consequences.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;Temporary satisfaction gets you arrested. You got to go to court, can&#8217;t get a job, your grades go down.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s all part of a mentoring program at Betty T. Ferguson Recreational Center in Miami Gardens, one of the toughest neighborhoods in South Florida.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;You&#8217;re just 14 years old, and you already have fears that it could be you getting shot next?&#8221;</p>
<p>Their teacher is Jonathan Spikes, who founded Affirming Youth, an organization which focuses on teaching kids self-worth.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;When you find yourself getting upset, take a deep breath.&#8221;</p>
<p>He&#8217;s teaching a lesson from his &#8220;Let&#8217;s Talk It OUT&#8221; program, which is all about resolving conflict without violence.</p>
<p>The program is so successful, it&#8217;s currently being taught in Miami-Dade County Public Schools.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;Who else has those types of feelings?&#8221;</p>
<p>Jonathan grew up in the Scott Projects in Liberty City. He knows about gun violence first hand.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;When I was 6 years old, my brother, he was shot in the knee.&#8221;</p>
<p>And then at 21, Jonathan saw another one of his brothers get shot in the street. This brother didn&#8217;t survive.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;It fueled me to go out and go back to my community and say, &#8216;Listen, we have options, you have choices.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Jonathan has dedicated his life to teaching inner city kids the alternatives to violence.</p>
<p>Miami Lakes High School students Devry Russell and Kwaynesha Spencer say they have definitely learned from Jonathan.</p>
<p>Devry Russell: &#8220;The way he turned it out at the end, to show us that there are more negative effects than positive effects, really made everybody think about what they should be doing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kwaynesha Spencer: &#8220;I&#8217;d rather someone teach me how to do things, that has actually gone through the situation, than someone to just come out and say you shouldn&#8217;t do it.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, ZIP code by ZIP code, Jonathan will continue to spread his message of hope to the children who need it most.</p>
<p>Jonathan Spikes: &#8220;Now they know they have options. They don&#8217;t have to get negative consequences.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you&#8217;d like to know more about the programs Jonathan offers, log on to <a href="http://www.jonathanspikes.org">www.jonathanspikes.org</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">175885</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/10/161013_mentoring_program.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/10/161013_mentoring_program.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/10/161013_mentoring_program.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">161013_mentoring_program</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Above and Beyond the Call of Duty</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-above-and-beyond-the-call-of-duty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 03:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=170900</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Broward County deputy came to the aid of a man in need. The Nightteam&#8217;s Nicole Linsalata is on Dania Beach, where the deputy went...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Broward County deputy came to the aid of a man in need. The Nightteam&#8217;s Nicole Linsalata is on Dania Beach, where the deputy went &#8220;Above and Beyond the Call of Duty.&#8221;</p>
<p>BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster met Charles Hilliard during her off hours. She realized he didn&#8217;t have a car and she thought she could help. She and her BSO colleagues decided to take it one step further.</p>
<p>In a life of ups and downs, Charles chooses to celebrate the ups, especially in church.</p>
<figure id="attachment_170902" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-170902" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-170902" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_charles_hilliard.jpg?w=300" alt="Charles Hilliard" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_charles_hilliard.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_charles_hilliard.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-170902" class="wp-caption-text">Charles Hilliard</figcaption></figure>
<p>He is a survivor of throat cancer, and he has a job at Finish Line Feed in Dania Beach. One of his customers is Deputy Doster, a horse owner.</p>
<p>BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster: &#8220;Every time I see him at work, he&#8217;s running circles around guys that are half his age, and I&#8217;m just always impressed with him. He told me that he was on hard times and that he had been involved in a car accident, and he doesn&#8217;t have transportation.&#8221;</p>
<figure id="attachment_170903" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-170903" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-170903" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_marilyn_doster.jpg?w=300" alt="BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_marilyn_doster.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_marilyn_doster.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-170903" class="wp-caption-text">BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster</figcaption></figure>
<p>The vibrant 58-year-old was walking to work every day or using the bus.</p>
<p>Anna Hilliard, Charles&#8217; wife: &#8220;I didn&#8217;t want him walking in the rain or the cold, you know? So I said, &#8216;Charles, we just have to set up a budget, put it in our budget to go get a car.'&#8221;</p>
<p>But that seemed far off, until the day Deputy Doster offered him a 2004 Acura that she owns but does not really use.</p>
<p>BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster: &#8220;He asked me how much, and I told him, &#8216;I&#8217;m going to give it to you,&#8217; and he was just ecstatic, and at that moment I knew that I was doing the right thing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Charles Hilliard: &#8220;My heart dropped.&#8221;</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-170904" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_2004_acura_sedan.jpg?w=300" alt="160928_2004_acura_sedan" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_2004_acura_sedan.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_2004_acura_sedan.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p>And then there&#8217;s this.</p>
<p>BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster: (to Charles) &#8220;Our Senior Day Shift Squad took up a donation, so we can help you get the registration and transfer the title, and it&#8217;s all taken care off.&#8221;</p>
<p>Another several hundred dollars he and his family don&#8217;t have to worry about. He is grateful for his friends at the Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office and for the faith that, he says, helps keep him going.</p>
<p>There are still a few things that need to be done with the car. Deputy Doster was able to find an automotive shop, Ken&#8217;s Automotive in Dania Beach. They are taking care of it at no charge.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">170900</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_hope_and_healing_above_and_beyond.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5146146648001_5146140398001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5146140398001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_hope_and_healing_above_and_beyond.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_hope_and_healing_above_and_beyond.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">160928_hope_and_healing_above_and_beyond</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_charles_hilliard.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Charles Hilliard</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_marilyn_doster.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">BSO Deputy Marilyn Doster</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160928_2004_acura_sedan.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">160928_2004_acura_sedan</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Santonio Carter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-santonio-carter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Riggin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=168422</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We know Santonio Carter as the man whose 6-year-old son was gunned down in front of his home. But inner city kids know him as...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We know Santonio Carter as the man whose 6-year-old son was gunned down in front of his home. But inner city kids know him as the guy who is always there to help. It was a crime that shocked the nation. Six-year-old King Carter shot and killed outside his home. In tonight&#8217;s Hope and Healing, 7&#8217;s Craig Stevens shows us how the shooting put King Carter&#8217;s father on a mission to help other kids.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s been seven months since 6-year-old King Carter was killed.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;The pain is unbearable. Ain&#8217;t no coping with the pain.&#8221;</p>
<p>But his father Santonio has turned that pain into purpose. He says his son&#8217;s death made him determined to help inner city kids.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;After that doors just opened. So many kids who don&#8217;t have a father in their life.&#8221;</p>
<p>The kids, from the northwest Miami-Dade neighborhood, came to him to simply say sorry about his son.</p>
<p>But they stayed &#8212; for help with their own lives.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;They come to me about everything. Advice about girls, about drugs, advice about drugs, about school.&#8221;</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;So right now I got like thousands of little boys.&#8221;</p>
<p>Santonio, who grew up in Miami&#8217;s inner city, says some of the stories have even shocked him.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;I talk to some young kids who thought about suicide before. They ain&#8217;t even 10 years old.&#8221;</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;I thought I went through something. Some 10-year-olds got some real rough stories.&#8221;</p>
<p>Corey Hayes: &#8220;One day I want to be like my big brother.&#8221;</p>
<p>Cory and Shirddrick are brothers. They call themselves the Swaggg Boyz, and they have big dreams.</p>
<p>Corey Hayes: &#8220;You never know. You might get a record deal.&#8221;</p>
<p>Their father is in jail. Santonio has stepped in as a father figure to encourage and guide them.</p>
<p>Shirddrick Myrick: &#8220;He tell me to stay out of trouble. &#8216;First you gotta focus on school, then your career.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Romeo Taylor: &#8220;Now we moved to Opa-locka where there&#8217;s still a lot of shooting and killing, and I don&#8217;t want my family around that. I&#8217;m trying to get them away.&#8221;</p>
<p>Romeo Taylor is also looking to Santonio to help him with a music career. Santonio is a rapper himself.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;My first album came out when I was 14. I sold 50,000 copies.&#8221;</p>
<p>Since he has walked the same streets, Santonio can walk in the shoes of the boys he&#8217;s trying to help.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;When I came into the music world, it just stopped me from running in the streets. A lot of my friends who continued to run the streets, he died, he went in jail, he got set up.&#8221;</p>
<p>And now he&#8217;s hoping to use his music to change lives, by creating an after-school program called &#8220;BOOM.&#8221;</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;BOOM, stands for Branding Our Own Movement. Benefiting Off Our Mission. Being Our Own Man.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a place where the boys can pursue a passion, and a positive path forward.</p>
<p>Romeo Taylor: &#8220;Do something extraordinary and big so the whole family can get out of the hood.&#8221;</p>
<p>And a place where a man who could have lost all hope can instead try to heal by helping the next generation.</p>
<p>Santonio Carter: &#8220;They&#8217;re developing into bright young men. Bright, productive young men as we speak.&#8221;</p>
<p>The goal is for the #BOOM project to become a certified after-school program and to expand nationwide.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong><br />
BOOM Contact: Santonio Carter<br />
Email: <a href="mailto:blazecarterblk@gmail.com">blazecarterblk@gmail.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">168422</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160921-santonio-carter.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5136191484001_5136189162001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5136189162001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160921-santonio-carter.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160921-santonio-carter.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">160921-santonio-carter</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Law and School</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-law-and-school/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 03:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=165784</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Miami law firm is teaming up with a middle school in the heart of Liberty City. The attorneys want to give students the extra...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Miami law firm is teaming up with a middle school in the heart of Liberty City. The attorneys want to give students the extra push they need to help them succeed in life. 7&#8217;s Katrina Bush has tonight&#8217;s edition of Hope and Healing.</p>
<p>It may look like your average classroom, and sound like your average classroom, but there is something special going on here.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because when attorney Marlon Hill walks out of a courtroom and into this seventh and eighth grade civics class, the students become his priority.</p>
<p>Marlon and his law firm teamed up with Brownsville Middle School, but Marlon wanted to do more than just write a check. He wanted to show these inner city kids that they can be successful and do anything with their lives.</p>
<p>Marlon A. Hill, partner at Hamilton, Miller &amp; Birthisel: &#8220;It&#8217;s very important for us, as a community, that we have to play a role in giving every child a chance and help them to achieve their best potential.&#8221;</p>
<figure id="attachment_165785" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-165785" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-165785" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill.jpg?w=300" alt="Marlon A. Hill" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-165785" class="wp-caption-text">Marlon A. Hill</figcaption></figure>
<p>Marlon admits the odds are against many of these kids, but he believes, if you mentor them and give them hope, they will overcome their difficulties and succeed.</p>
<p>Marlon A. Hill: &#8220;You have to make the time and dedicate resources to make this happen. It&#8217;s a conscious choice for the community to be better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Students Brandon Cassamajor and Amber Paige have big dreams.</p>
<p>Brandon Cassamajor, Brownsville student: &#8220;I wanna go to med school, become a doctor because of my godmother. She has cancer and she&#8217;s still a nurse.&#8221;</p>
<figure id="attachment_165786" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-165786" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-165786" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_brandon_cassamajor.jpg?w=300" alt="Brandon Cassamajor" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_brandon_cassamajor.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_brandon_cassamajor.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-165786" class="wp-caption-text">Brandon Cassamajor</figcaption></figure>
<p>Amber Paige, Brownsville student: &#8220;I want to be the president of the United States. I plan on first passing middle school and going to college on scholarship. I would like to either go to Stanford, Harvard or Yale.&#8221;</p>
<p>And that&#8217;s exactly what Marlon wants to hear from these students.</p>
<p>Marlon A. Hill: &#8220;There&#8217;s no coincidence that this happens where we have an Amber who declares to you with such clarity, that when she grows up she wants to be the president of the United States, and she explains exactly how she&#8217;s going to get there.&#8221;</p>
<figure id="attachment_165787" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-165787" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" class="size-medium wp-image-165787" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_amber_paige.jpg?w=300" alt="Amber Paige" width="300" height="169" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_amber_paige.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_amber_paige.jpg?resize=300,169 300w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-165787" class="wp-caption-text">Amber Paige</figcaption></figure>
<p>In the midst of all the hard work, there is some fun ahead. Marlon is working with the school district to create a full-fledged &#8220;Legal Studies Law Academy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marlon A. Hill: &#8220;Our vision is to build out two classrooms here, to build out a mock, 21st century courtroom. We&#8217;ll have a judge, we&#8217;ll have witnesses, we&#8217;ll have a jury, a bailiff, a clerk.&#8221;</p>
<p>He is hoping to raise the money and have the courtroom up and running by next year. In the meantime, Marlon will continue to take pride in his shining stars.</p>
<p>Marlon A. Hill: &#8220;Everyone wants hope. No one wants to be broken. Everyone wants to be healed.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you would like to find out how to donate money toward building the courtroom at Brownsville Middle School, go to <a href="http://give.miamifoundation.org/hmbc">http://give.miamifoundation.org/hmbc</a> .</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">165784</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill_brownsville_classroom.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5124038260001_5124012788001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5124012788001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill_brownsville_classroom.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill_brownsville_classroom.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">160913_marlon_hill_brownsville_classroom</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_marlon_hill.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Marlon A. Hill</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_brandon_cassamajor.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Brandon Cassamajor</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160913_amber_paige.jpg?w=300" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Amber Paige</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hope and Healing: Girls on the Run</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/hope-and-healing/hope-and-healing-girls-on-the-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 03:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hope and Healing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=163690</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Being a teenager in this day and age may be harder than ever before, but one program is putting teen girls on the right track....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Being a teenager in this day and age may be harder than ever before, but one program is putting teen girls on the right track. The nighteam&#8217;s Nicole Linsalata has this story of &#8220;Hope and Healing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Anabell Vasquez, runner: &#8220;My name is Anabell Vasquez and I&#8217;m 13 years old.&#8221;</p>
<p>Livia Benoit, runner: &#8220;My name is Livia Benoit and I am 13 years old.&#8221;</p>
<p>Saia Amarilla, runner: &#8220;My name is Saia Amarilla and I am 13 years old.&#8221;</p>
<p>And although these girls were once strangers, they have something in common &#8212; dealing with being 13 years old.</p>
<p>Nicole Linsalata: &#8220;What do you think the hardest part about being a girl, a teenaged girl?&#8221;</p>
<p>Livia Benoit: &#8220;Trying to fit in probably.&#8221;</p>
<p>Saia Amarilla: &#8220;Some of us girls don&#8217;t think we could do anything that we would want to do because of the way that we see other girls do it, &#8217;cause they can do it much better than we can. So our confidence goes down.&#8221;</p>
<p>So these girls are taking those feelings and leaving them on the track. It&#8217;s called Girls on the Run, an international program to help girls 8 to 13 build confidence in strength.</p>
<p>Anabell, who lives in North Miami, needed that last year.</p>
<p>Nicole Linsalata: &#8220;What was going on in seventh grade?&#8221;</p>
<p>Anabell Vasquez: &#8220;It was just like everybody was more judgmental. They would curse at me and stuff, so it was kind of hard.&#8221;</p>
<p>Nicole Linsalata: &#8220;What did you do?&#8221;</p>
<p>Anabell Vasquez: &#8220;I would cry. I&#8217;d cry a lot.&#8221;</p>
<p>She would even cut herself.</p>
<p>Anabell Vasquez: &#8220;I guess it&#8217;s just a way to release all the stress inside.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now getting out on the track, running, breathing, sweating, helps them release all those emotions in a different way.</p>
<p>Coach: &#8220;We have a lesson where ask the girls, &#8216;What was the one thing when you woke up this morning that make you angry?&#8217; Let&#8217;s jog around the track, and we&#8217;re gonna scream, while running around a track. By the end of that one lap, they were laughing, they were giggling.&#8221;</p>
<p>It has also given Livia and Saia their own ways to work out their own dilemmas.</p>
<p>Livia Benoit: &#8220;I get to talk it out, like I don&#8217;t feel shy. I feel like I have friends to talk to.&#8221;</p>
<p>Saia Amarilla: &#8220;I don&#8217;t care what other people think. It doesn&#8217;t matter what they say.&#8221;</p>
<p>All that matters is friendship and getting stronger &#8212; step by step.</p>
<p>Anabell Vasquez: &#8220;It&#8217;s like you think about all those problems and then you stop, and you take a breath, and you&#8217;re all right.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">163690</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160907-hope-and-healing-girls.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://f1.media.brightcove.com/4/4368278029001/4368278029001_5116348503001_5116347188001.mp4?pubId=4368278029001&#038;videoId=5116347188001' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160907-hope-and-healing-girls.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/160907-hope-and-healing-girls.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">160907-hope-and-healing-girls</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
