<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Miami Heat &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 05:15:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Miami Heat &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Butler takes over, Heat top Pelicans 103-93</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-takes-over-heat-top-pelicans-103-93/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 04:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#8217;s absence to beat the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>NEW ORLEANS (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#x2019;s absence to beat the New Orleans Pelicans 103-93 on Thursday night.<p>With a repertoire of strong inside moves and accurate mid-range shooting, Butler made 10 of 14 shots and eight of nine free throws to help the Heat keep the Pelicans at bay. Butler added a late step-back 3 to give him 10 points during an 11-2 run that put Miami up 98-87 with 2:50 to go.</p><p>Kelly Olynyk hit his first four 3-point shots and finished with 18 points and 10 rebounds, and Goran Dragic scored nine of his 13 points in the second half for Miami.</p><p>Brandon Ingram scored 17 points and Steven Adams scored 15 for New Orleans. Nickeil Alexander-Walker scored 13 and Josh Hart 12 for the Pelicans.</p><p>Hart, normally a reserve, was inserted in the starting lineup after Williamson was scratched because of a toe injury.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/TheMozKnowz/status/1367691307582423041?s=20</embed></div><p>While the Pelicans struggled mightily to make shots during the first three quarters, Miami was unable to put New Orleans away early.</p><p>When Hart made a half-court shot as the horn sounded to signal the end of the third period, the Heat&#x2019;s lead was just 77-70.</p><p>Alexander-Walker then pulled the Pelicans to 77-73 with a 3 to open the fourth quarter, which was largely competitive until Butler began asserting himself more in the final five minutes.</p><p>TIP-INS</p><p>Heat: Andre Iguodala scored 10 points, highlighted by a late driving dunk that virtually sealed the victory. &#x2026; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra is now 16-17 against Pelicans coach Stan Van Gundy, his longtime friend and mentor. &#x2026; This is the fourth time in the last seven seasons that the Heat haven&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t been better than .500 at the All-Star break. But during Spoelstra&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s 12-year tenure, Miami has won 62% of its games after the break. Only San Antonio and Houston have better post-break records in the Spoelstra era. &#x2026; Miami shot 49.3% (36 of 73) but missed 20 of 30 3-point shots.</p><p>Pelicans: In addition to being without Williamson, New Orleans also played without JJ Redick, who was bothered by a sore right heel. &#x2026; The Pelicans shot just 39.8% (33 of 83) and missed 33 of 43 3-point shots. &#x2026; Rookie Kira Lewis Jr. scored 11 points in 17 minutes off the bench. &#x2026; Lonzo Ball scored 10 but missed nine of 11 shots from deep.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Heat: Hosts Orlando on March 11.</p><p>Pelicans: Host Minnesota on March 11.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876379</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hawks win McMillan&#8217;s debut as interim coach, top Heat 94-80</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hawks-win-mcmillans-debut-as-interim-coach-top-heat-94-80/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Trae Young took over late and made sure Nate McMillan would win his debut as interim coach of the Atlanta Hawks. Young...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Trae Young took over late and made sure Nate McMillan would win his debut as interim coach of the Atlanta Hawks.</p>
<p>Young scored 18 points, including 13 straight for his team in the fourth quarter, and the Hawks snapped Miami’s six-game winning streak by beating the Heat 94-80 on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>John Collins scored 17 for Atlanta, which lost at Miami on Sunday and fired coach Lloyd Pierce on Monday. Kevin Huerter scored 16 for the Hawks and Clint Capela had 10 points and 17 rebounds.</p>
<p>“Losing Coach Pierce, we all had to do better,&#8221; McMillan said. “And that was the challenge to this team tonight. He took a hit because we didn&#8217;t do what we were supposed to be doing out there. And I thought tonight, they did better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Duncan Robinson and Goran Dragic each scored 14 for Miami, which missed a chance to get over .500 for the first time this season. Bam Adebayo scored 11 for the Heat, who shot 37% — their fourth-worst showing of the season.</p>
<p>“We had been trending much better offensively,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “It just was a flat offensive game. It was not a fluid game for us on that side of the floor.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tony Snell added 11 for the Hawks.</p>
<p>“Ugly game, but in the end you win a lot of games giving up 80 points,&#8221; Huerter said. “Great bounceback from the last 24 hours. And now we&#8217;ve got to finish the first half of the season strong tomorrow in Orlando.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami was outrebounded 47-26, by far its worst margin of the season, and was held to a season-low in points. The Heat were again without Jimmy Butler, who missed his second consecutive game with right knee inflammation.</p>
<p>Miami shot 29% in the opening quarter and 36% in the half, including a 2-for-15 start from 3-point range. But by limiting Young for the second consecutive game — he had just two points by halftime and five points after three quarters — the Heat hung around, trailing 44-37 at the break and leading 66-63 going into the fourth.</p>
<p>Then Young got hot in the fourth, when the Heat shot just 5 for 18, and just like that what had been the NBA’s longest active winning streak entering the night was finished.</p>
<p>It was Miami&#8217;s lowest point total in its home building since scoring 79 against Milwaukee on Jan. 19, 2016. The Heat were held to 85 or fewer points for the fifth time this season, by far the most in the NBA — with Butler missing four of those five games.</p>
<p>“Defenses are going to be disruptive and do different things to try to guard us,&#8221; Robinson said. “But there are always counters and ways to be effective. We just have to find solutions.&#8221;</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Hawks: Bogdan Bogdanovic returned after missing 25 games with an avulsion fracture in his right knee. He had five points in 16 minutes. &#8230; Atlanta had 23 turnovers to Miami’s nine and won anyway. “You&#8217;re not going to win many games with that amount,&#8221; McMillan said.</p>
<p>Heat: Tyler Herro has a 3-pointer in 32 straight games, tying for the fifth-longest streak in team history. He’s one shy of matching Tim Hardaway — who had two separate 33-game streaks. &#8230; Robinson is four away from 400 career 3-pointers. He’s played 123 games; Young is the fastest to make 400 3s in NBA history, and it took him 159 games.</p>
<p>SLOW FIRST</p>
<p>Just as he did Sunday in Miami, Young went scoreless in the first quarter. The last time he was blanked in the opening quarter of consecutive games was Dec. 10 and 11, 2019, against the Heat and Chicago.</p>
<p>The Hawks had lost 13 consecutive games when he was scoreless in first quarters.</p>
<p>SLOW HALF</p>
<p>The 81 combined points at the half were the fourth fewest by halftime in an NBA game this season. Miami-Dallas had 77 on Jan. 1, New York-Cleveland on Jan. 29 had 80 and Toronto-Minnesota on Feb. 19 also had 80.</p>
<p>The 37 points allowed matched Atlanta’s best first-half defensive effort in its last 145 games. The last time they gave up that few was Jan. 6, 2019 — also against Miami.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Hawks: Visit Orlando on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Heat: Visit New Orleans on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874785</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AP source: NBA set to remove restriction on 2-way deals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ap-source-nba-set-to-remove-restriction-on-2-way-deals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874783</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The NBA has moved closer to a deal where players on two-way contracts would be eligible to appear on the active roster...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The NBA has moved closer to a deal where players on two-way contracts would be eligible to appear on the active roster for as many games as their teams would like this season, a person with knowledge of the situation said Tuesday.</p>
<p>The proposal to lift what was a 50-game limit on the active roster for two-way players got overwhelming support Tuesday and is likely to be passed by the NBA’s board of governors, said the person who spoke to The Associated Press on condition of anonymity because that final approval is pending. The approval is expected later this month.</p>
<p>No team has used two-ways more this season than Miami, with Gabe Vincent and Max Strus having a combined 42 appearances this season entering Tuesday’s game against Atlanta. Vincent has also been a part-time starter for the Heat, and Miami was one of the teams concerned that those 50-game appearance limits on the active roster was fast approaching.</p>
<p>“We all appreciate that they see that each team is in a different place,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “We felt that we’ve competed in this season with great honor and respect to the league. &#8230; Our two-ways are playing for us. There are a few other teams that are in that circumstance. It’s just an uneven and unpredictable year for so many teams. Not even all the teams are in the same range of amount of games played up to this point, with all the postponements.”</p>
<p>The NBA relaxed the rule on two-way players for this season in anticipation of postponements and rosters being taxed by virus-related issues. The rule in past years has been that two-way players could spend 45 days with the NBA club and the rest of the time with a franchise’s G League team. But with a shortened G League season this year, and not all teams having clubs in that league this season, there were obvious reasons to change things.</p>
<p>Players on two-way deals are earning $449,155 this season.</p>
<p>“It just makes all the sense in the world to not have to even think about that or concern yourself with days, particularly when we are playing them,” Spoelstra said of the looming change. “It’s what’s fair to the teams. It’s what makes the most sense and is fair to the players. We are just glad that it was seen that way, objectively, because not everybody is in the same circumstance.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874783</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180621_NBA_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat top Hawks for 6th straight win, get back to .500</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-top-hawks-for-6th-straight-win-get-back-to-500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 05:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873224</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat are back at .500, not even a couple weeks removed from being near the very bottom of the Eastern...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat are back at .500, not even a couple weeks removed from being near the very bottom of the Eastern Conference.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn scored 24 points, Bam Adebayo had 16 points and 13 rebounds, and the Heat extended the NBA’s longest current winning streak to six games by beating the Atlanta Hawks 109-99 on Sunday night.</p>
<p>“That was a big-time game for us,” Nunn said. “Took a step in the right direction.”</p>
<p>Previous Achiuwa had 14 points in 12 minutes for Miami, which used a 10-0 run late in the fourth quarter to pull away from a game that was tied at 95 with 3:00 left. Tyler Herro had 12 of his 14 points for Miami in the fourth and Goran Dragic scored 13 for the Heat (17-17).</p>
<p>John Collins led all scorers with 34 points for Atlanta, plus grabbed 10 rebounds. Clint Capela finished with 20 points and 14 rebounds for the Hawks, while Trae Young added 15 points, nine assists and eight rebounds.</p>
<p>But Young shot just 3 for 14.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s seen the pressure,&#8221; Hawks coach Lloyd Pierce said. “He knows teams are going to throw different defenses at us. A lot of it&#8217;s focused on taking the ball out of his hands. And we have ways to punish, but again, if you don&#8217;t make shots there&#8217;s nothing really we can do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Huerter scored 13 for the Hawks, who were just 8 for 35 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>The teams play again Tuesday in Miami when the Heat — who have won 10 of their last 13 — will try to get over .500 for the first time all season. Miami played Sunday without Jimmy Butler, sidelined by right knee inflammation.</p>
<p>“With Jimmy out, I thought guys really stepped up and filled in in a lot of different places,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>Miami led 54-44 at the half, a big part of that because of their defense on Young. He was scoreless until 2:53 remained in the half, the deepest he’s gone into a game this season without a point.</p>
<p>Collins was 4 for 4 in the second quarter, helping keep the Hawks within striking distance.</p>
<p>He stayed dominant in the third. Collins had 19 in that quarter alone — the second-most any player has had in a quarter against Miami this season, one shy of the 20 that Philadelphia’s Joel Embiid had in the third quarter of the 76ers’ win over the Heat on Jan. 12.</p>
<p>Capela added 10 in the third quarter and the Hawks briefly recaptured the lead before going into the fourth down just 78-77. Collins and Capela were 13 for 18 in the third; the rest of the Hawks were 1 for 8 and Young — just as he was in the first quarter — was scoreless.</p>
<p>“JC was really setting the tone by being aggressive,&#8221; Capela said.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Hawks: Young’s scoreless first quarter was his fifth of the season. The Hawks are 0-5 in those games this season and 0-13 in those games since the finale of his rookie year. &#8230; Rajon Rondo’s last seven games in Miami have come with him playing for seven different teams: Boston, Dallas, Sacramento, Chicago, New Orleans, the Lakers and now Atlanta.</p>
<p>Heat: The six straight wins is Miami&#8217;s longest such regular-season streak since a seven-game run midway through the 2017-18 season. The Heat had a seven-game win streak in last season&#8217;s playoffs as well. &#8230; Among those in the crowd of about 3,000 was celebrity chef Guy Fieri. &#8230; Adebayo now has six consecutive double-doubles, tying a career-best.</p>
<p>BUTLER’S KNEE</p>
<p>The Heat are listing Butler as day-to-day. Spoelstra said Butler was with the team for shootaround Sunday morning and the knee “didn’t loosen up the way he wanted it to.” Spoelstra added that he believes the issue is minor.</p>
<p>FLORIDA MEN</p>
<p>This game was the first of four consecutive the Hawks will play in Florida — they’re at Miami again Tuesday, at Orlando on Wednesday and vs. Toronto in Tampa to start the second half on March 11. They are scheduled to play four straight in California from March 20-26, and have had only one four-game stretch in Georgia so far this season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873224</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Butler, Dragic carry Heat past NBA-best Jazz, 124-116</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-dragic-carry-heat-past-nba-best-jazz-124-116/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 03:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Jimmy Butler and the Miami Heat got their most significant win of the season and took down the team with the NBA’s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Jimmy Butler and the Miami Heat got their most significant win of the season and took down the team with the NBA’s best record in the process.</p>
<p>Butler scored a season-high 33 points, reserve Goran Dragic tied his season-best with 26 and the Heat held on to beat Utah 124-116 on Friday night — handing the Jazz (26-7) just their third loss in their last 25 games.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo scored 19 points and grabbed 11 rebounds for Miami, which has won a season-best five straight games. Duncan Robinson scored 15 and Kendrick Nunn added 12 for the Heat.</p>
<p>Donovan Mitchell scored 30 for the Jazz, who got 17 from Bojan Bogdanovic and 15 from Rudy Gobert. Mike Conley scored 14 for Utah, which got 13 apiece from Jordan Clarkson and Joe Ingles.</p>
<p>Miami outrebounded Utah 49-36 and held the Jazz to 15-for-46 shooting from 3-point range.</p>
<p>The Heat had to dig deep time and again in the fourth to pull out the win.</p>
<p>Dragic found Andre Iguodala for an open 3-pointer, then made another himself on the next Heat possession for a 114-107 lead.</p>
<p>Bogdanovic’s 3-pointer with 3:39 left started the last Jazz flurry, Conley got a layup on the next Utah possession and Gobert made two free throws on the next. Just like that, the Jazz were within 116-115.</p>
<p>But they got no closer, with Dragic taking a charge to erase what would have been a basket by Conley with 1:58 left. The Jazz wound up missing their last six shots.</p>
<p>The Jazz are shooting 41.2% on 3-pointers in the first halves of games this season against everyone other than Miami, and only 22.2% in the opening half of their two games against the Heat. They were 7 for 24 before the break on Friday, part of the reason why Miami went into intermission up 57-53.</p>
<p>There were six ties, six lead changes, and neither team led by more than six in that first half. And Miami held on for a 96-94 lead after three quarters — the prerequisite for beating the Jazz this season. Utah came into Friday 24-0 when leading after three quarters, 2-6 when trailing.</p>
<p>They’re 2-7 now.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Jazz: Derrick Favors played in his 607th career regular-season game with Utah, breaking a tie with Rickey Green for ninth on the team’s all-time list. Next up: Bryon Russell, 628. &#8230; Gobert had a free throw 1:53 into the game for his 6,000th career point.</p>
<p>Heat: Adebayo was listed as questionable coming into the game because of a knee issue. &#8230; Tyler Herro (bruised hip) missed his third straight game with that injury and 11th missed game this season overall. &#8230; It was the sixth game in Heat history in which both teams had at least 94 points through three quarters. Three of those have come since Feb. 26, 2020.</p>
<p>FUNDAMENTALS</p>
<p>The teams were a combined 14 for 14 from the foul line in the first half. It was the second time the Jazz had been part of a game in which both teams shot 100% from the line in the opening 24 minutes this season, and the first such game for the Heat since a “home” game in the bubble last season against Toronto.</p>
<p>RAINING 3’S</p>
<p>Utah has more 3-pointers through 33 games, 559, than any other NBA team has ever made through not just 33 games — but even 35 games. Houston had 554 3’s made through the first 35 games of the 2017-18 season. The previous 33-game mark was 522, by those 2017-18 Rockets.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Jazz: Visit Orlando on Saturday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host Atlanta on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872208</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Butler leads Heat to 4th straight win, 116-108 over Raptors</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-leads-heat-to-4th-straight-win-116-108-over-raptors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 04:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870870</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Jimmy Butler and the Miami Heat are continuing to claw their way back from a brutal start to the season. Butler scored...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Jimmy Butler and the Miami Heat are continuing to claw their way back from a brutal start to the season.</p>
<p>Butler scored 27 points, 14 of them in the final quarter, and the Heat won their fourth consecutive game by topping the Toronto Raptors 116-108 on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Butler also had 10 assists and eight rebounds for the Heat, plus a season-high three 3-pointers — two of them in the final minutes. Bam Adebayo had 19 points and 12 rebounds for Miami, Duncan Robinson added 17 points and Goran Dragic scored 15 in his return from an ankle injury.</p>
<p>It was the eighth win in the last 11 games for the Heat, who started the season 7-14.</p>
<p>Kyle Lowry, returning from a thumb injury, scored 24 for Toronto. Fred VanVleet also had 24 for the Raptors, Norman Powell scored 17 and OG Anunoby had 14 for Toronto.</p>
<p>Powell made a 3-pointer as the shot clock was expiring to get Toronto within 100-98 before Butler had the game’s next three plays of any significance — a 3-pointer, a steal on the ensuing possession and a layup to push Miami’s lead back to seven.</p>
<p>Another 3-pointer by Butler with 3:23 left restored the seven-point edge, and Miami kept the lead the rest of the way.</p>
<p>Lowry scored 12 of Toronto’s first 20 points in the opening 6 ½ minutes, and he made a 31-footer over Miami’s zone midway through the second quarter to tie it at 48.</p>
<p>The next 2:51 belonged to Miami.</p>
<p>The Heat went on a 17-2 spurt in that time, six players scoring during the run, to open a 15-point lead and wound up taking a 66-56 lead into the locker room for halftime.</p>
<p>Toronto scored the first 10 points of the second half, erasing that entire deficit, but a 17-6 answer by the Heat helped them take a 92-85 lead into the fourth.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Raptors: Pascal Siakam got his fourth foul with 1:18 left in the half, after Miami successfully used its challenge to overturn a blocking call that became a charge. It was the second time in his career that he had four fouls by halftime, the other coming Dec. 18, 2016, at Orlando. &#8230; Toronto fell to 1-5 on the second night of a back-to-back this season.</p>
<p>Heat: Tyler Herro (hip) remained sidelined. &#8230; Capacity was increased for this game, and the Heat had about 3,000 fans in the arena including some in the upper deck for the first time this season. &#8230; Andre Iguodala was 4 for 5 on 3-pointers for Miami. &#8230; It was the 10th time in the last 14 meetings between the clubs that the final margin was less than 10 points.</p>
<p>SPO KNOWS</p>
<p>Heat coach Erik Spoelstra now has 667 wins, including playoffs, with Miami. That ties Red Holzman of the New York Knicks for the fifth-most by any coach with one franchise. The only others with more: Gregg Popovich with San Antonio, Jerry Sloan with Utah, Red Auerbach with Boston and Phil Jackson with the Los Angeles Lakers.</p>
<p>SEE YOU</p>
<p>The Heat won the season series over Toronto, 2-1. Miami has also finished its regular-season series against Washington, Oklahoma City, Sacramento and the Los Angeles Clippers. Toronto has also finished its season series with Milwaukee, Philadelphia, New Orleans, Sacramento and Minnesota.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Raptors: Host Houston on Friday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host Utah on Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870870</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/09/092719-jimmy-butler.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/09/092719-jimmy-butler.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/09/092719-jimmy-butler.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">092719 jimmy butler</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>3,000 fans will be allowed to attend Miami Heat games at AmericanAirlines Arena</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/3000-fans-will-be-allowed-to-attend-miami-heat-games-at-americanairlines-arena/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 14:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870331</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Heat is gearing up to have more fans in the stands at home games. The AmericanAirlines Arena&#8217;s capacity will double starting on Wednesday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Heat is gearing up to have more fans in the stands at home games.</p>
<p>The AmericanAirlines Arena&#8217;s capacity will double starting on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Now 3,000 fans will be able to watch the Miami Heat play as they take on the Toronto Raptors at 8 p.m.</p>
<p>Last month, the team only allowed 1,500 fans inside of the arena.</p>
<p>COVID-19 protocols will still be in place as fans will be required to wear masks at all times &#8212; except when eating or drinking.</p>
<p>Attendees will also be screened by COVID-19 sniffing dogs before entering the arena.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870331</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/miami-heat-fans-e1614174585651.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d083bbcc-5292-4ab4-9582-3a0f3977151c/43c85acc-1864-44b7-863a-394f6710ef9d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219828~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d083bbcc-5292-4ab4-9582-3a0f3977151c/43c85acc-1864-44b7-863a-394f6710ef9d/main.mp4*~hmac=5c2780d6d24815ffcc2fddd0cce75aed6557a81161ab115c008ce9aad42d4711' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/miami-heat-fans-e1614174585651.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/miami-heat-fans-e1614174585651.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami heat fans</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat pull away to beat Thunder 108-94 in finale of road trip</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-pull-away-to-beat-thunder-108-94-in-finale-of-road-trip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 05:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Duncan Robinson scored 22 points and made six 3-pointers, leading the Miami Heat to a 108-94 victory over the Oklahoma City...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Duncan Robinson scored 22 points and made six 3-pointers, leading the Miami Heat to a 108-94 victory over the Oklahoma City Thunder on Monday night in the finale of their seven-game road trip.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn added 20 points and nine assists, Bam Adebayo had 19 points and 13 rebounds, and they hooked up on an alley-oop dunk during Miami’s 15-0 run to start the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Robinson ended it with a 3-pointer that gave the Heat a 94-77 lead midway through the final period. The Heat did it all with five-time NBA All-Star Jimmy Butler on the sideline for the last 12 minutes.</p>
<p>“It was great, just the enthusiasm,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “I think those guys wanted to play well while he was on the bench and see if we could push the lead.</p>
<p>“Then, when we took that first timeout, I looked at Jimmy, and Jimmy was in the huddle and he said, ’Hey guys, keep going. Let’s give it another two or three minutes and see how it goes.&#8217;”</p>
<p>Spoelstra said Butler’s comments energized the group, which kept its double-digit margin and won the final three games of its trip to finish 4-3.</p>
<p>Shai Gilgeous-Alexander scored 27 points for the Thunder, who were outscored 63-40 after halftime.</p>
<p>“I give them a lot of credit. They came out of halftime really focused and we had to earn everything on both ends of the floor in the second half,” Thunder coach Mark Daigneault said. “They just outplayed us. … We definitely enjoy competing against a team like them, because we learn a lot about ourselves. They just outlasted us tonight.”</p>
<p>The Heat made five of their first eight 3-point attempts. Max Strus capped the hot start with one with 4:19 remaining in the first quarter.</p>
<p>Miami missed its next 12 3-point shots. Robinson finally ended the drought with a 31-foot jumper with 43 seconds left until the break.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Thunder shot 54% from the floor through the first 24 minutes. Gilgeous-Alexander fueled Oklahoma City’s 54-45 halftime advantage, scoring 18 points on 6-of-7 shooting. His only miss of the half came via a 27-foot stepback as time expired in the first period.</p>
<p>Miami responded with 34 points in the third quarter to take a 79-72 lead with under a minute left. Gilgeous-Alexander rattled off five points in the final 31.6 seconds to bring the Thunder within two entering the final period before Miami promptly blew it open.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Tyler Herro (right hip contusion) was ruled out ahead of Monday’s game. He is day to day, according to Spoelstra. … The Heat haven’t played at home since a Feb. 9 win over the New York Knicks. … Jimmy Butler played in his 600th career game.</p>
<p>Thunder: Al Horford (rest) was not available for Oklahoma City’s second game in as many nights. Isaiah Roby started in Horford’s place. … The Thunder fell to 2-4 when playing the second game of a back-to-back. … Darius Bazley finished with 13 points on 5-of-9 shooting and five rebounds.</p>
<p>END OF THE ROAD</p>
<p>The Heat lost three consecutive games before beating the Sacramento Kings on Feb. 18, the Los Angeles Lakers on Saturday and the Thunder on Monday. Adebayo attributes the team’s time on the road to the group’s strong finish and strengthened bond within the locker room.</p>
<p>“We got better,” Adebayo said. “I feel like it was one of those situations, it felt like the bubble again where we got a chance to be cohesive and feel like brothers again. … When we’re at home, we can’t really hang out with each other. So, being able to be in the hotel and be safe, it feels like the bubble.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Thunder: Host the San Antonio Spurs on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host the Toronto Raptors on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869572</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat hold off depleted Lakers 96-94 in NBA Finals rematch</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-hold-off-depleted-lakers-96-94-in-nba-finals-rematch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 05:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868596</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES (AP) — Although the Miami Heat&#8217;s road trip started slowly, Kendrick Nunn thinks they are picking up steam because of a team chemistry...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Although the Miami Heat&#8217;s road trip started slowly, Kendrick Nunn thinks they are picking up steam because of a team chemistry that is growing at every stop.</p>
<p>The Heat even kept it together to pull out a win over the defending NBA champions despite a fourth quarter that nearly went wrong.</p>
<p>Nunn scored 27 points, Jimmy Butler had 24 points and eight rebounds, and Miami held off the Los Angeles Lakers 96-94 Saturday night in an NBA Finals rematch.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo had 16 points and 10 rebounds for the Heat in the teams’ first meeting since the Lakers won their 17th championship with a six-game victory over Miami in the Florida bubble four months ago. The Heat scored only 15 points in the fourth quarter, but they held the Lakers to 17 and hung on when Alex Caruso missed a long jumper at the buzzer.</p>
<p>“You can tell that the chemistry is building,” said Nunn, who hit five 3-pointers. “We’ve been together for a week and a half, and it just gives us more of a feel for each other. We’re moving in the right direction now. We dropped a couple early, but we’re starting to give ourselves the best chance at the end of the game.”</p>
<p>The victory was Miami&#8217;s second straight following a three-game skid during this seven-game road trip. The defending Eastern Conference champions (13-17) have been under .500 since Jan. 12, but their confidence is growing.</p>
<p>“We’re seeing progress the last few weeks,” coach Erik Spoelstra said. “I think our defensive mental toughness was better in this game to get some stops when we weren’t able to knock down some shots in the fourth quarter.”</p>
<p>LeBron James had 19 points, nine assists and nine rebounds as the champs lost their second straight game without starters Anthony Davis and Dennis Schröder.</p>
<p>James stole the Heat&#8217;s inbounds pass with 8.4 seconds left to create one last chance for the Lakers, but the 17-time All-Star passed out of a double team to Caruso, who capped his scoreless 20-minute night by missing.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re figuring out how to play without one of our creators in Dennis and one of our stars in AD,” Caruso said. “That&#8217;s going to take a little time, and obviously we don&#8217;t have practice time.”</p>
<p>Davis missed his third straight game after aggravating his strained right calf last weekend, and Schröder missed his second straight under the NBA’s health and safety protocols.</p>
<p>Kyle Kuzma scored 23 points while hitting four 3-pointers, and Montrezl Harrell had 18 points and 10 rebounds for the Lakers.</p>
<p>The injury absences don&#8217;t account for the Lakers&#8217; shooting woes over the last 10 games, including a 39% performance against Miami. LA missed five of its last six shots, including Wesley Matthews&#8217; rushed, off-balance 3-pointer with 15 seconds left.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re going to continue to work on our habits and be great for each other,” James said. “We all put in the work, so it’s not that. The law of averages will even itself out. We had lapses last season, and we had them during the playoffs. We know they’ll even them out over the course of the year.”</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Avery Bradley, a starter for the Lakers last season who missed their playoff run after opting out of the NBA restart, missed this game for Miami with a calf strain. &#8230; Goran Dragić missed his eighth straight game with a sprained left ankle.</p>
<p>Lakers: Schröder will miss at least two more games in quarantine, coach Frank Vogel said. The Lakers hope he&#8217;ll return Friday against Portland.</p>
<p>HERRO HURT</p>
<p>Tyler Herro left after playing less than 14 minutes due to a hip pointer. He will be re-evaluated Sunday, Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>“We’re used to it,” Spoelstra said of the Heat&#8217;s latest injury. “Every game there’s going to be something. This is developing a level of toughness in our group.&#8221;</p>
<p>Max Strus missed eight 3-pointers in Herro’s place.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: At Thunder on Monday.</p>
<p>Lakers: Host Wizards on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868596</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Butler&#8217;s 3rd straight triple-double paces Heat past Kings</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butlers-3rd-straight-triple-double-paces-heat-past-kings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 05:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=867538</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Jimmy Butler had 13 points, 13 assists and 10 rebounds for his third consecutive triple-double, and the Miami Heat beat the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Jimmy Butler had 13 points, 13 assists and 10 rebounds for his third consecutive triple-double, and the Miami Heat beat the Sacramento Kings 118-110 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo also had a triple-double with 16 points, 10 assists and 12 rebounds to help Miami to its first win in Sacramento in nearly five years. Tyler Herro scored 27 points and Kelly Olynyk added a season-high 22 points and seven rebounds.</p>
<p>Already the only player in franchise history with triple-doubles in consecutive games after doing it against the Clippers and Warriors, Butler made it three in a row with season-highs in assists and rebounds against the Kings.</p>
<p>One day after blowing a 15-point halftime lead and losing to the Warriors in overtime, the Heat built another early big lead and this time held on against the short-handed and sloppy Kings.</p>
<p>Miami led by 23 points in the third before Sacramento made four consecutive 3s and closed the quarter on a 19-9 run to pull within 89-79.</p>
<p>The Heat pulled away early in the fourth after Herro made a 3-pointer and three-point play on consecutive possessions.</p>
<p>Marvin Bagley III had 19 points and 10 rebounds for Sacramento. De’Aaron Fox added 11 points and 10 assists.</p>
<p>The Kings have lost five straight following a season-best four-game win streak.</p>
<p>Miami got a big lift in the first half from Herro, who had 14 points in the first quarters after making seven of his first nine shots. Andre Iguodala added a steal in the backcourt and dunk to put the Heat up 57-43.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Miami’s last win in Sacramento was on April 1, 2016. … Duncan Robinson made the first shot in the first, second and fourth quarters.</p>
<p>Kings: Starters Harrison Barnes (left foot strain) and Richaun Holmes (right knee soreness) did not play. . Glenn Robinson III had nine rebounds in the first half, his most in any full game since Nov. 6, 2019. Robinson didn’t get another rebound.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Play the Lakers in Los Angeles on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Kings: Visit the Bulls on Saturday night. Sacramento has won its last three games at the United Center.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">867538</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curry and his supporting cast rally Warriors past Heat in OT</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/curry-and-his-supporting-cast-rally-warriors-past-heat-in-ot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 19:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=867232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Stephen Curry&#8217;s supporting cast knew he would finally break out — and he had no doubt either. “Utmost confidence it will...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Stephen Curry&#8217;s supporting cast knew he would finally break out — and he had no doubt either.</p>
<p>“Utmost confidence it will fall eventually,” Curry said. “I just was missing, so not losing confidence is huge.”</p>
<p>Curry hit a go-ahead 3-pointer with 1:15 left in overtime, passed to Andrew Wiggins for another the next time down before delivering a final dagger from deep, rallying the Golden State Warriors to a 120-112 win over the Miami Heat on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>“Everything was in rhythm for Steph. Percentages always catch up for him,” Kent Bazemore said. “We just stayed with it, which is good on him, just staying with it and keep letting it fly. He was huge for us late there.”</p>
<p>Bazemore tipped in Wiggins&#8217; miss with 1:32 left for one of his two big baskets in OT and finished with a season-high 26 points — his second 20-point performance this season.</p>
<p>Curry scored 25 points playing a season-high 42 minutes and overcame an off shooting night by finding his stroke when it mattered most. He added 11 assists and seven rebounds.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s just a testament to who he is,” Bazemore said. &#8220;When you&#8217;ve got a guy like that who believes in you and instills that confidence in you, you feel like you can do anything.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler had his second straight triple-double with 13 points, 12 rebounds and 11 assists for the Heat, who never trailed in regulation.</p>
<p>Curry&#8217;s 3 with 2:26 left in regulation cut it to 103-101 and he stole the ball from Butler on the other end moments later. Bazemore made consecutive hoops to tie it with 52 seconds remaining. Kelly Oubre Jr. missed a 3 for the win.</p>
<p>“The last few minutes of the fourth we were just scrambling out there and I thought Baze kind of led the charge. He really made some huge plays for us and kept us in it,&#8221; coach Steve Kerr said. “Then of course Steph, this is so typical of Steph, he&#8217;s just the kind of player and the kind of person who can be in the midst of one of his worst shooting nights of the year and still hit three enormous shots to help us win the game.”</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn scored 19 points for Miami, coming off a 125-118 loss at the Clippers on Monday night.</p>
<p>Golden State started with a 13-3 burst out of halftime to make it a game again after falling behind 61-46 at the break.</p>
<p>Wiggins wound up with 23 points as Curry mostly struggled.</p>
<p>Curry was 3 for 11 in the first half, missing eight of his nine 3-point tries. He finished 5 of 20 from long range as Golden State went 18 for 52 and got outrebounded 50-45.</p>
<p>&#8220;Once it got close and it became a possession game. That’s when Curry came alive,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>Draymond Green was a late scratch by the Warriors because of right ankle soreness they didn&#8217;t know about until just before tipoff given the team didn&#8217;t hold a morning shootaround. Mychal Mulder made his fourth career start in Green&#8217;s place and first of the season.</p>
<p>IGGY&#8217;S BACK</p>
<p>Andre Iguodala received a nice welcome back when he checked into the game for the first time in the final two minutes of the opening quarter. He then scored 10 points against his old team.</p>
<p>The 2015 NBA Finals MVP did a little bit of everything in six seasons for the Warriors from 2013-19.</p>
<p>“That’s why Andre will always be one of my favorites just his selflessness and willingness to do whatever it takes to win a game,” Kerr said.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Butler has grabbed eight or more rebounds in nine straight games. &#8230; The Heat dropped to 4-10 on the road with their third straight loss away from home. &#8230; The Heat swept last season&#8217;s series with the Warriors and had their three-game winning streak in the series snapped.</p>
<p>Warriors: C Kevon Looney was re-evaluated before missing his eighth straight game with a sprained left ankle. He has resumed some portions of practice and Kerr hopes he will be back on the floor in the latter part of an upcoming four-game road trip. &#8230; Rookie James Wiseman is scheduled to have his sprained left wrist examined again Thursday and if all is well could return as soon as Friday vs. the Magic. &#8220;I can’t wait to get on the floor, which should be pretty soon,” Wiseman said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: At Sacramento on Thursday night to complete a back-to-back. Miami lost 105-104 at home to the Kings on Jan. 30.</p>
<p>Warriors: At Orlando on Friday night with a chance at their first three-game winning streak of the season before a scheduled game in Curry&#8217;s hometown of Charlotte on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">867232</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Morris comes up big in Clippers&#8217; 125-118 win over Heat</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/morris-comes-up-big-in-clippers-125-118-win-over-heat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 19:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=865987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES (AP) — Marcus Morris had season highs of 32 points and six 3-pointers, and the Los Angeles Clippers beat the Miami Heat 125-118...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Marcus Morris had season highs of 32 points and six 3-pointers, and the Los Angeles Clippers beat the Miami Heat 125-118 on Monday night for their fourth straight victory.</p>
<p>The Clippers won without four starters, including Kawhi Leonard and Paul George, who were out for the second straight night because of injuries.</p>
<p>“A total team effort. We kept grinding,” Clippers coach Tyronn Lue said.</p>
<p>Morris recorded a season-high 23 points during Sunday&#8217;s win over Cleveland and he came back strong, scoring 26 in the first half. He was making a rare start with most of the regulars out.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m a hooper. Whatever you need me to do,” Morris said. “I don’t just be talking.”</p>
<p>The Clippers have won eight of 11.</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler had 30 points, 10 rebounds and 10 assists for the Heat. He made all 10 of his free throws. Bam Adebayo added 27 points and 12 rebounds, and reserve Tyler Herro scored 27 points.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m not going to say we gave one away, we didn’t deserve to win,” Butler said. “We weren&#8217;t protecting the paint or rotating or running them off the line to make them miss. They were just comfortable the whole game.”</p>
<p>Ivica Zubac added 22 points for the Clippers. Lou Williams had 18 points and 10 assists, and two-way player Amir Coffey had a season-high 15 points and a career-high five 3-pointers. Coffey was in the G League a few days ago, and made 14 3s in his last game there.</p>
<p>“When you&#8217;re short-handed, you really find out what your team is made of,” said Terrance Mann, who added 15 points. “It brings your team closer.”</p>
<p>Los Angeles had 31 assists for the second straight game, something the franchise hasn&#8217;t done since December 2014.</p>
<p>“Sharing the basketball, getting into the paint and making a play for your teammate, we did it all night long,” Lue said. “It’s fun playing that way.”</p>
<p>The Clippers led by one heading into the fourth. They got back-to-back 3-pointers by Luke Kennard and Mann dunked to push their lead to 11 points.</p>
<p>Herro hit his fourth 3-pointer and followed with a basket to draw the Heat to 121-116 before the Clippers controlled the final seconds.</p>
<p>“We had some breatkdowns. They capitalized on the important ones at swing moments of the game,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “We just did not do things well enough, consistently enough.”</p>
<p>Williams&#8217; slick behind-the-back pass to Reggie Jackson gave the Clippers a nine-point lead in the third. Miami ran off 10 straight points, capped by Herro&#8217;s 3-pointer, to go back in front 76-75. Neither team led by more than three points the rest of the quarter. Coffey&#8217;s fifth 3-pointer put the Clippers ahead 92-91 going into the fourth.</p>
<p>The Clippers outscored the Heat 20-9 to open the second quarter, using runs of 7-0 and 11-0 that were highlighted by four 3-pointers from Coffey to take a 53-44 lead.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Fell to 4-9 on the road. &#8230; They&#8217;ve dropped nine of their last 14. &#8230; They were without Avery Bradley (right calf strain), Goran Dragic (left ankle sprain), Meyers Leonard (left shoulder surgery) and Chris Silva (left hip flexor strain).</p>
<p>Clippers: Williams had 10 assists in back-to-back games for the second time in his career. &#8230; Improved to 3-1 this season with Leonard and George out. &#8230; Nicolas Batum sat out with a migraine and Patrick Beverley rested on the second night of a back-to-back. &#8230; Have won five in a row over the Heat. &#8230; George watched the game in shorts and a sweatshirt.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Visit Golden State on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Clippers: Host Utah on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">865987</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jazz beat Heat 112-94 for seventh straight victory</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/jazz-beat-heat-112-94-for-seventh-straight-victory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 05:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=864785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Utah turned to its defense when its outside shots weren’t falling. The Jazz held Miami scoreless over six-minute stretches of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Utah turned to its defense when its outside shots weren’t falling.</p>
<p>The Jazz held Miami scoreless over six-minute stretches of both the second and third quarters, turning a close game into another blowout.</p>
<p>Donovan Mitchell scored 26 points and Utah won its seventh straight, beating the Heat 112-94 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>“We know the shots are not always going to fall,” said center Rudy Gobert, who 16 points, 12 rebounds and three blocks. “It’s basketball. But we know we get a chance to win every single night with our defense.”</p>
<p>Bojan Bogdanovic added 19 points and Georges Niang had 14 for Utah, which has won 18 of its last 19 games since a 4-4 start.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn scored 20 points for Miami, which missed 11 straight shots to open the third quarter. Jimmy Butler added 15 points, eight rebounds and five assists. Bam Adebayo finished with 14 points, 10 rebounds and six assists.</p>
<p>The Heat had a four-game winning streak snapped.</p>
<p>“We just did not do things with a great motor and purpose,” Miami coach Erik Spoelstra said. “If you get caught late in the clock, they can really swallow you up with their discipline and their size, with Gobert in the paint.”</p>
<p>Mitchell made three straight baskets in just 58 seconds, including back-to-back reverse layups, to spark a 16-0 Jazz run to open the second half. Royce O’Neale capped the run with a steal and slam, giving Utah a 63-42 lead.</p>
<p>Miami did not score its first points of the second half until Tyler Herro hit a jumper with 5:51 left in the third quarter. The drought lasted 14 straight possessions for the Heat.</p>
<p>“We let our offense dictate our defense,” Butler said. “We started missing shots, not getting back, not rebounding. And then they started scoring, so it’s always going to look like that whenever you’re not guarding. You got to anchor down and guard somebody.”</p>
<p>Utah struggled to build any consistent rhythm on offense during the opening quarter against a tenacious Heat defense, going 1 for 12 from 3-point range. So the Jazz attacked the rim to get the offense going.</p>
<p>“When we have guys that are really good at creating those advantages, then we are able to have the defense commit and try to take away the rim and we’re able to have all those 3s,” Gobert said. “That’s what makes it so hard. We’re able to get really really good pressure on the rim and the defense has to make decisions.”</p>
<p>The shots started falling in the second quarter. Utah scored baskets on six straight possessions early in the period and tied it at 31 on a layup from Bogdanovic. Jordan Clarkson scored a basket and assisted on four others during that stretch.</p>
<p>Herro and Max Strus scored back-to-back baskets to make it 36-31 the Heat then missed eight straight shots and went six minutes without scoring.</p>
<p>Utah answered with a 14-0 run in that stretch to take a 45-36 lead. The Jazz finally went ahead for the first time on back-to-back baskets from O’Neale and Clarkson.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Goran Dragic (left ankle sprain) and Avery Bradley (right calf strain) did not travel with the team to Utah. … Strus is averaging 18.0 points over his last two games. He scored 15 against the Jazz. … Kelly Olynyk finished with 10 rebounds.</p>
<p>Jazz: Mike Conley missed his fourth straight game (right hamstring tightness). … Gobert’s half-court heave at the first-quarter buzzer was his first 3-point field goal attempt since the 2016-17 season. He is 0 for 4 from 3-point range for his career. … Utah outscored Miami 13-2 in second-chance points and 20-10 in fast-break points.</p>
<p>ELITE COMPANY</p>
<p>Joe Ingles finished with a team-high six assists, tying him with Pete Maravich for seventh place on the Jazz career list with 1,844. He is averaging 5.9 assists in February while making four starts.</p>
<p>QUOTABLE</p>
<p>“It’s like passing money around at a casino. Everybody gets a little piece.” – Niang on how dangerous the Jazz offense is because so many players touch the ball on a typical possession.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Visit the Los Angeles Clippers on Monday.</p>
<p>Jazz: Host the Philadelphia 76ers on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">864785</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jimmy Butler has triple-double, leads Heat past Rockets</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/jimmy-butler-has-triple-double-leads-heat-past-rockets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 04:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=863693</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOUSTON (AP) — Jimmy Butler had a triple-double with 27 points, 10 rebounds and 10 assists and the Miami Heat overcame a slow start to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOUSTON (AP) — Jimmy Butler had a triple-double with 27 points, 10 rebounds and 10 assists and the Miami Heat overcame a slow start to beat the slumping Houston Rockets 101-94 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Miami won its fourth straight and handed Houston its fourth loss in a row.</p>
<p>Butler had his first triple-double of the season and 10th overall. The Heat came close to having two players with triple-doubles, with Bam Adebayo finishing with 10 points, 13 rebounds and eight assists before fouling out with about a minute left.</p>
<p>Miami trailed by 13 in the first half, but used a big run and great defense in the third to take a 12-point lead into the fourth quarter. They remained up by 12 after a dunk by Adebayo before Houston used a 9-0 run to get to 97-94 with less than a minute to go.</p>
<p>The Heat missed two shots after that but got the rebound both times, with Butler grabbing the second one. He was fouled and made two free throws with 10 seconds to go and the Heat added two more free throws in the final seconds to secure the win.</p>
<p>John Wall and Eric Gordon led the Rockets with 17 points each.</p>
<p>Miami pushed the lead to 15 on a 3-pointer by Max Strus with about eight minutes to go before Houston used a 10-3 spurt, capped by a 3 from DeMarcus Cousins, to get within 88-80 three minutes later.</p>
<p>A 3-pointer by John Wall got the Rockets within seven not long after that, but Miami scored the next five points to pull away again — 95-83.</p>
<p>The Heat used a 12-0 run to take a 70-59 lead with about 3 1/2 minutes left in the third quarter. They pushed the lead to 12 entering the fourth quarter after limiting Houston to just 10 points in the third.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: The team learned shortly before game time that Tyler Herro would not be available in accordance with the NBA’s health and safety protocols, which would mean he either tested positive, had an inconclusive test or was flagged because contact tracing data suggested that he may have been exposed to someone else positive for COVID-19. The Heat were scheduled to fly to Salt Lake City later Thursday night for a game there Saturday against the Utah Jazz. It was not immediately clear if Herro would be cleared to fly with his team there, if he would remain behind in Houston, or return to Miami. If Herro is forced to stay behind, it might only mean they didn’t get a new test result back.</p>
<p>Rockets: Christian Wood missed his fourth straight game with a sprained right ankle. &#8230; Cousins had 16 points and 11 rebounds.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Play the second game of a seven-game trip at Utah on Saturday.</p>
<p>Rockets: Begin a three-game trip at New York on Saturday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">863693</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat dig deep, hold off Knicks 98-96 to sweep home-and-home</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-dig-deep-hold-off-knicks-98-96-to-sweep-home-and-home/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 03:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=862440</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — A Heat-Knicks game, down to the wire, just like old times. Jimmy Butler and Bam Adebayo made sure it wouldn&#8217;t get away...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — A Heat-Knicks game, down to the wire, just like old times.</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler and Bam Adebayo made sure it wouldn&#8217;t get away from Miami.</p>
<p>The duo did all of Miami&#8217;s scoring for much of the second half, Butler finishing with a game-high 26 points, and the Heat beat New York 98-96 on Tuesday night to finish off a sweep of a home-and-home series.</p>
<p>“This was more of a throwback Miami Heat-New York Knicks game from the ‘90s, where there weren&#8217;t a lot of open shots in the last 14, 16 minutes of the game,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “You were just going to have to grind out a win.&#8221;</p>
<p>RJ Barrett had a chance to tie it on the final play, but his layup bounced off the rim and Miami won three straight for the first time this season. Kelly Olynyk scored 20 points for Miami, Adebayo had 19 and Tyler Herro finished with 15 — including the 3-pointer with 1:04 left that put Miami up for good.</p>
<p>The Knicks scored 14 points in the fourth quarter, and went to the line 16 times in the game — compared with 39 for Miami. The difference in free-throw attempts was 13-2 in the fourth, and Knicks coach Tom Thibodeau noticed.</p>
<p>“I want to look at the film,&#8221; Thibodeau said. “It just seemed a little strange to me in terms of &#8230; I&#8217;ll leave it at that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Elfrid Payton led the Knicks with 18 points, and Derrick Rose — in his first game back with New York — had 14 off the bench. Barrett scored 13 and Julius Randle finished with 12 for New York.</p>
<p>Herro scored Miami’s final basket of the first half, a layup with 30 seconds left.</p>
<p>For the next 18 1/2 minutes of game time, Butler and Adebayo would be the only Heat players to score. They combined for all 19 Miami points of the third quarter and the first eight of the fourth, before Herro hit a jumper with 6:06 remaining.</p>
<p>Miami led 57-55 after a first half that featured wild mood swings. The Heat opened on a 20-9 run, the Knicks then went on a 13-0 run to cap what became a 33-10 burst, and Miami immediately followed that with an 11-0 run of its own.</p>
<p>New York led by as many as 10 in the third, taking an 82-76 lead into the fourth. But the Heat found a way at the end.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re figuring this thing out, slowly but surely,&#8221; Butler said.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>New York: Frank Ntilikina missed the game because of a contact-tracing issue, Thibodeau said. &#8230; This was New York&#8217;s lone regular-season visit to Miami this season. The Knicks will play host to the Heat once in the NBA&#8217;s second half, sometime between mid-March and mid-May.</p>
<p>Miami: Goran Dragic (ankle) remained out. &#8230; The Heat start a seven-game Western Conference trip Thursday in Houston. &#8230; Butler made a 3-pointer in the third quarter, his first of the season in 15 tries and his first in Miami’s home building since March 2.</p>
<p>2’S ARE WILD</p>
<p>Miami made 12 2-pointers, the lowest in franchise history. The Heat made only four in the first half, two fewer than the previous low in the NBA this season. The last time a team had fewer 2-pointers in a first half was Oct. 27, 2018, when Atlanta made three against Chicago. The record for fewest 2s in a full game since the shot-clock era began is seven, by Washington last season — against Miami.</p>
<p>HELLO, AGAIN</p>
<p>Rose has now played three games as an opponent at AmericanAirlines Arena this season — two last month with Detroit, one with the Knicks. Such a quirk happens about twice a year on average; James Ennis (Philadelphia and Orlando) did it last year. Jason Collins and Jason Kidd (both in the 2003-04 and 2007-08 seasons) have done it twice since Miami moved into its current building in January 2000.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>New York: Visit Washington on Friday.</p>
<p>Miami: Visit Houston on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">862440</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adebayo, Butler help Heat beat Knicks in opener of series</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/adebayo-butler-help-heat-beat-knicks-in-opener-of-series/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 04:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=860484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — Bam Adebayo had 24 points and 11 rebounds, Jimmy Butler had a big second half and just missed a triple-double and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — Bam Adebayo had 24 points and 11 rebounds, Jimmy Butler had a big second half and just missed a triple-double and the Miami Heat beat the New York Knicks 109-103 on Sunday in the opener of a home-and-home series.</p>
<p>Butler finished with 17 points, 10 rebounds and nine assists. He shot just 3 for 11 from the field but scored 12 points after halftime.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn and Tyler Herro each added 16 points for the Heat, who won their second straight after dropping seven of eight.</p>
<p>“We just stayed with it,” Butler said. “All in all, we guarded, rebounded and played together. I think that’s what this thing is all about.”</p>
<p>Julius Randle had 26 points, 13 rebounds and seven assists, but the Knicks had their two-game win streak snapped. Reggie Bullock made seven 3-pointers and scored 21 points.</p>
<p>“You’ve got to give them credit and it’s not just Jimmy,” Knicks coach Tom Thibodeau said. “They have Bam as well and they have great shooting around them, but you’ve got to make plays down the stretch and you’ve got to understand the fourth quarter’s different.”</p>
<p>The teams meet again Tuesday in Miami.</p>
<p>Also Sunday, the Knicks agreed to a trade with Detroit that brings Derrick Rose back to New York and reunites him with Thibodeau, a person with knowledge of the details said. The Knicks are sending Dennis Smith Jr. and a second-round pick to Detroit, the person told The Associated Press on condition of anonymity because the deal was not yet official.</p>
<p>Butler, as he often did during Miami&#8217;s run to the NBA Finals, made many of the big plays down the stretch. He snapped a 94-all tie with a jumper with 4:17 to play and followed with a pair of free throws. After a Knicks basket, he drove into the lane and passed to Kelly Olynyk, who scored while being fouled, completing the three-point play to make it 101-96.</p>
<p>“He can read the game and what’s necessary for that possession and it doesn’t have to just be about him scoring,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “He made some big defensive plays and when you have a guy that you can just give the ball to on the other end and know that you’re going to get a coherent possession offensively it just takes a lot of pressure off your basketball team mentally.”</p>
<p>The Knicks jumped to a 15-5 lead but the defenses soon settled in and Miami led 25-23 after one. New York then went 7 for 11 from behind the arc in the second and shot 68.4% overall, but Miami hit 65% of its shots and held a 60-59 edge at the break.</p>
<p>The Heat then limited the Knicks to 18 points in the third to take an 82-77 lead to the final period.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Miami used its 16th different starting lineup in its 23 games, with Nunn making his third start. But with Goran Dragic sitting out with a sprained left ankle as Miami&#8217;s latest injury, Spoelstra said: “Nobody’s going to feel sorry for us and we don’t want any pity.&#8221;</p>
<p>Knicks: Randle was 5 for 5 in the second quarter, with three 3-pointers, for 13 points. &#8230; C Nerlens Noel missed his second straight game with a sore left knee.</p>
<p>BUTLER&#8217;S DONE IT</p>
<p>Butler began his career playing for Thibodeau in Chicago, where he averaged 2.6 points as a rookie in the lockout-shortened 2011-12 season. Thibodeau said he and Bulls leadership viewed Butler as someone who would be a solid rotation player, not one who would become a regular All-Star who averaged more than 20 points by the time he left Chicago.</p>
<p>“To say that we saw him as a superstar, we didn’t see that,” Thibodeau said. “But that’s why you should never measure what’s inside a person’s heart, his head, his drive. He is such a great worker and so smart. He got better every year and to the point now where he’s one of the elite players in the league and the impact that he has on the game is unbelievable.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">860484</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beal starts 0 for 13, Heat roll past Wizards 122-95</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/beal-starts-0-for-13-heat-roll-past-wizards-122-95/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 04:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=858695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Washington’s Bradley Beal thought he had an open path to a layup in the opening minutes, unaware that Miami’s Bam Adebayo was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Washington’s Bradley Beal thought he had an open path to a layup in the opening minutes, unaware that Miami’s Bam Adebayo was going to swat his shot out of bounds with ease.</p>
<p>Beal’s night didn’t get any better.</p>
<p>And the Heat looked like themselves again.</p>
<p>Beal — the NBA’s scoring leader, averaging 34.8 points entering Friday — missed his first 13 shot attempts, reserve Kendrick Nunn had 25 points and Miami rolled to a 122-95 win over the Wizards.</p>
<p>Adebayo scored 21 for Miami, which got 17 points from Kelly Olynyk, 17 more from Tyler Herro and a 14-point, nine-assist, eight-rebound night from Jimmy Butler.</p>
<p>Beal scored only seven for Washington, the first time this season he has been held below 25. Alex Len scored 18, Russell Westbrook scored 13 and Rui Hachimura added 12 for the Wizards, who won in Miami on Wednesday by holding the Heat to 35 second-half points — then gave up 40 in the first quarter on Friday.</p>
<p>Miami led by as many as 37, the biggest Heat lead of the season — and biggest Washington deficit of the season.</p>
<p>Everything was different for the Heat. They had a morning shootaround, a break from the norm. They changed the starting lineup, inserting Goran Dragic for Herro. Heat coach Erik Spoelstra even challenged a foul call, something he hardly ever does, and was successful.</p>
<p>And Beal simply couldn’t buy a basket.</p>
<p>He was 0 for 6 in the first quarter and 0 for 6 again in the second. He missed his first shot of the third before getting a 3-pointer to fall with 9:46 left in the period.</p>
<p>That was his last shot of the night. Washington lifted all five of its starters with 4:14 left in the third, down 93-61.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Wizards: Beal&#8217;s scoring average fell to 33.3. &#8230; Washington’s 5-14 start matches the seventh-worst in franchise history. &#8230; The Wizards are 2-0 with Westbrook in the lineup against Brooklyn this season, and 0-11 when he’s in the lineup against any other team.</p>
<p>Heat: Dragic left in the third quarter with a sprained left ankle. X-rays were negative. &#8230; The Heat won the season series with the Wizards 2-1, the 15th time in the last 18 seasons that they at least split with Washington.</p>
<p>REFEREE DUO</p>
<p>Lauren Holtkamp-Sterling and Ashley Moyer-Gleich were two of the officials, joined by crew chief Brian Forte. It was the second time in NBA history that two women worked a game; Natalie Sago and Jenna Schroeder were on a crew in Orlando together last month.</p>
<p>FREE THROWS</p>
<p>Adebayo went to the line 11 times in the first quarter alone, making them all. It was the first time a Heat player made that many free throws in any quarter since Dwyane Wade made 14 in the fourth against Cleveland in 2007.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Wizards: Visit Charlotte on Sunday.</p>
<p>Heat: Visit New York on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">858695</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monk runs wild, scores 36 as Hornets top Heat 129-121 in OT</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/monk-runs-wild-scores-36-as-hornets-top-heat-129-121-in-ot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 04:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=853769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Malik Monk had the best scoring game of his career, and the Charlotte Hornets got a comeback they won’t soon forget. Monk...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Malik Monk had the best scoring game of his career, and the Charlotte Hornets got a comeback they won’t soon forget.</p>
<p>Monk came off the bench to score 36 points and make nine 3-pointers, Devonte’ Graham added 24 points and the Hornets rallied from a 10-point deficit in the final 2:47 of regulation to beat the Miami Heat 129-121 in overtime on Monday night.</p>
<p>The 36 points was a Hornets&#8217; reserve record, one better than the 35 that Graham had against Indiana on Nov. 5, 2019.</p>
<p>“I was ready, and I was just locked in,&#8221; Monk said.</p>
<p>Monk sent the Hornets to OT by making a 3-pointer with 16.6 seconds left, and Charlotte never trailed in the extra period. Cody Zeller had 19 points and 12 rebounds, Gordon Hayward scored 19 and LaMelo Ball finished with 14 points and seven assists for Charlotte in his first start.</p>
<p>“It’s been a resilient group all year,” Hornets coach James Borrego said. “We never dropped the sword. Our mentality is to keep fighting to the end. Down 10 with two-plus minutes to go, nobody hung their heads.”</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler scored 25 points and Bam Adebayo added 23 for Miami, which got 19 from Max Strus. The Heat used a 24-7 run to turn a seven-point deficit into a 10-point lead late in the fourth, then gave up 28 points in the final 7:47.</p>
<p>“At the end of the day, if you have a double-digit lead you have to find a way to get stops and finish it off,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “We weren&#8217;t able to do that.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Hornets made 21 3-pointers, tying the third-most in franchise history. They also set a season-high for points and topped the 30-assist mark for the ninth time this season.</p>
<p>Duncan Robinson had 16, while Tyler Herro and Kelly Olynyk each scored 11 for Miami. Herro’s status was in question because someone he lives with tested positive for COVID-19 on Saturday. But Herro was cleared to play Monday afternoon, which indicates that the housemate likely got a false positive and returned multiple negative tests since.</p>
<p>“We have to get stops. That&#8217;s the bottom line,&#8221; Adebayo said. “You can play as much offense as you want, but you have to get stops.&#8221;</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Hornets: Ball got the first start of his career for Charlotte because Terry Rozier missed the game with a sprained right ankle. &#8230; Charlotte hadn’t won consecutive games in Miami since 2007. &#8230; The Hornets could be down another starter. PJ Washington left in the third quarter; the initial diagnosis was a sprained right foot. Washington finished with six points in 24 minutes.</p>
<p>Heat: Strus’ previous career-high was 12. &#8230; Meyers Leonard was not with the team Monday; he was getting his injured shoulder checked by a doctor. He hurt his ankle Feb. 3, 2020 and between that and the shoulder issue has appeared in eight of Miami’s 65 games since.</p>
<p>MARCH 11 MEMORIES</p>
<p>It was the first game between the teams since March 11, the night the NBA suspended last season because of the pandemic. “In some ways it feels like forever ago and then I walked into this building and it feels like yesterday. &#8230; Things have never been the same since. Hopefully we’re back there soon,” Borrego said.</p>
<p>NOTHING HAPPENED</p>
<p>Olynyk had a 3-pointer blocked in the second quarter, the ball ricocheted off Hayward’s head, Olynyk got it back, Herro missed a 3, Adebayo got that rebound, lost the ball and it eventually wound up back with Olynyk — who made a 3. Except it didn’t happen; the NBA replay center ruled a few minutes later that Olynyk’s made 3 was after the shot clock expired.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Hornets: Host Philadelphia on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host Washington on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">853769</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat say Herro may miss time for virus-related issue</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-say-herro-may-miss-time-for-virus-related-issue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 05:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=852554</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat may have another player missing games for virus-related reasons, after second-year guard Tyler Herro revealed that someone who lives...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat may have another player missing games for virus-related reasons, after second-year guard Tyler Herro revealed that someone who lives with him tested positive for COVID-19.</p>
<p>Herro is listed as questionable on the team’s injury report for Monday’s game against the Charlotte Hornets, that announcement coming Sunday afternoon — less than 24 hours after Herro learned of the positive test and his potential exposure.</p>
<p>The reason the Heat cited for having Herro on the report is the NBA’s health and safety protocols, which only means it is a virus-related reason and does not suggest that he tested positive. Herro was not with the team for practice Sunday.</p>
<p>Miami — off to a 7-12 start after going to the NBA Finals last season — has already had eight players miss a combined 30 games for virus-related reasons, including a 10-game absence for All-Star forward Jimmy Butler. If Herro cannot play Monday, he’d become the ninth Heat player on that list.</p>
<p>“By any means necessary right now,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “We’ve been through so much. I think everybody is able to adapt to this. This is what’s required right now.”</p>
<p>Not long after Miami beat Sacramento 105-104 to snap a five-game losing streak Saturday night, Herro publicly stated that someone living in his home had just tested positive. Herro is tested daily and obviously had not tested positive Saturday, since the NBA and Heat permitted him to be on the floor; he played a team-high 40 minutes and scored 15 points.</p>
<p>But even being around someone who has the virus sets the NBA’s contact-tracing wheels into motion, to determine if Herro could have been exposed. That investigation will determine if Herro — who had the virus last season, before the NBA’s restart bubble at Walt Disney World was launched — will have to quarantine and if so, for how long. Such absences have typically been about a week, some a bit shorter.</p>
<p>“We all know how crazy this time is going,” Herro said Saturday. “Someone who lives with me tested positive before the game and I found out at halftime. I don’t know; hopefully, I don’t have to quarantine. It’s just crazy what’s going on. It’s crazy.”</p>
<p>Herro is averaging 17.5 points this season. He missed seven games in January because of neck spasms. Butler returned from his virus-related hiatus with a season-high 30 points, the last two of them coming with 42.1 seconds left in Saturday’s win.</p>
<p>Part of the NBA probe into Herro’s situation will determine if he is a close contact, as defined by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. That would mean he would have been within 6 feet of an infected person “for a cumulative total of 15 minutes or more over a 24-hour period” in the past two days.</p>
<p>The Heat could get three guards back on Monday. Kendrick Nunn didn’t play Saturday; he wasn’t cleared by game time while awaiting the results of a COVID-19 test, though he did get the negative result back during the game. Avery Bradley (knee) and Goran Dragic (groin) also may be able to return from injuries.</p>
<p>“Ever since the pandemic hit, everything’s been kind of in the air,” Nunn said. “You take every day for what it is. Adversity &#8230; things happen.”</p>
<p>Miami has used 14 starting lineups in its first 19 days, because of all its virus and injury issues. If Herro can&#8217;t play Monday, a 15th lineup would seem possible.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re living with the punches right now,&#8221; Heat center Bam Adebayo said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">852554</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;We have to figure this out&#8217;: Heat say turnaround will come</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/we-have-to-figure-this-out-heat-say-turnaround-will-come/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 19:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=849927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — As if losing the NBA Finals isn’t bad enough, there now seems to be a curse that stretches into the following season....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — As if losing the NBA Finals isn’t bad enough, there now seems to be a curse that stretches into the following season.</p>
<p>The Miami Heat aren’t believing that quite yet — even after a disastrous start to the 2020-21 campaign.</p>
<p>The reigning Eastern Conference champions are 6-12, matching the franchise’s worst 18-game start since opening 4-14 in 2007-08. The roster has been decimated by injuries and virus-related issues, and the current losing streak reached five games after a 108-104 loss to the Los Angeles Clippers in a game where Miami led by 18 points early but wound up trailing by as many as 19.</p>
<p>“Heat Nation, we are going to figure this out,” All-Star center Bam Adebayo said. “Just bear with us. We are going to figure this out. I can promise them that we are going to figure this out. I know that they’re tired of seeing us lose. We’re tired of losing. We have to figure this out.”</p>
<p>The next chance to get things right comes Saturday when Miami hosts Sacramento.</p>
<p>The year after losing the finals has not been kind to the most recent teams who have dropped the title series. Cleveland lost the finals in 2018, LeBron James left to join the Los Angeles Lakers and the Cavaliers haven’t been close to the same since. Golden State lost the finals in 2019, saw most of the roster get hurt, watched Kevin Durant leave for Brooklyn and finished last season with the NBA’s worst record.</p>
<p>It’s not that bad for the Heat. Bad enough, though.</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler has missed 12 of Miami’s 18 games, mostly because of the league’s health and safety protocols established for safe play during the coronavirus pandemic. Avery Bradley, brought in as a free agent, has missed 10 games, and most of that is because of virus-related issues. Tyler Herro missed seven games with neck spasms. Meyers Leonard, a key performer last season, has appeared in only three games this season and is now out with a shoulder injury.</p>
<p>The Heat have used 13 starting lineups, are 0-10 when shooting less than 48%, set an NBA record on Wednesday by missing 15 3-point tries in the first quarter and are shooting 29% from beyond the arc in this five-game losing streak.</p>
<p>“You can’t make an excuse for it,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “You just have to continue to grind, to learn, to compete for each other, get better. There are certain points where we are and we just need to be more consistent with it. We will be getting guys back soon enough.”</p>
<p>Miami’s seven most experienced players, in terms of years in the NBA, were all unavailable Thursday.</p>
<p>This was the lineup the Heat started the fourth quarter with against the Clippers: Gabe Vincent and Max Strus, who are on two-way contracts; Precious Achiuwa, who is a rookie; KZ Okpala, a second-year pro who played in five games last season; and Herro, a second-year guard who hadn’t played in two weeks.</p>
<p>“A lot of dudes that are playing right now are the young guys, including me,” Adebayo said.</p>
<p>Help is on the way. The Heat hope Butler can play Saturday. Dragic isn’t expected to be out for long. Herro, in his return game Thursday, had a big fourth quarter to lead a comeback attempt.</p>
<p>He insists the turnaround is coming.</p>
<p>“No one’s sorry for us,” Herro said. “There’s no excuses. We’re just going to continue to get better and hopefully one day we can get everybody back and show everybody what we’re made of.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">849927</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/bam-adebayo-e1611949838213.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/bam-adebayo-e1611949838213.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/bam-adebayo-e1611949838213.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">bam adebayo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clippers rally from 18 points down, top ailing Heat 109-105</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/clippers-rally-from-18-points-down-top-ailing-heat-109-105/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 05:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=849182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Actual ticketholders were back at a Miami Heat game for the first time since March. The Los Angeles Clippers had many of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MIAMI (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Actual ticketholders were <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-welcome-fans-to-home-games-for-1st-time-since-pandemics-start/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">back at a Miami Heat game</a> for the first time since March. The Los Angeles Clippers had many of them deciding to leave early.<p>Nicolas Batum scored 18 points and the Clippers used a 20-2 run in the third quarter to help fuel what became a 109-105 victory over the short-handed and reeling Heat on Thursday night.</p><p>Lou Williams had 17 points for the Clippers, who were again without Kawhi Leonard and Paul George because of the league&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s virus protocols and Patrick Beverley with right knee soreness.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Big win for us tonight,&#x201D; Batum said.</p><p>The Clippers won despite trailing by 18 early, the franchise&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s biggest comeback win since rallying from 31 down to beat Golden State in a playoff game on April 15, 2019.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We just continue to keep playing, kept fighting, kept competing, just trying to play the right way,&#x201D; Clippers coach Tyronn Lue said.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/TheMozKnowz/status/1355006102132416514?s=20</embed></div><p>Tyler Herro returned after missing seven games with neck spasms and scored 19 points for Miami, which dropped its fifth straight and is 6-12 after going to the NBA Finals last season. The Heat welcomed back about 1,500 fans, all of whom had to get past virus-sniffing dogs or pass a rapid coronavirus test, for the first time since last season was suspended on March 11 as the pandemic was beginning.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;This group is good in this locker room,&#x201D; Herro said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;And we&#x2019;re going to figure it out soon.&#x201D;</p><p>Miami got 30 points from its two-way contract players, Gabe Vincent (18) and Max Strus (12). Bam Adebayo finished with 16 points, 13 rebounds and seven assists for Miami.</p><p>The Heat were without seven players. Jimmy Butler was listed as questionable Thursday afternoon but was eventually downgraded to out and missed his 10th consecutive game because of the league&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s virus protocols. Also out: Avery Bradley, Goran Dragic, Moe Harkless, Meyers Leonard, Chris Silva and Andre Iguodala, all injured.</p><p>Miami had 33 points in the first 11 minutes &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; and 36 points in the next 25 minutes. The Clippers were within 50-48 at the half, then Batum had four 3-pointers in a third quarter where Los Angeles would outscore Miami 40-19.</p><p>The Heat got within three in the final seconds, but the Clippers survived.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;In a perfect world, we&#x2019;d like to be in a better place than we are right now &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; but we&#x2019;re not,&#x201D; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We just have to continue to grind.&#x201D;</p><p>TIP-INS</p><p>Clippers: Reggie Jackson and Marcus Morris each had 16 for the Clippers. &#x2026; If the Clippers win Friday in Orlando, they&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;d be 15-5 and match the team&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s best 20-game start in the L.A. era. The 1974-75 Buffalo Braves were 16-4. &#x2026; The Clippers improved to 5-0 after losses this season. &#x2026; They were assessed a technical with 27.5 seconds left for calling too many time-outs.</p><p>Heat: Miami &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; playing game No. 18 &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; used its 13th starting lineup, tying Houston for the NBA&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s most. The Heat used 15 regular-season lineups a year ago. &#x2026; Iguodala turned 37 on Thursday, sharing a birthday with Heat assistant Octavio de la Grana.</p><p>WILD SWINGS</p><p>The Heat won the first quarter by 14 points and fourth quarter by 15. The Clippers won the second by 12 and third by 21.</p><p>WELCOME BACK</p><p>It was a return for Clippers associate head coach Dan Craig, who spent 17 years with Miami before leaving after last season. Craig also won a G League championship with Miami&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s affiliate, the Sioux Falls Skyforce.</p><p>FORAN HONORED</p><p>Longtime Heat strength and conditioning coach Bill Foran was announced Thursday as the inaugural recipient of the National Basketball Strength &amp; Conditioning Coaches Association Lifetime Achievement Award. It will bear Foran&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s name.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Clippers: Visit Orlando on Friday.</p><p>Heat: Host Sacramento on Saturday.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">849182</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat welcome fans to home games for 1st time since pandemic&#8217;s start</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-welcome-fans-to-home-games-for-1st-time-since-pandemics-start/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 21:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=848725</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Heat allowed select fans to attend their game versus the Los Angeles Clippers at the AmericanAirlines Arena, marking the first time fans were...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Heat allowed select fans to attend their game versus the Los Angeles Clippers at the AmericanAirlines Arena, marking the first time fans were allowed inside the building since the start of the coronavirus pandemic last year.</p>
<p>With the help of COVID-19 detection dogs, the Heat allowed 1,500 season ticket holders into the downtown Miami arena for the Thursday night game.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ll ask you to stand in line, to put your hands by your sides,&#8221; said Matthew Jafarian, the Heat&#8217;s Executive Vice President of Business Strategy. &#8220;The dog will simply walk past you. If they don&#8217;t detect anything, they&#8217;ll continue to move on, and you get into the arena.&#8221;</p>
<p>Heat officials said if the COVID-19 detection dog sits down, there is no argument as to whether or not that fan can remain at the arena. They will get a refund and must leave the premises.</p>
<p>&#8220;If they do detect something on you, they&#8217;ll sit down by you,&#8221; Jafarian added. &#8220;A nice, gentle signal to the handler to let somebody know this person is presumptive positive. We will ask you to step out of the line, and we&#8217;ll give you a refund and send you on your way.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Heat have lost four straight games heading into their game against the Clippers, and they hope fans will help them break their current losing streak.</p>
<p>&#8220;Having people in the building, you know, that&#8217;s what our guys play for,&#8221; Heat head coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>The players said they are anxiously awaiting the fans&#8217; arrival.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s something we&#8217;re looking forward to: just getting the fans back in,&#8221; guard Kendrick Nunn said.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s good to keep gradually getting Heat nation in there,&#8221; center Bam Adebayo said.</p>
<p>&#8220;We truly miss them and their support,&#8221; guard Avery Bradley said. &#8220;Having them in and creating that atmosphere for us, that&#8217;s what the game is all about. I feel like it really energizes us.&#8221;</p>
<p>Testing began at around 6:45 p.m. outside of the arena.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m so proud to be here tonight,&#8221; Heat fan Biscayne Birdman said. &#8220;Whether we win or lose, who cares. I&#8217;m in the house with our boys &#8212; bottom line. We&#8217;re finally here at least, for at least 20% of our season ticket holders, so I am admired, and I feel ecstatic, and I feel like a little kid at Disney World.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s very meaningful,&#8221; Heat fan Michelle Hollister said. &#8220;We&#8217;re glad to be able to be out and do something normal, somewhat normal, and cheer on our team.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tight security was seen as fans entered the downtown Miami arena, which included the COVID-19 detection dogs. However, fans did not seem to mind the added layer of security.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s a lot better to go to the game to know you&#8217;re safe than watch from home,&#8221; Heat fan Tzvi Grossman said. &#8220;We&#8217;ve been on the couch too long.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Feels good, and the K-9 dogs &#8212; I think, personally, it&#8217;s great,&#8221; Heat fan Anibal Liguere said.</p>
<p>The Heat plan to increase the number of fans allowed into the arena as the season progresses. Thursday night, no COVID-19 was detected as a result of the dog&#8217;s screening.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">848725</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/012821-covid-detection-dog.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ff64ae18-d012-4706-9477-81f63bd0019c/817dcead-0e89-46ef-9b13-6f76143b11f6/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219908~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ff64ae18-d012-4706-9477-81f63bd0019c/817dcead-0e89-46ef-9b13-6f76143b11f6/main.mp4*~hmac=7c8642bbff0396141b536b3ab3904084e45c261433b12c4d9f3fe6f8d9207d33' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/012821-covid-detection-dog.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/012821-covid-detection-dog.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">012821 covid detection dog</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nuggets run away from short-handed Heat, 109-82</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nuggets-run-away-from-short-handed-heat-109-82/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 03:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=847826</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Denver Nuggets might not want this road trip to end. The Miami Heat cannot get Jimmy Butler back quickly enough. Nikola...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Denver Nuggets might not want this road trip to end.</p>
<p>The Miami Heat cannot get Jimmy Butler back quickly enough.</p>
<p>Nikola Jokic had 21 points and 11 rebounds and the Nuggets won their fifth straight, building a 25-point halftime lead and beating the Heat 109-82 on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Michael Porter Jr. scored 17 points, JaMychal Green added 15 and Jamal Murray had 14 for Denver, which improved to 4-0 on its five-game road trip — the first four-win trip for the Nuggets since December 2013. A win Friday in San Antonio would give Denver its first 5-0 trip since January 2012, and the Nuggets have won 10 of 13 since since a 1-4 start.</p>
<p>“When we were 1-4, there was no panic,&#8221; Murray said. “It&#8217;s five games in. &#8230; Turned things around pretty quick.&#8221;</p>
<p>Butler watched from the Miami bench, significant since Wednesday’s game was the first in more than two weeks where he could be with his team. He&#8217;s now missed the last nine Heat games because of virus-related protocols.</p>
<p>The Heat are 2-7 in this stretch without him and have dropped four straight. Herro (neck spasms) missed a seventh consecutive game, Dragic was out with a groin strain, and Kendrick Nunn led Miami with 17 points.</p>
<p>The Heat got Avery Bradley back for the first time in nine games; he, like Butler, was out in accordance with the NBA’s virus protocols.</p>
<p>“It was great to see the guys, everybody, even though everybody wasn’t available,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>Bradley had eight points in 18 minutes.</p>
<p>“Even though we came up short tonight, felt great to be back out there,” Bradley said.</p>
<p>Denver led 58-33 at the half, the Nuggets’ biggest halftime lead this season and biggest in a road arena since holding a 31-point lead at the break in Chicago on March 21, 2018. The Heat missed 15 3-pointers in the first quarter — an NBA record for an opening period, and a team record for any quarter.</p>
<p>Denver’s lead was down to seven early in the fourth, but back-to-back 3s by Porter and Green got the Nuggets’ edge back to 13 and another 3 by Jokic made it 94-74 with 5:35 left.</p>
<p>“That team was missing Jimmy Butler, Goran Dragic, Tyler Herro, a lot of their top players,” Denver coach Michael Malone said. “I don’t know if we’re as good as we played tonight and I know they’re a hell of a lot better than they played.”</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo scored 15 for Miami.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Nuggets: Guard P.J. Dozier (right hamstring strain) missed the game and the Nuggets are bracing for it to be a multi-game absence. &#8230; The 33 points allowed by Denver in the first half was not only a season best, but it was nearly 24 points below the Nuggets’ average through the first 17 games.</p>
<p>Heat: Wednesday was the start of a six-game homestand for Miami. After that, the Heat play eight of their next nine on the road. &#8230; Duncan Robinson’s first 3-pointer was the 400th of his career, including playoffs. He’s the 12th Heat player to make that many.</p>
<p>TRIBUTES</p>
<p>The Heat held a pregame moment of silence to commemorate Tuesday being the one-year anniversary of Kobe Bryant’s death and last week’s death of Baseball Hall of Famer Hank Aaron. And in his pregame remarks, Malone paid tribute to longtime NBA journalist Sekou Smith, who died Tuesday after a short battle with COVID-19. “I’m devastated for his family,” Malone said.</p>
<p>DOG TIME</p>
<p>Miami is welcoming back a small number of fans Thursday, with coronavirus-detection dogs being utilized to screen guests before entering the arena.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Nuggets: Visit San Antonio on Friday night.</p>
<p>Heat: Host the Los Angeles Clippers on Thursday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">847826</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harden, Durant help Nets break away late, beat Heat 98-85</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/harden-durant-help-nets-break-away-late-beat-heat-98-85/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 05:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=844993</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — Kevin Durant wasn’t making shots. James Harden was barely taking them. That sent the Brooklyn Nets into a defensive struggle, and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — Kevin Durant wasn’t making shots. James Harden was barely taking them.</p>
<p>That sent the Brooklyn Nets into a defensive struggle, and the NBA’s highest-scoring team handled it well until their superstars showed up.</p>
<p>Harden and Durant each scored 20 points despite three relatively quiet quarters, and the Nets broke away with a big run in the fourth to beat the Miami Heat 98-85 on Monday night.</p>
<p>Kyrie Irving added 16 points for the Nets, who completed a sweep of the Heat in two games that couldn&#8217;t have been more different. Brooklyn won 128-124 on Saturday, then took the rematch despite barely topping its lowest-scoring game of the season.</p>
<p>“I think our defense held tight the whole game,” Durant said. “Once we were able to start making some shots there in the fourth, we were able to pull away. But our defense won us this game for sure.”</p>
<p>Harden had only 10 points and five shots through three, then scored 10 more in the 18-2 spurt that turned a tie game into a 96-80 lead. The NBA&#8217;s assists leader finished with eight, but struggled to search for his own shot until changing his mentality in the fourth.</p>
<p>“Just being aggressive,” he said. “I think I wasn’t very aggressive throughout the course of the game.”</p>
<p>Durant shot just 4 for 17 through three, then hit two 3-pointers in the fourth, the latter snapping a 78-all tie and igniting the big run.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo had 26 points, 10 rebounds and five assists in a strong follow-up to his career-high 41 points Saturday. But outside of Goran Dragic&#8217;s 21 points, there was little else for a short-handed Heat team that is without Jimmy Butler and Avery Bradley because of health and safety protocols. Tyler Herro, Meyers Leonard and Maurice Harkless are injured.</p>
<p>But it looked for a while as though they could pull it out anyway, shutting down a team that came in averaging 120.3 points per game until midway through the final period.</p>
<p>“Their talent just took over at the end,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “I love the way our guys competed.”</p>
<p>The Nets were 4 for 21 (19%) in the first quarter, missing all 10 3-pointers in their lowest-scoring period of the season, which ended with Miami leading 21-15.</p>
<p>The second quarter was slightly easier on the eyes — and rims. Miami took a 45-41 edge into halftime, going just 4 for 19 on 3s but doubling the Nets&#8217; makes after they went 2 for 17.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Adebayo beat the buzzer to end the third quarter with a 3-pointer that gave Miami a 71-70 lead. He also made a 3 as time expired to end the first half Saturday, followed by a long jumper in the final second of the third quarter. &#8230; Duncan Robinson was 1 for 10, all from 3-point range.</p>
<p>Nets: Durant missed his first six 3-point attempts before sinking one in the third quarter. He finished 3 for 12 behind the arc and has scored 20 points in every game this season. &#8230; The Nets have won five straight at home.</p>
<p>KYRIE AND KOBE</p>
<p>Irving arrived at the arena wearing a No. 8 Kobe Bryant Lakers jersey. In a video posted by the Nets, he <a href="https://twitter.com/BrooklynNets/status/1353841306959835136?s=20">pulled his jacket open</a> for a full view of the jersey, saying: “You know who I was rocking tonight. Come on, it’s obvious.”</p>
<p>The Nets were scheduled to play at the Knicks last Jan. 26, hours after the helicopter crash that killed Bryant. Irving left the arena, too distraught to play following the death of his friend.</p>
<p>HARDEN&#8217;S ADJUSTMENTS</p>
<p>Harden had just two baskets, both in the fourth quarter, during Saturday&#8217;s game. He then took only two shots in the first half Monday in another passive performance.</p>
<p>But coach Steve Nash said before the game he wasn&#8217;t worried about the three-time scoring champion as he adjusts to his new team.</p>
<p>“Would I like James to be more aggressive? Yes. Will he be more aggressive in time? I think so,” Nash said. “I think once he gets more comfortable with his teammates, when he gets in better shape, when he’s adapted to this whole new environment, we’ll see an improved James scoring the ball.&#8221;</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Host the Denver Nuggets on Wednesday to start a six-game homestand.</p>
<p>Nets: Open a three-game road trip Wednesday at Atlanta.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">844993</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Durant, Irving help Nets hold off Adebayo, Heat 128-124</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/college/durant-irving-help-nets-hold-off-adebayo-heat-128-124/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 04:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=841979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — Brooklyn&#8217;s three superstars were just enough to overcome Bam Adebayo&#8217;s brilliant individual effort. Kevin Durant scored 31 points, Kyrie Irving took...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — Brooklyn&#8217;s three superstars were just enough to overcome Bam Adebayo&#8217;s brilliant individual effort.</p>
<p>Kevin Durant scored 31 points, Kyrie Irving took over late and had 28 and the Nets overcame Adebayo&#8217;s career-high 41 points to beat the Miami Heat 128-124 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>James Harden finished with 12 points, 11 assists and seven rebounds as the Nets won for the first time with their Big Three playing together. They lost consecutive games with dismal defensive efforts in Cleveland and barely got enough stops to hold off a short-handed Heat team that had been limited to 81 points by Toronto a night earlier.</p>
<p>“It’s not every day you see this collection of guys playing together in NBA history, so we want to take full advantage of that,” Irving said.</p>
<p>Irving helped pull the Nets through with 12 points in the final 5:48 after the Heat had erased nearly all of an 18-point deficit.</p>
<p>Joe Harris added 23 points and seven 3-pointers for Brooklyn, but the Nets needed Irving&#8217;s 18 points in the final quarter of a game they had largely controlled.</p>
<p>“All three of those guys, they’re just so damn skilled. Off the dribble, their shooting ability, their ability to see open players, and that’s why they&#8217;re three of the best in this business,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “And those are shots that only great players can manufacture.”</p>
<p>Goran Dragic scored 19 points and Kendrick Nunn and Duncan Robinson each had 18 for the Heat, who remain without Jimmy Butler and Tyler Herro. Adebayo also had nine assists while blowing past his previous best scoring night of 30 points.</p>
<p>“I wish we’d gotten the W; 40 don’t mean nothing unless you got the W, for real,” Adebayo said.</p>
<p>Durant was 5 for 5 and scored 13 points in the third quarter, with the last of his three 3-pointers in the period making it 96-80. Adebayo beat the buzzer with a jumper, than Miami opened the fourth with a 13-0 run to get within 96-95.</p>
<p>“We were up 20 points throughout, 16, 14 going to the fourth quarter, so we were in good shape. But we’ve got to put together four quarters of great basketball,” Durant said.</p>
<p>Irving, Harden and Durant quickly combined for eight straight points but Adebayo kept coming, and the Nets needed a couple of clutch baskets from Irving and late free throws to pull it out.</p>
<p>Harris had four 3-pointers and 12 points in the first quarter. The Nets were ahead 60-42 with a little more than two minutes left in the half, but Miami trimmed it to 66-56 on Adebayo&#8217;s 3-pointer just before the buzzer.</p>
<p>Harden didn&#8217;t make a basket until the fourth, threatening to go without one in a game for the first time since he left Oklahoma City. He finally attempted his first shot with 0.7 seconds left in the first quarter and was fouled behind the arc, making all three free throws for a 36-25 lead.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Moe Harkless started at forward but exited in the second quarter with a bruised left thigh after banging legs with a Nets player along the baseline. He hadn&#8217;t even played in the series opener against Toronto and got only six minutes Friday.</p>
<p>Nets: Jeff Green scored 11 points. &#8230; The Nets came in averaging an NBA-best 121.5 points at home.</p>
<p>THE SHIRT OFF HIS BACK</p>
<p>Irving and Adebayo have been friends for years but that means little during the coronavirus pandemic. Irving was trying to get Adebayo’s pink-and-blue Heat jersey after the game <a href="https://twitter.com/ESPNNBA/status/1353189653248151552?s=20">before security intervened</a>, as new NBA initiatives try to keep opposing players separated to stop the spread of the virus.</p>
<p>“Oh, he definitely wants it,” Adebayo said. “I’m going to send him one on my own time.”</p>
<p>Irving was fined $50,000 recently for not wearing a mask during an indoor gathering and said he was trying to stay out of trouble.</p>
<p>“I just want to follow NBA protocols,” he said.</p>
<p>LINE THEM UP</p>
<p>Miami used its 11th different starting lineup in its 15th game, while coach Steve Nash sent out a different first five for the 12th time in Brooklyn&#8217;s 18 games. Part of that is because of player absences and part because he is still experimenting following the Harden trade, which he may still need to do before settling on his preferred starters.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m not sure we’re there yet,&#8221; Nash said. &#8220;It might be ideal to be there but I don’t know that we are, so I don’t want to commit to that yet.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The teams meet again Monday at Barclays Center.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">841979</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Powell, Raptors regroup after blowing lead, beat Heat 101-81</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/powell-raptors-regroup-after-blowing-lead-beat-heat-101-81/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 05:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=840638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TAMPA , Fla. (AP) — Norman Powell scored 23 points, OG Anunoby added 21 and the Toronto Raptors recovered in the second half after blowing...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TAMPA , Fla. (AP) — Norman Powell scored 23 points, OG Anunoby added 21 and the Toronto Raptors recovered in the second half after blowing a 21-point lead to beat the Miami Heat 101-81 on Friday night.</p>
<p>Pascal Siakam had 15 points, 14 rebounds and five assists for the Raptors, who never trailed on their way to avenging a 111-102 loss to the Heat on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>“This was pretty much night and day,” Toronto coach Nick Nurse said of his team&#8217;s defensive effort. “We were definitely flying around on D. It&#8217;s a good two-game scenario in that we learned a lesson. In the NBA, if you come out and you don&#8217;t play, you&#8217;re going to get beat.”</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn led the Heat (6-8) with 20 points, but the injury-riddled defending Eastern Conference champions made just seven of 31 3-point shots (22.7%) in losing for the fourth time in six games. Bam Adebayo had 14 points and eight rebounds.</p>
<p>The Raptors (6-9) led 34-13 when Powell&#8217;s layup completed an 18-2 run with 2:52 left in the first quarter. They were 8 of 11 on 3-point shots in the period.</p>
<p>“I thought we did a good job of not getting stagnant. We kept moving, cutting, and we were able to make plays off that movement,” Powell said.</p>
<p>Powell, starting in place of the injured Kyle Lowry, scored 19 points in the first half, and the Raptors survived another dose of Miami&#8217;s confusing zone defense.</p>
<p>“We would have had a really good offensive night, too, without all those turnovers,” said Nurse.</p>
<p>Toronto shot 46% overall with 22 turnovers.</p>
<p>Goran Dragic had two layups and a baseline jumper and Gabe Vincent added three layups in a 19-5 Miami run that opened the second half and tied it at 61.</p>
<p>But Powell answered with a layup, launching a 12-0 Toronto run, and the Heat never recovered.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Played again without F Jimmy Butler and G Avery Bradley (coronavirus protocol), G Tyler Herro (neck spams) and C Meyers Leonard (left shoulder strain).</p>
<p>Raptors: Lowry did not play because of a toe infection. He tried to play through the injury Wednesday night and is hopeful of playing Sunday, Nurse said. &#8230; Siakam played with a sore groin after a bad fall on Wednesday night. &#8230; Powell averages 17.8 points and is shooting 55% in his four starts this season.</p>
<p>RAPTORS ALMOST CENTERLESS</p>
<p>Tuesday’s release of Alex Len left the Raptors with two centers. Chris Boucher is listed as a forward/center and starting center Aron Baynes, listed as a center-forward, played only 15.6 minutes per game before logging 23 minutes Friday night. “We didn’t see a need for a third center with Chris emerging,” said Nurse. “We’ve got a (roster) spot here and we’ll try to upgrade it with a biggerish-type player.”</p>
<p>HEAT GOING THROUGH TOUGH STRETCH</p>
<p>Miami coach Erik Spoelstra is trying to make the most of the many injury hits taken by his roster in the first 14 games of the season. Spoelstra stressed the minutes gained by younger players who would otherwise be watching. “We put this roster together based on (a next-man-up) identity,” Spoelstra said. “Because of all the missing parts this season &#8230; this is good for all of our guys.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Saturday night&#8217;s game at Brooklyn will be Miami&#8217;s third road game in four days.</p>
<p>Raptors: Play at Indiana Sunday afternoon in the first game of a two-day series. The game has been moved up to a 1 p.m. tipoff.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">840638</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat using COVID detection dogs as they welcome fans</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-using-covid-detection-dogs-as-they-welcome-fans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 17:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=838102</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Miami Heat fans will finally be able to watch games in person once again as the NBA released a list of safety measures put in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami Heat fans will finally be able to watch games in person once again as the NBA released a list of safety measures put in place for upcoming games.</p>
<p>On Thursday, the team announced fans who want to watch a Heat game at the AmericanAirlines Arena can do so with new COVID-19 health and safety measures in place.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re far from being in a place where you can pack an arena,&#8221; Heat head coach Erik Spoelstra said. &#8220;To be able to start to invite people in and do it in the absolute safest way, I think it&#8217;s a step in the right direction. Then, we just have to continue to do everything with great vigilance.&#8221;</p>
<p>Up to 2,000 spectators will be allowed in to watch the Heat play the Los Angeles Clippers next Thursday. The new measures in place are to help mitigate the risk of COVID-19 exposure.</p>
<p>All guests will participate in a mandatory health screening questionnaire as they enter the arena, and they will also have to go through metal detectors and hand sanitizing stations.</p>
<p>They will also be checked by COVID-19 detection dogs upon arrival. The dogs are in use at the Helsinki, Finland airport, where officials said they have been successful. If the dog sits, the person is denied entry.</p>
<p>&#8220;The more we can explore anything for early detection and make it available to as many people as possible helps,&#8221; said Spoelstra. &#8220;I&#8217;d love to have my dog, little 9-pound dog, learn how to do that.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;First and foremost, try to keep everybody safe, hoping everybody&#8217;s following the proper protocols,&#8221; Heat forward Andre Iguodala said. &#8220;We got a huge spike with holiday travel, and we got to make sure everybody is safe.&#8221;</p>
<p>Guests who become sick or do not feel well at the arena will be taken to an isolation room on site.</p>
<p>All guests over the age of 2 will be required to wear a face mask.</p>
<p>Fans aren&#8217;t the only ones who are excited to make a comeback.</p>
<p>&#8220;Super excited,&#8221; said Heat forward Kelly Olynyk. &#8220;Obviously, we haven&#8217;t had as much fans for a long, long time, the game feels different, the vibes, the energy, the atmosphere. Especially playing at home, it&#8217;ll be real nice to have some Heat fans in there.&#8221;</p>
<p>For more information on the health and safety measures put in place for Heat games, <a href="https://www.nba.com/heat/health-and-safety" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">838102</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/miami-heat-virus-safety.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8d4f49c2-2b25-4b78-a3b0-58bd607b39ad/9595355b-2de6-45dc-a497-18dec78adce1/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219846~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8d4f49c2-2b25-4b78-a3b0-58bd607b39ad/9595355b-2de6-45dc-a497-18dec78adce1/main.mp4*~hmac=b822ffe2d31fbc2e642cdd01c3b68f09f571b33bdcac10d5f7692c28cae7cc81' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/miami-heat-virus-safety.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/miami-heat-virus-safety.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami heat virus safety</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nunn scores 28 to lead Heat past Raptors 111-102</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nunn-scores-28-to-lead-heat-past-raptors-111-102/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 03:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=837266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — The Miami Heat were missing a lot of firepower Wednesday night. They did have Kendrick Nunn and a zone defense that...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — The Miami Heat were missing a lot of firepower Wednesday night. They did have Kendrick Nunn and a zone defense that the Toronto Raptors couldn&#8217;t figure out</p>
<p>Nunn scored 28 points and the injury-plagued Heat pulled away in the second half for a 111-102 win.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo had 14 points, 13 rebounds and seven assists for Miami, and Kelly Olynyk came off the bench with 15 points, eight rebounds and eight assists.</p>
<p>Despite missing four key players — including Jimmy Butler, Tyler Herro, Avery Bradley and Meyers Leonard — the Heat (6-7) won their second straight.</p>
<p>“I don&#8217;t know what percentage of our scoring wasn&#8217;t here tonight, but we have a lot of guys who can score 20 points,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “In this (injury) situation, either you put your tail between your legs or you rise to the occasion for your team.”</p>
<p>Fred VanVleet had 24 points and nine assists for the Raptors (5-9), whose three-game winning streak ended. Pascal Siakam and OG Anunoby scored 18 points each for Toronto, which shot 30.2% (13 for 43) in the second half and 39.8% (35 for 88) overall.</p>
<p>“It seemed like we were stuck on 85 for a long stretch late in the game,” VanVleet said. “We&#8217;ll have to get some better looks instead of shooting 3s all the time. When you don&#8217;t make shots against a zone it has a snowball effect. They get more aggressive and it makes it harder.”</p>
<p>After scoring Toronto&#8217;s first seven points of the game, Kyle Lowry finished with eight points, 10 rebounds and seven assists.</p>
<p>Nunn, who had scored just 33 points all season before his 18-point game Monday night, came off the bench and shot 9 of 12 and grabbed eight rebounds in 35 minutes.</p>
<p>Nunn scored on a layup and a 3-pointer to put the Heat up by 11 early in the second quarter, but Terence Davis scored twice during a 9-0 run that got the Raptors quickly back in it.</p>
<p>Nunn hit two more 3-pointers and Olynyk scored eight points on a 21-9 Miami spurt in the third quarter, and the Heat took an 88-83 lead into the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Two straight 3-pointers by Goran Dragic gave Miami a double-digit lead in the closing minutes.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s irrelevant what the (defensive) scheme is,” Spoestra said of the Heat&#8217;s effective zone defense. “Our man defense was good as well. I was more looking to whether we were committed to multiple efforts and we had those tonight.&#8221;</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Herro missed a third game with neck spasms. &#8230; Butler and Bradley missed their fifth straight games while in coronavirus protocol. &#8230; Leonard warmed up, but sat out a fifth game with a shoulder injury. &#8230; Adebayo entered the game as the only NBA player averaging at least 19.5 points, nine rebounds, 5.1 assists, 1.2 blocks and one steal.</p>
<p>Raptors: Lowry needs 14 points to reach 10,000 for his career, all with Toronto. Only five other active NBA players have scored 10,000 points with their current team. &#8230; Chris Boucher&#8217;s franchise-tying record of six straight games of 15 or more points off the bench ended.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Play the Raptors again Friday night in the second game of a four-game road trip.</p>
<p>Raptors: Friday&#8217;s game against Miami will conclude a five-game homestand at Amalie Arena.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">837266</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/kendrick-nunn-e1611244281856.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/kendrick-nunn-e1611244281856.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/kendrick-nunn-e1611244281856.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">kendrick nunn</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat-Pistons game delayed to allow for additional testing</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-pistons-game-delayed-to-allow-for-additional-testing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=834720</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Monday’s game in Miami between the Heat and the Detroit Pistons was pushed back five hours, with the league and teams making...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MIAMI (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Monday&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s game in Miami between the Heat and the Detroit Pistons was pushed back five hours, with the league and teams making that decision so additional COVID-19 testing could be processed.<p>The game was scheduled to begin at 3 p.m. EST and was pushed back to 8 p.m, the league announced Monday afternoon.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/MiamiHEAT/status/1351236583467442188</embed></div><p>It&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s the latest development, albeit a relatively minor one, as a wave of schedule changes in the NBA has now stretched into a second week. The league has postponed 13 games involving 18 teams since Jan. 10, including one matchup that was to have taken place on Monday&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s Martin Luther King Jr. Day game schedule &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Cleveland at Washington.</p><p>Phoenix was scheduled to play Monday in Memphis, ending a weeklong unplanned break for the Suns. Phoenix had three games delayed because of virus-related issues, which can include players dealing with positive COVID-19 tests, inconclusive tests or having to quarantine because contact tracing indicated they could have been exposed to someone who tested positive.</p><p>There have been 14 games called this season for coronavirus-related reasons so far. In addition to the 13 in recent days, the other was a planned Dec. 23 matchup between Oklahoma City and Houston that was pushed back because the Rockets did not have enough eligible players.</p><p>Delaying the Heat-Pistons start time did not affect Detroit&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s travel schedule. The team was already planning to remain in Miami until Tuesday.</p><p>Postponed games, when possible, will be made up in the second half of the season, which will take place from March 11 &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; the one-year anniversary of last season shutting down because of the pandemic &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; through May 16. The league has not yet released that half of the schedule and isn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t expected to do so until late February at the earliest.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">834720</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pistons come into Miami and roll past reeling Heat, 120-100</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/pistons-come-into-miami-and-roll-past-reeling-heat-120-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 05:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=833619</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Detroit Pistons had their most dominant quarter in nearly two years. And last season’s NBA Finals trip for the Miami Heat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Detroit Pistons had their most dominant quarter in nearly two years. And last season’s NBA Finals trip for the Miami Heat suddenly seems long ago.</p>
<p>Jerami Grant scored 24 points, Derrick Rose had 23 off the bench and the Pistons — the team with the NBA’s worst record — came into Miami and beat the Heat 120-100 on Saturday night, sending the reigning Eastern Conference champions to a third consecutive loss.</p>
<p>The teams meet again Monday in Miami.</p>
<p>“I definitely think it was the most complete game we played so far,&#8221; Grant said.</p>
<p>Blake Griffin scored 15 for Detroit, which outscored Miami 38-19 in the third quarter. It was the biggest margin the Pistons outscored an opponent by in their last 331 quarters, going back to April 9, 2019.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo scored 28 points for Miami, which got 22 from Duncan Robinson, 16 from KZ Okpala and 12 from Goran Dragic.</p>
<p>“We didn&#8217;t play to &#8230; the Miami Heat culture that we represent,&#8221; Adebayo said. “I feel like we&#8217;re letting not only us and our teammates down, but the staff, we&#8217;re letting this organization down, the fans down. We&#8217;re built on the culture. The culture is take a bunch of guys, counted out, overlooked, and you figure it out. Right now, we&#8217;re not doing it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami was without Jimmy Butler and Avery Bradley (both coronavirus-related), Tyler Herro (neck spasms) and Meyers Leonard (shoulder). The Heat got six players back — including Adebayo, Okpala and Dragic — from the NBA’s health and safety protocols list after satisfying quarantines mandated after contact tracing showed they may be exposed.</p>
<p>“These are the circumstances,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “It&#8217;s not just for us. There are a lot of teams going through it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Pistons got a reminder of the virus-dominated world postgame. Moments after going into the locker room for what should have been a few minutes of joy, they got told to go for an extra round of testing — so they came back out, went across the court into a far corner of the arena to get those done. The Heat also were tested postgame.</p>
<p>Those moves came after a week where the NBA postponed 12 games for virus-related reasons and put in tougher protocols with hopes of keeping players and coaches safer.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s part of our new NBA,&#8221; Pistons coach Dwane Casey said. “The only thing you can count on are the unusual things that happen during the day. &#8230; It&#8217;s not just about basketball. It&#8217;s about lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Pistons led by as many as 23, their biggest lead this season. Miami has trailed by at least 23 points in four of its first 11 games; that happened in four of 73 Heat regular-season games last season.</p>
<p>Isaiah Stewart had 10 points and 11 rebounds for the Pistons.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Pistons: Rose returned after missing Detroit’s last two games with left knee soreness. &#8230; Before Saturday, Detroit’s last quarter that was won by 19 or more was the fourth against Memphis in the next-to-last game of the 2018-19 season. The Pistons outscored the Grizzlies 36-14.</p>
<p>Heat: Robinson got credited for what officially is his fifth career dunk, the first that happened at AmericanAirlines Arena. &#8230; Okpala got his first NBA start.</p>
<p>STRUGGLING HEAT</p>
<p>Miami, which has used eight starting lineups in 11 games, is 4-7. Only seven of the team’s 33 seasons have started worse.</p>
<p>MIAMI TIES</p>
<p>The Pistons have plenty of Miami ties. They started former Heat guard Wayne Ellington, had Delon Wright — brother of Dorell Wright, a 2006 NBA champion with the Heat — come off the bench and have former Heat guard Rodney McGruder on the roster as well. Plus, rookie Saddiq Bey nearly signed with the Miami Hurricanes before choosing Villanova.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">833619</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Milton sparks 76ers past undermanned Heat 125-108</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/milton-sparks-76ers-past-undermanned-heat-125-108/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 03:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=831842</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Ben Simmons called trade rumors part of the NBA. With another triple-double, he showed why he&#8217;s coveted around the league — and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Ben Simmons called trade rumors part of the NBA. With another triple-double, he showed why he&#8217;s coveted around the league — and needed in Philly.</p>
<p>Simmons had 10 points, 10 assists and 12 rebounds and Shake Milton returned from COVID-related issues and scored 31 points and lead the Philadelphia 76ers to a 125-108 win over the Miami Heat on Thursday night.</p>
<p>“There’s far worse things going on in the world,” Simmons said of recent trade talk. &#8220;If you tell me I’ll never play the game again, that would be a different story.”</p>
<p>The Sixers swept the two-game home set against a Heat team that continues to play with a depleted roster because of issues related to the virus outbreak. Jimmy Butler, Bam Adebayo and Goran Dragic sat out, and the Heat were roughed up early by Milton, Tyrese Maxey and Tobias Harris.</p>
<p>Consider, the 76ers led 73-58 at the break — with only nine combined points from All-Stars Joel Embiid and Simmons. Embiid has emerged early as one of the top players in the NBA, and a 45-point, 16-rebound game Tuesday against the Heat was one of his best. He had only nine points on Thursday, but was barely needed.</p>
<p>Duncan Robinson led the Heat with 22 points and Gabe Vincent had 21.</p>
<p>“I don’t want to hear anything about fatigue,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. &#8220;Philly just outplayed us.”</p>
<p>Simmons had his 30th career triple-double a day after he was dangled as trade bait to Houston in a potential deal for James Harden. Harden landed in Brooklyn in a trade that not only made the Nets the new favorites to win the Eastern Conference, it could ruffle the relationship between Simmons and the franchise that made him the No. 1 pick of the 2016 draft. Coach Doc Rivers talked it out with Simmons after trade rumors swirled earlier this season. Rivers and Simmons had a brief chat at shootaround, leaving the new Sixers coach to say everything was fine.</p>
<p>“This is a business. Things like that happen,” Simmons said. &#8220;The only thing I can control is how I approach my workouts, the games, and my day to day things. I’m just trying to be professional and do the right thing and help my team get wins.”</p>
<p>The Sixers rolled early with the best record in the NBA until COVID issues sent them on a three-game losing streak &#8212; including a loss last week when they had just seven players against Denver &#8212; but have returned to form as more players returned to the active roster. Milton and Matisse Thybulle returned off the bench after a three-game break and Harris, who had 18 points, was back in the starting lineup. Only starting guard Seth Curry, who tested positive last week for coronavirus, remained sidelined against the Heat.</p>
<p>The combination is good enough for Rivers.</p>
<p>“I said it before, I like our team,” he said. “I like today after the trade that we are the same team.”</p>
<p>Milton sank all three 3s and scored 19 points in the half and Maxey, a first-round pick out of Kentucky, continues to shine with his enthusiasm and floaters that made him an instant fan favorite. Sixers fans on social media were seemingly more outraged when Maxey, who scored 15 points, was rumored as part of a Harden deal more than how they felt about Simmons possibly leaving town.</p>
<p>“As long as I’m here, I’m going to try to make Ben a better player,” Rivers said. “And to me, that is the most important part of our relationship.”</p>
<p>EMBIID AND SIMMONS</p>
<p>Embiid had a brief scare when he went up for a basket and slammed his head on the court when he was fouled by Chris Silva. Embiid came up holding the back of his head after the non-shooting foul. Sixers were yelling “He shot the ball! He shot it!” at the refs, to no avail. No worries, the Sixers kept possession and Maxey connected on an alley-oop to Simmons for a 61-47 lead.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: F/C Meyers Leonard sat out with a strained left shoulder. &#8230; G Tyler Herro left the game early with back spasms.</p>
<p>76ers: F Mike Scott left in the first half with a sore right knee. &#8230; Milton was 11 of 15 from the floor with seven assists. &#8230; G Isaiah Joe hit four 3s and scored 12 points.</p>
<p>HE SAID IT</p>
<p>“This is who we are and we have to develop those competitive habits.” — Spoelstra, on his undermanned team.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Return home for a Saturday game against Detroit.</p>
<p>76ers: Play Saturday at Memphis.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">831842</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Embiid scores 45, Mathias wins it for 76ers in OT on 3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/embiid-scores-45-mathias-wins-it-for-76ers-in-ot-on-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 03:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=829864</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Joel Embiid had 45 points and 16 rebounds, Dakota Mathias’ only basket of the game was a go-ahead 3-pointer with 26.1 seconds...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Joel Embiid had 45 points and 16 rebounds, Dakota Mathias’ only basket of the game was a go-ahead 3-pointer with 26.1 seconds left and the Philadelphia 76ers hung on to beat the undermanned Miami Heat 137-134 in overtime on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Embiid had one of the great games of his career and carried the Sixers with a perfect third quarter and clutch buckets in OT to put them on the brink of victory.</p>
<p>It was little-known Mathias with the stunner that won it. Mathias, who went undrafted in 2018 and signed this season with the Sixers as a two-day G League player, got the ball from the top of the arc and buried it for the 134-132 lead.</p>
<p>With Jimmy Butler, Bam Adebayo and Goran Dragic among the Heat sitting out for COVID-related reasons, they pushed the Sixers into OT with a mad-dash end to the fourth. Tyler Herro helped the Heat overcome Embiid’s dominant effort when his 3-pointer tied the game 115-all with 2:25 left. Precious Achiuwa scored two straight baskets &#8212; the first off Philly’s shot clock violation, then off a turnover &#8212; for a 119-115 lead.</p>
<p>Embiid buried the pull-up jumper just inside the 3-point arc with 3.3 seconds left that tied it 120-120 and sent the game into overtime. It was his only bucket of the fourth after he made all eight shots in the third.</p>
<p>Embiid’s go-ahead three-point play with 2:37 left in OT put the Sixers up 126-124, and Herro matched his regulation theatrics with another tying 3 for 129-all.</p>
<p>Danny Green matched the 76ers&#8217; record with nine 3-pointers and scored 29 points and Mike Scott had 16 points.</p>
<p>Herro finished with 34 points, Duncan Robinson had 26 and Gabe Vincent 24.</p>
<p>The game otherwise belonged to Embiid.</p>
<p>Embiid picked up the slack in the third quarter after scoring just 10 points in the first half to help the Sixers snap a two-game losing streak.</p>
<p>He smacked the ball away under the basket to break up a Miami possession, then hustled down to hit Isiah Joe for a 3 and cut the hole to four. Embiid followed that by shaking off a double team and tossing an underhand shot for the basket. He made the free throw and Sixers were down one. Embiid made it back-to-back three-point plays when he got the Heat to bite on a pump-fake from the free-throw line.</p>
<p>The big man even handled the rock with ease and went the length of the floor to hit a little fadeaway and extend the lead.</p>
<p>He was 16 of 23 from the floor and made all 13 free throws.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: F/C Meyers Leonard sat out with a strained left shoulder. &#8230; The Heat continued to struggle with roster issues after their game Sunday against Boston was postponed because they couldn’t field the minimum number of players.</p>
<p>76ers: Coach Doc Rivers said Ben Simmons had to be summoned back to New York after he tried to return to Philadelphia when the team needed to stay an extra day for additional COVID-19 testing. “Obviously, that night we were all in disarray, a bunch of guys were ordering cars, because we all did think we could go back home,” Rivers said. “Ben was on his way, I called him and told him he couldn’t because of league protocols, and he just turned around and came back.” Simmons had five points, 12 assists and fouled out. &#8230; Dwight Howard moved into 13th on the NBA’s career blocked shots list.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Heat stay in Philly and finish the two-game set on Thursday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">829864</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat-Celtics game postponed by NBA due to virus protocols</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-celtics-game-postponed-by-nba-due-to-virus-protocols/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=827698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; The NBA is continuing its season as planned even after concerns about COVID-19 exposure forced the postponement of Miami’s game at Boston on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; The NBA is continuing its season as planned even after concerns about COVID-19 exposure forced the postponement of Miami’s game at Boston on Sunday, a day where no fewer than 15 players around the league were officially declared unable to play for virus-related reasons.</p>
<p>The Celtics had seven of those players and Miami had another. But after Heat guard Avery Bradley was ruled out for Sunday — his test result was not announced, just his status — the rest of the Miami players needed their contact-tracing data analyzed to determine if they had been potentially exposed.</p>
<p>That process would not have been completed in time for the 7 p.m. game, so the league called it off. Boston was preparing to play the game with eight available players; the Celtics have 17 on their roster, seven were out due to the COVID-19 protocols and two more with injuries.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Heat simply were not cleared to play anyone.</p>
<p>“We anticipated that there would be game postponements this season and planned the schedule accordingly,” NBA spokesman Mike Bass said in a statement distributed to The Associated Press and other outlets. “There are no plans to pause the season, and we will continue to be guided by our medical experts and health and safety protocols.”</p>
<p>The NBA had 148 games on the schedule so far through Sunday; the Boston-Miami game was only the second to be postponed for virus-related reasons. The other was Dec. 23, an Oklahoma City at Houston game where the Rockets did not have the required eight players available.</p>
<p>But many teams are feeling the effects of missing players because of testing or other possible exposure. Brooklyn’s Kevin Durant had the virus last spring, but he had to miss three games last week after being exposed to someone who had tested positive for COVID-19. He returned to the Nets on Sunday night.</p>
<p>“You are starting to see what is going on in our country directly affect the NBA because we are no longer in that safety net of the bubble,” said Denver coach Michael Malone, whose club has been without Michael Porter Jr. for its last six games — and counting — because of the league&#8217;s protocols.</p>
<p>The Heat were staying in Boston overnight Sunday and are scheduled to play in Philadelphia, another team with virus issues, on Tuesday and Thursday. The 76ers had eight eligible players and used only seven Saturday in a loss to Denver, doing so in part because some were ruled out in accordance with the virus protocols.</p>
<p>The Celtics were to have been without Jaylen Brown, Javonte Green, Semi Ojeleye, Jayson Tatum, Tristan Thompson, Grant Williams and Robert Williams on Sunday. That’s the most any team has ruled out for a game because of virus-related issues so far this season but does not necessarily mean any of the affected Celtics tested positive.</p>
<p>They were in Miami for a game on Wednesday, and Bradley played in that game for the Heat.</p>
<p>Additionally, a fourth Dallas player was added to the COVID-19 protocol list Sunday, but Maxi Kleber is listed as questionable instead of out for Monday’s home game against New Orleans. Starters Josh Richardson and Dorian Finney-Smith and backup Jalen Brunson are still listed as out. Those three stayed behind in Denver after a win over the Nuggets on Thursday and missed Saturday’s victory at home against Orlando.</p>
<p>The NBA and National Basketball Players Association put together a plan last year to finish the season in a bubble environment at Walt Disney World in Central Florida, where nobody tested positive and no games were missed because of the virus. But NBA Commissioner Adam Silver told teams last month that issues would be “inevitable” with games going on outside a bubble, and he’s been proven correct.</p>
<p>“I think the NBA’s doing all they can and they’re doing a great job, and the (National Basketball Players Association) as well, working together to do a great job to make sure we are as safe as possible,” Indiana guard Victor Oladipo said. “It’s tough. You can try your best and unfortunately there will still be some people that catch it.”</p>
<p>Bradley — who signed with the Heat during the offseason — opted not to join the Los Angeles Lakers, his former team, in the bubble last year because he has a child with breathing problems and did not want to take any unnecessary risks. He chose to play this season, calling living in a COVID-affected world “the new normal.&#8221;</p>
<p>“The numbers are spiking,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said Saturday. “That is the reality. We are committed to proceeding with our industry and we’re doing it with all the best science and adherence to the protocols, but ultimately we’re not in control.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">827698</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/210110_Miami_Heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/337cd072-5684-49cd-b20c-c6ee36af065b/675e8cda-cca3-4e30-b4d2-d2e6c7e0766d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219833~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/337cd072-5684-49cd-b20c-c6ee36af065b/675e8cda-cca3-4e30-b4d2-d2e6c7e0766d/main.mp4*~hmac=bf151ea9dec892af1729a7f0cf43b5c37a53863530498fde91dbc299eca82a8d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/210110_Miami_Heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/210110_Miami_Heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210110_Miami_Heat</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pritchard&#8217;s putback pushes Celtics past Heat, 107-105</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/pritchards-putback-pushes-celtics-past-heat-107-105/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 04:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=824486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Payton Pritchard wasn&#8217;t there last season when the Boston Celtics lost to the Miami Heat in the Eastern Conference finals. He helped...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Payton Pritchard wasn&#8217;t there last season when the Boston Celtics lost to the Miami Heat in the Eastern Conference finals.</p>
<p>He helped Boston get a measure of revenge Wednesday.</p>
<p>Pritchard&#8217;s putback with two-tenths of a second left capped a wild finish, and the Celtics beat the Heat 107-105 in the first matchup this season of last year&#8217;s East finalists.</p>
<p>Jayson Tatum scored 27 points and Jaylen Brown had 21 for the Celtics, who wasted an early 17-point lead and a 10-point lead in the final minute before winning.</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler had 26 points for Miami, which got 16 points from Duncan Robinson, 15 points from Bam Adebayo and 14 from Goran Dragic.</p>
<p>The Celtics went on a late 13-0 run to go up 10 with 1:17 left — only to see the Heat score 10 points in 55 seconds to tie the game on a pair of 3-pointers by Robinson, one while getting fouled, and another from Dragic.</p>
<p>Smart missed a layup on Boston&#8217;s last possession, but Pritchard swooped in for the rebound. Miami&#8217;s last-ditch try was knocked away as time expired.</p>
<p>The teams knelt for the national anthem in response to the decision earlier in the week to not charge the police officer who shot Jacob Blake, a Black man, in Wisconsin last year — as well as Wednesday&#8217;s events at the U.S. Capitol, where a violent mob loyal to President Donald Trump delayed Congress from certifying the results of November’s election and paving the way for President-elect Joe Biden to be sworn in later this month.</p>
<p>Boston made five 3-pointers in the first 5:45 for an early 21-9 lead, and the Celtics held Miami to one field goal in an eight-minute span of the second quarter on the way to leading by as many as 17.</p>
<p>The Heat cut the lead to eight by halftime, part of what became a 39-17 run that saw Miami lead by five in the third quarter. Grant Williams went over everybody for a putback in the final second of the third for Boston, and the teams were tied at 80 entering the last 12 minutes.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Celtics: It was the 31st time Boston’s Brad Stevens coached against Miami’s Erik Spoelstra. Stevens has faced only Brett Brown (37 times) and Mike Budenholzer (36) more. &#8230; Jeff Teague (sprained left ankle) remained out and Smart returned after a one-game absence with a sprained right thumb.</p>
<p>Heat: Miami’s streak of a different starting five in every game this season ended; the Heat used the same opening lineup as they did Monday against Oklahoma City. &#8230; The Heat play their next four games on the road and aren’t back home until facing Detroit on Jan. 16.</p>
<p>FASTEST 300</p>
<p>Miami’s Duncan Robinson made his 300th 3-pointer in his 95th career game, 22 games faster than anyone else in NBA history. Portland’s Damian Lillard and Dallas’ Luka Doncic both got there in 117 games.</p>
<p>FIRST 48</p>
<p>It was the 48th time, including playoffs, that the teams have met at AmericanAirlines Arena: each team has won 24 of those games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Celtics: Host Washington on Friday.</p>
<p>Heat: Visit Washington on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">824486</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat go on 20-0 run, roll past Thunder 118-90</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-go-on-20-0-run-roll-past-thunder-118-90/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 05:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=822593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Kelly Olynyk became the latest option in Miami’s starting lineup. He made a case to stick around. Olynyk made five 3-pointers on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Kelly Olynyk became the latest option in Miami’s starting lineup. He made a case to stick around.</p>
<p>Olynyk made five 3-pointers on his way to 19 points, Bam Adebayo led all scorers with 20 on 9-for-10 shooting and the Heat beat the Oklahoma City Thunder 118-90 on Monday night.</p>
<p>Miami has played six games, alternating losses then wins in all six, and has used a different starting five every time.</p>
<p>“I think the starting lineup is so overstated in so many ways,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “The more important thing is us building consistency to how we want to play.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jimmy Butler scored 18 points for Miami, which used a 20-0 third quarter run to turn what was a four-point game into a runaway. Olynyk had 11 points in that spurt, including three 3-pointers, and the Heat stretched the lead to 35 — their biggest such cushion of the young season.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s a different flow and a different game when you start,&#8221; Olynyk said. “You can kind of let the game come to you. &#8230; But nonetheless, you&#8217;ve got to play your role, whatever it is.&#8221;</p>
<p>Shai Gilgeous-Alexander scored 18 points for the Thunder, who sat their starters in the fourth quarter. Darius Bazley scored 16 and Luguentz Dort scored 12 for Oklahoma City — which saw its chance slip completely away during that five-minute stretch of the third quarter.</p>
<p>“We want to be a team that plays 48 minutes,” Thunder coach Mark Daigneault said.</p>
<p>The Thunder were just 13 of 48 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>“The way our offense is set up, guys are going to get open looks,&#8221; Bazley said. “A lot of the teams we play, they&#8217;re like packed into a shell &#8230; guys are set up to get good looks, especially when you&#8217;re playing off the ball.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Heat shot 57%; the Thunder shot 37%. Duncan Robinson scored 12 points for the Heat, all of them coming from 3-point range.</p>
<p>Adebayo became the fourth player to have multiple games shooting 9-for-10 or better in Heat history, joining Hassan Whiteside (five times), Alonzo Mourning (four) and Udonis Haslem (three). Adebayo also went 9 for 10 on Jan. 5, 2020 against Portland.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Thunder: Rookie Aleksej Pokusevski (concussion protocol) missed the game. &#8230; Oklahoma City was down 63-49 at the half, its biggest deficit at the break so far this season. &#8230; The Thunder went 0 for 10 from the field during Miami’s 20-0 run, seven of those misses from 3-point range.</p>
<p>Heat: Butler missed all six of his shots in Dallas on Friday, so the Heat got him a layup on the first possession of the game Monday. &#8230; The Heat debuted their latest “Vice” court and uniform. &#8230; Miami has played six games; it has led by at least 20 in two and trailed by at least 20 in two others.</p>
<p>REF HURT</p>
<p>Crew chief Kane Fitzgerald left with 3:50 remaining in the first quarter with a left leg injury, possibly to his hamstring. That left two officials to finish the game, referee Aaron Smith and umpire Brandon Schwab — a non-staff official.</p>
<p>RARE WIN</p>
<p>Miami got a home win over the Thunder for the first time since Dec. 3, 2015. The Thunder didn’t come to Miami in 2017 or 2020; the 2017 quirk was just based on the way the schedules fell, and last season’s “home” game for the Heat was played inside the bubble at Walt Disney World.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Thunder: Visit New Orleans on Wednesday, the third game of a five-game trip.</p>
<p>Heat: Host Boston on Wednesday, a rematch of the 2020 Eastern Conference finals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">822593</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/kelly-olynyk.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/kelly-olynyk.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/kelly-olynyk.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">kelly olynyk</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doncic puts up 27 and 14 to lead Mavericks past Heat 93-83</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/doncic-puts-up-27-and-14-to-lead-mavericks-past-heat-93-83/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 04:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=819617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DALLAS (AP) — Luka Doncic had season highs of 27 points and 14 rebounds for his first double-double of the season to lead the Dallas...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DALLAS (AP) — Luka Doncic had season highs of 27 points and 14 rebounds for his first double-double of the season to lead the Dallas Mavericks past the Miami Heat 93-83 on Friday night.</p>
<p>Tim Hardaway Jr. added 18 points as the Mavericks rebounded from a 118-99 loss at home to Charlotte on Wednesday during which they trailed by 30 points in the second half.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo scored 19 points and Avery Bradley 15 for Miami.</p>
<p>The Mavericks scored the final nine points of the second quarter to lead 46-31 at halftime. They padded their lead with a 10-2 run to open the third quarter and led by as many as 24 before a late Heat surge.</p>
<p>When Doncic hit a step-back 3-pointer late in the first half, it ended a personal 12-shot drought from long range. He finished 3 for 9 behind the arc and added seven assists.</p>
<p>The 21-year-old two-time All-Star with 29 career triple-doubles recently acknowledged he&#8217;s out of shape early this season.</p>
<p>“Luka’s going to get there,” Dallas coach Rick Carlisle said. “He’s busting his tail. He’s working hard. You saw him working out after the game (Wednesday). Everything for him now is trending in a good direction conditioning-wise.”</p>
<p>Heat All-Star Jimmy Butler scored two points, both on free throws, and shot 0 for 6 from the floor over 27 minutes in his first appearance since playing only the first half on Christmas against New Orleans because of a sprained right ankle.</p>
<p>Miami missed all 12 of its 3-point attempts in the first half and finished 7 for 33 behind the arc.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Miami has used different starting lineups in all five games this season. … G Gabe Vincent, who played 15 minutes in his season debut Wednesday, was inactive with a right knee injury.</p>
<p>Mavericks: James Johnson was fined $40,000 by the NBA for instigating a fourth-quarter incident in Wednesday’s loss.</p>
<p>WE&#8217;RE NOT IN FLORIDA ANYMORE</p>
<p>The Heat played their previous 35 games in the Sunshine State — 29 playoff games in the Orlando bubble, preseason games at home and in Tampa, four games this season at home and in Orlando – since playing at Washington on March 8. Because of pandemic protocols, coach Erik Spoelstra reported no highlights in coming to Dallas.</p>
<p>“You get on a plane, you land, you take a bus, go to your hotel, order room service and that’s it,” Spoelstra said. “It’s a little bit different than our NBA experience in a typical year. That’s just the deal, and we’re grateful that we have an opportunity to continue to play.”</p>
<p>SECOND EFFORT NEEDS WORK</p>
<p>The Heat and Mavericks went into the game bringing up the rear in the NBA in second-chance points, averaging 7.8 and 7.5 respectively. And they couldn’t match those figures Friday. Dallas converted four offensive rebounds into seven points, Miami five offensive boards into four points.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: On Monday they host the Oklahoma City Thunder, who will be playing their second of five straight on the road.</p>
<p>Mavericks: Begin their second three-game road trip of the young season Sunday at Chicago, then play at Houston the next night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">819617</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat avenge embarrassment, rally to top Bucks 119-108</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-avenge-embarrassment-rally-to-top-bucks-119-108/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 04:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=817737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat engineered a 58-point turnaround against the Milwaukee Bucks in 24 hours. And just like that, an embarrassing loss was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat engineered a 58-point turnaround against the Milwaukee Bucks in 24 hours.</p>
<p>And just like that, an embarrassing loss was avenged.</p>
<p>Goran Dragic scored 26 points off the bench, Bam Adebayo finished with 22 points, 10 assists and eight rebounds and the Heat beat the Bucks 119-108 on Wednesday night — one day after Milwaukee made an NBA-record 29 3-pointers on the way to a 47-point romp on Miami’s home floor.</p>
<p>“They were better than us last night,&#8221; Dragic said. “Tonight, we had to fight.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tyler Herro scored 21 points and grabbed a career-best 15 rebounds for Miami, which trailed by 14 early in the second half and rallied to get a split of the two-game, two-night series against the team that finished with the NBA’s best record in each of the past two regular seasons.</p>
<p>“Started to feel like Miami Heat basketball again,” Herro said.</p>
<p>Giannis Antetokounmpo had a triple-double — 26 points, 13 rebounds, 10 assists — for the Bucks. Donte DiVincenzo scored 15 and Jrue Holiday 13 for Milwaukee, while Khris Middleton was held to eight on 3-for-15 shooting.</p>
<p>“We need to be more consistent. We need to be better,&#8221; Bucks coach Mike Budenholzer said. “But I think there&#8217;s positives. We&#8217;ve played well for big stretches of games. We&#8217;ve just got to extend those.&#8221;</p>
<p>Milwaukee is 2-3 this season; the Bucks started 24-3 last season. Milwaukee missed 25 of its last 34 shots on Wednesday, and Miami — perhaps ironically, given how Tuesday went — outscored the Bucks 15-3 from beyond the arc in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>“Got to figure ourselves out as a team,&#8221; Antetokounmpo said. “We&#8217;re going to be consistent. &#8230; At the end of the day, we&#8217;re going to play our game, going to find open shots and hope they fall.&#8221;</p>
<p>Avery Bradley scored 16 and Kelly Olynyk had 15 for Miami.</p>
<p>Milwaukee’s lead was 72-58 early in the second half, 84-73 with 3:44 left in the third. It was all Miami from there, with the Heat — who were without Jimmy Butler for a second straight game because of a sprained right ankle — outscoring the Bucks 40-15 over the next 12 minutes</p>
<p>Herro beat the third-quarter buzzer with a 3-pointer to get Miami within three, Dragic opened the final quarter with another 3 to tie it and the Heat, who trailed by as many as 51 on Tuesday, took the lead for good on a 3 by Olynyk with 9:04 left.</p>
<p>“You want to constantly develop some grit and some toughness during the course of a long season,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “And our guys responded in an appropriate fashion.&#8221;</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Bucks: Brook Lopez, arguing that Adebayo flopped for a foul in the first half, theatrically fell to the court before Adebayo took the ensuing free throws. &#8230; Pat Connaughton scored 12 and Bobby Portis had 11 for Milwaukee.</p>
<p>Heat: Andre Iguodala got his first start as a member of the Heat, meaning for the 17th consecutive year — 2004 through 2020 — he has started at least one game. &#8230; The Heat gave up 21 points in the first 4:15 Tuesday on the way to a 144-97 loss; they set a tone by giving up four in the first 4:15 on Wednesday.</p>
<p>2020 RECORD</p>
<p>Milwaukee finished the calendar year 33-20 (28-15 regular season, 5-5 playoffs). Miami finished 2020 at 36-29 (22-22 regular season, 14-7 playoffs).</p>
<p>4 FOR 4</p>
<p>The Heat have used four starting lineups in their first four games, a franchise first. The only other teams to use four lineups in four games this season: Cleveland and Minnesota. The Bucks have had the same starters in all five games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Bucks: Host Chicago on Friday.</p>
<p>Heat: Visit Dallas on Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">817737</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bucks set NBA record for 3&#8217;s, roll past Heat 144-97</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/bucks-set-nba-record-for-3s-roll-past-heat-144-97/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 03:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=816675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — On Sunday, the Milwaukee Bucks endured their worst 3-point effort in just over a year. On Tuesday, they set the NBA record...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — On Sunday, the Milwaukee Bucks endured their worst 3-point effort in just over a year.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, they set the NBA record for 3&#8217;s in a game.</p>
<p>Go figure.</p>
<p>The Bucks made a record 29 3-pointers in their 144-97 romp past the reigning Eastern Conference champion Miami Heat on Tuesday night. They shot 29 for 51 from deep, two nights after going 7 for 38 in a loss to New York.</p>
<p>“Some nights, the basketball gods are with you a little bit,” Bucks coach Mike Budenholzer said. “It&#8217;s probably one of those nights.”</p>
<p>Milwaukee used 13 players and 12 made at least one 3-pointer — the only exception being two-time reigning MVP Giannis Antetokounmpo. Khris Middleton had four 3&#8217;s and scored 25 points, Jrue Holiday made six 3&#8217;s in his 24-point night and Donte DiVincenzo was 5-for-6 from deep to finish with 17 points.</p>
<p>Antetokounmpo had only nine points. But his brother, Thanasis Antetokounmpo — who was 0 for 11 from 3-point range in his career entering the night — got into the act and made one from deep.</p>
<p>“I knew we were shooting well,” said Bucks center Brook Lopez, who made three 3&#8217;s. “I didn&#8217;t know we were anything close to that.”</p>
<p>The record-breaker was made by Sam Merrill, who got the 28th 3-pointer with 6:07 remaining, giving the Bucks a 131-86 lead.</p>
<p>The previous record for 3’s in a game was 27, set by the Houston Rockets against the Phoenix Suns on April 7, 2019. Milwaukee’s previous most was 22, against Sacramento on Nov. 4, 2018. The most previously allowed in a game by Miami was 24, on Feb. 5 against the Los Angeles Clippers.</p>
<p>Milwaukee was up 10-0 after 78 seconds, 21-3 after about four minutes, and the tone was set in the first meeting between the teams since last season&#8217;s playoffs, when the Heat eliminated the Bucks in five games.</p>
<p>“It looked like they have been thinking about this game for 80 days,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>Milwaukee led 46-26 after one quarter, 83-51 at the half.</p>
<p>Tyler Herro scored 23 points for the Heat. Miami’s Jimmy Butler missed the game with a sprained right ankle; it&#8217;s unknown if he&#8217;ll play Wednesday when the Heat and Bucks meet again.</p>
<p>“Tomorrow, we&#8217;re going to have to come out with a lot more energy or we&#8217;re going to get embarrassed again,” Herro said.</p>
<p>It was the biggest road win in Bucks history, topping the 39-point margin at New York on April 10, 1987. The 47-point margin matched the second-worst loss in Heat history; they lost 138-91 to Pat Riley and the Los Angeles Lakers in the eighth game of Miami’s first season.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Bucks: Milwaukee had 16 3’s by halftime, the most of any half in team history. &#8230; The Bucks’ last three games have all been decided long before the final buzzer, with them beating Golden State by 39 on Christmas, then losing by 20 in New York on Sunday and leading by as many as 51 on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Heat: The worst Heat loss was 148-80 against Cleveland in 1991. &#8230; Tuesday&#8217;s 32-point halftime deficit was second worst in team history, topped by a 33-point hole on March 8, 1989 when Riley and the Lakers led 76-43 at the break. &#8230; Herro had 20 points by halftime, the first time he’s done that in his career.</p>
<p>WELCOME BACK</p>
<p>The Heat had about 100 fans at the game, all family and friends of players and employees. “I think it is a boost for the family, just to be able to have some normalcy and have a real opportunity to support their loved ones,” said Spoelstra, whose wife Nikki attended.</p>
<p>STREAK ENDS</p>
<p>Giannis Antetokounmpo’s streak of 108 consecutive regular-season games — and 132 overall — with at least 10 points ended. It was the first time since Feb. 13, 2017 that he played, scored less than 10 points and the Bucks won anyway.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The teams meet again Wednesday in Miami.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">816675</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spoelstra stays perfect on Christmas, Heat beat Pels 111-98</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/spoelstra-stays-perfect-on-christmas-heat-beat-pels-111-98/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 21:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=812075</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Erik Spoelstra remained perfect on Christmas, and a record-tying show from Duncan Robinson helped him stay that way. Robinson made seven 3-pointers...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Erik Spoelstra remained perfect on Christmas, and a record-tying show from Duncan Robinson helped him stay that way.</p>
<p>Robinson made seven 3-pointers — tying the Christmas single-game mark — and scored 23 points, helping the Heat beat the New Orleans Pelicans 111-98 to start the NBA’s holiday quintupleheader Friday.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s super special to play in Christmas,&#8221; Robinson said. “I certainly don&#8217;t take it for granted.&#8221;</p>
<p>Goran Dragic scored 18 points, Bam Adebayo had 17 and Avery Bradley finished with 12 for Miami, and Spoelstra improved his Christmas record as Heat coach to 8-0.</p>
<p>“I wasn&#8217;t even aware of that,&#8221; Spoelstra said. “Just shows you that we&#8217;ve had some really good teams here and teams that have had the opportunity to play on Christmas.&#8221;</p>
<p>Precious Achiuwa and Tyler Herro each scored 11 for Miami, which lost Jimmy Butler at halftime with right ankle stiffness.</p>
<p>Zion Williamson had 32 points and 14 rebounds in 38 minutes for New Orleans — the rebounds and minutes both being career highs. Brandon Ingram finished with 28 points.</p>
<p>But the Pelicans shot 40% to Miami’s 51%.</p>
<p>“We made some defensive mistakes that we shouldn&#8217;t have,&#8221; said Josh Hart, who scored 12 for New Orleans. “Lack of communication. We&#8217;ve got to communicate better on the defensive end.&#8221;</p>
<p>Robinson’s seven 3s tied the Christmas mark Ingram set last year.</p>
<p>“The guy is a great, great shooter. He&#8217;s going to have nights like that,&#8221; Pelicans coach Stan Van Gundy said. “But at least three of them were ones where we could have done a better job.&#8221;</p>
<p>JJ Redick’s 3-pointer with 7:43 left cut Miami’s lead to 91-85 and came during a stretch when the Heat went five minutes without a field goal. But the Pelicans got no closer.</p>
<p>The Heat restored order by scoring 11 of the game’s next 13 points, and when Achiuwa — the rookie who had strong defensive minutes — forced Williamson into a turnover with 3:55 left, the entire Miami bench rose in celebration.</p>
<p>“We knew they would make a run, but we stayed composed,&#8221; Dragic said.</p>
<p>New Orleans led 17-9 midway through the opening quarter — and got outscored 52-21 by Miami over the next 13½ minutes, with the Heat hitting nine of their 13 first-half 3s in that span on the way to a 23-point lead.</p>
<p>The Pelicans chipped away, getting within 66-53 at the half and 88-79 after three. But New Orleans shot only 30% in the final quarter and Ingram went scoreless in those 12 minutes after playing the entire third period.</p>
<p>Van Gundy lamented playing Ingram so much in the third.</p>
<p>“Probably not optimal play-calling on my part, either,&#8221; Van Gundy said.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Pelicans: Williamson&#8217;s previous career high was 34 minutes. &#8230; Redick fouled out for the second time in 898 career regular-season games, and missed six of his seven shots. &#8230; The Pelicans are now 1-3 on Christmas.</p>
<p>Heat: Andre Iguodala started the second half for Butler. &#8230; Miami improved to 11-2 on Christmas. It hadn’t played on the holiday since beating New Orleans in 2015, and hasn’t lost on Dec. 25 since 2007.</p>
<p>SEASON’S GREETINGS</p>
<p>Heat forward Moe Harkless this week helped pay rent for about 50 New York families in dire economic circumstances this holiday season, plus covered lost wages and other essential expenses. “Means the world to me,” Harkless said.</p>
<p>COMING HOME</p>
<p>Veteran ref John Goble was crew chief and got to be home for Christmas; he’s a Miami native. Marc Davis (lives in Chicago, crew chief Friday in Milwaukee) and John Goble (lives in Connecticut, crew chief Friday in Boston) also got to work near home for Christmas.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Pelicans: Host San Antonio on Sunday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host Milwaukee on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">812075</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Artist paints mural in Wynwood with Miami Heat players wearing masks to encourage others to do same</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/artist-paints-mural-in-wynwood-with-miami-heat-players-wearing-masks-to-encourage-others-to-do-same/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 18:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=810877</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A 60-foot mural featuring the Miami Heat and frontline fighters has been revealed in Wynwood. The mural honors healthcare workers and showcases Heat players in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A 60-foot mural featuring the Miami Heat and frontline fighters has been revealed in Wynwood.</p>
<p>The mural honors healthcare workers and showcases Heat players in an effort to remind everyone to wear a mask.</p>
<p>It can be found on the corner of Northwest 36th Street and Fifth Avenue.</p>
<p>The artist behind the mural, Kyle Holbrook, said he will be celebrating Christmas virtually this year to be safe.</p>
<p>&#8220;The whole point of it is to remind Miamians and visitors &#8212; because everybody&#8217;s coming down here to Miami &#8212; to wear your masks, and let&#8217;s do it together in solidarity against COVID-19,&#8221; said Holbrook.</p>
<p>The mural also serves as a celebration to the Miami Heat for being 2020 Eastern Conference champions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">810877</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/mask-up-mural.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fd07c59f-e9e4-4585-9157-69d95d2fef0c/e3138812-b197-4e5a-848d-37aa9d55845c/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219844~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fd07c59f-e9e4-4585-9157-69d95d2fef0c/e3138812-b197-4e5a-848d-37aa9d55845c/main.mp4*~hmac=3d81d6d8a41eb7c35b8f30e43b2b96ab01fbaaae7a6e3f46b9fc136384b218bd' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/mask-up-mural.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/mask-up-mural.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mask up mural</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fournier has late surge, helps Magic beat Heat 113-107</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/fournier-has-late-surge-helps-magic-beat-heat-113-107/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 04:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=810266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — For a third time in the past four years, the Orlando Magic opened their season on their home court with a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — For a third time in the past four years, the Orlando Magic opened their season on their home court with a stirring victory beat the rival Miami Heat.</p>
<p>Clearly, though, it will take more than just a victory over the defending Eastern Conference champion Heat for the Magic to back up forward Aaron Gordon’s bold talk of the team being &#8220;overlooked.’’</p>
<p>Evan Fournier hit a go-ahead 3-pointer late in the fourth quarter, converted a three-point play off another driving layup in the final minute and scored 25 points in the Magic’s 113-107 victory over Miami on Wednesday.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a good win and you always want to win the first game, especially when it’s at home,’’ said Fournier, who scored nine points in the final period for Orlando. &#8220;It’s definitely rewarding to win against a team like Miami because it’s always tough to play against them.’’</p>
<p>The Sunshine State rivals opened the regular season against one another for the sixth time. Oddly, the two rivals have started their seasons in Orlando four times in the past five years. The Magic are 5-1 in their six openers against their rivals from South Florida.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo led Miami with 25 points and 11 rebounds, Goran Dragic added 20 points, and Jimmy Butler had 19 points and seven assists. The Heat turned the ball over 22 times, leading to 24 Magic points.</p>
<p>&#8220;One, empty possessions. Two, we didn’t get the necessary ball movement … and thirdly, (the Magic) are a good defensive team,’’ said Heat coach Erik Spoelstra’s, whose team was playing for the first time since losing to the Los Angeles Lakers in the NBA Finals in October.</p>
<p>Miami led 83-79 after three periods and it was up 93-91 with 4:29 to play following Adebayo&#8217;s dunk. However, Fournier soon after swung the momentum to the Magic’s side with his strong finish. Fournier, who is looking to bounce back this season after struggling in last season’s playoffs, made all three of his shots in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Gordon had 20 points and seven rebounds, Terrence Ross chipped in 19 and Nikola Vucevic added 15 points and 11 rebounds. Point guard Markelle Fultz added 15 points and made two clutch free throws with 1:11 to play.</p>
<p>Gordon is confident that the Magic can open some eyes with their play this season.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don’t think, outside of Orlando, people have a lot of belief in us,’’ said the forward, who made 8 of 11 shots. &#8220;I don’t think they think that we’re going to become potential contenders or even have a playoff slot and I don’t think that’s true. I feel like we’re really ready to make that next leap.’’</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Dragic, who played well despite struggling with a foot injury much of training camp, was upset with his team’s hustle. &#8220;We talked and thought we did not play hard enough,’’ Dragic said. &#8220;This is what we need to correct.’’</p>
<p>Magic: The Magic held a moment of silence prior to tipoff to honor franchise co-founder Jimmy Hewitt. He died last month at the age of 79. Hewitt, along with Pat Williams, helped bring the NBA in the 1989-90 season.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: Hosts New Orleans on Friday.</p>
<p>Magic: At Washington on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">810266</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat partners with Pepsi, others to provide gifts and food to 12 M-DCPS families</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-partners-with-pepsi-others-to-provide-gifts-and-food-to-12-m-dcps-families/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 18:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=809640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8216;Tis the season for giving and the Miami Heat, along with several other companies, are doing just that. On Wednesday, the Miami Heat, Pepsi, TD...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8216;Tis the season for giving and the Miami Heat, along with several other companies, are doing just that.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, the Miami Heat, Pepsi, TD Bank, FedEx and Comcast helped 12 Miami-Dade County Public Schools students and their families.</p>
<p>&#8220;You just trying to make a difference,&#8221; Miami Heat legend Glen Rice said. &#8220;That&#8217;s what it&#8217;s all about. You get an opportunity, and you see someone express their joy of meeting you. They don&#8217;t understand that we get the same joy when we get an opportunity to meet them. For me, it&#8217;s a blessing.&#8221;</p>
<p>They participated in a drive-thru distribution outside of the AmericanAirlines Arena where the families will receive several gifts and food items just in time for Christmas.</p>
<p>Gifts include a holiday gift bag from FedEx, an eight-month internet service subscription and a Chromebook laptop from Comcast, JBL headphones, toys and even Miami Heat gear and basketballs.</p>
<p>A total of 500 additional students will also receive eight months of internet access.</p>
<p>Miami-Dade County Public Schools Superintendent Alberto Carvalho was eager to hand out gifts to students.</p>
<p>&#8220;When you provide a family, not just a child, but the entire family, connectivity for eight months, that&#8217;s powerful,&#8221; Carvalho said.</p>
<p>Miami-Dade County Mayor Daniella Levine Cava also took part in the distribution.</p>
<p>&#8220;I tell you it is just joyful to be here helping these young people who are really working hard,&#8221; Levine Cava said. &#8220;They&#8217;re all in a mentoring program. They&#8217;re doing well in school. They&#8217;ve got a scholarship coming their way, so it&#8217;s not just about the holidays for them. It&#8217;s about a brighter future.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami Heat mascot Burnie was also in attendance at the drive-thru distribution.</p>
<p>The Miami Heat will be playing against the Orlando Magic at 7 p.m.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">809640</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/burnie.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/350c9f67-b1b4-4d37-8dac-c7445ccab212/4e1d7dd9-1912-4ae8-af3b-0ca115ce7555/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219933~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/350c9f67-b1b4-4d37-8dac-c7445ccab212/4e1d7dd9-1912-4ae8-af3b-0ca115ce7555/main.mp4*~hmac=10be70909084842c1324e907eef16cf377fc6a6794f52b5cd5aeeb53ea4957af' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/burnie.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/burnie.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">burnie</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat teams up with Feeding South Florida to host food distribution in West Miami-Dade</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-teams-up-with-feeding-south-florida-to-host-food-distribution-in-west-miami-dade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 18:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=802683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Heat partnered with Feeding South Florida to host a drive-thru food distribution in West Miami-Dade. The event was held at the Tamiami Fairgrounds,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Heat partnered with Feeding South Florida to host a drive-thru food distribution in West Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>The event was held at the Tamiami Fairgrounds, located at 11201 SW 24th St., on Friday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re giving away fresh vegetables, protein, dairy&#8211; hopefully, things that families can use to make a great holiday meal over the weekend,&#8221; said Feeding South Florida Executive President Sari Vatsae. &#8220;It&#8217;ll serve about four people per household.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Miami Heat and the Micky and Madeleine Arison Family Foundation recently made a donation of $800,000 to Feeding South Florida, bringing their total donation in response to the pandemic to $1 million.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">802683</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/miami-heat-food-drive.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d3b11462-0672-4359-881d-dbdfd5356040/4ce71271-8911-47db-b5b6-e61eeb1ea008/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219842~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d3b11462-0672-4359-881d-dbdfd5356040/4ce71271-8911-47db-b5b6-e61eeb1ea008/main.mp4*~hmac=7d8173345cb7dccadd3a8bc36ef8430c968c30b395b751ad0f5bf1de71c2d0e3' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/miami-heat-food-drive.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/miami-heat-food-drive.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami heat food drive</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat to begin season without fans in attendance</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-to-begin-season-without-fans-in-attendance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 22:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=796706</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Heat will begin the 2020-2021 NBA season without fans in attendance. The team announced Thursday there will be no fans for their one...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Heat will begin the 2020-2021 NBA season without fans in attendance.</p>
<p>The team announced Thursday there will be no fans for their one home preseason game on Monday against the New Orleans Pelicans and for their season opener on Christmas Day.</p>
<p>In addition to the protocols put in place by the NBA, the Heat are exploring other safety options once it&#8217;s determined fans are allowed into the AmericanAirlines Arena.</p>
<p>Under the tentative plan, fans would be would screened by COVID-19 detection dogs before they enter the arena.</p>
<p>The Heat said the canine use is pain-free, fast, accurate and non-invasive.</p>
<p>A canine&#8217;s sense of smell is 1,000 to 100 million times more sensitive than that of a human&#8217;s.</p>
<p>The team notes that COVID-19 detection dogs are being used at Helsinki Airport in Finland, and the early results are promising.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">796706</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/121120-aa-arena.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/121120-aa-arena.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/121120-aa-arena.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">121120 aa arena</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat, Marlins, Dolphins collaborate for Thanksgiving food drive</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-marlins-dolphins-collaborate-for-thanksgiving-food-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 01:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=784286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Three South Florida sports teams came together to feed a need in the community by organizing their respective Thanksgiving food drives. The pandemic couldn&#8217;t slow...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three South Florida sports teams came together to feed a need in the community by organizing their respective Thanksgiving food drives.</p>
<p>The pandemic couldn&#8217;t slow down South Florida&#8217;s top three sports teams from doing their part to help the community, as the Miami Dolphins made sure to score touchdowns with families in Miami Gardens by providing 850 boxed meals filled with delicious sides and a nice turkey.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s an opportunity for you to really sit down with your family and to give thanks and to be happy and to just relax for a moment,&#8221; Dolphins Senior Director of Community Affairs Leslie Nixon said. &#8220;Having the burden of trying to figure out where your next meal is gonna come from, how you&#8217;re gonna pay the bills is really tough. Again, if we can take that burden off a family member&#8217;s plate and just allow them to enjoy each other&#8217;s company, that&#8217;s really what Thanksgiving means.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Miami Marlins joined forces with Feeding South Florida to dish out 1,000 Thanksgiving dinners. Sponsored by Tito&#8217;s Handmade Vodka, the Marlins&#8217; 12th Annual Home Plate Meals Thanksgiving distribution is something Derek Jeter and the team feels is a big hit for the community during the holidays.</p>
<p>&#8220;This has always been one of our favorite times of the year to give back, and considering everything that&#8217;s gone on this year, it&#8217;s a little extra meaningful,&#8221; Jeter said. &#8220;We said early on right when we took over this organization that we wanted to be this community&#8217;s team, and part of that is being here to support the community.&#8221;</p>
<p>For two decades, Miami Heat Hall of Famer Alonzo Mourning provided hundreds of hearty meals with all the trimmings where no virus was going to stop the tradition for the Awesome 33 Thanksgiving Giveaway.</p>
<p>&#8220;Being able to provide that during a very, very difficult time, during a very devastating pandemic, to be able to provide the relief and support to all the 300 families is truly a blessing,&#8221; said Mourning.</p>
<p>The Dolphins said they&#8217;ll give out almost 22,000 meals by Thanksgiving Day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">784286</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/97c3685c-6e8f-462d-97e8-7968a5c2e76e/da314c77-7945-46f8-a02c-8687589d8cc9/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217602~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/97c3685c-6e8f-462d-97e8-7968a5c2e76e/da314c77-7945-46f8-a02c-8687589d8cc9/main.mp4*~hmac=12d74011688a465fbc67e0bc148e6a43ff382a7c1a338982a6382ad29b7daad6' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">112320 Marlins_Thanksgiving food drive</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat take Precious Achiuwa with No. 20 pick in NBA draft</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-take-precious-achiuwa-with-no-20-pick-in-nba-draft/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 04:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=782005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Precious Achiuwa was the best player in the American Athletic Conference in his lone collegiate season. The Miami Heat hope that success...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Precious Achiuwa was the best player in the American Athletic Conference in his lone collegiate season. The Miami Heat hope that success can now translate to the NBA.</p>
<p>The 6-foot-9 Achiuwa was taken by the Heat with the No. 20 pick in Wednesday’s NBA draft, giving the reigning Eastern Conference champions more frontcourt depth and athleticism. Achiuwa averaged 15.8 points and 10.8 rebounds for Memphis last season, shooting 49% from the field and posted 18 double-doubles in 31 games.</p>
<p>“My hope was to end up in a great organization,&#8221; Achiuwa said. “And thank God, my prayers got answered. I&#8217;m part of a great organization.&#8221;</p>
<p>Achiuwa flourished as the year went on, taking over as Memphis&#8217; best player once James Wiseman left college after just three games. Wiseman was the No. 2 pick in Wednesday&#8217;s draft, going to Golden State.</p>
<p>Achiuwa&#8217;s first love as a kid growing up in Nigeria was soccer, which will make him a perfect fit in the Heat locker room: Jimmy Butler is a huge soccer fan, as is free agent guard Goran Dragic — who wants to be back with the Heat next season.</p>
<p>Miami is coming off a season where it went to the NBA Finals as the No. 5 seed in the East, finding a way in the restart bubble at Walt Disney World to get past three higher-seeded teams — sweeping Indiana in the first round, then needing five games to beat a Milwaukee team that finished with the league’s best regular-season record, then went six games to top Boston in the conference finals.</p>
<p>The Heat lost the NBA Finals to the Los Angeles Lakers in six games, and there are signs that they may largely run it back this season with a similar roster. Duncan Robinson and then-rookie Tyler Herro emerged as major threats last season, Butler flourished in his first Heat season and Bam Adebayo became an All-Star for the first time.</p>
<p>“I think I can add a lot to the table, add a lot of aggression and be that support for Bam inside,” Achiuwa said.</p>
<p>The Heat were not scheduled to have a second-round pick.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">782005</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Udonis Haslem returning to Heat for 18th season</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/udonis-haslem-returning-to-heat-for-18th-season/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 17:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=778505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Udonis Haslem announced Friday that he’s returning for an 18th season with the Miami Heat, and left the door open for extending...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Udonis Haslem announced Friday that he’s returning for an 18th season with the Miami Heat, and left the door open for extending his career after that.</p>
<p>Only five NBA players have spent a career of that length with one franchise. Dirk Nowitzki spent 21 years with Dallas, Kobe Bryant 20 years with the Los Angeles Lakers, Tim Duncan spent 19 with San Antonio, John Stockton spent 19 with Utah and Reggie Miller spent 18 with Indiana.</p>
<p>Haslem doesn’t play regularly and hasn’t for years: He got into just four games last season and has scored 76 points in the last four seasons combined. His impact on the team comes from what he says and does in the locker room, and that’s why Heat coach Erik Spoelstra lobbied for Haslem to come back.</p>
<p>“He’s just an incredible rock of stability and leadership and mentorship,” Spoelstra said during the NBA Finals last month. “That’s at all levels. It’s not just to our young players. It’s to our veteran players. And he provides just great guidance and mentorship to this head coach as well. I love him.”</p>
<p>So will this be the end?</p>
<p>“Spo told me don&#8217;t answer that question,&#8221; Haslem said at his announcement, held inside one of the Subway restaurants he owns in South Florida. “Spo said we&#8217;ll continue to talk about it.&#8221;</p>
<p>By NBA rule, the Heat cannot negotiate with Haslem until Nov. 20 and the earliest he can sign his new contract — his ninth with the Heat — is Nov. 22. It’ll be a one-year deal worth $2,564,753.</p>
<p>Haslem’s next appearance for the Heat will make him the oldest player in franchise history. His final appearance this past season was Aug. 14, at 40 years and 66 days old. That’s three days younger than Juwan Howard was when he played his final Heat game on April 17, 2013.</p>
<p>Haslem was one of three 40-somethings to play in the NBA last season: Vince Carter was 43 when he retired after the season and Jamal Crawford, 40, appeared in one game with the Brooklyn Nets during the NBA restart at Walt Disney World.</p>
<p>Crawford is about 2 1/2 months older than Haslem and is unsigned for next season.</p>
<p>Haslem is Miami’s all-time leading rebounder, ranks second behind only Dwyane Wade in games and minutes played, and is No. 7 on the Heat career scoring list.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">778505</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Udonis-Haslem.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8d2e5f8a-70f8-4144-a4d9-fb17fc2da45c/d5e353c9-9e45-4aef-8f23-5b93f26ef3e4/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219867~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8d2e5f8a-70f8-4144-a4d9-fb17fc2da45c/d5e353c9-9e45-4aef-8f23-5b93f26ef3e4/main.mp4*~hmac=04b79c538b131f24dff0299a8eba38ab38fa0c1cc36cbc61ee67fac8f769a4ce' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Udonis-Haslem.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Udonis-Haslem.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Udonis Haslem</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat legends surprise Miami Gardens veteran with $3,000 check, new team gear</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-legends-surprise-miami-gardens-veteran-with-3000-check-new-team-gear/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 22:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=777419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Members of the Miami Heat spent Veterans Day giving thanks to heroes in their community. Heat legends Shane Battier, Glen Rice and Alonzo Mourning, along...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Members of the Miami Heat spent Veterans Day giving thanks to heroes in their community.</p>
<p>Heat legends Shane Battier, Glen Rice and Alonzo Mourning, along with Burnie, the team&#8217;s mascot, were in Miami Gardens Wednesday to surprise veteran Tommy Collins.</p>
<p>The organization gifted Collins some new Heat gear, new home fixtures and a $3,000 check.</p>
<p>It was one of several stops the organization made throughout the day to commemorate those who put their lives on the line for their country.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">777419</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111120-Miami-Heat_Veterans-Day-surprise.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f8cac242-313d-4492-8b85-6b264ead18a0/c22af750-4680-48c1-a163-a96513afff41/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219828~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f8cac242-313d-4492-8b85-6b264ead18a0/c22af750-4680-48c1-a163-a96513afff41/main.mp4*~hmac=604da6335e3a91c2c5e46beb8111dbaf7f69ecb915e8b999eb256ac78504b8f4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111120-Miami-Heat_Veterans-Day-surprise.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111120-Miami-Heat_Veterans-Day-surprise.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">111120 Miami Heat_Veterans Day surprise</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat&#8217;s Meyers Leonard takes his family cross-country with help from Coors Light</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heats-meyers-leonard-takes-his-family-cross-country-with-help-from-coors-light/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 20:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=776027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After Miami Heat&#8217;s Meyers Leonard became an internet sensation for how he likes to drink his Coors Light beers, the company reached out to him...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After Miami Heat&#8217;s Meyers Leonard became an internet sensation for how he likes to drink his Coors Light beers, the company reached out to him with a once-in-a-lifetime offer.</p>
<p>Heat fans have seen the fire and passion Leonard has for the game, but what they may not have seen is how he can also enjoy a long bus ride and just chill.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve always wanted to do a cross-country trip,&#8221; he said. &#8220;I&#8217;ve tried talking my wife into it, wasn&#8217;t always the easiest thing to do, but this just made sense.&#8221;</p>
<p>Leonard, his wife Elle and dog Coco left Miami on the Coors Lite Chillstream bus back on Oct. 29.</p>
<p>The bus included a driver and their trip covered over 3,300 miles as they stopped in cities where family members lived.</p>
<p>The trip ended 10 days later in Los Angeles.</p>
<p>On one of those days, a strange thing happened when the bus broke down.</p>
<p>&#8220;I did a workout in the middle of Nebraska in a truck stop parking lot like a complete psychopath would with combat boots and no shirt on,&#8221; said Leonard.</p>
<p>He caught the attention of Coors Light back when he was in the NBA bubble posting videos of himself shotgunning his favorite beers.</p>
<p>Leonard also received a lot of attention for standing, not kneeling, during the National Anthem before the games.</p>
<p>He cited his respect for the military for the reason as to why he stood.</p>
<p>His brother Bailey served in Afghanistan with the Marines.</p>
<p>During his cross-country road trip, he met people who acknowledged what he had done.</p>
<p>&#8220;A lot of people would get like almost emotional and shake my hand and say, &#8216;Thank you so much for what you did. I was in the military.&#8217; That meant something to my family and I,&#8221; Leonard said.</p>
<p>Leonard, who stands 7 feet, 1 inch tall, is an impending free agent but also hasn&#8217;t ruled out a return to Miami.</p>
<p>&#8220;I know that I can help a team win. I&#8217;ve shown that,&#8221; he said. &#8220;I&#8217;m interested in winning. I&#8217;m interested in having a role. I&#8217;m interested in being a leader in a locker room, you know, all those sorts of things &#8212; and I loved Miami, by the way, so we&#8217;ll see what happens. I think that there&#8217;s some mutual interest there. The NBA&#8217;s a business, and we&#8217;ll just have to see.&#8221;</p>
<p>For the time being, Leonard will stay and train in LA.</p>
<p>He and his wife Elle are also keeping busy marketing their protein bar Level that has been successful on their website.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">776027</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/meyer-leonard-e1604951777680.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/60a3b9e6-fc8f-4cbb-87f4-ad2041ad0b6c/9ab3da4c-d804-48f9-b7a4-d02f8e8a812f/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219956~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/60a3b9e6-fc8f-4cbb-87f4-ad2041ad0b6c/9ab3da4c-d804-48f9-b7a4-d02f8e8a812f/main.mp4*~hmac=4a8511965b0bd4518086bcce387ae84fd1f4d030ca96050a7a3b280bb8e0d999' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/meyer-leonard-e1604951777680.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/meyer-leonard-e1604951777680.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">meyer leonard</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bubble Kings: Lakers run past Heat for 17th NBA championship</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/bubble-kings-lakers-run-past-heat-for-17th-nba-championship/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 02:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=758828</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LAKE BUENA VISTA, Fla. (AP) — The ultimate anguish. The ultimate joy. This season, for LeBron James and the Los Angeles Lakers, had it all....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LAKE BUENA VISTA, Fla. (AP) — The ultimate anguish. The ultimate joy.</p>
<p>This season, for LeBron James and the Los Angeles Lakers, had it all. And it ended in the only fashion that they deemed would be acceptable, with them back atop the basketball world.</p>
<p>For the first time since Kobe Bryant&#8217;s fifth and final title a decade ago, the Lakers are NBA champions. James had 28 points, 14 rebounds and 10 assists, and the Lakers beat the Miami Heat 106-93 on Sunday night to win the NBA Finals in six games.</p>
<p>“Our organization wants their respect. Laker Nation wants their respect,&#8221; James said. “And I want my damn respect, too.&#8221;</p>
<p>Anthony Davis had 19 points and 15 rebounds for the Lakers, who dealt with the enormous anguish that followed the death of the iconic Bryant in January and all the challenges that came with leaving home for three months to play at Walt Disney World in a bubble designed to keep inhabitants safe from the coronavirus.</p>
<p>It would be, James predicted, the toughest title to ever win.</p>
<p>“We have a Ph.D in adversity, I&#8217;ll tell you that much,&#8221; Lakers coach Frank Vogel said. “We&#8217;ve been through a lot.&#8221;</p>
<p>They made the clincher look easy. James won his fourth title, doing it with a third different franchise — and against the Heat franchise that showed him to to become a champion.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo had 25 points and 10 rebounds for Miami, which got 12 points from Jimmy Butler — the player who, in his first Heat season, got the team back to title contention. Rajon Rondo scored 19 points for the Lakers, who put together the elite talents of James and Davis with this moment in mind.</p>
<p>And Davis, as white and gold confetti coated the floor around him, spent his first moments as an NBA champion thinking of Bryant.</p>
<p>“All we wanted to do was do it for him,&#8221; Davis said. “And we didn&#8217;t let him down. &#8230; I know he&#8217;s looking down on us, proud of us.&#8221;</p>
<p>With that, the league’s bubble chapter, put together after a 4 1/2-month suspension of play that started March 11 because of the coronavirus pandemic and came with a promise that it would raise awareness to the problems of racial injustice and police brutality, is over. So, too, is a season that saw the league and China get into political sparring, the death on Jan. 1 of commissioner emeritus David Stern — the man who did so much to make the league what it is — and then the shock on Jan. 26 that came with the news that Bryant, his daughter Gianna and seven other died in a helicopter crash.</p>
<p>The Lakers said they were playing the rest of the season in his memory.</p>
<p>They delivered what Bryant did five times for L.A. — a ring, and the clincher was emphatic.</p>
<p>“You have written your own inspiring chapter in the great Laker history,&#8221; Lakers owner Jeanie Buss said. “And to Laker Nation, we have been through a heartbreaking tragedy with the loss of our beloved Kobe Bryant. Let this trophy serve as a reminder of when we come together, believe in each other, incredible things can happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>Game 6 was over by halftime, the Lakers taking a 64-36 lead into the break. The Heat never led and couldn’t shoot from anywhere: 35% from 2-point range in the half, 33% from 3-point range and even an uncharacteristic 42% from the line, not like any of it really mattered. The Lakers were getting everything they wanted and then some, outscoring Miami 36-16 in the second quarter and doing all that with James making just one shot in the period.</p>
<p>Rondo, now a two-time champion and the first to win NBA rings as a player in the cities of Boston and Los Angeles — the franchises now tied with 17 titles apiece — was 6 for 6 in the half, the first time he’d done that since November 2007. The Lakers’ lead was 46-32 with 5:00 left in the half, and they outscored Miami 18-4 from there until intermission.</p>
<p>Ball game. The 28-point halftime lead was the second-biggest in NBA Finals history, topped only by the Celtics leading the Lakers 79-49 on May 27, 1985.</p>
<p>“We didn&#8217;t get the final result that we wanted,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “But even what I mentioned to the guys, these are going to be lifetime memories that we have together. This locker room &#8230; we&#8217;re going to remember this year, this season, this experience and that locker room brotherhood for the rest of our lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>True to form, the Heat — a No. 5 seed in the Eastern Conference that finished with a losing record last season, a team that embraced the challenge of the bubble like none other — didn&#8217;t stop playing, not even when the deficit got to 36 in the third quarter.</p>
<p>“We’re trending in the right direction,&#8221; Butler said. “We’re going to learn from this. We’re going to get better. We’re going to come back.&#8221;</p>
<p>A 23-8 run by Miami got the Heat to 90-69 with 8:37 left. But the outcome was never in doubt, and before long confetti was blasted into the air as the Lakers&#8217; celebration formally and officially began.</p>
<p>“Laker Nation,&#8221; Vogel, now a first-time champion who saw his title hopes as Indiana&#8217;s coach thwarted three times by James and the Heat, bellowed during the trophy ceremony. “We did it.&#8221;</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Lakers: Davis did not wear the gold-painted sneakers that he had for Game 5; instead, he went with red-and-black ones Sunday. &#8230; Among the ring-winners: Dion Waiters, who began this season with the Heat; 19-year-old Talen Horton-Tucker (he turns 20 Nov. 25) and Kostas Antetokounmpo — the brother of two-time NBA MVP Giannis Antetokounmpo of the Milwaukee Bucks.</p>
<p>Heat: Goran Dragic (torn left plantar fascia) checked in late in the first quarter, his first appearance since Game 1 of the series. “I just wanted to be out there to help my team as much as possible. It is what it is. The Lakers were better,&#8221; an emotional Dragic said. &#8230; Jae Crowder had 12 points and Duncan Robinson had 10 for the Heat.</p>
<p>JOIN THE CLUB</p>
<p>John Salley and Robert Horry were, until Sunday, the only players to win championships with three different franchises. James (Miami, Cleveland) and Danny Green (San Antonio, Toronto) added their names to that list with this title.</p>
<p>HEAT SEASON</p>
<p>Miami led the NBA with 94 games played this season — 30 more than Minnesota, which played the fewest in the NBA. The Heat finished with 1,247 3-pointers this season, including playoffs, 290 more than any other year in team history.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Nobody knows. The draft is set for Nov. 18, but the dates for the start of free agency, training camps and next season’s schedule could be weeks away from being finalized.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">758828</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/201011_Miami_Heat_remarkable_run.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/201011_Miami_Heat_remarkable_run.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/201011_Miami_Heat_remarkable_run.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201011_Miami_Heat_remarkable_run</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
