<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Coronavirus &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/tag/coronavirus/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 03:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Coronavirus &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Russian disinformation campaign working to undermine confidence in COVID-19 vaccines used in US</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/russian-disinformation-campaign-working-to-undermine-confidence-in-covid-19-vaccines-used-in-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 01:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878015</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Online platforms directed by Russian intelligence are spreading disinformation about two of the coronavirus vaccines being used in the US, a State Department spokesperson confirmed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Online platforms directed by Russian intelligence are spreading disinformation about two of the coronavirus vaccines being used in the US, a State Department spokesperson confirmed to CNN on Sunday.</p>
<p>The agency&#8217;s Global Engagement Center identified three Russian outlets &#8212; News Front, New Eastern Outlook and Oriental Review &#8212; that are spreading not only misinformation about the virus, but also regarding &#8220;international organizations, military conflicts, protests; and any divisive issue that they can exploit,&#8221; according to the spokesperson.</p>
<p>&#8220;These sites all vary in their reach, tone, and audience &#8212; but they all are spreading Russian propaganda and disinformation. The State Department&#8217;s finding of a link between these sites and Russian Intelligence is a result of a joint interagency conclusion,&#8221; the spokesperson said.</p>
<p>The GEC leads efforts &#8220;to recognize, understand, expose, and counter foreign state and non-state propaganda and disinformation efforts aimed at undermining or influencing the policies, security, or stability of the United States, its allies, and partner nations,&#8221; according to its website.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/russian-disinformation-campaign-aims-to-undermine-confidence-in-pfizer-other-covid-19-vaccines-u-s-officials-say-11615129200" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Wall Street Journal </a>first reported on the disinformation.</p>
<p>The campaign comes as the US and other countries race to vaccinate people using three vaccines developed in record time by the drug makers Pfizer/BioNTech, Moderna and Johnson &amp; Johnson. US officials have been working to increase confidence in the drugs in recent months as studies showed a concerning level of vaccine hesitancy among some people, though that has decreased as the rollout has progressed.</p>
<p>A spokesman for the Kremlin denied to the Journal that the country&#8217;s intelligence services were spearheading the disinformation campaign.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s nonsense. Russian special services have nothing to do with any criticism against vaccines,&#8221; the spokesman, Dmitry Peskov, told the newspaper.</p>
<p>The Journal reported that, &#8220;Russian state media and Russian government Twitter accounts have made overt efforts to raise concerns about the cost and safety of the Pfizer vaccine in what experts outside the US government say is an effort to promote the sale of Russia&#8217;s rival Sputnik V vaccine.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;The emphasis on denigrating Pfizer is likely due to its status as the first vaccine besides Sputnik V to see mass use, resulting in a greater potential threat to Sputnik&#8217;s market dominance,&#8221; a forthcoming report by the Alliance for Securing Democracy says, according to the Journal.</p>
<p>One outlet in the disinformation campaign, News Front, used international reports to play &#8220;up the risk that a person who receives the Pfizer or Moderna Inc. vaccines could contract Bell&#8217;s palsy, in which facial muscles are paralyzed,&#8221; according to the Journal, which noted that while a small number of side effects have been reported by vaccine recipients, the shots are overwhelmingly safe and effective.</p>
<p>Pamela Eisele, a spokeswoman for Pfizer, told the newspaper that so far, &#8220;millions of people have been vaccinated with our vaccine following the endorsement of regulators in multiple countries.&#8221;</p>
<p>A spokeswoman for Moderna didn&#8217;t immediately respond to the Journal&#8217;s request for comment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878015</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports nearly 4,100 cases of COVID-19 on Sunday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-nearly-4100-cases-of-covid-19-on-sunday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(WSVN) &#8211; There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,683 deaths. As of 4 p.m. Sunday,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(WSVN) &#8211; There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,683 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 4 p.m. Sunday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,944,995 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 4,098 from Saturday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 63 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 419,479 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County (5.33% positivity) and 199,643 total cases in Broward (6.99% positivity).</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 123,304, and 5,986 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,954 hospital admissions statewide. To date, 3,462,520 people in the state have been vaccinated.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877929</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vaccine site in Florida City overrun after false rumors said all could come</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/vaccine-site-in-florida-city-overrun-after-false-rumors-said-all-could-come/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FLORIDA CITY, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; A South Florida vaccination site had so few eligible takers Saturday that it started inoculating any adult who wanted a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FLORIDA CITY, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; A South Florida vaccination site had so few eligible takers Saturday that it started inoculating any adult who wanted a shot rather than let the vaccine on hand go to waste.</p>
<p>Word spread, and on Sunday, the Florida City site was overwhelmed, particularly after local state Sen. Annette Taddeo incorrectly tweeted that the federally run site would again take all comers. The Democrat, who was the party&#8217;s lieutenant governor candidate in 2014, later deleted that tweet and corrected herself.</p>
<p>Frustration and confusion set in among the hundreds of people who came to the site run by the Federal Emergency Management Agency.</p>
<p>Among those were Kathy Benezra.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m quite upset. They changed the rules in the morning,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Police had to calm the crowd when the site again enforced the state&#8217;s eligibility rules: 65 and older; frontline medical workers and police officers, teachers and firefighters over 50; and younger people with a physician&#8217;s note saying they would be endangered if they caught the virus.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article249760473.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the Miami Herald</a>, a Florida City police officer through a megaphone told 200 people waiting in line, “If you do not meet the criteria, you will not be vaccinated today.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;A lot of people went away once they heard the criteria, but [the line] was all the way around the block,&#8221; said Benezra.</p>
<p>Benezra said she got there at around 7 a.m. because she heard the site was giving vaccinations to anyone over the age of 18 who wanted one.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve been here, and now the rules have changed,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The confusion appeared to stem from what happened on Saturday.</p>
<p>Vaccines must be refrigerated at extremely cold temperatures and used that day once they are removed. Rather than letting doses go to waste, workers on Saturday reportedly began giving them out to any adult regardless of profession or medical history.</p>
<p>That is not unusual &#8211; many drugstores, for example, will inject anyone in the store at closing time if they have leftover vaccines that would spoil otherwise.</p>
<p>Word of what reportedly happened at the Florida City site quickly spread online, and people came from miles to the small town on the Florida peninsula&#8217;s southern tip to get their shots.</p>
<p>The FEMA-run site administers 500 doses per day.</p>
<p>Mike Jachles with the Florida Association of Public Information Officers issued a statement that reads in part, &#8220;The FEMA-supported sites are adhering to the governor&#8217;s most recent executive order.&#8221;</p>
<p>Many who met the eligibility requirements received their vaccine doses at the larger FEMA-run site at Miami-Dade College&#8217;s North Campus.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was very easy, and I&#8217;m very happy to live in this country,&#8221; said patient Magda Caceres..</p>
<p>&#8220;Super quick, super easy,&#8221; said patient Viviane Carneiro.</p>
<p>Schoolteachers and school employees of all ages are also eligible at FEMA-supported sites.</p>
<p>&#8220;Once the governor opened it up to teachers, I&#8217;m like, &#8216;I&#8217;m out here as soon as I can,'&#8221; said Angel Beswick.</p>
<p>For her, the MDC site was the happiest place on Earth.</p>
<p>&#8220;It feels like I&#8217;m at Disney World, honestly. I&#8217;m so excited,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>As the race to vaccinate continues, Miami-Dade County Mayor Daniella Levine Cava urged the governor to <a href="https://twitter.com/MayorDaniella/status/1368636288170139648?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expand eligibility requirements</a>.</p>
<p>Sunday night, state officials reported 3,878 vaccinations at the three FEMA-run sites in South Florida. Of these inoculations, 3,160 took place at the MDC North Campus site, 321 at the Florida City site and 397 at the site located in Sweetwater.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign, <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health’s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877886</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e6a6b095-305e-4268-b30e-f3dce3a92d40/31a5600a-64fd-42f4-8840-39600067b2d1/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219472~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e6a6b095-305e-4268-b30e-f3dce3a92d40/31a5600a-64fd-42f4-8840-39600067b2d1/main.mp4*~hmac=cc47177d472206de319fcbc2d73936f4d27701f0d4ff731e89a2c52f37b30133' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Workers worry about safety, stress as states ease mask rules</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/workers-worry-about-safety-stress-as-states-ease-mask-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 14:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSON, Mississippi (AP) — Leo Carney worries that bigger crowds and mask-less diners could endanger workers at the Biloxi, Mississippi, seafood restaurant where he manages...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSON, Mississippi (AP) — Leo Carney worries that bigger crowds and mask-less diners could endanger workers at the Biloxi, Mississippi, seafood restaurant where he manages the kitchen. Maribel Cornejo, who earns $9.85 an hour as a McDonald&#8217;s cook in Houston, can&#8217;t afford to get sick and frets co-workers will become more lax about wearing masks, even though the fast food company requires them.</p>
<p>As more jurisdictions join Texas, Mississippi and other states in <a href="https://apnews.com/article/texas-other-states-ease-covid-19-restrictions-af9fc214690270fe617864abc772ecce">lifting mask mandates</a> and easing restrictions on businesses, many essential workers — including bartenders, restaurant servers and retail workers — are relieved by changes that might help the economy but also concerned they could <a href="https://apnews.com/article/rochelle-walensky-coronavirus-pandemic-fe2e65c19506b99ebdb8f1e0badc846b">make them less safe</a> amid a pandemic that health experts warn is far from over.</p>
<p>Many business owners on the Mississippi Gulf Coast were glad Gov. Tate Reeves decided to eliminate mask requirements, limits on seating in restaurants and most other binding restrictions. “But the workers themselves&#8230; especially ones that have pre-existing conditions, they’re scared right now,” Carney said.</p>
<p>“This just puts us back in a situation where we’re on the frontlines, under the gun again,” said Carney, who sees Black Mississippians facing the greatest risks from the decision that took effect Wednesday. COVID-19 has disproportionately affected Black and Latino people in the United States, and many Gulf Coast restaurants have a significant number of Black employees.</p>
<p>Public health experts tracking the trajectory of more contagious virus variants have warned that lifting restrictions too soon could lead to another lethal wave of infections. Although vaccination drives are accelerating as drug manufacturers ramp up production, many essential workers are not yet eligible for COVID-19 vaccines in Mississippi and other states.</p>
<p>Alabama’s state health officer on Friday advised residents to keep following standard infection-prevention recommendations even though the governor is letting the state’s <a href="https://apnews.com/article/kay-ivey-extends-alabama-mask-order-coronavirus-bd11f67b77915a7cd9320b714f222869">mask mandate expire </a>next month.</p>
<p>“There is nothing magical about the date of April 9. We don’t want the public to think that’s the day we all stop taking precautions,” State Health Officer Scott Harris said.</p>
<p>The governors of Iowa, Montana, North Dakota also have ended mask requirements or plan to suspend them soon. The governor of South Carolina on Friday lifted an executive order requiring face coverings in government office buildings and restaurants, leaving it up to state administrators and restaurant operators to develop their own guidelines.</p>
<p>Governors in several other states, including Michigan and Louisiana, eased the operating limits for bars, restaurants and other businesses in recent days.</p>
<p>The National Retail Federation, the largest retail trade association in the U.S., issued a statement Wednesday encouraging shoppers to wear masks. Some retail chains, including Target and supermarket operator Albertson&#8217;s, plan to continue requiring them for both customers and workers in states that no longer make them mandatory.</p>
<p>Texas Retailers Association President and CEO George Kelemen said he thinks many members will continue to require workers — but not necessarily customers — to wear masks and other protective gear.</p>
<p>“Retailers know their customers best,” he said.</p>
<p>McDonald’s cook Cornejo, 43, said the end of Texas’ mask mandate next week alarms her because several of her co-workers already were lax about keeping their faces covered. She said co-workers she has asked to pull their masks back over their noses politely acquiesced, but not always for long.</p>
<p>“There are just different attitudes,” said Cornejo, whose 19-year-old son began working as a cashier at the same restaurant to help pay the family’s bills. “Some say it’s just too difficult to keep it on for eight hours, especially when it gets hot.”</p>
<p>The director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Dr. Rochelle Walensky, encouraged Americans to “do the right thing” by continuing to abide by recommendations for routine mask use and social distancing &#8211; even if their states lift restrictions.</p>
<p>Dr. William Schaffner, a professor of preventive medicine at Vanderbilt University in Tennessee, said individuals who wear masks still risk infection from unmasked shoppers and diners. He called Texas Gov. Greg Abbott’s decision to lift COVID-19 restrictions starting March 10 “entirely too soon and entirely too carefree.”</p>
<p>While deaths and new confirmed cases have plummeted from their January peaks nationwide, they’re still running at high levels, while outbreak indicators in some states have risen in recent weeks. In Mississippi, for example, the 7-day rolling average of the virus positivity rate rose from 11.47% on Feb. 19 to 12.14% on March 5, and the state&#8217;s 7-day rolling average of daily deaths increase during the same period from 15 per day to 20.71 per day.</p>
<p>Workers in cities that still have mask mandates or jobs at businesses that maintain their own virus-prevention rules anticipate defiance from customers emboldened by their governors’ actions and weary of taking precautions.</p>
<p>Molly Brooks, 25, a barista at a Farmers Branch, Texas, coffee shop, said she has regularly dealt with customers who walked out or bullied her and her colleagues when they were asked to wear a mask. Brooks worries how they&#8217;re going to enforce the rule, which the coffee shop plans to keep in place, now that Texas&#8217; governor lifted the statewide mask mandate.</p>
<p>“We are gearing up for the emotional toll that this is going to take,” said the 25-year-old barista, who started working for the coffee shop in November while looking for a job in education. “The people who don&#8217;t want to wear them are still going to fight&#8230;and now they are going to have even more ammunition.”</p>
<p>Square Books in Oxford, Mississippi, home of the University of Mississippi, will require masks and allow only eight customers at a time. Although General Manager Lyn Roberts believes the rules will make many customers feel safe, bookstore employee Paul Fyke said he observed a change in Oxford almost as soon as the Board of Aldermen chose to follow the governor&#8217;s lead and did away with the college town&#8217;s mask mandate.</p>
<p>“I mean, really, even on the drive home, you can kind of already see there were places where, for a lot of people, it was triumph,” he said on Thursday, the day after Oxford&#8217;s mask requirement ended. “They were happy to be removing them.”</p>
<p>Still, some workers are cautiously hopeful that fewer restrictions will bring more customers, tips and job security after a year short on all three.</p>
<p>In San Francisco, where the mayor last week announced the return of indoor dining and the reopening of movie theaters and gyms, Dino Keres had no qualms about serving drinks to customers bellying up to the bar inside Sam&#8217;s Grill.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s partly because he was about to get his second vaccine dose, but also because nobody on staff was infected when indoor dining was briefly permitted last fall. What’s more, masks are required unless people are eating, and indoor seating is limited to 25% of capacity.</p>
<p>“We have already went through this once, and now the timing feels about right to try it again,” Keres said Thursday.</p>
<p>Ro Hart, an assistant general manager and hostess at Tony’s Pizza Napoletana in San Francisco, said the return of indoor dining in the city provoked a mixture of joy and anxiety.</p>
<p>“We are happy to be bringing in more revenue, but we are little nervous, too, because we have to be more stringent about making sure everyone keeps their masks on when they’re not eating,” Hart said, adding that she would be far more worried if San Francisco didn&#8217;t require masks.</p>
<p>“We feel for our brothers and sisters at all those restaurants in Texas,” she said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877775</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200710_Disney_employees_face_masks</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Parade held in Palm Beach County for 7 vets unable to board Honor Flight due to pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/parade-held-in-palm-beach-county-for-7-vets-unable-to-board-honor-flight-due-to-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 04:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877646</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DELRAY BEACH, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A parade in Palm Beach County served as a special salute for seven veterans who were unable to go on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DELRAY BEACH, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A parade in Palm Beach County served as a special salute for seven veterans who were unable to go on an annual flight to the nation capital due to the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>Palm Beach County Sheriff&#8217;s deputies and fire rescue vehicles took part in a caravan that drove past the veterans&#8217; homes, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>Honor Flight South Florida aimed to ensure some of the nation&#8217;s oldest veterans had an unforgettable reminder of how grateful people are for their service.</p>
<p>The vets were supposed to be passengers on an Honor Flight to Washington, D.C. last year. They would have had the chance to visit memorials that were built in honor of them and their fallen comrades.</p>
<p>But their trip was postponed due to the pandemic.</p>
<p>U.S. Army Lt. Col. Bill Schwartz, a World War II vet, was the parade&#8217;s grand marshal.</p>
<p>&#8220;To see this kind of a welcome, I mean, it&#8217;s overbearing, and it&#8217;s wonderful,&#8221; he said, &#8220;It&#8217;s a little icing on the cake for those who served.&#8221;</p>
<p>Schwartz was part of the first wave on Normandy Beach and one of the few to survive that D-Day battle.</p>
<p>The caravan started in Delray Beach and stopped at the homes of the veterans in the Boca Raton area, where their families and neighbors gathered to join in the celebration.</p>
<p>Honor Flight South Florida plans on a few more honor parades to pay tribute to more veterans who had to have their Honor Flights postponed.</p>
<p>The organization plans to bring back Honor Flights later in 2021, with the first ones scheduled to go out in September.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877646</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1259a82-101d-4dc6-bcd5-6fe5102908c8/2d9593c7-10bc-4401-b14a-202d1a014c61/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217003~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1259a82-101d-4dc6-bcd5-6fe5102908c8/2d9593c7-10bc-4401-b14a-202d1a014c61/main.mp4*~hmac=544ea4a71c593e719fee112b93dd87ff01ad8c063876a8a707b7df50a32d704f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smooth vaccination process at MDC North site despite large turnout, rainy weather</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/smooth-vaccination-process-at-mdc-north-site-despite-large-turnout-rainy-weather/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[More than 3,000 people came to the federal COVID-19 vaccination site at Miami Dade College&#8217;s North Campus, but despite the large crowds, patients described a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than 3,000 people came to the federal COVID-19 vaccination site at Miami Dade College&#8217;s North Campus, but despite the large crowds, patients described a smooth relatively short process.</p>
<p>It was busy and bustling Saturday morning at the <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-opens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">massive FEMA-run site</a>, located in Northwest Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>Among those who lined up for their dose was 83-year-old Henry Sturrup.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m certainly glad I came here this morning,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It was the best thing that could have happened to me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Others said they waited hours just for a parking spot, but once they had one, the crew made the process of actually receiving a shot quick and easy.</p>
<p>&#8220;Great job, amazing people. They&#8217;re heroes; I love it,&#8221; said patient Roberto Carneiro.</p>
<p>Rainy weather rolled in Saturday afternoon, but it didn&#8217;t stop some from coming out.</p>
<p>&#8220;I am grateful for the opportunity to be protected,&#8221; said Mercedes Medina, a professor at Miami Dade College.</p>
<p>Medina said she is at a higher risk of getting seriously ill from COVID-19 because she has diabetes.​</p>
<p>She said she been teaching virtually, and after being fully vaccinated, she hopes to see her students in person soon.</p>
<p>&#8220;There&#8217;s something about that live engagement that I miss,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I love the remote teaching that gives flexibility, but it shouldn&#8217;t be in place of live teaching.&#8221;</p>
<p>At one point, the downpour caused a pause in operations at the site, but crews were able to reopen once the rain abated.</p>
<p>With the rain likely playing a part, some patients said their wait was much shorter than those who showed up earlier.</p>
<p>Medina said she waited in the car line for just 10 minutes, and the vaccination process took about 30.</p>
<p>&#8220;They were very organized,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The FEMA-run site is open seven days a week from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m.</p>
<p>All Florida residents 65 and older can get a vaccine, as well as police officers and firefighters 50 and older.</p>
<p>Anyone over the age of 18 who is a teacher, school employee or has underlying health conditions is also allowed to receive the vaccine.</p>
<p>Patients who have one those of medical conditions need to bring a doctor&#8217;s note or <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this form</a> signed by a doctor.</p>
<p>When adding the totals from sites in Sweetwater and Florida City to those at the MDC location, state officials said, 4,093 people were vaccinated on Saturday. Of these inoculations, 3,093 took place at the MDC site, 2,344 with the Pfizer vaccine and 749 with the single-shot Johnson&amp; Johnson vaccine.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign, <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health’s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877491</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b39b3bf8-a6ff-44a9-b31e-7d51b5aaf4b0/a2dd09ec-1524-4684-adf3-b2ecfef91ec6/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217390~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b39b3bf8-a6ff-44a9-b31e-7d51b5aaf4b0/a2dd09ec-1524-4684-adf3-b2ecfef91ec6/main.mp4*~hmac=1efae1ee946514ab7951ece3a9518bc695080efb7e9ca37bd43d6468ec45d8e7' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 4,600 cases of COVID-19 on Saturday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/fdoh-reports-over-4600-cases-of-covid-19-on-saturday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,620 deaths. As of 2:30 p.m. Saturday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,620 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2:30 p.m. Saturday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,940,897 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 4,684 from Friday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 98 deaths.</p>
<div id="see-through" class="seethrough-in-article-ad" data-google-query-id="CLrpt42znO8CFRgXAQodDBMDGQ">
<div id="google_ads_iframe_/1055211/wsvn/see-through_0__container__"></div>
</div>
<p>There are now 418,411 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 198,995 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 123,033, and 5,975 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,863 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877369</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus_generic_</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden, Dems prevail as Senate OKs $1.9T virus relief bill</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/biden-dems-prevail-as-senate-oks-1-9t-virus-relief-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — An exhausted Senate narrowly approved a $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill Saturday as President Joe Biden and his Democratic allies notched a victory they...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — An exhausted Senate narrowly approved a $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill Saturday as President Joe Biden and his Democratic allies notched a victory they called crucial for hoisting the country out of the pandemic and economic doldrums.</p>
<p>After laboring all night on a mountain of amendments — nearly all from Republicans and rejected — bleary-eyed senators approved the sprawling package on a 50-49 party-line vote. That sets up final congressional approval by the House next week so lawmakers can whisk it to Biden for his signature.</p>
<p>The huge measure — its cost is nearly one-tenth the size of the entire U.S. economy — is Biden’s biggest early priority. It stands as his formula for addressing the deadly virus and a limping economy, twin crises that have afflicted the country for a year.</p>
<p>“This nation has suffered too much for much too long,” Biden told reporters at the White House after the vote. “And everything in this package is designed to relieve the suffering and to meet the most urgent needs of the nation, and put us in a better position to prevail.”</p>
<p>Saturday&#8217;s vote was also a crucial political moment for Biden and Democrats, who need nothing short of party unanimity in a 50-50 Senate they run with Vice President Kamala Harris&#8217; tiebreaking vote. They hold a slim 10-vote House edge.</p>
<p>Not one Republican backed the bill in the Senate or when it initially passed the House, underscoring the barbed partisan environment that&#8217;s characterized the early days of Biden&#8217;s presidency.</p>
<p>A small but pivotal band of moderate Democrats leveraged changes in the legislation that incensed progressives, hardly helping Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., guide the measure through the House. But rejection of their first, signature bill was not an option for Democrats, who face two years of running Congress with virtually no room for error.</p>
<p>In a significant sign, the chair of the Congressional Progressive Caucus, representing around 100 House liberals, called the Senate&#8217;s weakening of some provisions “bad policy and bad politics” but “relatively minor concessions.” Rep. Pramila Jayapal, D-Wash., said the bill retained its “core bold, progressive elements.”</p>
<p>“They feel like we do, we have to get this done,” Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y., said of the House. He added, “It&#8217;s not going to be everything everyone wants. No bill is.”</p>
<p>In a written statement, Pelosi invited Republicans &#8220;to join us in recognition of the devastating reality of this vicious virus and economic crisis and of the need for decisive action.”</p>
<p>The bill provides direct payments of up to $1,400 for most Americans and extended emergency unemployment benefits. There are vast piles of spending for COVID-19 vaccines and testing, states and cities, schools and ailing industries, along with tax breaks to help lower-earning people, families with children and consumers buying health insurance.</p>
<p>Republicans call the measure a wasteful spending spree for Democrats’ liberal allies that ignores recent indications that the pandemic and economy was turning the corner.</p>
<p>“The Senate has never spent $2 trillion in a more haphazard way,&#8221; said Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky. He said Democrats&#8217; “top priority wasn&#8217;t pandemic relief. It was their Washington wish list.”</p>
<p>The Senate commenced a dreaded “vote-a-rama” — a continuous series of votes on amendments — shortly before midnight Friday, and by its end around noon dispensed with about three dozen. The Senate had been in session since 9 a.m. EST Friday.</p>
<p>Overnight, the chamber looked like an experiment in sleep deprivation. Several lawmakers appeared to rest their eyes or doze at their desks, often burying their faces in their hands. At one point, Sen. Brian Schatz, D-Hawaii, at 48 one of the younger senators, trotted into the chamber and did a prolonged stretch.</p>
<p>Sen. Dan Sullivan, R-Alaska, missed the votes to attend his father-in-law’s funeral.</p>
<p>The measure follows five earlier ones totaling about $4 trillion enacted since last spring and comes amid signs of a potential turnaround.</p>
<p>Vaccine supplies are growing, deaths and caseloads have eased but remain frighteningly high, and hiring was surprisingly strong last month, though the economy remains 10 million jobs smaller than pre-pandemic levels.</p>
<p>The Senate package was delayed repeatedly as Democrats made eleventh-hour changes aimed at balancing demands by their competing moderate and progressive factions.</p>
<p>Work on the bill ground to a halt Friday after an agreement among Democrats on extending emergency jobless benefits seemed to collapse. Nearly 12 hours later, top Democrats and West Virginia Sen. Joe Manchin, perhaps the chamber&#8217;s most conservative Democrat, said they had a deal, and the Senate approved it on a party-line 50-49 vote.</p>
<p>Under their compromise, $300 weekly emergency unemployment checks — on top of regular state benefits — would be renewed, with a final payment Sept. 6. There would also be tax breaks on some of that aid, helping people the pandemic abruptly tossed out of jobs and risked tax penalties on the benefits.</p>
<p>The House relief bill, largely similar to the Senate&#8217;s, provided $400 weekly benefits through August. The current $300 per week payments expire March 14, and Democrats want the bill on Biden&#8217;s desk by then to avert a lapse.</p>
<p>Manchin and Republicans have asserted that higher jobless benefits discourage people from returning to work, a rationale most Democrats and many economists reject.</p>
<p>The agreement on jobless benefits wasn&#8217;t the only move that showed moderates&#8217; sway.</p>
<p>The Senate voted Friday to eject a House-approved boost in the federal minimum wage to $15 an hour by 2025, a major defeat for progressives. Eight Democrats opposed the increase, suggesting that Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and other liberals pledging to continue the effort will face a difficult fight.</p>
<p>Party leaders also agreed to restrict eligibility for the $1,400 stimulus checks for most Americans. That amount would be gradually reduced until, under the Senate bill, it reaches zero for people earning $80,000 and couples making $160,000. Those ceilings were higher in the House version.</p>
<p>Many of the rejected GOP amendments were either attempts to force Democrats to cast politically awkward votes or for Republicans to demonstrate their zeal for issues that appeal to their voters.</p>
<p>These included defeated efforts to bar funds from going to schools that don&#8217;t reopen their doors or let transgender students born male participate in female sports. One amendment would have blocked aid to so-called sanctuary cities, where local authorities don&#8217;t help federal officials round up immigrants in the U.S. illegally.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877361</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1b604760-368c-431a-bf7a-51afb4eb3851/ceda37c6-0318-4ce8-be8e-2f462705280e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219266~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1b604760-368c-431a-bf7a-51afb4eb3851/ceda37c6-0318-4ce8-be8e-2f462705280e/main.mp4*~hmac=a612601c17e3b4d22170015de4d10cf47dc18354afbfab811e83adc47f4dda64' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>California OKs reopening of ball parks, Disneyland</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/california-oks-reopening-of-ball-parks-disneyland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a year after coronavirus restrictions shuttered major entertainment spots.</p>
<p>The state on Friday relaxed guidelines for reopening outdoor venues as a fall and winter surge seemed to be ending, with COVID-19 infection rates, hospitalizations and deaths plummeting and vaccination rates rising.</p>
<p>New public health rules would allow live concerts at stadiums and sports arenas to reopen with limited attendance April 1. Amusement parks also will be permitted to reopen in counties that have fallen from the state&#8217;s purple tier — the most restrictive — to the red tier.</p>
<p>In all cases, park capacities will be limited, and COVID-19 safety rules such as mask-wearing requirements will apply.</p>
<p>The move followed a week of milestones, with California ramping up vaccinations for the poorest neighborhoods, counties reopening more businesses and Gov. Gavin Newsom passing a measure aimed at encouraging schools that have restricted students to online learning to reopen classrooms this month.</p>
<p>“Steady opening is consistent with the data. As cases decline, we want to return to work and school,” said Dr. Jeffrey Klausner, clinical professor of preventive medicine at the University of Southern California. “Outdoor activities in particular have always been low risk. Opening these sites makes sense.”</p>
<p>The reopening can&#8217;t come too soon for Kenny King Jr., a resident of Pleasant Hill in the San Francisco Bay Area who became an annual Disneyland passholder a decade ago. He typically takes his family to the Southern California park five times a year, but the last visit was just over a year ago for his birthday.</p>
<p>King, 38, said he&#8217;s excited to return with his 8-year-old daughter, who had just started enjoying rides such as Big Thunder Mountain Railroad and Space Mountain, and to take his 2-year-old son, who was mesmerized by the lights and sounds when he visited last year.</p>
<p>“That’s something that we just made our family thing — Disney trips,” King said. “We’ll sit there at the house sometimes and we’ll be like ‘man, I just miss Disneyland.&#8217; ”</p>
<p>Also applauding were the thousands of workers who were laid off by Disneyland, Universal Studios Hollywood, Knott&#8217;s Berry Farm and other big locations. Ten thousand lost their jobs alone at Disneyland and its related attractions in Orange County, not to mention the knock-on effect to nearby restaurants and hotels.</p>
<p>Andrea Zinder, president of the local United Food and Commercial Workers Union that represents Disney workers, said employees are “excited to go back to work and provide Californians with a bit more magic in their lives.”</p>
<p>Most of the major theme parks are in Southern California, which is still in the purple category. However, Los Angeles, Orange and San Diego counties were expecting to reopen within the next few weeks as their COVID-19 numbers fall.</p>
<p>Only 16 of 58 counties currently are in the red tier, and two small counties are in the orange tier. None are yet in the yellow tier, the lowest and least restrictive.</p>
<p>Theme parks in the red tier will be limited to 15% capacity.</p>
<p>Outdoor sports will be limited to 100 people in the purple tier but will increase up to 67% in the yellow tier.</p>
<p>The San Diego Padres, Los Angeles Angels and Oakland Athletics all announced they will have fans in the stands for opening day April 1. The Los Angeles Dodgers and San Francisco Giants both start their seasons on the road and said they would announce their plans later.</p>
<p>Teams and event organizers can only sell tickets regionally in the purple tier. In the other tiers, teams and organizers can sell tickets to anyone living in California. No concessions will be allowed in the purple tier, while in others, concession sales will only be available at seats.</p>
<p>Richard Haick of San Pablo, California, already bought ticket vouchers for the Oakland A’s return and hopes to take his 10-year-old son to a game soon. His son plays Little League baseball and is very excited to attend games.</p>
<p>“It’s nice to have, even in a reduced capacity, some sense of normal,” said Haick, a 45-year-old photographer.</p>
<p>The quicker pace of reopening is tied to a new plan to vaccinate California’s most vulnerable residents. Once 2 million people across 400 ZIP codes in the most disadvantaged neighborhoods receive at least one vaccine dose, it will be easier for counties to exit the state’s most restrictive tier. Once 4 million people in those neighborhoods are vaccinated, counties will be able to open up even more.</p>
<p>It all puts California in a drastically different position than a year ago, when Gov. Gavin Newsom imposed the statewide stay-at-home order that restricted travel, shuttered businesses and forced millions of people onto unemployment. California still has among the most severe restrictions of any state and continues to discourage out-of-state visitors.</p>
<p>The state is pinning its hopes of a full reopening on inoculating enough of its 40 million residents to halt widespread COVID-19 infections.</p>
<p>More than 10 million doses had been given only three months since the first shot was given, the Department of Public Health said.</p>
<p>Just over 3 million people have been fully vaccinated, or about 10% of the population 16 and older.</p>
<p>There are hopeful signs. This week, the seven-day average rate of positive results from tests dropped this week to 2.2%, a record low.</p>
<p>Although pressure has been building to reopen the economy, health officials said the changes in guidelines were a cautious and measured rather than a wholesale approach.</p>
<p>“We will &#8230;. keep our foot on the brake, not the gas, our eyes on the road, hands on the wheel and navigate based on data and science,” said Dr. Mark Ghaly, secretary of the state Health and Human Services Agency.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877338</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219189~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4*~hmac=9db0e975a924b2cb465a0111975a103e3c17569f6dd83db5e8e6be277872acd9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">sleeping beauty castle disneyland</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;We&#8217;re walking into the mouth of the monster&#8217; by loosening Covid-19 restrictions, expert says</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/were-walking-into-the-mouth-of-the-monster-by-loosening-covid-19-restrictions-expert-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877317</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; More states are relaxing measures to protect against Covid-19 as variants circulate in the United States &#8212; a combination that means &#8220;we&#8217;re walking into the mouth of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; More states are<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/05/health/us-coronavirus-friday/index.html"> relaxing measures</a> to protect <a href="https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2020/health/coronavirus-us-maps-and-cases/">against Covid-19</a> as variants circulate in the United States &#8212; a combination that means &#8220;we&#8217;re walking into the mouth of the monster,&#8221; an infectious disease expert said.</p>
<p>A variant first identified in the UK has now been reported in 2,672 cases in 46 states as of Thursday, according to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. And it is spreading quickly.</p>
<p>&#8220;We literally are sitting on top of that, at a time when instead of actually getting better prepared for it, we&#8217;re opening up and inviting the virus in,&#8221; said Michael Osterholm, director of the Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy at the University of Minnesota.</p>
<p>&#8220;Right now, that (UK variant) is about to take off the United States,&#8221; Osterholm told <a href="https://www.cnn.com/shows/the-lead">CNN&#8217;s Jake Tapper.</a> &#8220;A number of states have seen it go from 1 or 2% of the viruses identified, to now over 20 to 30%.&#8221;</p>
<p>This week, <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/03/politics/greg-abbott-texas-criticism-coronavirus-handling/index.html">Texas </a>and Mississippi joined the list of states to remove mandates for citizens to wear masks and expanded capacity for businesses.</p>
<p>With vaccine eligibility opening up to most US adults by the summer, support for measures to protect against the virus is waning, according to a new survey.</p>
<p>Although less than a third of people said there should be fewer measures, support for additional restrictions has been on the decline since November, according to new research from the Pew Research Center.</p>
<p>But health experts say the road to herd immunity still has a long way ahead, and masks and other restrictions are still crucial to managing the pandemic.</p>
<p>A new CDC study demonstrates &#8220;that masks work,&#8221; CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said during a White House Covid-19 briefing on Friday.</p>
<p>&#8220;You have decreases in cases and deaths when you wear masks and you have increases in cases and deaths when you have in-person restaurant dining, and so we would advocate for policies &#8212; certainly while we&#8217;re at this plateau of a high number of cases &#8212; that would listen to that public health science,&#8221; Walensky said.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>States range on loosening restrictions</h3>
<p>As the US moves closer to widespread vaccinations, many states are changing their policies around Covid-19 restrictions.</p>
<p>In Maine, Gov. Janet Mills said Friday the state will continue to require masks, but she announced a new framework to slowly reopen the state. By March 26, capacity for indoor gatherings in the state will increase to 50% and outdoor will increase to 75%.</p>
<p>And in West Virginia, beginning Saturday, some businesses including restaurants, bars, gyms and museums can open with 100% seating capacity, but social distancing will still be required, Gov. Jim Justice said Friday.</p>
<p>In Texas, any business will be allowed to open 100% beginning March 10, and the order for residents to wear masks has been lifted.</p>
<p>Not all state leaders feel comfortable with the changes.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m deeply concerned about states that lift the mask mandate because what you&#8217;re doing is sending a signal that it&#8217;s not important anymore, and that is not true. In fact, it is just as important as ever,&#8221; North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper said.</p>
<p>&#8220;I would encourage my fellow governors and local officials who are making decisions in some states to keep the mask mandate, to show good examples and to continue doing responsible things.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Detroit mayor declines Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine allocation</h3>
<p>Many experts have celebrated the authorization of the third coronavirus vaccine: Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s, which is a single shot and is stored at temperatures more convenient for transportation and storage.</p>
<p>But there has been some pushback.</p>
<p>Detroit Mayor <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/04/health/detroit-mayor-johnson-and-johnson-vaccine/index.html">Mike Duggan on Thursday said the city declined</a> an initial allocation of the newly authorized vaccine.</p>
<p>Duggan turned down the shipment because the city is able to meet current demand with its supply of the Pfizer/BioNTech and Moderna vaccines &#8212; even as his administration expanded vaccine eligibility Thursday to residents ages 50 and older with chronic medical conditions.</p>
<p>All three vaccines are highly effective at preventing serious illness from Covid-19, and health officials have urged people to take any Covid-19 vaccine they are offered.</p>
<p>&#8220;The day may come in March or April when every single Moderna and Pfizer is committed, and we still have people who need a vaccine. And at that point we will set up a Johnson &amp; Johnson center. I don&#8217;t see that in the next couple of weeks,&#8221; Duggan said.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>CDC guidance for the vaccinated</h3>
<p>CDC guidance for people who have been vaccinated is coming soon, Walensky said. The guidance had been expected to release this week.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our goal and what is most important is that people who have been vaccinated and those not yet vaccinated are able to understand the steps they can take to protect themselves and their loved ones,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>More than 82 million vaccine doses have been given out in the US, and after a year of life turned upside down, many want to know what the future holds.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think people need practical advice about how to go about their everyday lives,&#8221; said Julia Marcus, an infectious disease epidemiologist at Harvard. &#8220;I think without guidance, people may make decisions that are not informed.&#8221;</p>
<p>While the guidelines will not give the vaccinated permission to start living like it&#8217;s 2019 again, according to a Biden administration official, the guidelines do offer some hope that the end of total social isolation is near.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877317</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York cinemas reopen, brightening outlook for theaters</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/new-york-cinemas-reopen-brightening-outlook-for-theaters/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — After growing cobwebs for nearly a year, movie theaters in New York City reopen Friday, returning film titles to Manhattan marquees...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — After growing cobwebs for nearly a year, movie theaters in New York City reopen Friday, returning film titles to Manhattan marquees that had for the last 12 months instead read messages like “Wear a mask” and “We’ll be back soon.”</p>
<p>Shortly after noon at the Angelika Film Center on Houston Street, Holly Stillman was already feeling emotional coming out of the first New York showing of Lee Isaac Chung’s tender family drama “Minari.” “My mask is drenched,” she said.</p>
<p>But she was equally overwhelmed by being back in a cinema. Though Stillman feared the experience would be too restrictive because of COVID-19 protocols, she instead found it euphoric.</p>
<p>“It was just you and the movie screen,” said Stillman. “It was wonderful to smell the popcorn as soon as I got into the theater — even though I don’t eat popcorn.”</p>
<p>Less than half of movie theaters are open nationwide, but reopenings are quickening. Theaters in many other areas reopened last summer around the release of Christopher Nolan’s “Tenet,” but that attempted comeback fizzled. Throughout, theaters remained shut in the five boroughs. For a year almost to the date, one of the world’s foremost movie capitals stayed dark.</p>
<p>For a theatrical business that has been punished by the pandemic, the resumption of moviegoing in New York — is a crucial first step in revival.</p>
<p>“It’s a symbolic moment,” said Michael Barker, co-president of the New York-based Sony Pictures Classics, which on Friday released the Oscar contenders “The Father” and “The Truffle Hunters” in Manhattan theaters. “It says that there is hope for the theatrical world to reactivate itself.”</p>
<p>For some moviegoers who consider the big screen the only way to see a movie, the long-in-coming day had almost religious significance.</p>
<p>“Moviegoing for me is like going to church,” said JM Vargas, who had tickets Friday to “Minari,” “The Last Dragon” and “Chaos Walking.” “I’ve been waiting a year to go back to church.”</p>
<p>Cinemas in the city are currently operating at only 25% capacity, with a maximum of 50 per each auditorium. As in other places, mask wearing is mandatory, seats are blocked out and air filters have been upgraded.</p>
<p>Many theaters were caught off guard when Gov. Andrew Cuomo said cinemas could, under those conditions, reopen. Some of the city’s prominent theaters, including the Film Forum, the Alamo Drafthouse, the Metrograph and Regal Cinemas were targeting openings in the coming weeks. Some needed more time to prepare. After sitting dormant all winter, the Cinema Village in Manhattan two weeks earlier burst a pipe, flooding the lobby — one last bit of bad luck in a grueling year.</p>
<p>“This was the worst horror movie. I don’t think any Hollywood director could have dreamed it up,” said Nicolas Nicolaou, owner of the Cinema Village and theaters in Queens and New York. “We didn’t realize we’d be 100% shutdown for this long.”</p>
<p>New York, along with Los Angeles (where theaters are still closed), is one of the top movie markets. For smaller films, it’s a vital epicenter of word-of-mouth. For blockbusters, it’s a lucrative necessity. Without New York or Los Angeles open, Hollywood studios have pushed most of their larger productions until more theaters are open, or they’ve steered films to streaming services.</p>
<p>“The New York opening is very significant to the theater business in New York, in the nation and in the globe,” says John Fithian, president of the National Association of Theater Owners. “We in the movie theater business live off of movies that play all around the country and all around the world. We keep seeing those movies leave the theatrical release schedule to move to later dates because there just haven’t been enough markets. New York is the most important of those markets.”</p>
<p>Lately, with President Biden’s prediction that every adult can be vaccinated by the end of May, the outlook for theaters has been brightening for the first time in a long time. Last weekend, “Tom &amp; Jerry” overperformed at the box office with $14.1 million in ticket sales, even while it streamed on HBO Max. Though Universal Pictures pushed the “Fast &amp; Furious” sequel “F9” from late May to late June, other movies have moved up on the calendar, reversing the postponement tide.</p>
<p>Sony Pictures said it will release “Peter Rabbit 2: The Runaway” in May. Paramount Pictures’ “A Quiet Place II” moved into the May 28 date vacated by “F9.” The Walt Disney Co.’s “Black Widow” currently remains slated for May 7. Adding to the optimism: Southern California theaters are expected to reopen over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>“It’s not that we’re going back to record-breaking business this summer,” said Fithian. “We’re going to crawl, then we’re going to walk and then we’re going to run. It’s going to take into 2022 before sustained profitability comes back into the business.”</p>
<p>But at least on Friday, New York’s cinema lobbies were, if not crowded, again bustling. Sold-out signs for the evening adorned box-office windows. Even a little star power returned. Liam Neeson was to stop by the AMC at Lincoln Square to introduce “The Marksman.”</p>
<p>At the IFC Center in Greenwich Village, masked moviegoers flocked to films to play catch up — even if the movies were streaming. IFC is hosting a four-week “What’d We Miss?” series of movies the theater couldn’t play over the last 12 months, including “First Cow” and “MLK/FBI.”</p>
<p>“We’re used to being present for the birth of these movies for New York audiences when they move into the public realm,” said John Vanco, senior vice president of the IFC Center. The circumstances, he granted, weren’t ideal. But they were better than nothing. “I don’t look at 25% as being not good enough,” said Vanco. “I look at it as better than 0%.”</p>
<p>At the IFC, Tykon Herman settled in for “Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom,” and had tickets for a 5 p.m. of “The Trial of the Chicago 7.”</p>
<p>“I’m one of the very few that don’t have Netflix,” said Herman, laughing. “I’m just old-fashioned. I’ve loved the theater experience from the time I saw ‘E.T.’ It’s not going to be the same but sitting down in front of this screen makes me feel like things may be getting back to normal soon.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877232</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Europe staggers as infectious variants power virus surge</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/europe-staggers-as-infectious-variants-power-virus-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In a matter of just days, 45 children and 14 staff members had tested positive.</p>
<p>Genetic analysis confirmed what officials already suspected: The highly contagious coronavirus variant first identified in England was racing through the community, a densely packed city of nearly 40,000 with a chemical plant and a Pirelli bicycle tire factory a 15-minute drive from the heart of Milan.</p>
<p>“This demonstrates that the virus has a sort of intelligence. &#8230; We can put up all the barriers in the world and imagine that they work, but in the end, it adapts and penetrates them,’’ lamented Bollate Mayor Francesco Vassallo.</p>
<p>Bollate was the first city in Lombardy, the northern region that has been the epicenter in each of Italy’s three surges, to be sealed off from neighbors because of virus variants that the World Health Organization says are powering another uptick in infections across Europe. The variants also include versions first identified in South Africa and Brazil.</p>
<p>Europe recorded 1 million new COVID-19 cases last week, an increase of 9% from the previous week and a reversal that ended a six-week decline in new infections, WHO said Thursday.</p>
<p>“The spread of the variants is driving the increase, but not only,’’ said Dr. Hans Kluge, WHO regional director for Europe, citing “also the opening of society, when it is not done in a safe and a controlled manner.”</p>
<p>The variant first found in the U.K. is spreading significantly in 27 European countries monitored by WHO and is dominant in at least 10 countries: Britain, Denmark, Italy, Ireland, Germany, France, the Netherlands, Israel, Spain and Portugal.</p>
<p>It is up to 50% more transmissible than the virus that surged last spring and again in the fall, making it more adept at thwarting measures that were previously effective, WHO experts warned. Scientists have concluded that it is also more deadly.</p>
<p>“That is why health systems are struggling more now,” Kluge said. “It really is at a tipping point. We have to hold the fort and be very vigilant.”</p>
<p>In Lombardy, which bore the brunt of Italy’s spring surge, intensive care wards are again filling up, with more than two-thirds of new positive tests being the UK variant, health officials said.</p>
<p>After putting two provinces and some 50 towns on a modified lockdown, Lombardy&#8217;s regional governor announced tightened restrictions Friday and closed classrooms for all ages. Cases in Milan schools alone surged 33% in a week, the provincial health system&#8217;s chief said.</p>
<p>The situation is dire in the Czech Republic, which this week registered a record-breaking total of nearly 8,500 patients hospitalized with COVID-19. Poland is opening temporary hospitals and imposing a partial lockdown as the U.K. variant has grown from 10% of all infections in February to 25% now.</p>
<p>Two patients from hard-hit Slovakia were expected to arrive Saturday for treatment in Germany, where authorities said they had offered to take in 10 patients.</p>
<p>Kluge cited Britain’s experience as cause for optimism, noting that widespread restrictions and the introduction of the vaccine have helped tamp down the variants there and in Israel. The vaccine rollout in the European Union, by comparison, is lagging badly, mostly because of supply problems.</p>
<p>In Britain, the emergence of the more transmissible strain sent cases soaring in December and triggered a national lockdown in January. Cases have since plummeted, from about 60,000 a day in early January to about 7,000 a day now.</p>
<p>Still, a study shows the rate of decline slowing, and the British government says it will tread cautiously with plans to ease the lockdown. That process begins Monday with the reopening of schools. Infection rates are highest in people ages 13 to 17, and officials will watch closely to see whether the return to class brings a spike in infections.</p>
<p>While the U.K. variant is dominant in France, forcing lockdowns in the French Riviera city of Nice and the northern port of Dunkirk, the variant first detected in South Africa has emerged as the most prevalent in France&#8217;s Moselle region, which borders Germany and Luxembourg. It represents 55% of the virus circulating there.</p>
<p>Austria&#8217;s health minister said Saturday the U.K. variant is now dominant in his country. But the South Africa variant is also a concern in a district of Austria that extends from Italy to Germany, with Austrian officials announcing plans to vaccinate most of the 84,000 residents there to curb its spread. Austria is also requiring motorists along the Brenner highway, a major north-south route, to show negative test results.</p>
<p>The South Africa variant, now present in 26 European countries, is a source of particular concern because of doubts over whether the current vaccines are effective enough against it. The Brazilian variant, which appears capable of reinfecting people, has been detected in 15 European countries.</p>
<p>WHO and its partners are working to strengthen the genetic surveillance needed to track variants across the continent.</p>
<p>The mayor of Bollate has appealed to the regional governor to vaccinate all 40,000 residents immediately, though he expects to be told the vaccine supply is too tight.</p>
<p>Bollate has recorded 3,000 positive cases and 134 deaths — mostly among the elderly — since Italy was stricken a year ago. It took the brunt in the resurgence in November and December, and was caught completely off guard when the U.K. variant arrived, racing through school-age children before hitting families at home.</p>
<p>“People are starting to get tired that after a year there is no light at the end of the tunnel,” Vassallo said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877227</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">010221 coronavirus_UK variant_B117</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fighting Biden virus aid, GOP rekindles Obama-era strategy</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/fighting-biden-virus-aid-gop-rekindles-obama-era-strategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Republicans have one goal for President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief package: erode public support for the rescue plan by portraying it...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Republicans have one goal for President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion <a href="https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-legislation-coronavirus-pandemic-bills-2ffd868f5d3abed426e34e9427174813">COVID-19 relief package</a>: erode public support for the rescue plan by portraying it as too big, too bloated and too much wasteful public spending for a pandemic that’s almost over.</p>
<p>Senate Republicans prepared Saturday to vote lockstep against the relief bill, taking the calculated political risk that Americans will sour on the big-dollar spending for vaccination distribution, unemployment benefits, money for the states and other outlays as unnecessary, once they learn all the details.</p>
<p>Reviving a page from their 2009 takedown of President Barack Obama’s costly recovery from the financial crisis, they expect their opposition will pay political rewards, much like the earlier effort contributed to the House Republicans&#8217; rise to power.</p>
<p>It’s a tested strategy but comes at an uncertain, volatile time for the nation. Americans are experiencing flickers of optimism at the one-year anniversary of the deadly outbreak as more people are vaccinated. But new strains of the virus and a still shaky economy could unleash another devastating cycle of infections, lockdowns and deaths. More than 500,000 Americans have died.</p>
<p>So far, public support for Biden’s approach to the pandemic is high. Overall, 70% of Americans back the Democratic president’s handling of the virus response, including 44% of Republicans, according to <a href="https://apnews.com/article/ap-norc-poll-americans-largely-back-biden-virus-response-d365bff571c24f9d3575bcbd051780aa">a new poll </a>from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research.</p>
<p>Biden and Democrats warn that now is not the time to let up on aid, and that it&#8217;s better to risk doing too much than too little. They say the costs of paring back the rescue risk stalling out the economic recovery, as many believe happened in 2009.</p>
<p>“When the house is in flames, you don’t argue about how much of the fire to put out,” said Sen. Patty Murray, D-Wash., during Friday’s session.</p>
<p>“You do whatever it takes until the crisis is over,” she said. “And you do it as fast as you can.”</p>
<p>The debate in Congress reflects a fundamental divide in the country over how to contain and crush the pandemic and get the nation back to normal.</p>
<p>Nearly 10 million <a href="https://apnews.com/article/unemployment-united-states-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-27d58c2e9e2931985e537a08c761507d">jobs </a>have been lost and some 11 million households face evictions. While Democratic leaders generally side with health professionals supporting social distancing restrictions and easing into school and workplace reopenings, congressional Republicans have been more eager to conduct business as close to usual as possible.</p>
<p>The U.S. is not alone in confronting the daunting dilemma that holds serious ramifications about the size and scope of aid that&#8217;s needed to prevent further economic catastrophe.</p>
<p>Senate Republican leader Mitch McConnell, who is leading his minority party toward the &#8220;no&#8221; vote, said <a href="https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-bills-coronavirus-pandemic-ca3816a34f2405c3576251fda95ddbe3">Biden’s 628-page bill</a> is a Democratic “wish list” doesn’t meet the moment because the pandemic is lifting and the economy is ready for a “roaring recovery.&#8221;</p>
<p>“We are already on track to bounce back from the crisis,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Republicans argue Congress has already approved historic sums to counter the pandemic and worry the big spending will overheat the economy, spiking inflationary fears, though economists are mixed on those concerns. They have an opening with voters who the polling shows are skeptical of Biden&#8217;s handling of the economy.</p>
<p>McConnell expressed similar optimism last spring when he hit “pause” on new spending after approval of the initial round of aid. Around that time, then-President Donald Trump pledged that Americans would be all but back to normal by Easter Sunday.</p>
<p>But as Texas announced this past week it would seek to end face-mask wearing requirements, one of the key strategies public health officials say helps stop the spread of the virus, familiar political fault-lines and anxieties are resurfacing. Texas was among the first states to reopen in May, loosening restrictions at the start of the pandemic’s second wave that coursed through summer.</p>
<p>Jason Furman, the former chairman of Obama&#8217;s Council of Economic Advisers who now teaches at Harvard, agrees that parts of Biden’s package are too big, suggesting the $350 billion to states and cities could be reduced or have stricter guardrails against waste. But he said the bigger economic danger is in not doing enough.</p>
<p>Vaccines alone are not enough to ensure a healthy economy, he said. Households are struggling and businesses are confronting changing consumer habits and spending. The Biden package offers $1,400 direct payments to individuals, phased out for those earning $80,000 a year.</p>
<p>“If you add up the financial needs of households and the shortfalls facing states the American Rescue Plan overfills these,” he said by email. “But no legislation is perfect and, as I said, if the downside is families get a little more money in one particular year that is much less bad than if Congress fails to act.”</p>
<p>As Biden embarked on a go-it-alone partisan strategy, relying on Democratic votes for passage, Republicans are in fighting mode.</p>
<p>Senate Republicans forced an all-night reading of the bill Thursday, delaying the start of debate.</p>
<p>On Friday, senators launched an overnight session on amendments, most from Republicans, designed in part to change the bill, but also to highlight costly expenditures and less popular provisions. By early Saturday, most were failing.</p>
<p>Democrats&#8217; own amendment, to reduce extra <a href="https://apnews.com/article/senate-nears-virus-relief-bill-vote-fa965b1b413d811ad10549b3460c6643">jobless benefits from $400 a week to $300</a>, was splitting their ranks and causing further delays, before it eventually was accepted.</p>
<p>Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., who forced the bill reading, used charts and props to help Americans understand the size of the $1.9 trillion package.</p>
<p>“The human mind can&#8217;t really contemplate what a trillion is,” he said, before launching into examples. He suggested a stack of $1 bills would extend the distance halfway to the moon.</p>
<p>GOP Sen. Mike Braun of Indiana said by the time they&#8217;re done they hope to turn public opinion around.</p>
<p>“We’re going to expose every ugly detail of it,” he said.</p>
<p>The White House is well aware of the challenges ahead. Many of Biden&#8217;s staff members are veterans of the 2009 battles.</p>
<p>Press secretary Jen Psaki said Friday that at the time they didn&#8217;t do enough to explain to the American people the benefits in ways &#8220;that people would be talking about at their dinner tables.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877222</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/102419-lindsey-graham.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/102419-lindsey-graham.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/102419-lindsey-graham.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">102419 Sen. Lindsey Graham</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senate Dems strike jobless aid deal, COVID relief bill OK in sight</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/senate-dems-strike-jobless-aid-deal-relief-bill-ok-in-sight/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate leaders and moderate Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin struck a deal over emergency jobless benefits, breaking a logjam that had stalled the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate leaders and moderate Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin struck a deal over emergency jobless benefits, breaking a logjam that had stalled the party&#8217;s showpiece $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill.</p>
<p>The compromise, announced by the West Virginia lawmaker and a Democratic aide late Friday, seemed to clear the way for the Senate to begin a climactic, marathon series of votes and, eventually, approval of the sweeping legislation.</p>
<p>The overall bill, President Joe Biden’s foremost legislative priority, is aimed at battling the killer pandemic and nursing the staggered economy back to health. It would provide direct payments of up to $1,400 to most Americans and money for COVID-19 vaccines and testing, aid to state and local governments, help for schools and the airline industry and subsidies for health insurance.</p>
<p>The Senate next faced votes on a pile of amendments that were likely to last overnight, mostly on Republican proposals virtually certain to fail but designed to force Democrats to cast politically awkward votes.</p>
<p>More significantly, the jobless benefits agreement suggested it was just a matter of time until the Senate passes the bill. That would ship it back to the House, which was expected to give it final congressional approval and whisk it to Biden for his signature.</p>
<p>White House press secretary Jen Psaki said Biden supports the compromise on jobless payments.</p>
<p>The day&#8217;s lengthy standoff underscored the headaches confronting party leaders over the next two years — and the tensions between progressives and centrists — as they try moving their agenda through the Congress with their slender majorities.</p>
<p>Manchin is probably the chamber’s most conservative Democrat, and a kingmaker in the 50-50 Senate. But the party can’t tilt too far center to win Manchin’s vote without endangering progressive support in the House, where they have a mere 10-vote edge.</p>
<p>Aiding unemployed Americans is a top Democratic priority. But it’s also an issue that drives a wedge between progressives seeking to help jobless constituents cope with the bleak economy and Manchin and other moderates who have wanted to trim some of the bill’s costs.</p>
<p>Biden noted Friday&#8217;s jobs report showing that employers added 379,000 workers — an unexpectedly strong showing. That&#8217;s still small compared to the 10 million fewer jobs since the pandemic struck a year ago.</p>
<p>“Without a rescue plan, these gains are going to slow,&#8221; Biden said. “We can’t afford one step forward and two steps backwards. We need to beat the virus, provide essential relief, and build an inclusive recovery.&#8221;</p>
<p>The overall bill faces a solid wall of GOP opposition, and Republicans used the unemployment impasse to accuse Biden of refusing to seek compromise with them.</p>
<p>“You could pick up the phone and end this right now,” Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., said of Biden.</p>
<p>But in an encouraging sign for Biden, a poll by The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research found that 70% of Americans support his handling of the pandemic, including a noteworthy 44% of Republicans.</p>
<p>The House approved a relief bill last weekend that included $400 weekly jobless benefits — on top of regular state payments — through August. Manchin was hoping to reduce those costs, asserting that level of payment would discourage people from returning to work, a rationale most Democrats and many economists reject.</p>
<p>As the day began, Democrats asserted they&#8217;d reached a compromise between party moderates and progressives extending emergency jobless benefits at $300 weekly into early October.</p>
<p>That plan, sponsored by Sen. Tom Carper, D-Del., also included tax reductions on some unemployment benefits. Without that, many Americans abruptly tossed out of jobs would face unexpected tax bills.</p>
<p>But by midday, lawmakers said Manchin was ready to support a less generous Republican version. That led to hours of talks involving White House aides, top Senate Democrats and Manchin as the party tried finding a way to salvage its unemployment aid package.</p>
<p>The compromise announced Friday night would provide $300 weekly, with the final check paid on Sept. 6, and includes the tax break on benefits.</p>
<p>Before the unemployment benefits drama began, senators voted 58-42 to kill a top progressive priority, a gradual increase in the current $7.25 hourly minimum wage to $15 over five years.</p>
<p>Eight Democrats voted against that proposal, suggesting that Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and other progressives vowing to continue the effort in coming months will face a difficult fight.</p>
<p>That vote began shortly after 11 a.m. EST and was not formally gaveled to a close until nearly 12 hours later as Senate work ground to a halt amid the unemployment benefit negotiations.</p>
<p>Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell chided Democrats, calling their daylong effort to work out the unemployment amendment a “spectacle.&#8221;</p>
<p>“What this proves is there are benefits to bipartisanship when you&#8217;re dealing with an issue of this magnitude,&#8221; McConnell said.</p>
<p>Republicans criticized the overall relief bill as a liberal spend-fest that ignores that growing numbers of vaccinations and signs of a stirring economy suggest that the twin crises are easing.</p>
<p>“Democrats inherited a tide that was already turning.” McConnell said.</p>
<p>Democrats reject that, citing the job losses and numerous people still struggling to buy food and pay rent.</p>
<p>“If you just look at a big number you say, ‘Oh, everything&#8217;s getting a little better,'&#8221; said Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y. “It&#8217;s not for the lower half of America. It&#8217;s not.&#8221;</p>
<p>Friday&#8217;s gridlock over unemployment benefits gridlock wasn&#8217;t the first delay on the relief package. On Thursday Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., forced the chamber&#8217;s clerks to read aloud the entire 628-page relief bill, an exhausting task that took staffers 10 hours and 44 minutes and ended shortly after 2 a.m. EST.</p>
<p>Democrats made a host of other late changes to the bill, designed to nail down support. They ranged from extra money for food programs and federal subsidies for health care for workers who lose jobs to funds for rural health care and language assuring minimum amounts of money for smaller states.</p>
<p>In another late bargain that satisfied moderates, Biden and Senate Democrats agreed Wednesday to make some higher earners ineligible for the direct checks to individuals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877008</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030521 senate chamber floor</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fauci, Gloria Estefan discuss COVID concerns on Instagram Live</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/fauci-gloria-estefan-discuss-covid-concerns-on-instagram-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gloria Estefan and Dr. Anthony Fauci engaged in a conversation about COVID-19 on Instagram Live. Fauci, President Joe Biden&#8217;s chief medical adviser, joined the singer...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gloria Estefan and Dr. Anthony Fauci engaged in a conversation about COVID-19 on Instagram Live.</p>
<p>Fauci, President Joe Biden&#8217;s chief medical adviser, joined the singer virtually for a discussion, Friday.</p>
<p>The two spoke on a range of topics relating to the coronavirus pandemic, including vaccination concerns and the efforts of the scientific community.</p>
<p>&#8220;Even though it took less than a year to get the vaccine, when it usually takes several years, that speed is a reflection of scientific advances,&#8221; said Fauci. &#8220;Safety was not compromised, nor was scientific integrity compromised.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fauci also took questions from commenters on other related topics, such as the benefits of the United States returning to the World Health Organization.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876954</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a132b296-ff67-4b9f-a059-3a456e8a2e1d/13c1e4c6-be28-4847-9770-637c9b5201aa/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217319~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a132b296-ff67-4b9f-a059-3a456e8a2e1d/13c1e4c6-be28-4847-9770-637c9b5201aa/main.mp4*~hmac=532bc40f265b8c202e69c557f21067fe2bf7a131b8108d92295ed5d62cb28313' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Levine Cava mulls lifting Miami-Dade curfew in April as vaccinations ramp up across South Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/levine-cava-mulls-lifting-miami-dade-curfew-in-april-as-vaccinations-ramp-up-across-south-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 21:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Miami-Dade Mayor Daniella Levine Cava said she is considering lifting the countywide curfew in early April if the positivity rate stays below a certain percentage,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Miami-Dade Mayor Daniella Levine Cava said she is considering lifting the countywide curfew in early April if the positivity rate stays below a certain percentage, as new federal vaccination sites continue to increase access to the COVID-19 vaccine.<p>According to a spokesperson for the mayor, Levine Cava sent a memo to the county commissioners on Friday outlining her decision to lift the curfew by April 5 if current trends continue and the 14-day average is at or below 5.5% at that time.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/MayorDaniella/status/1368016304284778503</embed></div><p>In a statement, Levine Cava wrote, &#x201C;We can&#x2019;t afford to let our guard down when we are so close to the finish line. I am confident that by continuing to work together with our residents and businesses, we can drive down our positivity rate below the 5.5% mark needed to minimize community spread of COVID-19.&#x201D;</p><p>The curfew extends from midnight until 6 a.m.</p><p>Hours earlier, 7News cameras captured patients at the <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-opens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FEMA vaccination site</a> at Miami-Dade College&#x2019;s North Campus.</p><p>Patients said they waited no longer than an hour to receive their vaccine. They were given the opportunity to choose between the Pfizer vaccine and the single-shot Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine.</p><p>&#x201C;I decided to go Johnson &amp; Johnson,&#x201D; said Vian Azzou.</p><p>Levine Cava touted the increase in inoculations countywide.</p><p>&#x201C;The total number of vaccines is maybe approaching 50,000 per week,&#x201D; she said.</p><p>The MDC site currently has the capacity to vaccinate 3,000 people a day.</p><p>Patient Dion Maclin said he also opted for the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine.</p><p>&#x201C;There may be some travel plans. Me and my family have been talking about traveling a little bit,&#x201D; he said, &#x201C;but we&#x2019;re still going to be cautious until we&#x2019;re all through this.&#x201D;</p><p>In addition to the FEMA sites now up and running, locations like Publix and Winn-Dixie supermarkets are expanding access as well.</p><p>Who can get vaccinated depends on the site itself.</p><p>State sites allow Floridians 65 and older to receive their vaccine, as well as those 18 or older with severe health conditions as long as they bring <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this form</a> filled out and signed by their doctor.</p><p>They also welcome school employees and first responders 50 years of age or older.</p><p>At the federally supported sites, any school employee 18 or older can receive their shot.</p><p>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis said access may soon be expanding.</p><p>&#x201C;If the demand is softening, we can then go and get some of the folks who are 60 to 65, and get them in, and then we&#x2019;ll move to 55 and do it,&#x201D; he said.</p><p>On Friday, the Florida Department of Health reported <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5900-cases-of-covid-19-on-friday/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">5,975 new cases</a> of the virus and a positivity rate of 5%. The state&#x2019;s death toll has risen to 31,522.</p><p>Dr. Anthony Fauci said he is worried people are becoming too comfortable and predicts another surge of cases on the horizon.</p><p>&#x201C;Many countries in Europe have seen just that. They had a decrease in cases over a six-week period, they plateaued, and now, over the past week, they saw an increase in cases by 9%,&#x201D; he said.</p><p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign,&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p><p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#x2019;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876830</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b035774e-e968-4470-9979-98bf49749be1/ac99f926-bfd1-42d9-b5f5-e67610fb84d3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219370~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b035774e-e968-4470-9979-98bf49749be1/ac99f926-bfd1-42d9-b5f5-e67610fb84d3/main.mp4*~hmac=84e641ecd827a5ab35285ba68ee2a99cfc8dd716cafbc7ba9ccbf86bea7849fa' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 5,900 cases of COVID-19 on Friday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5900-cases-of-covid-19-on-friday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 19:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,522 deaths. As of 2:30 p.m. Friday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,522 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2:30 p.m. Friday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,936,207 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,975 from Thursday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 135 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 417,447 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 198,387 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 122,709, and 5,958 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,632 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876769</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nicklaus Children&#8217;s hospital offers COVID-19 vaccine to people ages 16 to 21 with medical conditions</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/nicklaus-childrens-hospital-offers-covid-19-vaccine-to-people-ages-16-to-21-with-medical-conditions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 15:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital in Miami has announced they will provide Pfizer-BioNTech&#8217;s COVID-19 vaccine to children and young adults with medical conditions at risk for serious...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital in Miami has announced they will provide Pfizer-BioNTech&#8217;s COVID-19 vaccine to children and young adults with medical conditions at risk for serious illness if they contract the virus.</p>
<p>Starting on Monday, vaccine appointments can be requested on the <a href="https://www.nicklauschildrens.org/about-us/coronavirus-updates/covid-19-vaccines" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hospital&#8217;s website</a> for those between the ages of 16 and 21 with a doctor&#8217;s note.</p>
<p>“Nicklaus Children’s is committed to our mission of prioritizing the children and young adults of our community and beyond,&#8221; said Matthew A. Love, the President and CEO of Nicklaus Children’s Health System, the parent organization of the hospital. &#8220;While most children are only mildly affected by COVID-19, those with complex conditions may be at risk of severe illness if they contract the virus. We are honored to be able to offer the vaccine to support the care of vulnerable children in Florida.&#8221;</p>
<p>The hospital said those being treated for one or more of the following conditions identified by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention are eligible to receive the vaccine:</p>
<ul>
<li>Asthma (moderate to severe)</li>
<li>Cancer</li>
<li>Cerebrovascular disease</li>
<li>Chronic kidney disease</li>
<li>Cystic fibrosis</li>
<li>Diabetes (type 1 or 2)</li>
<li>Down syndrome</li>
<li>Heart conditions</li>
<li>Hypertension</li>
<li>Immunocompromised conditions</li>
<li>Liver disease</li>
<li>Neurologic conditions</li>
<li>Obesity</li>
<li>Pulmonary fibrosis</li>
<li>Sickle cell disease</li>
<li>Thalassemia</li>
</ul>
<p>The hospital received an additional allotment of the Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine, which allowed them to offer the shot to more people. As of Friday, the hospital has vaccinated 500 eligible patients.</p>
<p>Diego Diaz has been doing his first year at Duke University online in South Florida because the 18-year-old has Cystic fibrosis.</p>
<p>&#8220;I have to be very careful when I go outside, so I mostly stay indoors, and the few times I do go outside, I still have to be more cautious than most,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Diaz was recently one of the 700 at-risk patients at Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital to get the COVID-19 vaccine.</p>
<p>&#8220;With this shot, I&#8217;m more comfortable applying for housing for next year,&#8221; Diaz said.</p>
<p>Those older than 21 and under the medical care of a pediatrician or pediatric specialist are being evaluated on a case-by-case basis, hospital officials said.</p>
<p>Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital Chief Medical Officer Dr. Marcos Mestre said most children handle COVID-19 well and that this vaccination is more about teenagers helping the older at-risk population.</p>
<p>&#8220;We know adolescents don&#8217;t always like to follow the rules and like to hang out together and whatnot, so it also helps in terms of preventing the spread,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Dr. Mestre said for many kids, including Diaz, the vaccine means freedom.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s very common that I get a response that the family, after they&#8217;ve received the vaccine, have tears of joy because they&#8217;ve been locked up so long with their child who&#8217;s at risk, and they&#8217;d do anything for their child, so once they get that for their child, they feel like they&#8217;re seeing the light at end of the tunnel,&#8221; said Dr. Mestre.</p>
<p>Any Florida resident 16 to 21 who is at risk can register to receive the vaccine at Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876556</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Community-Vaccinations064.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/56767763-425b-45d4-a400-1cc34efe71cf/5367afec-1ccc-4860-8397-cae1e2ca4601/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216621~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/56767763-425b-45d4-a400-1cc34efe71cf/5367afec-1ccc-4860-8397-cae1e2ca4601/main.mp4*~hmac=96aeb975cd025be13e4d22e3dfb95890b8f6497bdad325883952061c7fa8e66c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Community-Vaccinations064.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Community-Vaccinations064.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Young adult getting vaccinated</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dems trim jobless benefits, Senate debates virus relief bill</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/dems-trim-jobless-benefits-senate-debates-virus-relief-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats agreed Friday to pare back emergency jobless benefits but extend them for an extra month, bidding to solidify support as the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats agreed Friday to pare back emergency jobless benefits but extend them for an extra month, bidding to solidify support as the Senate approached a voting marathon on a $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill.</p>
<p>The deal came as the chamber worked toward approving a final version of the massive package, probably over the weekend, of President Joe Biden&#8217;s top legislative priority. That would give the House time to approve the legislation and whisk it to Biden for his signature.</p>
<p>First, the Senate was preparing to vote on a mountain of amendments, mostly by GOP opponents. Virtually all are destined to fail but are designed to force Democrats to take politically awkward votes.</p>
<p>Among them, though, was a Democratic plan that was expected to pass that would trim the House bill&#8217;s $400 weekly emergency unemployment benefits.</p>
<p>Under the compromise, those payments — payable on top of regular state benefits — would be reduced to $300, but run an extra month through September. Taxes also would be reduced on unemployment benefits. A Senate Democratic aide provided details of the deal on condition of anonymity to describe private talks.</p>
<p>Biden and Senate leaders had agreed Wednesday to retain the House bill&#8217;s higher $400 version. The reduction to $300 seemed to reflect a need to secure support for the overall bill, particularly from moderate Democrats.</p>
<p>Republicans are attacking the bill as a liberal spend-fest that ignores that growing numbers of vaccinations and signs of a stirring economy suggest that the twin crises are easing.</p>
<p>“Our country is already set for a roaring recovery,&#8221; said Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., in part citing an unexpectedly strong report on job creation. “Democrats inherited a tide that was already turning.”</p>
<p>Democrats reject that, citing the 10 million jobs the economy has lost during the pandemic and numerous people still struggling to buy food and pay rent.</p>
<p>“If you just look at a big number you say, ‘Oh, everything&#8217;s getting a little better,'&#8221; said Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y. “It&#8217;s not for the lower half of America. It&#8217;s not.&#8221;</p>
<p>In an encouraging sign for Biden, a poll by The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research found that 70% of Americans support his handling of the pandemic, including a noteworthy 44% of Republicans.</p>
<p>Moments after the Senate took up the legislation Thursday, Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., forced the chamber&#8217;s clerks to read aloud the entire 628-page measure. The exhausting task took the staffers 10 hours and 44 minutes and ended shortly after 2 a.m. EST, with Johnson alternately sitting at his desk and pacing around the mostly empty chamber.</p>
<p>Democratic leaders made more than a dozen late additions to their package on Thursday. That reflected their need to cement unanimous support from all their senators — plus Vice President Kamala Harris’ tie-breaking vote — to succeed in the precariously divided 50-50 chamber.</p>
<p>The Senate’s 51-50 vote to start debating the package, with Harris pushing Democrats over the top, underscored how they were navigating the package through Congress with virtually no margin for error. In the House their majority is a scrawny 10 votes.</p>
<p>The bill, aimed at battling the killer virus and nursing the staggered economy back to health, will provide direct payments of up to $1,400 to most Americans. There’s also money for COVID-19 vaccines and testing, aid to state and local governments, help for schools and the airline industry, tax breaks for lower-earners and families with children, and subsidies for health insurance.</p>
<p>The new provisions offered items appealing to all manner of Democrats. Progressives got money boosting feeding programs, federal subsidies for health care for workers who lose jobs, tax-free student loans, and money for public broadcasting and consumer protection investigations.</p>
<p>Moderates won funds for rural health care, language assuring minimum amounts of money for smaller states and a prohibition on states receiving aid using the windfalls to cut taxes. And for everyone, there was money for infrastructure, cultural venues, start-up companies and afterschool programs.</p>
<p>The late changes left House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., the task of keeping her chamber’s numerous progressives on board. Liberals already suffered a blow when their No. 1 priority — a federal minimum wage increase to $15 hourly that was included in the House package — was booted from the bill in the Senate for violating the chamber&#8217;s rules and for lack of moderates&#8217; support.</p>
<p>In another bargain that satisfied moderates, Biden and Senate Democrats agreed Wednesday to tighten eligibility for the direct checks to individuals. The new provision completely phases out the $1,400 payments for individuals earning at least $80,000 and couples making $160,000, well lower than the original ceilings.</p>
<p>Congress wants to send the bill to Biden before March 14, when a previous round of emergency benefits for people tossed out of work by the pandemic expires.</p>
<p>Johnson told reporters he was forcing the bill&#8217;s reading to “shine the light on this abusive and obscene amount of money. ” Schumer Friday morning praised the staffers who worked late as “the unsung heroes of this place” and said of Johnson, “I hope he enjoyed his Thursday evening.”</p>
<p>The economic recovery began to stall late last year as the virus surged, causing a shortfall in hiring in recent months. The Labor Department said Friday that the economy added 379,000 jobs last month, indicating unexpected strength as virus cases fall and consumers boost spending but still leaving a long way for the country&#8217;s job market fully recovers.</p>
<p>The nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office estimates economic growth will exceed 4% this year without Biden’s rescue package. Republicans cite that as evidence the economy is pointed upward, but Democrats say a strong economic stimulus is still needed to prevent a relapse.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876330</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7f79f8f2-e34b-4c74-a181-22061d92955e/603f466b-fdad-4f4f-a7bc-ed2a22175048/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219842~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7f79f8f2-e34b-4c74-a181-22061d92955e/603f466b-fdad-4f4f-a7bc-ed2a22175048/main.mp4*~hmac=2726d626e647185a55a6cc4c1b9d259cfafd8022a0d30b6928ed09649c3e5edf' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030521 senate chamber floor</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 300 receive Pfizer vaccine at John Knox Village in Pompano Beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/over-300-receive-pfizer-vaccine-at-john-knox-village-in-pompano-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 23:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[More than 300 residents, staff and health care providers received their shots of the Pfizer vaccine at a retirement community in Pompano Beach. 7News cameras...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 residents, staff and health care providers received their shots of the Pfizer vaccine at a retirement community in Pompano Beach.</p>
<p>7News cameras captured seniors receiving their shots at the John Knox Village of Florida, Thursday afternoon.</p>
<p>First and second doses were administered.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876186</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_John_Knox_Village_vaccination.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4b48fe3e-6d98-4c92-9522-3cfce04042ff/963ddb85-89f0-4182-960f-b4299e411e6a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219185~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4b48fe3e-6d98-4c92-9522-3cfce04042ff/963ddb85-89f0-4182-960f-b4299e411e6a/main.mp4*~hmac=b2853d3b229fa00bc613b077c5b638747a867f272ab1b3470141f442f48c8805' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_John_Knox_Village_vaccination.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_John_Knox_Village_vaccination.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210304_John_Knox_Village_vaccination</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New COVID-19 vaccination site opens at Sweetwater park</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-covid-19-vaccination-site-opens-at-sweetwater-park/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 23:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A new vaccination site in Sweetwater is now distributing doses. The city administered shots at Ronselli Park, on Southwest 114th Avenue and Second Street, Thursday,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new vaccination site in Sweetwater is now distributing doses.</p>
<p>The city administered shots at Ronselli Park, on Southwest 114th Avenue and Second Street, Thursday, and 500 doses will be administered daily through next Wednesday.</p>
<p>People can walk up to the site without an appointment.</p>
<p>Sweetwater Mayor Orlando Lopez said he has high hopes for what the site can get done.</p>
<p>&#8220;If we do hit our goal of 500 a day from this point forward, we&#8217;re gonna be able to provide this vaccine to approximately 4,000 people, whether it is Sweetwater residents or adjacent neighborhoods,&#8221; Lopez said.</p>
<p>The vaccination location will be open from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876180</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-sweetwater-vaccine.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9a60f261-47d7-48e7-953d-011310ca7665/4ecae762-29ec-4a8b-96c7-9a62dd9f8a0a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216521~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9a60f261-47d7-48e7-953d-011310ca7665/4ecae762-29ec-4a8b-96c7-9a62dd9f8a0a/main.mp4*~hmac=d594cacfeb0558f11ea0a62328ad4e05e2c74a865ee7f122ee6b1cdfc7750ff8' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-sweetwater-vaccine.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-sweetwater-vaccine.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030421 sweetwater vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 6,000 new cases of COVID-19 on Thursday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-6000-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-thursday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875999</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,387 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,387 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,930,232 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 6,118 from Wednesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 120 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 416,021 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 197,542 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 122,226, and 5,937 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,338 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875999</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeSantis faces growing charges of vaccine favoritism</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/desantis-faces-growing-charges-of-vaccine-favoritism/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 18:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and state health officials came under deeper scrutiny amid revelations that seniors in a wealthy enclave in Key...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and state health officials came under deeper scrutiny amid revelations that seniors in a wealthy enclave in Key Largo received hundreds of life-saving vaccinations as early as mid -January, giving ammunition to critics who say the Republican governor is favoring wealthy constituents over ordinary Floridians.</p>
<p>The revelations were the latest example of wealthy Floridians getting earlier access to coronavirus vaccines, even as the state has lagged in efforts to get poorer residents vaccinated.</p>
<p>DeSantis pushed back Thursday, saying a local hospital — not the state — was behind the vaccinations of more than 1,200 residents of the exclusive Ocean Reef Club in Key Largo, Florida, and that the state “wasn&#8217;t involved in it in any shape or form.”</p>
<p>Despite the governor&#8217;s denials of quid pro quos, the charges of favoritism were amplified by money pouring into the governor&#8217;s campaign coffers from wealthy benefactors with ties to communities awarded vaccination sites — like the one in Key Largo. One resident of Ocean Reef, Republican former Illinois Gov. Bruce Rauner, last week gave the Florida governor&#8217;s campaign committee $250,000.</p>
<p>Revelations about Ocean Reef residents getting vaccinated were <a href="https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/florida-keys/article249666463.html">first reported by the Miami Herald</a>.</p>
<p>The inequitable distribution of the COVID-19 vaccines is becoming a public relations challenge for the governor. As of Wednesday, nearly 3.3 million Floridians had received at least one shot of the two-step vaccination process, about three-quarters of them 65 or older. But less than 6% have been Black — about a third of their share of the state&#8217;s population.</p>
<p>Florida Agriculture Commissioner Nikki Fried joined Democratic U.S. Rep. Charlie Crist in calling for federal officials to probe the DeSantis administration’s vaccine distribution programs.</p>
<p>“If this isn’t public corruption, I don’t know what is,” Fried said Thursday at a press conference in the Florida Capitol, calling on the FBI&#8217;s public corruption to launch an investigation.</p>
<p>“Give campaign contributions big dollars, get special access to vaccines &#8212; ahead of seniors, ahead of our teachers, ahead of our farmworkers and so many of our residents here in our state of Florida who are scared and who are wanting these vaccines.”</p>
<p>Citing reporting from the Herald, Fried noted that DeSantis in February had his biggest fundraising haul since 2018, when he was running for governor.</p>
<p>In asking the U.S. Department of Justice to look into matter, Crist, a former Florida governor, asserted last week that DeSantis were benefiting &#8220;political allies and donors, over the needs of higher-risk communities and existing county waitlists.”</p>
<p>Both Crist and Fried are considering campaigns to oppose DeSantis in next year&#8217;s gubernatorial election.</p>
<p>Other Florida Democrats, including the top Democrat in the state Senate, Gary Farmer, joined in the call for a federal investigation.</p>
<p>&#8220;The exchange of hard-to-get vaccines for political contributions is nothing short of criminal,&#8221; Farmer said in a letter dashed off to acting U.S. Attorney General Monty Wilkinson.</p>
<p>During a Thursday news conference, DeSantis expressed no misgivings about the early vaccinations at the exclusive Key Largo community.</p>
<p>“If you are 65 and up, I am not worried about your income bracket,&#8221; he said. “I am worried about your age bracket because it’s the age, not the income, that shows the risk.”</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the governor called the controversy “a manufactured narrative with political motivations.”</p>
<p>“Leadership matters and because of Governor Ron DeSantis’ commitment to ensuring vaccine access to all seniors – regardless of background, income or zip code – millions of seniors have received the vaccine, resulting in over 50 percent of our state’s senior population being vaccinated, the highest in the nation,” said the spokesperson, Meredith Beatrice.</p>
<p>The Republican Party of Florida came to the governor’s defense, calling the controversy “another bogus conspiracy theory.”</p>
<p>“It doesn’t matter what party you belong to, whether you are rich or poor, if you qualify for the vaccine, you can get a vaccine,” said Helen Aguirre Ferre, the state party’s executive director.</p>
<p>The Ocean Reef Club, a senior community in Key Largo, had more than 1,200 homeowners vaccinated through their second dose by late January, according to a message to community members by the management obtained by the Miami Herald.</p>
<p>Those vaccinations came at a time when “the majority of the state has not received an allocation of first doses,” the management noted.</p>
<p>Officials from Monroe County, home to Key Largo, said the affluent club’s medical center received the vaccines through the Baptist Health hospital as part of the governor’s program to vaccinate communities with a populations of people 65 and older. County spokeswoman Kristen Livengood said the allocations were coordinated through Baptist and the state of Florida.</p>
<p>In recent weeks, other reports have surfaced of wealthy retirement communities getting exclusive access to vaccine doses through pop-up vaccine sites. Democrats have criticized him for choosing those places, but the governor’s office has noted that more than half of them have been in Democratic stronghold counties of Broward and Palm Beach. Supporters of DeSantis say he has also coordinated clinics with faith-based groups in underserved areas.</p>
<p>Jared Moskowitz, a Democrat and the state&#8217;s director of the Division of Emergency Management, said the administration is working “diligently” to increase vaccine access in underserved communities.</p>
<p>After Publix was made the sole distributor of vaccines in Palm Beach County in late January, the mayors of predominately Black farming communities in the area urged the governor to reconsider, and the state set up a vaccine station shortly after.</p>
<p>While critics point to disparities in vaccine distributions as a call for more outreach into underserved areas of the state, including in communities of color and impoverished neighborhoods, DeSantis noted that &#8220;demand was relatively tepid in FEMA sites in Miami, Tampa, Orlando and Jacksonville. The governor said the four sites had the capacity to administer 12,000 doses but only vaccinated 6,500 people.</p>
<p>—-</p>
<p>A previous version of the story erroneously reported the donation amount given by former Illinois Gov. Bruce Rauner to the Florida governor&#8217;s campaign committee.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875989</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Ron_DeSantis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9869b8c4-f2be-4b0b-954e-a8840c8a45ba/f4320913-c238-4fde-b63e-3c996e3f9730/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217159~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9869b8c4-f2be-4b0b-954e-a8840c8a45ba/f4320913-c238-4fde-b63e-3c996e3f9730/main.mp4*~hmac=a5f6f5a53ecdddd677dba160e875c5b26dbadd57e09fa6d723520039961c103a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Ron_DeSantis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Ron_DeSantis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210304_Ron_DeSantis</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 6K new cases of COVID-19 on Wednesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-6k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-wednesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.92 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,267 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Wednesday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.92 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,267 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Wednesday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,924,114 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 6,014 from Tuesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 132 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 414,776 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 196,771 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 121,652, and 5,911 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,024 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875252</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New mass vaccination site at MDC North opens</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-opens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 13:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A new federal mass vaccination site has opened at Miami-Dade College’s North Campus in an effort to get the vaccine to people who need it...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new federal mass vaccination site has opened at Miami-Dade College’s North Campus in an effort to get the vaccine to people who need it the most.</p>
<p>The site opened on Wednesday and will operate from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m. each day.</p>
<p>“This is an eight-week mission, as of right now, and we have 2,000 to 3,000 every day,” said Florida Division of Emergency Management spokesperson Bruce Roberts. &#8220;We are doing close to 40 to 50 vaccinations at a time.&#8221;</p>
<p>On Wednesday, site officials said 1,500 vaccine doses were administered. Site officials at around noon said about 800 people have been vaccinated just on Thursday alone.</p>
<p>The corner of Miami Dade College’s North campus parking lot is one of the first sites in South Florida where people can pick what vaccine they want to receive: Pfizer or Johnson and Johnson.</p>
<p>“I’m very grateful, and I’m very appreciative,” said recipient Michelle Demel.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s definitely a big relief,&#8221; said another recipient.</p>
<p>Demel opted for the Johnson and Johnson vaccine due to it being a single dose.</p>
<p>“I just wanted it done. I wanted it over,” Demel said.</p>
<p>&#8220;I heard that this did not have a lot of side effects. It&#8217;s a one-time shot, I don&#8217;t like taking medicines. One-time shot, so I choose to take it,&#8221; said Nevalea Lewis, who got the Johnson and Johnson vaccine.</p>
<p>&#8220;I figured it&#8217;s one shot and I know that I&#8217;d be covered,&#8221; said Shaun Baldie, who got the Johnson and Johnson vaccine.</p>
<p>While others in line chose the two-dose Pfizer.</p>
<p>“Important to me because I don’t want to catch that virus. That’s why I came to take it,” said Pfizer recipient Nathaniel Hughley.</p>
<p>As of Wednesday, anyone in Florida 65 and older is eligible to receive a COVID-19 vaccine as well as first responders at least 50 years old and all teachers.</p>
<p>The state is also allowing anyone 18 years and older with a severe underlying health condition to receive the vaccine if they <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fill out a form</a> and have it signed by their healthcare provider.</p>
<p>&#8220;If you&#8217;re 65 and over, if you meet the other criteria &#8212; firefighter, law enforcement 50 and over, or a school teacher or employee, or the medically vulnerable with the form &#8212; you can come here and get vaccinated and hopefully get in and out very quickly,&#8221; said Mike Jachles with the Florida Division of Emergency Management.</p>
<p>The federally run site doesn’t require appointments, but people are urged to pre-register to reserve their place in line.</p>
<p>Those walking away fully immunized said for them, there’s no returning to pre-pandemic life just yet.</p>
<p>“We’re going to keep wearing our mask and keeping our distance from people until everyone just hopefully gets vaccinated. Maybe by the summer we can get on a road trip or something and get away for a while,” said Pfizer recipient Peggy Rice.</p>
<p>Denise Walker, who received her second Pfizer vaccine, said following safety guidelines is still important.</p>
<p>&#8220;We still have to practice that and respect other people who haven&#8217;t had the shot,&#8221; said Walker.</p>
<p>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis spoke at a media conference in Citrus County, discussing the possibility of expanding access to the vaccine soon.</p>
<p>&#8220;The age-based approach we think is the most effective to reduce mortality,&#8221; said DeSantis. &#8220;At the same time, the federal government is the one sending us the vaccine. If they want it to be for all ages, then they have the ability to go and do that.&#8221;</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign, <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>. The form can also be found below.</p>
<div class="sunbeam-pdf" data-url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">
	<a title="Open PDF in new window" href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank">
		<div class="sunbeam-pdf-canvas-wrap">
			<canvas class="sunbeam-pdf-canvas"></canvas>
		</div>
	</a>
	<div class="sunbeam-pdf-toolbar">
		<a title="Open PDF in new window" class="button sunbeam-pdf-download" href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank">Download</a>
		<div class="sunbeam-pdf-navigation hidden">
			<button class="sunbeam-pdf-navigation-prev disabled">Previous</button>
			<button class="sunbeam-pdf-navigation-next">Next</button>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>

<p>&#8212;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874947</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7dddd654-7333-4df8-aa0a-7f3ad684e403/30b2c631-d0d8-40b9-9d62-aa262b305c9a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216685~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7dddd654-7333-4df8-aa0a-7f3ad684e403/30b2c631-d0d8-40b9-9d62-aa262b305c9a/main.mp4*~hmac=c5dcb8218842304908e80e1d787f9c6f2402fba728c14bc1e4c08af9f0bd8a67' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New mass vaccination site at MDC North set to open on Wednesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-set-to-open-on-wednesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 22:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A new federal mass vaccination site at Miami-Dade College&#8217;s North Campus is scheduled to open on Wednesday, and officials said the site is a great...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new federal mass vaccination site at Miami-Dade College&#8217;s North Campus is scheduled to open on Wednesday, and officials said the site is a great way to get the vaccine to people who need it the most.</p>
<p>Dozens of National Guard members could be seen at the site on Tuesday, and officials said the site will administer 2,000 doses every day. The Federal Emergency Management Agency has also released photos of the vaccine arriving to the new site.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are glad, and we are proud to have this site right here at the north campus to be able to reach so many people that need access to this vaccine,&#8221; MDC North Interim President Fermin Vazquez said.</p>
<p>&#8220;We will be doing the Pfizer and Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine here starting tomorrow,&#8221; Florida Division of Emergency Management spokesperson Bruce Roberts said.</p>
<p>Following two executive orders from Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, Jackson Health, Miami-Dade&#8217;s largest public hospital, expanded requirements for who can receive the vaccine. The healthcare system announced they will start to schedule appointments for anyone over 50 years old with a doctor&#8217;s note.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are no longer just going with the 13 medical conditions that the CDC recommended,&#8221; Jackson Health CEO Carlos Migoya said. &#8220;As of tomorrow, anyone over 50 years of age will need a doctor&#8217;s note, who, under the doctor&#8217;s recommendation, this patient has medical conditions that are high risk if infected by COVID, and therefore, the doctor is recommending vaccination.&#8221;</p>
<p>DeSantis defended Florida&#8217;s response to the pandemic during his State of the State address on Tuesday.</p>
<p>&#8220;The cases and hospitalizations for seniors in Florida have plummeted as vaccinations have increased,&#8221; DeSantis said. &#8220;Since Jan. 30, the number of seniors hospitalized for COVID has declined by 80%, and cases amongst seniors have declined by 71%. Florida was right to prioritize the elderly. Seniors first works.&#8221;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Overtown Youth Center is up and running and open seven days a week from 8:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. with no appointment necessary.</p>
<p>&#8220;We’re providing a very precious resource like vaccinations to an area that, historically, has not had the same amount of resources as other places,&#8221; Overtown Youth Center Director Gerardo Castillo said.</p>
<p>Officials said they have the capacity to give out 200 shots per day, but they have so far administered only about half.</p>
<p>&#8220;People being able to see a COVID vaccination site in an African American community. It’s monumental,&#8221; Overtown Youth Center CEO Tina Brown said.</p>
<p>In about three weeks, officials at the MDC North vaccination site said they will distribute 5,000 doses of the vaccine every day.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874522</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-mdc-north-vaccine-site.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/525f03e2-c0a8-44f0-b091-362445fe94bb/ae34e30f-269e-4c96-acbd-b296a8bba20f/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216688~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/525f03e2-c0a8-44f0-b091-362445fe94bb/ae34e30f-269e-4c96-acbd-b296a8bba20f/main.mp4*~hmac=60b3309b1a1eeffce63b5ad3eead85952b065d89e3eaad780614876c7ff5111a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-mdc-north-vaccine-site.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-mdc-north-vaccine-site.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030221 mdc north vaccine site</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden vows enough vaccine for all US adults by end of May</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/biden-vows-enough-vaccine-for-all-us-adults-by-end-of-may/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 21:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874548</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said the U.S. expects to take delivery of enough coronavirus vaccine for all adults by the end of May...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said the U.S. expects to take delivery of enough coronavirus vaccine for all adults by the end of May — two months earlier than anticipated — and he pushed states to get at least one shot into the arms of teachers by the end of March to hasten school reopenings.</p>
<p>Biden also announced Tuesday that drugmaker Merck will help produce rival Johnson &amp; Johnson’s newly approved one-shot vaccine, likening the partnership between the two drug companies to the spirit of national cooperation during World War II.</p>
<p>“We’re now on track to have enough vaccine supply for every adult in America by the end of May,” Biden said.</p>
<p>Despite the stepped-up pace of vaccine production, the work of inoculating Americans could extend well into the summer, officials said, depending both on the government’s capacity to deliver doses and Americans’ willingness to roll up their sleeves.</p>
<p>Biden’s announcements quickly raised expectations for when the nation could safely emerge from the pandemic with the promise of speedier vaccinations, but even as he expressed optimism, Biden quickly tempered the outlook for a return to life as it was before the virus hit.</p>
<p>“I’ve been cautioned not to give an answer to that because we don’t know for sure,” Biden said, before saying his hope for a return to normal was sometime before “this time next year.”</p>
<p>As Biden spoke, states across the country were moving to relax virus-related restrictions. This despite the objections of the White House and the nation&#8217;s top infectious disease expert, Dr. Anthony Fauci, who have warned against any relaxation of virus protocols until more Americans are vaccinated.</p>
<p>In Texas, GOP Gov. Greg Abbott moved to lift his state’s mask-wearing mandate and a host of other limitations. Michigan’s Democratic Gov. Gretchen Whitmer eased capacity limits on restaurants and both public and residential gatherings.</p>
<p>Fauci has previously said the nation must achieve a vaccination rate of about 80% to reach “herd immunity.&#8221; Only about 8% of the population has been fully vaccinated, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, though the pace of vaccination has been increasing. The U.S. set a new daily record for injections last Thursday and Friday.</p>
<p>In hopes of increasing vaccinations even further. the Biden administration told governors to make preparations to administer even more doses in the coming weeks. More shots are also headed toward the federally backed program to administer doses in retail pharmacies, which federal officials believe can double or triple their pace of vaccination.</p>
<p>More than 800,000 doses of the J&amp;J vaccine will also be distributed this week to pharmacies, on top of the 2.4 million they are now getting from Pfizer and Moderna.</p>
<p>Those pharmacies will be key in getting the vaccines into the arms of teachers — particularly in the roughly 20 states where they have not been prioritized for shots. The aim is to help reopen schools to better educate students who have been at risk of falling behind during the pandemic and reduce the burden on parents who have had to choose between childcare and a job.</p>
<p>&#8220;Let’s treat in-person learning as the essential service that it is,&#8221; Biden said. Teachers will be able to sign up directly through participating retail pharmacies, the administration said.</p>
<p>White House press secretary Jen Psaki also announced Tuesday that the federal government was increasing supply of the Moderna and Pfizer vaccines to states next week to 15.2 million doses per week, up from 14.5 million previously. States will also receive 2.8 million doses of the J&amp;J shot this week.</p>
<p>On a call with governors Tuesday, White House coronavirus coordinator Jeff Zients said states should prepare to administer 16 million to 17 million total weekly doses of Pfizer and Moderna vaccines by the end of March, climbing to 17 million to 18 million weekly by early April. The supply of J&amp;J doses to states, expected to dip after the initial shipment this week, will climb to 4 million to 6 million weekly doses by the end of March and 5 million to 6 million doses weekly through the end of April.</p>
<p>Officials have said J&amp;J faced unexpected production issues with its vaccine and produced only 3.9 million doses before being cleared for emergency use authorization on Saturday. The company has promised to deliver 100 million doses by the end of June.</p>
<p>Before the approval of the J&amp;J shot, Biden had suggested that it would take until the end of July to have enough vaccine for every adult in the U.S.</p>
<p>Facing questions about the company&#8217;s slipping delivery schedule, J&amp;J Vice President Richard Nettles told lawmakers on Capitol Hill last week that the company had faced “significant challenges” because of its “highly complex” manufacturing process.</p>
<p>Psaki said that an &#8220;across-the-administration effort” was required to get the two historic rivals to work together on the vaccines, even though conversations between J&amp;J and Merck have been going on for months.</p>
<p>“There’s a difference between conversations and it moving forward,” she said.</p>
<p>The White House said Merck would devote two plants to the production process. One would make the vaccine and the other would handle inserting the vaccine into vials and ensuring strict quality controls. Psaki said the Biden administration was using its powers under the Defense Production Act to help Merck retool to work on the production.</p>
<p>Still it was not immediately clear when the effect of Merck’s assistance would be reflected in supply. Federal officials have cautioned that setting up the highly specialized manufacturing lines to produce vaccines would take months.</p>
<p>Compared to the two-dose versions produced by Moderna and Pfizer, the J&amp;J vaccine is less resource-intensive to distribute and administer, making it critical for U.S. plans to spread vaccinations around the world — but only once Americans are inoculated. The J&amp;J vaccine can be stored for months at refrigerated temperatures, rather than frozen, and doesn’t require patients to return for a second dose three or four weeks later.</p>
<p>J&amp;J has set up a global production network that includes brewing bulk vaccine at its Janssen facility in the Netherlands, and with a company in the U.S., Emergent BioSolutions, and another in India, Biological E. Ltd. Other contract manufacturers are lined up to help with later steps, including putting the vaccine into vials, in the U.S., Italy, Spain and South Africa.</p>
<p>In the scramble to create COVID-19 vaccines, the three Western drug makers who’ve dominated the vaccine industry for decades — Merck &amp; Co., Sanofi and GlaxoSmithKline — surprisingly all fell short. Merck halted its own plans to develop a coronavirus vaccine earlier this year, finding that their candidates were generating an inferior immune system response compared with other vaccines. It said it would instead focus its work on developing treatments for COVID-19.</p>
<p>Now, amid the global clamor for more vaccine doses, those heavyweights are helping manufacture doses for less-experienced rivals whose vaccines won the first emergency authorizations from regulators.</p>
<p>Merck has since said it was in talks to help other drug companies with vaccine production, but wouldn’t say Tuesday whether other deals are imminent.</p>
<p>“Merck remains steadfast in our commitment to contribute to the global response to the pandemic and to preparing to address future pandemics,” the Kenilworth, New Jersey-based company said in a statement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874548</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/biden-march-2.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/17b31de2-dc43-40dd-9c89-efdc1be07614/23a72bd6-108b-48b5-a325-bc87f6169928/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219617~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/17b31de2-dc43-40dd-9c89-efdc1be07614/23a72bd6-108b-48b5-a325-bc87f6169928/main.mp4*~hmac=27698a0e97948f7bf183b349f5f8185fb043eb3cb88711c6fd7e917051d60f7f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/biden-march-2.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/biden-march-2.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">biden</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas becomes biggest US state to lift COVID-19 mask mandate</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/texas-becomes-biggest-us-state-to-lift-covid-19-mask-mandate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Chalvire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 19:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas is lifting its mask mandate, Gov. Greg Abbott said Tuesday, making it the largest state to end an order intended...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas is lifting its mask mandate, Gov. Greg Abbott said Tuesday, making it the largest state to end an order intended to prevent the spread of the coronavirus that has killed more than 42,000 Texans.</p>
<p>The Republican governor has faced sharp criticism from his party over the mandate, which was imposed eight months ago, and other COVID-19 restrictions. It was only ever lightly enforced, even during the worst outbreaks of the pandemic.</p>
<p>Texas will also do away with limits on the number of diners that businesses can serve indoors, said Abbott, who made the announcement at a restaurant in Lubbock.</p>
<p>The decision comes as governors across the U.S. <a href="https://apnews.com/hub/coronavirus-pandemic">have been easing coronavirus restrictions</a>, despite warnings from health experts that the pandemic is far from over. Like the rest of the country, Texas has seen the number of cases and deaths plunge. Hospitalizations are at the lowest levels since October, and the seven-day rolling average of positive tests has dropped to about 7,600 cases, down from more than 10,000 in mid-February.</p>
<p>Only California and New York have reported more COVID-19 deaths than Texas.</p>
<p>“The fact that things are headed in the right direction doesn&#8217;t mean we have succeeded in eradicating the risk,&#8221; said Dr. Lauren Ancel Meyers, a professor of integrative biology and director of the University of Texas COVID-19 Modeling Consortium.</p>
<p>She said the recent <a href="https://apnews.com/article/texas-power-outage-winter-energy-pride-c260c340f619688dd511cc6645b40a04">deadly winter freeze in Texas</a> that left millions of people without power — forcing families to shelter closely with others who still had heat — could amplify transmission of the virus in the weeks ahead, although it remains too early to tell. Masks, she said, are one of the most effective strategies to curb the spread.</p>
<p>Abbott <a href="https://apnews.com/article/2194972e085fe372225202454d35746f">imposed the statewide mask mandate in July</a> during a deadly summer surge. But enforcement <a href="https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-texas-abilene-9a477ead36d3d70a473f9c02219b09b0">was spotty at best</a>, and some sheriffs refused to police the restrictions at all. And as the pandemic dragged on, Abbott ruled out a return to tough COVID-19 rules, arguing that lockdowns do not work.</p>
<p>Politically, the restrictions elevated tensions between Abbott and his own party, with the head of the Texas GOP at one point leading a protest outside the governor&#8217;s mansion. Meanwhile, mayors in Texas&#8217; biggest cities argued that Abbott wasn&#8217;t doing enough.</p>
<p>Most of the country has lived under mask mandates during the pandemic, with at least 37 states requiring face coverings to some degree. But those orders are increasingly falling by the wayside: North Dakota, Montana and Iowa have also lifted mask orders in recent weeks.</p>
<p>Ahead of the repeal in Texas, Democratic lawmakers urged Abbott to reconsider.</p>
<p>“Texas will experience more cases, more hospitalizations and more deaths,&#8221; state Rep. Richard Peña Raymond, a Democrat from the border city of Laredo, told Abbott in a letter Monday.</p>
<p>Laredo, whose population is predominately Latino, has endured some of the worst outbreaks of the pandemic, running out of beds in hospital intensive care units as recently as January. The international trade hub has been among Texas&#8217; most aggressive cities in trying to blunt the spread of the virus, taking measures that have included curfews.</p>
<p>“Elected by the people, your most fundamental obligation is their health and safety. Please do not abrogate your duty,&#8221; Raymond said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874410</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/040320-mask-drop-off.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/040320-mask-drop-off.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/040320-mask-drop-off.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">040320 mask drop off</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 7K new cases of COVID-19 on Tuesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-7k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-tuesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 19:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,135 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Tuesday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,135 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Tuesday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,918,100 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 7,179 from Monday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 136 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 412,908 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 196,114 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 121,226, and 5,892 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,731 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874386</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No appointment necessary for COVID-19 vaccines at Overtown Youth Center</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/no-appointment-necessary-for-covid-19-vaccines-at-overtown-youth-center/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 19:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Local leaders are expanding access to the COVID-19 vaccine by opening new vaccination sites across South Florida. City of Miami Mayor Francis Suarez and other...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Local leaders are expanding access to the COVID-19 vaccine by opening new vaccination sites across South Florida.<p>City of Miami Mayor Francis Suarez and other city leaders visited the vaccination site in Miami&#x2019;s Overtown neighborhood on Tuesday.</p><p>However, organizers at the site said they&#x2019;re not seeing as many people daily as they&#x2019;d like to.</p><p>&#x201C;People being able to see a COVID vaccination site in an African American community is monumental,&#x201D; said Overtown Youth Center CEO Tina Brown.</p><p>No appointment is necessary for those who want to get vaccinated at the Overtown Youth Center located at 450 NW 14th St.</p><p>The site is open seven days a week from 8:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m.</p><p>&#x201C;We&#x2019;re providing a very precious resource like vaccinations to an area that historically has not had the same amount of resources as other places,&#x201D; said Overtown Youth Center Director Gerardo Castillo.</p><p>&#x201C;For many African Americans who are residing in this community, they feel very comfortable because this site is literally in their backyard,&#x201D; said Brown.</p><p>Organizers of the site said they have the capacity of delivering 200 shots per day, but so far, since opening up last week, they&#x2019;ve administered around 100 shots each day.</p><p>7News cameras captured several people waiting outside of the site, hoping to get vaccinated if not enough seniors or healthcare workers show up.</p><p>&#x201C;If there are vials that are about to expire, obviously, we don&#x2019;t want those to go to waste, so we allow anyone who may be waiting outside to come in and get that vaccine,&#x201D; said Castillo.</p><p>Statewide, <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/desantis-police-firefighters-teachers-ages-50-will-be-eligible-for-covid-19-vaccines/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis expanded vaccine access</a> to police officers, firefighters and school personnel ages 50 and above.</p><p>The new order goes into effect on Wednesday.</p><p>National Guard troops arrived at Miami Dade College&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s North Campus on Tuesday morning, ahead of the vaccination site&#x2019;s opening on Wednesday.</p><p>It will become a federal mass vaccination site capable of administering 2,000 doses of the vaccine a day.</p><p>&#x201C;The cases and hospitalizations for seniors in Florida have plummeted as vaccinations have increased,&#x201D; said DeSantis. &#x201C;Since January 30, the number of seniors hospitalized for COVID has declined by 80% and cases among seniors have declined by 71%. Florida was right to prioritize the elderly. Seniors first works.&#x201D;</p><p>Jackson Health System announced it will offer the vaccine to Florida residents ages 50 and older who are sworn law enforcement officers aged 50 and above, all firefighters aged 50 and above and all K-12 school personnel aged 50 and above.</p><p>Anyone 50 and above with a signed doctor&#x2019;s note on the physician&#x2019;s letterhead or prescription pad with a recommendation that the patient be vaccinated will also be allowed to get their vaccine dose.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/JacksonHealth/status/1366809534006775814</embed></div><p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874361</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/vaccine.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5b7bc621-2492-42c6-8136-f38b30c7cb73/2d48ad49-4713-4d91-bb9d-70b9234792f6/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615220017~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5b7bc621-2492-42c6-8136-f38b30c7cb73/2d48ad49-4713-4d91-bb9d-70b9234792f6/main.mp4*~hmac=3da30efc775a48b2f1ec13e6e2cd8883276012acd8f3dd27812be7dc847a0681' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/vaccine.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/vaccine.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Official: Merck to help produce rival J&#038;J&#8217;s COVID-19 vaccine</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/official-merck-to-help-produce-rival-jjs-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 18:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Drugmaker Merck &#38; Co. will help produce rival Johnson &#38; Johnson’s newly approved coronavirus vaccine in an effort to expand supply more...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Drugmaker Merck &amp; Co. will help produce rival Johnson &amp; Johnson’s newly approved coronavirus vaccine in an effort to expand supply more quickly, a Biden administration official confirmed Tuesday.</p>
<p>The announcement comes as the White House looks to speed the production of the single-dose vaccine. Officials have said J&amp;J faced unexpected production issues with its vaccine and produced only 3.9 million doses ahead of its receiving emergency use authorization on Saturday. The company says it is on pace to deliver 100 million doses by the end of June.</p>
<p>Facing questions about the company&#8217;s slipping delivery schedule, J&amp;J Vice President Richard Nettles told lawmakers on Capitol Hill last week that the company had faced “significant challenges” because of its “highly complex” manufacturing process.</p>
<p>The assistance from Merck was expected to help J&amp;J meet its production commitments and expand supply even further, but the administration did not immediately provide specifics.</p>
<p>President Joe Biden is set to highlight the development in a speech Tuesday afternoon, as his administration now expects to have enough supply of the three approved vaccines to inoculate all eligible American adults by June — though actually delivering the injections could take longer.</p>
<p>It was not immediately clear when the effect of Merck&#8217;s assistance would be reflected in supply. Previously, federal officials have cautioned that setting up the highly specialized manufacturing lines to produce vaccines would take months.</p>
<p>A second official said Merck would devote two plants to the production process. One would make the vaccine and the other would handle inserting the vaccine into vials and ensuring strict quality controls.</p>
<p>The two administration officials confirmed Merck’s involvement on condition of anonymity ahead of Biden’s public announcement. The news was first reported by The Washington Post.</p>
<p>Merck halted its own plans to develop a coronavirus vaccine earlier this year, finding that their candidates were generating an inferior immune system response compared with other vaccines. It said it would instead focus its work on developing treatments for COVID-19.</p>
<p>Compared to the two-dose versions produced by Moderna and Pfizer, the J&amp;J vaccine is less resource intensive to distribute and administer, making it a critical piece to U.S. plans to spread vaccinations around the world — but only once Americans are inoculated. The J&amp;J vaccine can be stored for months at refrigerated temperatures, rather than frozen, and doesn&#8217;t require patients to return for a second dose three or four weeks later.</p>
<p>Ahead of the White House announcement, Merck wouldn’t discuss a deal with the New Brunswick, New Jersey-based Johnson &amp; Johnson to make doses of the COVID-19 vaccine or say whether it is talking with other companies about helping to make theirs.</p>
<p>“Merck remains steadfast in our commitment to contribute to the global response to the pandemic and to preparing to address future pandemics,” the Kenilworth, New Jersey-based company said in a statement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874348</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-vaccine.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8469a0d7-7b1b-4669-a30e-4cefe265f0e1/1dd9d683-ec3c-44a5-a7fe-3c06cd71eebd/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216522~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8469a0d7-7b1b-4669-a30e-4cefe265f0e1/1dd9d683-ec3c-44a5-a7fe-3c06cd71eebd/main.mp4*~hmac=0b026dff9d7fd10e5b819a87d985bd23c6fadaabb7bc71a843fa422d34579cfb' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-vaccine.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-vaccine.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US needs to hold on for another 2 or 3 months without easing up on Covid-19 measures, expert says. Here&#8217;s what&#8217;s at stake</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/us-needs-to-hold-on-for-another-2-or-3-months-without-easing-up-on-covid-19-measures-expert-says-heres-whats-at-stake/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 13:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874151</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Americans have received some good news lately about the coronavirus. But that doesn&#8217;t mean we&#8217;re in the clear yet, experts warn. A third Covid-19 vaccine &#8211;&#8211;...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Americans have received some good news lately about the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2020/health/coronavirus-us-maps-and-cases/">coronavirus</a>. But <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/01/health/us-coronavirus-monday/index.html">that doesn&#8217;t mean we&#8217;re in the clear yet,</a> experts warn.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/28/health/johnson-and-johnson-acip-meeting/index.html">A third Covid-19 vaccine &#8211;</a>&#8211; Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/27/health/johnson-johnson-coronavirus-vaccine-explainer/index.html">single shot</a> &#8212; has been authorized for emergency use and is now on its way to states across the country.</p>
<p>And for several weeks, Covid-19 cases and hospitalizations were trending downward, with several local and state leaders reporting some of the lowest numbers they&#8217;ve seen in months.</p>
<p>In California, Los Angeles County health officials announced the daily test positivity rate is the lowest it&#8217;s ever been. In New York, Gov. Andrew Cuomo said <a href="https://www.governor.ny.gov/news/governor-cuomo-announces-covid-19-hospitalizations-drop-lowest-level-december-12" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last week </a>that Covid-19 hospitalizations had dropped to the lowest levels since December 12. And West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice announced Monday that for the first time since November the state had gone a full day without reporting a virus-related death.</p>
<p>Despite the progress, Covid-19 numbers in the US are still alarmingly high. And they could quickly climb even higher if Americans let up now, one expert told CNN on Monday.</p>
<p>&#8220;We should not ease up, allow indoor dining, big groups &#8230; getting rid of mask mandates. We have to hold on for another two or three months in this condition,&#8221; said Dr. Zeke Emanuel, who was a health adviser for the Obama White House and was a member of the Biden <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/11/09/health/members-of-biden-covid-19-advisory-board/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Transition Covid-19 Advisory Board</a>. &#8220;We&#8217;re still having on average 2,000 deaths a day. We cannot become inured to that.&#8221;</p>
<p>If Americans relax too early, Covid-19 numbers are &#8220;going to reverse and go up,&#8221; he added.</p>
<p>A concerning trend has already begun.</p>
<p>While the number of <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/14/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Covid-19 cases saw a weeks-long steep decline,</a> the most recent seven-day average of new cases shows an increase of just over 2% compared to the prior seven days, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said Monday. About the same increase was reported in the most recent seven-day average of deaths, she added.</p>
<p>&#8220;With these new statistics I am really worried about reports that more states are rolling back the exact public health measures we have recommended to protect people from Covid-19,&#8221; Walensky said.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/09/health/us-coronavirus-tuesday/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Several state leaders</a> have begun to ease <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/04/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Covid-19 restrictions</a>. And on Monday more governors joined that list.</p>
<p>Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear <a href="https://kentucky.gov/Pages/Activity-stream.aspx?n=GovernorBeshear&amp;prId=638" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> many businesses can increase capacity to 60% &#8212; including barbershops and hair salons, bars and restaurants, bowling alleys, fitness centers, movie theaters and government offices.</p>
<p>&#8220;This capacity increase is an initial step where we will watch and see to ensure we don&#8217;t see a corresponding increase in cases,&#8221; the governor said in a statement.</p>
<p>Pennsylvania state officials <a href="https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/gov-wolf-revises-mitigation-order-on-gatherings-and-lifts-out-of-state-travel-restrictions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> they had revised maximum-occupancy limits for indoor and outdoor events and eliminated out-of-state travel restrictions, adding that measures like mask-wearing and social distancing will need to continue.</p>
<p>&#8220;We need to balance protecting public health with leading the state to a robust economic recovery,&#8221; Pennsylvania Gov. Tom Wolf said in a statement. &#8220;We are lifting mitigation efforts only when we believe it is safe to do so.&#8221;</p>
<h3>What&#8217;s at stake: thousands of lives</h3>
<p>But now is an especially crucial time for Americans to stay cautious and practice safety measures, the CDC director warned.</p>
<p>&#8220;Please hear me clearly,&#8221; Walensky said. At this level of cases with variants spreading, we stand to completely lose the hard-earned ground we have gained. These variants are a very real threat to our people and our progress.&#8221;</p>
<p>The highly contagious variants circulating in the US that are <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/24/health/us-coronavirus-wednesday/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">threatening to create another surge </a>include the B.1.1.7 variant, which was first identified in the UK and the CDC warns will become the <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/70/wr/mm7003e2.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">predominant variant</a> in the US this month. <a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/public/downloads/cidrap-covid19-viewpoint-report7.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">One report</a> that recently sounded the alarm said the proportion of cases of that variant were rapidly increasing in parts of the US and a &#8220;major peak in cases, hospitalizations and deaths in the near future remains a strong possibility.&#8221;</p>
<p>Continuing to wear face masks, maintaining social distance, practicing good hand hygiene and avoiding crowds could all help prevent that, experts have said.</p>
<p>&#8220;Really what&#8217;s at stake here, by taking off that mask, by dining indoors, is really thousands of people&#8217;s lives,&#8221; Emanuel said. &#8220;That just doesn&#8217;t seem like a very big burden to save other people&#8217;s lives and maybe even your own life.&#8221;</p>
<h3>Some leaders expecting first J&amp;J doses as early as Tuesday</h3>
<p>As the country works to vaccinate as many people as possible, local and state leaders are expecting their first doses of the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine this week.</p>
<p>Three Federal Emergency Management Agency vaccination sites in Texas are expected to receive about 24,000 doses of the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine Tuesday, according to Lara Anton, press officer for the Texas Department of State Health Services. It&#8217;s unclear if the doses will also be administered Tuesday.</p>
<p>More than 200,000 Johnson &amp; Johnson doses are expected to be available to the state for next week&#8217;s allocation, Anton said.</p>
<p>In Houston, Mayor Sylvester Turner said he expects the first delivery of the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine Tuesday.</p>
<p>&#8220;It certainly will be the best option for our transient populations,&#8221; he said of the one-dose vaccine. &#8220;For example, our homeless population, which is very difficult to get back for their second shot.&#8221;</p>
<p>In Colorado, health officials <a href="https://covid19.colorado.gov/press-release/janssen-vaccine-expected-to-arrive-in-colorado-this-week" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> they expect to receive more than 45,000 doses of the vaccine by Friday.</p>
<p>The authorization of the vaccine will &#8220;make it easier for the state to reach its vaccination goals as more people become eligible in the weeks to come,&#8221; said Dr. Eric France, the chief medical officer for the Colorado Department of Public Health and Environment.</p>
<p>Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine announced the state will receive more than 96,000 doses of the vaccine this week, boosting the state&#8217;s total number of doses expected this week to more than 448,000.</p>
<p>Because of the additional doses, DeWine said the state will be expanding its vaccine eligibility to Phase 1C on March 4: individuals who are living with Type 1 diabetes, are pregnant, are bone marrow transplant recipients or living with ALS, as well as people working in childcare services, funeral services and law enforcement and corrections officers.</p>
<p>The state will also start its Phase 2 on the same day, lowering age eligibility to people 60 or older.</p>
<p>Across the US, more than 50.7 million people have so far received at least their first dose of a Covid-19 vaccine, according to <a href="https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#vaccinations" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CDC data</a>. More than 25.4 million have received both doses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874151</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/coronavirus-2-e1614692097238.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9273aaca-389e-479b-abef-93f3aff575a7/342be40a-fd84-4089-8227-fed629f2eea0/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216647~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9273aaca-389e-479b-abef-93f3aff575a7/342be40a-fd84-4089-8227-fed629f2eea0/main.mp4*~hmac=921186328149ca8962622b132374f1eebb777d15d12bd41dd23a829df2a457c5' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/coronavirus-2-e1614692097238.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/coronavirus-2-e1614692097238.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus 2</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeSantis: Police, firefighters, teachers ages 50+ will be eligible for COVID-19 vaccines</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/desantis-police-firefighters-teachers-ages-50-will-be-eligible-for-covid-19-vaccines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announced he will be expanding COVID-19 vaccine access to more members of the community. Last week, DeSantis mentioned expanding vaccine access...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announced he will be expanding COVID-19 vaccine access to more members of the community.</p>
<p>Last week, DeSantis mentioned expanding vaccine access to more first responders and teachers, but on Monday morning, the governor said he will be making it official.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ll be signing an executive order later today to expand vaccine eligibility to all sworn law enforcement officers aged 50 and above, all firefighters aged 50 and above and all K-12 school personnel aged 50 and above,&#8221; he said during a media conference. &#8220;If you look at those numbers, the law enforcement and fire, some of them already got it because we focused on first responders, you&#8217;re talking about 20,000, 25,000 people maybe. Then with the schools, we probably could do all of that 50 up &#8212; K-12 personnel and police/fire with just our J&amp;J shipment.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Public Schools Superintendent Alberto Carvalho discussed how the expansion will benefit local employees.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re talking about school site employees working at K-12 institutions: teachers, custodians, cafeteria workers, bus drivers, bus aides,&#8221; he said, &#8220;those individuals who have direct contact with our school population, about 8,500 employees.&#8221;</p>
<p>DeSantis&#8217; announcement comes as Publix supermarkets begin administering the vaccine at 136 of their pharmacies across South Florida.</p>
<p>Pedro Lopez, a healthcare worker, received his first dose of the Moderna vaccine at a Publix pharmacy in Miami Shores, Monday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m definitely happy. I just didn&#8217;t want to get the virus,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Lopez said it took a little persistence to secure an appointment, but the registration process was simple and being able to come to a nearby Publix was convenient.</p>
<p>&#8220;It looks like it&#8217;s good news for a lot of people,&#8221; he said. &#8220;Luckily, I got in. I was able to register, register for myself, register for my wife &#8212; we&#8217;re healthcare workers &#8212; and I registered for my parents as well, so they should be coming in later on tonight.&#8221;</p>
<p>South Florida healthcare workers and seniors now have more options to get the vaccine, including at a Walmart in Lauderdale Lakes.</p>
<p>Lauderdale Lakes Mayor Hazelle Rogers visited the site to get her vaccine.</p>
<p>&#8220;We need to get the population out, put vaccines in arms, and that&#8217;s why I wanted to do this publicly, so my community will see that I took my vaccine,&#8221; said Rogers.</p>
<p>Monday night, Holy Cross Health in Fort Lauderdale announced they will be extending vaccine criteria to include people under 65 with certain medical conditions.</p>
<p>The vaccine rollout unfolds one day after the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/johnson-johnsons-covid-19-vaccine-gets-the-nod-from-cdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">got the go-ahead from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention</a> for emergency use for all adults.</p>
<p>It is ready to be shipped out to pharmacies and vaccination sites across the country.</p>
<p>Vaccine doses left a Kentucky UPS facility early Monday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;Supply will be limited for the next couple of weeks following this initial distribution of nearly four million doses,&#8221; said White House Coronavirus Response Coordinator Jeff Zients. &#8220;The company then expects to deliver approximately 16 million doses.&#8221;</p>
<p>Experts are making it clear that they recommend all three COVID-19 vaccines.</p>
<p>&#8220;All of these vaccines are very safe, and they&#8217;re very effective,&#8221; said Johnson &amp; Johnson CEO Alex Gorsky on CNN.</p>
<p>Unlike the Pfizer and Moderna alternatives, the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine only requires one shot and is easier to store.</p>
<p>&#8220;This means we now have three safe and highly effective vaccines that prevent serious illness, hospitalization and death from COVID-19,&#8221; said CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky.</p>
<p>As cellphone video of maskless revelers in close proximity continues to surface, Walensky cautioned that it is still too early to return to pre-pandemic routines.</p>
<p>&#8220;I am really worried about reports that more states are rolling back the exact public health measures we have recommended to protect people from COVID-19,&#8221; she said. &#8220;It&#8217;s not the time to relax the critical safeguards that we know can stop the spread of COVID-19 in our communities.&#8221;</p>
<p>As of Monday, the U.S. has reported 28,614,504 cases of the virus and 513,393 deaths.</p>
<p>Experts worry that cases and deaths are inching higher.</p>
<p>&#8220;The most recent seven-day average of cases, approximately 67,200, represents an increase of a little over 2% compared to the prior seven days,&#8221; said Walensky. &#8220;Similarly, the most recent seven-day average of deaths has also increased, more than 2% from the previous seven days to nearly 2,000 deaths per day.&#8221;</p>
<p>Starting Wednesday, Miami Dade College&#8217;s North Campus will become a <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/mdc-north-campus-among-4-federal-mass-vaccination-centers-announced-for-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">federal mass vaccination site</a> capable of administering thousands of doses a day.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873603</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ron-desantis.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e7c8f07e-42fe-4fa7-a022-c35fb990b6d8/58c8397c-ea87-466f-b289-59ca6ecebd60/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219961~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e7c8f07e-42fe-4fa7-a022-c35fb990b6d8/58c8397c-ea87-466f-b289-59ca6ecebd60/main.mp4*~hmac=dcd95b3f30c53d326ed232721818b3d6760069b0b1865f6571e67ac646f067ad' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ron-desantis.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ron-desantis.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ron desantis</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over less than 2K new cases of COVID-19 on Monday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-less-than-2k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-monday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,999 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Monday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,999 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Monday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,910,921confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 1,700 from Sunday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 147 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 410,952 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 195,217 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 120,868, and 5,861 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,426 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873633</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070657_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070657_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070657_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Johnson &#038; Johnson&#8217;s COVID-19 vaccine gets the nod from CDC</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/johnson-johnsons-covid-19-vaccine-gets-the-nod-from-cdc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Centers for Disease Control and Prevention vaccine advisers voted Sunday to recommend the Johnson &#38; Johnson COVID-19 vaccine for the US, and CDC...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Centers for Disease Control and Prevention vaccine advisers voted Sunday to recommend the Johnson &amp; Johnson COVID-19 vaccine for the US, and CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky almost immediately signed off on the recommendation.</p>
<p>It is the first of the three authorized COVID-19 vaccines that comes in a single dose.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Janssen vaccine has been shown to be safe and effective in preventing severe COVID-19 illness, hospitalization, and death,&#8221; Walensky said in a statement.</p>
<p>&#8220;This vaccine is also another important tool in our toolbox to equitably vaccinate as many people as possible, as quickly as possible,&#8221; she added.</p>
<p>&#8220;As a one-dose vaccine, people do not have to return for a second dose to be protected. In addition, this vaccine does not need to be kept in a freezer and can be stored at refrigerated temperatures — so it is easy to transport and store and allows for expanded availability in most community settings and mobile sites, as supply scales up.&#8221;</p>
<p>The US Food and Drug Administration <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/johnson-johnsons-1-dose-shot-cleared-giving-us-3rd-covid-19-vaccine/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">authorized the J&amp;J vaccine</a> on Saturday.</p>
<p>The CDC&#8217;s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices is a group of vaccine and public health experts that helps set guidelines for the CDC concerning the best practices with vaccinations. Members voted unanimously, with one recusal for a potential conflict of interest, to recommend the vaccine. They did not make any recommendations about specific groups who should receive the vaccine.</p>
<p>Now the federal government may then begin distributing the 3.9 million available doses of the vaccine, perhaps as soon as Monday.</p>
<p>&#8220;I just want to state explicitly how very grateful I am that we now have three highly effective vaccines,&#8221; said ACIP member Dr. Matthew Daley of the Institute for Health Research with Kaiser Permanente Colorado.</p>
<p>The company has pledged to have 20 million doses available by the end of March and 100 million doses by summer.</p>
<p>The vaccine, made by Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s Janssen vaccine arm, can be kept at regular refrigerator temperatures, which experts said would make it much easier to distribute than vaccines made by Moderna and Pfizer/BioNTech.</p>
<p>&#8220;During a pandemic, the data show that the best utilization of resources is to employ all available vaccines with acceptable vaccine efficacy. This will save cost and lives,&#8221; the CDC&#8217;s Dr. Sara Oliver told the ACIP meeting. A single-dose vaccine has an advantage, particularly in settings where a second dose &#8220;would be challenging.&#8221; For example, it could be used to help protect the homeless, people in the justice system, and those with limited access to health care like people who are homebound or live in rural areas, Oliver said.</p>
<p>The vaccine was tested in more than 44,000 people in the US, South Africa and Latin America. Globally, it was 66.1% effective against moderate to severe/critical COVID-19 at least four weeks after vaccination, according to an FDA analysis. In the US, it is considered 72% effective, and offered 86% protection against severe forms of the disease.</p>
<p>Overall, non-fatal serious adverse events were infrequent, according to the FDA&#8217;s analysis, and there were no reported cases of anaphylaxis following vaccination in the trial. There have been a small number of severe allergic reactions with the Moderna and Pfizer/BioNTech vaccines. For example, in the first week of the Pfizer vaccine rollout, there were only 29 cases out of 1.9 million doses administered, <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/70/wr/mm7002e1.htm?s_cid=mm7002e1_w" target="_blank" rel="noopener">according to the CDC.</a></p>
<p>More research is needed to now for sure, but the FDA analysis also hinted that the J&amp;J vaccine may help prevent asymptomatic infections.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2774707" target="_blank" rel="noopener">January study</a> from the CDC showed that most coronavirus cases are spread by people without symptoms. If a vaccine prevented asymptomatic infection, it might help reduce opportunities to transmit the disease &#8212; not just keep the vaccinated from getting sick.</p>
<p>There is some concern among public health leaders that some people will think the J&amp;J vaccine is &#8220;second class,&#8221; because its efficacy is lower than the Moderna and Pfizer vaccines, but the experts say it is important that people remember these are totally different vaccines.</p>
<p>The J&amp;J vaccine was tested at a time when there were more variants in circulation. Tested in South Africa and in Brazil, an FDA analysis found that the majority of the COVID-19 cases in the J&amp;J trials were due to variants that are thought to be more contagious.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine was tested against the South Africa variant in South Africa, tested against the variant in Brazil. The Moderna and Pfizer vaccines weren&#8217;t, we are not comparing the same thing,&#8221; said Dr. Ashish Jha, the dean of Brown University School of Public Health. &#8220;When you look at what we really compare about which is preventing hospitalizations and deaths, the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine comes in at 100% once it&#8217;s had a chance to work.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;This is a terrific vaccine and I would certainly, I would take it,&#8221; Jha said Sunday on CNN&#8217;s Inside Politics. &#8220;I would recommend it to my family and I think people who are worried about that headline number, I say ignore it because that&#8217;s not really what you care about.&#8221;</p>
<p>The three COVID-19 vaccines have not been compared head to head, so it would be impossible to know if one is better than the other.</p>
<p>&#8220;These are three highly efficacious vaccines,&#8221; said <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/fauci-i-would-take-whatever-vaccine-would-be-available-to-me/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dr. Anthony Fauci</a>, the director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases. &#8220;I can tell you I have been fully vaccinated with one that was available. It was the Moderna. If I were not vaccinated now and I had a choice of getting a J&amp;J vaccine now or waiting for another vaccine, I would take whatever vaccine would be available to me as quickly as possible.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;We want to get as many people vaccinated as quickly and expeditiously as possible,&#8221; Fauci said Sunday on CNN&#8217;s State of the Union. &#8220;So this is good news because we have another very good vaccine in the mix.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873137</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7caa6db2-d7d8-4cf6-8ba0-e05423b4172e/156d61eb-da9f-4a96-a990-954ebb37df81/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216649~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7caa6db2-d7d8-4cf6-8ba0-e05423b4172e/156d61eb-da9f-4a96-a990-954ebb37df81/main.mp4*~hmac=003309441f7e6e3051f4950e31acd5801de10103f9db80e07f711b91392dba16' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fauci: &#8216;I would take whatever vaccine would be available to me&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/fauci-i-would-take-whatever-vaccine-would-be-available-to-me/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 22:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation&#8217;s top infectious disease expert, on Sunday urged Americans to take any of the three &#8220;highly efficacious&#8221; coronavirus vaccines...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation&#8217;s top infectious disease expert, on Sunday urged Americans to take any of the three &#8220;highly efficacious&#8221; coronavirus vaccines now available to them and not delay getting one vaccine over another.</p>
<p>His comments come after the US Food and Drug Administration on Saturday <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/johnson-johnsons-1-dose-shot-cleared-giving-us-3rd-covid-19-vaccine/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">authorized Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s COVID-19 vaccine</a>, adding a third vaccine option for Americans.</p>
<p>&#8220;These are three highly efficacious vaccines. I can tell you I have been fully vaccinated with one that was available. It was the Moderna,&#8221; he told CNN&#8217;s Dana Bash on &#8220;State of the Union.&#8221; &#8220;If I were not vaccinated now and I had a choice of getting a J&amp;J vaccine now or waiting for another vaccine, I would take whatever vaccine would be available to me as quickly as possible for the simple reason of what I said a moment ago, we want to get as many people vaccinated as quickly and expeditiously as possible.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine is the first single dose COVID-19 vaccine available in the US and is considered 72% effective specifically for the US and offered 86% protection against severe forms of the disease in the country. The vaccine was tested in more than 44,000 people in the US, South Africa and Latin America. Globally, it was 66.1% effective against moderate to severe/critical COVID-19 at least four weeks after vaccination, according to an FDA analysis.</p>
<p>But while Fauci and health experts have touted the vaccine&#8217;s efficacy against the virus, there is some concern among Americans about its efficacy compared to vaccines from Pfizer and Moderna that are about 95% protective.</p>
<p>&#8220;You can understand that type of a concern, but in order to really compare vaccines, you have to compare them head-to-head and these were not compared head-to-head,&#8221; Fauci told Bash.</p>
<p>And while the initial supply of the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine is limited &#8212; the company says it only has about 4 million doses of its vaccine ready to ship &#8220;immediately&#8221; &#8212; it should have 20 million ready by the end of March.</p>
<p>The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, known as ACIP, will meet on Sunday to set the guidelines for who should get the vaccine. Their vote is scheduled for 3 p.m. ET.</p>
<h3>Vaccines and variants</h3>
<p>The J&amp;J vaccine comes as new variants of COVID-19 are circulating in the US, one of them in New York City, that is concerning researchers.</p>
<p>Researchers had told the VRBPAC committee that the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine was tested at a different time &#8212; when more virus was circulating and after new variants had arisen that have the ability to evade some of the immune response. Although they were not able to show that these variants were responsible for the apparent lower efficacy of Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s vaccine, they told the committee it could have been a factor.</p>
<p>The Pfizer and Moderna vaccines have shown to protect against some variants, but the companies are also racing to get ahead of virus variants by testing new booster and variant-specific vaccines.</p>
<p>Viruses mutate all the time. The more people who are infected, and the longer they are infected, the more chance the viruses have to change. But sometimes a mutation or pattern of mutations takes hold and gets passed along. If viruses with such patterns become more common, they&#8217;re called variants.</p>
<p>Fauci said Sunday the variants should be taken seriously and the best way to address the variants is to not only continue public health measures, but to also vaccinate as many people as possible &#8220;because even when you have variants, the vaccines will be important in preventing the spread.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;You get variants when the virus has sort of like a complete field of going wherever it wants to go because the people are vulnerable. If you prevent that by public health measures and vaccination, you&#8217;ll dampen the effect of these variants,&#8221; he said.</p>
<h3>COVID-19 restrictions</h3>
<p>Some states, including New York and Virginia, have begun to ease some COVID-19 restrictions as vaccinations increase. But health experts, including CDC Director Rochelle Walensky, have warned it may be too soon.</p>
<p>There is concern around a recent stall in the decline of COVID-19 cases and hospitalizations in the United States &#8212; which appears now to be &#8220;leveling off,&#8221; Walensky warned during a White House briefing on Friday.</p>
<p>&#8220;Over the last few weeks, cases and hospital admissions in the United States have been coming down since early January and deaths had been declining in the past week,&#8221; Walensky said. &#8220;But the latest data suggest that these declines may be stalling, potentially leveling off at still a very high number. We at the CDC consider this a very concerning shift in the trajectory.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fauci agreed, saying Sunday that the move to relax restrictions is &#8220;risky&#8221; as new variants continue to spread.</p>
<p>&#8220;If you look at that little plateau, particularly in the arena of having variants such as we have in California and such as we have in New York, it is really risky to say &#8216;it&#8217;s over, we&#8217;re on the way out, let&#8217;s pull back&#8217; because what we can see is that we turn up,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It isn&#8217;t hypothetical, Dana, because just look historically at the late winter, early spring of 2020 &#8230; summer of 2020 when we started to pull back prematurely, we saw the rebound.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872919</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/anthony-fauci-e1608817503175.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/anthony-fauci-e1608817503175.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/anthony-fauci-e1608817503175.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">anthony fauci</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 5K new cases of COVID-19 on Sunday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-sunday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 19:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.9 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,852 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Sunday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.9 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,852 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Sunday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,909,221 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,539 from Saturday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 118 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 410,717 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 194,992 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 120,735, and 5,857 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,344 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872845</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chen Senior Medical Center&#8217;s Miami-Dade, Broward locations administering vaccine amid rollout</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/chen-senior-medical-centers-miami-dade-broward-locations-administering-vaccine-amid-rollout/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 01:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[More South Florida seniors and frontline workers are receiving their shots of protection this weekend. Hundreds of at-risk residents, volunteers and health care workers were...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More South Florida seniors and frontline workers are receiving their shots of protection this weekend.</p>
<p>Hundreds of at-risk residents, volunteers and health care workers were vaccinated Saturday at Chen Senior Medical Center in Northwest Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>The center&#8217;s Broward location is also administering vaccines.</p>
<p>The event was created by the center&#8217;s primary care physicians and the Florida Department of Health in order to protect thousands of seniors in underserved communities.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve been going through a lot, &#8217;cause I do have medical conditions, and just to know I got my vaccine, it means the world to me,&#8221; said patient Monsy Martinez, &#8220;and I&#8217;m very blessed that Chen was able to provide it for me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, a scheduled boxing match ended vaccinations early at the Hard Rock Stadium. The site closed at 2 p.m. Those with afternoon appointments were notified to reschedule.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872550</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Chen_Senior_Medical_Center_COVID_vaccination.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c2067e01-6a52-4520-9fe0-f6af0284dc9b/63e93d36-b2d1-4c5b-bb4e-8dc5cef0712c/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219230~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c2067e01-6a52-4520-9fe0-f6af0284dc9b/63e93d36-b2d1-4c5b-bb4e-8dc5cef0712c/main.mp4*~hmac=0fa3a3768b32968a24514e4669576f0a976b21cd7be129806584a0b4fe2cd019' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Chen_Senior_Medical_Center_COVID_vaccination.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Chen_Senior_Medical_Center_COVID_vaccination.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210227_Chen_Senior_Medical_Center_COVID_vaccination</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring break crowds flock to Fort Lauderdale, Miami Beach amid COVID concerns</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/spring-break-crowds-flock-to-fort-lauderdale-miami-beach-amid-covid-concerns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The first weekend of spring break 2021 has brought large crowds to South Florida beaches, along with concerns about the potential for a coronavirus outbreak....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first weekend of spring break 2021 has brought large crowds to South Florida beaches, along with concerns about the potential for a coronavirus outbreak.</p>
<p>Back in the 1960s and 70s, Fort Lauderdale Beach was known as the place where the boys are. On Saturday, it looked like everyone else came down as well.</p>
<p>&#8220;Just enjoying the weather, getting away from the cold,&#8221; said a beachgoer.</p>
<p>Revelers riding in an SUV cheered and greeted 7News cameras as they drove near Fort Lauderdale Beach.</p>
<p>Spring breakers usually bring stress on cities like Fort Lauderdale and Miami Beach, but this year adds COVID-19 worries to the mix.</p>
<p>Local leaders said they welcome visitors to their beaches, but stressed that they have to play by the rules.</p>
<p>&#8220;We understand there&#8217;s a lot of angst to get out and enjoy our beautiful weather and our beautiful beach, but we&#8217;re just asking for cooperation from our college students that do decide to come to Fort Lauderdale,&#8221; said Fort Lauderdale Police Assistant Interim Cheif Frank Sousa.</p>
<p>No alcohol is allowed on the beach, and no Uber or Lyft drop-offs are permitted along A1A , which was packed Saturday afternoon. Electronic signs are in place to remind beachgoers to keep up their social distancing.</p>
<p>Fort Lauderdale Police officers have stayed visible throughout the weekend.</p>
<p>Local businesses echoed leaders&#8217; calls for patrons to adhere to safety regulations.</p>
<p>&#8220;Today we were very busy all day long,&#8221; said Fabio Vaccarella, chef and owner of Casa Del Mare Ristorante along North Fort Lauderdale Beach Boulevard.</p>
<p>Vaccarella said he has been trying to keep up with the crowds and enforcing the rules at his open-air restaurant.</p>
<p>&#8220;The reaction is 80% fine and some people, they don&#8217;t really believe in wearing face masks and don&#8217;t respect sometimes,&#8221; he said, &#8220;We try to do our best to make everybody happy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mask wearing has been sporadic at times among spring breakers.</p>
<p>&#8220;Hotels, yes. Restaurants, yes, but pretty much, bars and breweries don&#8217;t seem to care, and I feel like they should implement it more,&#8221; said Kyle Heusbourg, who is visiting from Minnesota.</p>
<p>In Miami Beach, city leaders are also hoping to keep things as calm as possible, with the beach open from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m. and sidewalk cafes shutting down at midnight.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think we&#8217;re expecting a larger than typical spring break,&#8221; said Miami Beach Mayor Dan Gelber.</p>
<p>There is also an increased police presence on South Beach.</p>
<p>Officials in Broward and Miami-Dade counties are urging revelers to party responsibly or risk arrest.</p>
<p>&#8220;I already had COVID, so I&#8217;m not worried about catching it,&#8221; said a Fort Lauderdale Beach reveler.</p>
<p>&#8220;COVID? I think I&#8217;ve had it, I think,&#8221; said another beachgoer. &#8220;Yep, still living.&#8221;</p>
<p>Officials in Broward County debated implementing a curfew during a three-week period but decided against it.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Fort Lauderdale officials said they will not hesitate to shut down a business temporarily if it&#8217;s caught violating the rules.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872522</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_Fort_Lauderdale_Beach_spring_breakers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ac87470d-8918-4d22-9ba8-4b267b40288d/8c978d0e-b12b-404d-912c-e7e568d3bb71/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219995~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ac87470d-8918-4d22-9ba8-4b267b40288d/8c978d0e-b12b-404d-912c-e7e568d3bb71/main.mp4*~hmac=f03ceecdb5e66f504a6cfeb50f52ec3439589cad6a3d5c833600c65221388765' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_Fort_Lauderdale_Beach_spring_breakers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_Fort_Lauderdale_Beach_spring_breakers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210227_Fort_Lauderdale_Beach_spring_breakers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Johnson &#038; Johnson’s 1-dose shot cleared, giving US 3rd COVID-19 vaccine</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/johnson-johnsons-1-dose-shot-cleared-giving-us-3rd-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 23:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872536</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. is getting a third vaccine to prevent COVID-19, as the Food and Drug Administration on Saturday cleared a Johnson &#38;...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. is getting a third vaccine to prevent COVID-19, as the Food and Drug Administration on Saturday cleared a Johnson &amp; Johnson shot that works with just one dose instead of two.</p>
<p>Health experts are anxiously awaiting a one-and-done option to help speed vaccinations, as they race against a virus that already has killed more than 510,000 people in the U.S. and is mutating in increasingly worrisome ways.</p>
<p>The FDA said J&amp;J’s vaccine offers strong protection against what matters most: serious illness, hospitalizations and death. One dose was 85% protective against the most severe COVID-19 illness, in a massive study that spanned three continents — protection that remained strong even in countries such as South Africa, where the variants of most concern are spreading.</p>
<p>“This is really good news,” Dr. Francis Collins, director of the National Institutes of Health, told The Associated Press Saturday. “The most important thing we can do right now is to get as many shots in as many arms as we can.”</p>
<p>J&amp;J initially is providing a few million doses and shipments to states could begin as early as Monday. By the end of March, J&amp;J has said it expects to deliver 20 million doses to the U.S., and 100 million by summer.</p>
<p>J&amp;J also is seeking authorization for emergency use of its vaccine in Europe and from the World Health Organization. The company aims to produce about 1 billion doses globally by the end of the year. On Thursday, the island nation of Bahrain became the first to clear its use.</p>
<p>“This is exciting news for all Americans, and an encouraging development in our efforts to bring an end to the crisis,” President Joe Biden said in a statement. “But I want to be clear: this fight is far from over,” he added, encouraging people to stick with masks and other public health measures.</p>
<p>On Sunday, a U.S. advisory committee will meet to recommend how to prioritize use of the single-dose vaccine. And one big challenge is what the public wants to know: Which kind is better?</p>
<p>“In this environment, whatever you can get — get,” said Dr. Arnold Monto of the University of Michigan, who chaired an FDA advisory panel that unanimously voted Friday that the vaccine’s benefits outweigh its risks.</p>
<p>Data is mixed on how well all the vaccines being used around the world work, prompting reports in some countries of people refusing one kind to wait for another.</p>
<p>In the U.S., the two-dose Pfizer and Moderna shots were 95% protective against symptomatic COVID-19. J&amp;J’s one-dose effectiveness of 85% against severe COVID-19 dropped to 66% when moderate cases were rolled in. But there’s no apples-to-apples comparison because of differences in when and where each company conducted its studies, with the Pfizer and Moderna research finished before concerning variants began spreading.</p>
<p>NIH’s Collins said the evidence shows no reason to favor one vaccine over another.</p>
<p>“What people I think are mostly interested in is, is it going to keep me from getting really sick?” Collins said. “Will it keep me from dying from this terrible disease? The good news is all of these say yes to that.”</p>
<p>Also, J&amp;J is testing two doses of its vaccine in a separate large study. Collins said if a second dose eventually is deemed better, people who got one earlier would be offered another.</p>
<p>The FDA cautioned that it&#8217;s too early to tell if someone who gets a mild or asymptomatic infection despite vaccination still could spread the virus.</p>
<p>There are clear advantages aside from the convenience of one shot. Local health officials are looking to use the J&amp;J option in mobile vaccination clinics, homeless shelters, even with sailors who are spending months on fishing vessels — communities where it’s hard to be sure someone will come back in three to four weeks for a second vaccination.</p>
<p>The J&amp;J vaccine also is easier to handle, lasting three months in the refrigerator compared to the Pfizer and Moderna options, which must be frozen.</p>
<p>“We’re chomping at the bit to get more supply. That’s the limiting factor for us right now,” said Dr. Matt Anderson of UW Health in Madison, Wisconsin, where staffers were readying electronic health records, staffing and vaccine storage in anticipation of offering J&amp;J shots soon.</p>
<p>The FDA said studies detected no serious side effects. Like other COVID-19 vaccines, the main side effects of the J&amp;J shot are pain at the injection site and flu-like fever, fatigue and headache.</p>
<p>An FDA <a href="https://www.fda.gov/media/146305/download?utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=govdelivery">fact sheet</a> for vaccine recipients says there is “a remote chance” that people may experience a severe allergic reaction to the shot, a rare risk seen with the Pfizer and Moderna vaccines. Such reactions are treatable, and vaccine recipients are supposed to be briefly monitored after the injection.</p>
<p>The vaccine has been authorized for emergency use in adults 18 and older for now. But like other manufacturers, J&amp;J is about to study how it works in teens before moving to younger children later in the year, and also plans a study in pregnant women.</p>
<p>All COVID-19 vaccines train the body to recognize the new coronavirus, usually by spotting the spikey protein that coats it. But they’re made in very different ways.</p>
<p>J&amp;J’s shot uses a cold virus like a Trojan horse to carry the spike gene into the body, where cells make harmless copies of the protein to prime the immune system in case the real virus comes along. It’s the same technology the company used in making an Ebola vaccine, and similar to COVID-19 vaccines made by AstraZeneca and China’s CanSino Biologics.</p>
<p>The Pfizer and Moderna vaccines are made with a different technology, a piece of genetic code called messenger RNA that spurs cells to make those harmless spike copies.</p>
<p>The AstraZeneca vaccine, already used in Britain and numerous other countries, is finishing a large U.S. study needed for FDA clearance. Also in the pipeline, Novavax uses a still different technology, made with lab-grown copies of the spike protein, and has reported preliminary findings from a British study suggesting strong protection.</p>
<p>Still other countries are using “inactivated vaccines,” made with killed coronavirus by Chinese companies Sinovac and Sinopharm.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872536</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8af92c21-d9bf-47f3-88ab-02878d875b7b/6696d06b-b87f-42db-b935-f5d118bcf424/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216617~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8af92c21-d9bf-47f3-88ab-02878d875b7b/6696d06b-b87f-42db-b935-f5d118bcf424/main.mp4*~hmac=6318a3e43db5567c4b454e168451115ef3524987024dbf4ddab7f30e78e94801' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210227_Johnson_and_Johnson_COVID_vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>WWII plane fly-past marks Capt. Tom Moore&#8217;s funeral</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/wwii-plane-flypast-marks-capt-tom-moores-funeral/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 13:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LONDON (AP) — Church bells rang out and a World War II-era plane flew Saturday over the funeral service of Captain Tom Moore to honor...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LONDON (AP) — Church bells rang out and a World War II-era plane flew Saturday over the funeral service of Captain Tom Moore to honor of the veteran who single-handedly raised millions of pounds for Britain&#8217;s health workers by walking laps in his backyard.</p>
<p>Soldiers performed ceremonial duties at the service for the 100-year-old Moore, whose charity walk inspired the nation and raised almost 33 million pounds ($46 million) for Britain&#8217;s National Health Service last year. Captain Tom, as he became known, died Feb. 2 in the hospital after testing positive for COVID-19.</p>
<p>The private service was small, attended by just eight members of the veteran&#8217;s immediate family. But soldiers carried his coffin, draped in the Union flag, from the hearse to a crematorium and formed a ceremonial guard. Others performed a gun salute, before a C-47 Dakota military transport plane flew past.</p>
<p>“Daddy, you always told us ‘Best foot forward’ and true to your word, that’s what you did last year,&#8221; Moore&#8217;s daughter Lucy Teixeira said at the service. “I know you will be watching us chuckling, saying ‘Don’t be too sad as something has to get you in the end.’&#8221;</p>
<p>His other daughter, Hannah Ingram-Moore, said the world was “enthralled” by her father&#8217;s “spirt of hope, positivity and resilience.”</p>
<p>“They, too, saw your belief in kindness and the fundamental goodness of the human spirit,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>A version of the song “Smile,&#8221; recorded for the funeral by singer Michael Bublé, was played, as well as “My Way” by Frank Sinatra, as requested by Moore. A bugler sounded “The Last Post” to close the service.</p>
<p>A church in Bedfordshire, where the family is based, rang its bell 100 times in Moore&#8217;s honor.</p>
<p>Moore, who served in India, Burma and Sumatra during World War II, set out to raise a modest 1,000 pounds for Britain’s NHS by walking 100 laps of his backyard by his 100th birthday last year. But donations poured in from across Britain and beyond as his quest went viral, catching the imagination of millions stuck at home during the first wave of the pandemic.</p>
<p>His positive attitude &#8211; “Please remember, tomorrow will be a good day” became his trademark phrase &#8211; inspired the nation at a time of crisis. Prime Minister Boris Johnson described him as a “hero in the truest sense of the word.″</p>
<p>He was knighted by Queen Elizabeth II in July in a socially distanced ceremony at Windsor Castle, west of London.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872330</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Tom-Moore.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Tom-Moore.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Tom-Moore.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tom Moore</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Broward Health expands COVID vaccine criteria to include people over 18 in &#8216;increased risk groups&#8217; amid rollout</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/broward-health-expands-covid-vaccine-criteria-to-include-people-over-18-in-increased-risk-groups-amid-rollout/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 23:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Broward Health has made access to the COVID-19 vaccine available to all adult patients with underlying conditions. Officials with the public hospital system announced Friday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Broward Health has made access to the COVID-19 vaccine available to all adult patients with underlying conditions.</p>
<p>Officials with the public hospital system announced Friday they will be expanding the criteria for vaccination to include anyone 18 years or older who falls under what they described as &#8220;increased risk groups.&#8221;</p>
<p>Patients with the following medical conditions will be allowed to make an appointment:</p>
<ul>
<li>asthma (moderate to severe)</li>
<li>cancer</li>
<li>cerebrovascular disease</li>
<li>chronic kidney disease</li>
<li>chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD)</li>
<li>cystic fibrosis</li>
<li>Down syndrome</li>
<li>heart conditions such as heart failure, coronary artery disease or cardiomyopathies</li>
<li>hypertension or high blood pressure</li>
<li>immunocompromised state from blood or bone marrow transplant, immune deficiencies, HIV, use of corticosteroids, or use of weakening medicines or solid organ transplant</li>
<li>liver disease</li>
<li>neurologic conditions, such as dementia</li>
<li>overweight or obese (body mass index of greater than 25)</li>
<li>pregnancy</li>
<li>pulmonary fibrosis</li>
<li>sickle cell disease</li>
<li>smoking</li>
<li>thalassemia</li>
<li>Type 1 diabetes mellitus</li>
<li>Type 2 diabetes mellitus</li>
</ul>
<p>This important expansion comes as a third COVID vaccine could be days away from arriving in the Sunshine State. On Friday, a Food and Drug Administration panel of advisers voted unanimously to <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/us-advisers-endorse-single-shot-covid-19-vaccine-from-jj/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">approve the single-shot Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine</a> with final emergency approval expected soon. The company said, once the federal government gives it the green light, millions of doses will be ready for shipment as early as next week.</p>
<p>Broward Health COVID-19 vaccine appointment requests were made available Friday afternoon but have since filled up and are suspended. As of Saturday, there is no word as to when more appointment slots will open. Officials encourage people to check back periodically for updates.</p>
<p>In another sign the vaccine rollout is going into high gear across South Florida, all Publix pharmacies in Miami-Dade and Broward counties, nearly 140 locations, will begin offering the vaccine by appointment only, starting Monday.</p>
<p>Registration for the Publix appointments started Friday morning and filled up <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/slots-to-receive-covid-19-vaccine-at-south-florida-publix-pharmacies-filled-within-2-hours/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">within two hours</a>.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the supermarket chain said they will schedule appointments starting at 7 a.m. on Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays depending on vaccine availability.</p>
<p>The grocery stores are joining a growing list of South Florida pharmacies that offer the vaccine.</p>
<p>All Navarro Discount Pharmacies and CVS y más stories in Miami-Dade are currently offering shots to seniors.</p>
<p>As part of an ongoing federal program, Miami Dade College North Campus will <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/mdc-north-campus-among-4-federal-mass-vaccination-centers-announced-for-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">become a mass vaccination site</a> capable of administering thousands of doses a day, starting Wednesday.</p>
<p>Dr. Rochelle Walensky, the director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, said the clock is ticking to get more shots into arms.</p>
<p>&#8220;Over the last few weeks, cases and hospital admissions in the United States have been coming down since early January, and deaths have been declining in the past week,&#8221; she said, &#8220;but the latest data suggests that these declines may be stalling, potentially leveling off at still a very high number. We at CDC consider this a very concerning shift in the trajectory.&#8221;</p>
<p>To check for appointment availability at Broward Health locations, click <a href="https://www.browardhealth.org/pages/being-healthy-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872039</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_Broward_Health_Medical_Center_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/96504d1e-e506-4f06-acc4-9b3de245cc2c/2e76bbd5-e141-4443-b0c5-6fc4329eb31e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218545~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/96504d1e-e506-4f06-acc4-9b3de245cc2c/2e76bbd5-e141-4443-b0c5-6fc4329eb31e/main.mp4*~hmac=88a0bc088d09d20a6d701afb3613b16e17a0cc843aa3c60f881f5d5146e8951d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_Broward_Health_Medical_Center_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_Broward_Health_Medical_Center_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210226_Broward_Health_Medical_Center_sign</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US advisers endorse single-shot COVID-19 vaccine from J&#038;J</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/us-advisers-endorse-single-shot-covid-19-vaccine-from-jj/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872012</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health advisers endorsed a one-dose COVID-19 vaccine from Johnson &#38; Johnson on Friday, putting the nation on the cusp of adding...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health advisers endorsed a one-dose COVID-19 vaccine from Johnson &amp; Johnson on Friday, putting the nation on the cusp of adding an easier-to-use option to fight the pandemic.</p>
<p>The Food and Drug Administration is expected to quickly follow the recommendation and make J&amp;J’s shot the third vaccine authorized for emergency use in the U.S. Vaccinations are picking up speed, but new supplies are urgently needed to stay ahead of a mutating virus that has killed more than 500,000 Americans.</p>
<p>After daylong discussions, the FDA panelists voted unanimously that the benefits of the vaccine outweighed the risks for adults. If the FDA agrees, shipments of a few million doses could begin as early as Monday.</p>
<p>“There’s an urgency to get this done,” said Dr. Jay Portnoy of Children’s Mercy Hospital in Kansas City, Missouri. “We’re in a race between the virus mutating and new variants coming out that can cause further disease and stopping it.”</p>
<p>More than 47 million people in the U.S., or 14% of the population, have received at least one shot of the two-dose vaccines from Pfizer and Moderna, which FDA authorized in December. But the pace of vaccinations has been strained by limited supplies and delays due to winter storms.</p>
<p>While early J&amp;J supplies will be small, the company has said it can deliver 20 million doses by the end of March and a total of 100 million by the end of June.</p>
<p>J&amp;J’s vaccine protects against the worst effects of COVID-19 after one shot, and it can be stored up to three months at refrigerator temperatures, making it easier to handle than the previous vaccines, which must be frozen.</p>
<p>One challenge in rolling out the new vaccine will be explaining how protective the J&amp;J shot is after the astounding success of the first U.S. vaccines.</p>
<p>“It’s important that people do not think that one vaccine is better than another,” said panelist Dr. Cody Meissner of Tufts University.</p>
<p>The two-dose Pfizer and Moderna shots were found to be about 95% effective against symptomatic COVID-19. The numbers from J&amp;J’s study are not that high, but it&#8217;s not an apples-to-apples comparison. One dose of the J&amp;J vaccine was 85% protective against the most severe COVID-19. After adding in moderate cases, the total effectiveness dropped to about 66%.</p>
<p>Some experts fear that lower number could feed public perceptions that J&amp;J’s shot is a “second-tier vaccine.” But the difference in protection reflects when and where J&amp;J conducted its studies.</p>
<p>J&amp;J’s vaccine was tested in the U.S., Latin America and South Africa at a time when more contagious mutated versions of the virus were spreading. That wasn’t the case last fall, when Pfizer and Moderna were wrapping up testing, and it’s not clear if their numbers would hold against the most worrisome of those variants.</p>
<p>Importantly, the FDA reported this week that, just like its predecessors, the J&amp;J shot offers strong protection against the worst outcomes, hospitalization and death.</p>
<p>While J&amp;J is seeking FDA authorization for its single-dose version, the company is also studying whether a second dose boosts protection.</p>
<p>Panel member Dr. Paul Offit warned that launching a two-dose version of the vaccine down the road might cause problems.</p>
<p>“You can see where that would be confusing to people thinking, ’Maybe I didn’t get what I needed,’” said Offit, a vaccine expert at Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia. “It’s a messaging challenge.”</p>
<p>J&amp;J representatives said they chose to begin with the single shot because the World Health Organization and other experts agreed it would be a faster, more effective tool in an emergency.</p>
<p>Cases and hospitalizations have fallen dramatically since their January peak that followed the winter holidays. But public health officials warned that those gains may be stalling as more variants take root in the U.S.</p>
<p>“We may be done with the virus, but clearly the virus is not done with us,” Centers for Disease Control and Prevention director Dr. Rochelle Walensky, said, speaking at the White House on Friday. She noted that new COVID-19 cases have increased over the past few days.</p>
<p>While it’s too early to tell if the trend will last, Walensky said adding a third vaccine “will help protect more people faster.” More vaccines are in the pipeline.</p>
<p>On Sunday, a CDC panel is expected to meet to recommend how to best prioritize use of the J&amp;J vaccine.</p>
<p>Other parts of the world already are facing which-is-best challenges. Italy’s main teachers’ union recently protested when the government decided to reserve Pfizer and Moderna shots for the elderly and designate AstraZeneca’s vaccine for younger, at-risk workers. AstraZeneca’s vaccine was deemed to be about 70% effective in testing. Canada became the latest country Friday to allow use of AstraZeneca’s vaccine.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872012</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022621-johnson-and-johnson-vaccine.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ca059714-722d-421e-a78e-d2aa0133e24f/d136f9c1-169a-4702-8729-92943b810bf6/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216582~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ca059714-722d-421e-a78e-d2aa0133e24f/d136f9c1-169a-4702-8729-92943b810bf6/main.mp4*~hmac=72c54ba59095ca62a16543f38cb4f374d1d5168704da580d3a93b36966856e1d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022621-johnson-and-johnson-vaccine.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022621-johnson-and-johnson-vaccine.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022621 johnson and johnson vaccine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports nearly 6K new cases of COVID-19 on Friday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-nearly-6k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-friday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 19:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,624 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Friday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,624 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Friday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,898,223 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,922 from Thursday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 146 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 408,096 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 193,560 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 119,911, and 5,799 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,021 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871890</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/coronavirus-testing-2-e1594391327260.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/coronavirus-testing-2-e1594391327260.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/coronavirus-testing-2-e1594391327260.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus testing</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Slots to receive COVID-19 vaccine at South Florida Publix pharmacies filled within 2 hours</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/slots-to-receive-covid-19-vaccine-at-south-florida-publix-pharmacies-filled-within-2-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 18:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Grocery stores are becoming the newest vaccination sites for doses of hope, and slots for receiving these vaccines filled up quickly. Registration to receive the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grocery stores are becoming the newest vaccination sites for doses of hope, and slots for receiving these vaccines filled up quickly.</p>
<p>Registration to <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/publix-to-begin-offering-covid-19-vaccines-in-miami-dade-and-broward/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">receive the COVID-19 vaccine at Publix pharmacies</a> began at 7 a.m. and were quickly filled by 9 a.m.</p>
<p>&#8220;Step right in and we&#8217;ll get you your COVID-19 vaccine, thank you,&#8221; said a Publix employee as he guided a recipient.</p>
<p>Beginning Monday, if you&#8217;re 65 and older or a healthcare worker, you will be able to get your vaccine at Miami-Dade and Broward County Publix pharmacies.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s great for the neighborhood, especially for the senior citizens that can&#8217;t travel far,&#8221; one woman said.</p>
<p>Clara Chiong said she&#8217;s happy to hear the news and wants to get vaccinated once cleared by her doctor.</p>
<p>&#8220;So far, I made it through this year, but my husband and I have been very careful,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>When it comes to access, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis said that it will open up as the supply increases.</p>
<p>&#8220;I would say, without question, barring any problems with vaccine distribution, you&#8217;re going to see the age lower at some time in March, for sure.&#8221;</p>
<p>Publix joined the growing list of South Florida pharmacies to offer the vaccine.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, all Navarro Discount pharmacies and CVS y Mas stores in Miami-Dade started offering appointments to South Florida seniors.</p>
<p>Starting next Wednesday, Miami-Dade College North Campus will become a federal mass vaccination site.</p>
<p>&#8220;It will be administering 2,000 vaccines each day on site and an additional 1,000 per day through mobile units that will travel directly to harder to reach communities,&#8221; said Miami-Dade County Mayor Daniella Levine Cava.</p>
<p>Shots are already underway at the Broward College North Campus.</p>
<p>This new permanent vaccination site is one of three in South Florida.</p>
<p>Oak Grove Park in North Miami Beach and Overtown Youth Center are also offering 200 doses a day.</p>
<p>As the Department of Health reported just over 6,600 new COVID cases statewide on Thursday, DeSantis said he will soon be announcing when teachers and law enforcement will be OK&#8217;ed to get the shot.</p>
<p>&#8220;Within the next 4-6 weeks, we&#8217;re looking at this potentially turning a corner just in terms of how ready access people have to it,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>For those who were unable to register, registration reopens on Monday at 7 a.m.</p>
<p>Depending on vaccination availability, there could be appointments up for grabs in Miami-Dade and Broward counties.</p>
<p>For more information or to make an appointment at Publix, <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine?utm_source=vanity&amp;utm_medium=direct&amp;utm_term=covidvaccine&amp;utm_campaign=PCN19449" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871802</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210213_Publix_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d28b7e9c-00d0-4f61-bc6d-314026406167/2a971ba0-93d0-4137-ac97-da9b0540b50d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216612~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d28b7e9c-00d0-4f61-bc6d-314026406167/2a971ba0-93d0-4137-ac97-da9b0540b50d/main.mp4*~hmac=9c30cd2e9f08e2e1ec2021119b21c6065d9223673582d26a857db785441659d0' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210213_Publix_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210213_Publix_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210213_Publix_sign</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDA advisers to consider third possible Covid-19 vaccine Friday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/fda-advisers-to-consider-third-possible-covid-19-vaccine-friday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871692</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; US Food and Drug Administration vaccine advisers are scheduled to meet Friday to discuss the potential emergency authorization of a third coronavirus vaccine...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; US Food and Drug Administration vaccine advisers are scheduled to meet Friday to discuss the potential emergency authorization of a third coronavirus vaccine for the US, this one made by Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s vaccine arm Janssen Biotech.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s the next step in a process that could end with the new vaccine&#8217;s rollout early next week. As with the two currently authorized vaccines, advisers and federal agencies are meeting over a weekend to try to get the vaccines to the US public as soon as possible.</p>
<p>The FDA has already considered the advanced, Phase 3 clinical trial testing data presented by Janssen and says it shows the vaccine is safe and effective. The Vaccines and Related Biological Products Advisory Committee or VRBPAC is made up of vaccine experts and other medical professionals, industry and consumer representatives who will consider presentations from FDA about its findings, as well as from Janssen.</p>
<p>They&#8217;ll also hear the latest from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention about the spread of the virus, including worrying new variants, and on the CDC&#8217;s surveillance for any safety worries from the currently authorized vaccines made by Pfizer/BioNTech and Moderna.</p>
<p>The VRPBAC will vote Friday on whether to recommend FDA emergency use authorization (EUA), and the FDA will then take that vote into consideration in deciding whether to authorize the vaccine.</p>
<p>On Sunday, a second advisory group weighs in. The CDC&#8217;s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices will look at all the same data and will discuss whether people should get the vaccine and if so who, and when. A vote is expected by 3 p.m. ET from ACIP. The CDC then takes the ACIP vote into consideration and the CDC director &#8212; who is currently Dr. Rochelle Walensky &#8212; will decide whether the vaccine has her agency&#8217;s OK.</p>
<p>After that, distribution can begin. The White House has promised to begin immediately, with 2 million doses going to states and the rest directly to pharmacies and community health centers. The federal government has said it expects to have up to 4 million doses of Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine on the first day. The company has promised to ramp up production to deliver 20 million doses by the end of March and 100 million doses by the end of June.</p>
<p>While Pfizer and Moderna&#8217;s vaccines require two doses for full efficacy, the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine requires only one dose, although the company is testing at two-dose regimen to see if it works any better.</p>
<p>Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s data indicates its vaccine was 66% effective across all global trials in preventing moderate to severe Covid-19 disease 28 days after immunization. It was 85% effective in preventing severe disease. No one who got the vaccine died from Covid-19.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871692</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/fda-e1611765341979.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b24b5d0c-50cb-41bd-a289-c3bf74e450fc/a09dff2a-1d75-4c14-aaba-1c18e751c4f5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216535~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b24b5d0c-50cb-41bd-a289-c3bf74e450fc/a09dff2a-1d75-4c14-aaba-1c18e751c4f5/main.mp4*~hmac=5e94b45a171fe91cf86f0a8d837cac9f3cf26a6a8075c78fecae57fc95d0480d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/fda-e1611765341979.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/fda-e1611765341979.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">fda</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDA approves Pfizer vaccine to be transported, stored at normal freezing temperatures</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/fda-approves-pfizer-vaccine-to-be-transported-stored-at-normal-freezing-temperatures/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 12:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871670</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) authorized the Pfizer vaccine to be transported and stored at normal freezing temperatures. The previous recommendation was for the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) authorized the Pfizer vaccine to be transported and stored at normal freezing temperatures.</p>
<p>The previous recommendation was for the doses to be stored at temperatures between -80 and -60 degrees Celsius.</p>
<p>Thursday&#8217;s announcement relieved some of the troubles with transporting and storing the shots.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871670</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/083120-FDA-building.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/580abf4c-4730-41dd-9bf2-c9e2a87c57b4/7f49c58e-842a-48c3-9f22-18a0666c4ee9/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216524~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/580abf4c-4730-41dd-9bf2-c9e2a87c57b4/7f49c58e-842a-48c3-9f22-18a0666c4ee9/main.mp4*~hmac=ca6b0773051f977bf307acdb001e107b018f8c5713f91123c86c05caee9dbbfa' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/083120-FDA-building.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/083120-FDA-building.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">083120 FDA building</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New coronavirus variant in New York spurs caution, concern</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/new-coronavirus-variant-in-new-york-spurs-caution-concern/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 11:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871628</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — Another mutated version of the coronavirus has popped up in New York City, and experts reacted to the the news with...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — Another mutated version of the coronavirus has popped up in New York City, and experts reacted to the the news with a mixture of caution and concern.</p>
<p>The new variant first appeared in the New York area in late November, and has since cropped up in neighboring states, according to researchers at the California Institute of Technology, one of two teams to share their work this week.</p>
<p>But how problematic the variant may be isn’t known yet. Viruses are constantly mutating — or making typos in their genetic code — as they spread and make copies of themselves.</p>
<p>“Most are not of particular concern,” said Francois Balloux, director of the University College London’s Genetics Institute.</p>
<p>However, he added, “Noticing them early, flagging them, raising concern is useful.&#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because some genetic tweaks can be worrisome, especially if they help the virus spread more easily, make it more deadly or curb the effectiveness of vaccines. Scientists use genome sequencing and other research to figure out which are a potential problem.</p>
<p>New York City health officials and Mayor Bill de Blasio on Thursday sought to tamp down worries about the new variant, emphasizing that the new research is preliminary and little is known about the variant.</p>
<p>“Some variants are just that, they’re variants.” said Dr. Jay Varma, senior health adviser to the mayor.</p>
<p>WHAT DID THEY FIND IN NEW YORK?</p>
<p>Two research groups — at Caltech and Columbia University in New York — released papers this week describing their findings about the new variant. Neither paper has been published or reviewed by other scientists.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2021.02.14.431043v2.full">Caltech researchers</a> found that the new variant showed up in about a quarter of the 1,200 virus sequences they looked at this month. The variant has also shown up in New Jersey and Connecticut and has made “isolated appearances across the country,” said CalTech&#8217;s Anthony West, a co-author of the paper.</p>
<p>On Thursday, <a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2021.02.23.21252259v1.full.pdf+html">Columbia University researchers</a> released their research that scrutinized about 1,100 virus samples from patients treated at the university&#8217;s medical center, dating back to November. During the second week of February, the new variant was identified in 12% of the samples, they reported. They also found patients infected with the mutated virus were more likely to be older and have been hospitalized.</p>
<p>Both groups noted that the new variant has a mutation that could potentially weaken the effectiveness of vaccines — a mutation seen in other worrisome variants.</p>
<p>“There is clearly something to keep an eye on,” Balloux said.</p>
<p>HOW MANY OTHER VARIANTS ARE THERE?</p>
<p>New variants have been showing up throughout the pandemic, but three are considered the most worrisome — they&#8217;ve been designated “variants of concern.&#8221; They were first detected in Britain, South Africa and Brazil but have spread to other countries.</p>
<p>The one identified in the U.K. late last year has since been found in <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/transmission/variant-cases.html">45</a> U.S. states, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</p>
<p>The strain is concerning because it has so many mutations, nearly two dozen. Some are on the spiky protein that the virus uses to attach to and infect cells — and that current vaccines and antibody drugs target.</p>
<p>One of the spike protein mutations is seen in the variants discovered early on in Brazil and South Africa, and, now, the new variant in New York.</p>
<p>A variant that has been spreading in California is also getting attention. It&#8217;s been found in 40% to 50% of samples examined by the Los Angeles Count Department of Public Health, according to Director Barbara Ferrer. But there isn&#8217;t enough rigorous research to determine what, if any, effect its mutations might have.</p>
<p>WHAT&#8217;S NEXT?</p>
<p>After what many described as a <a href="https://apnews.com/article/us-catch-up-coronavirus-variants-4290ca14029d97cdf01446cb32a96e3a">slow start</a>, the federal government in recent weeks has <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/cases-updates/variant-surveillance/genomic-surveillance-dashboard.html">ramped up</a> its genetic sequencing to look for and study virus variants to figure out which ones might be a problem. In the meantime, Ana S. Gonzalez Reiche, a virologist at Mount Sinai’s Icahn School of Medicine, urged caution.</p>
<p>“Without evidence, we don’t need to alarm ourselves about every variant detected,” she said.</p>
<p>Studies are <a href="https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-new-variants-b4d472f3d61c62a57aa68c4aa7c85012">raising concern</a> that first-generation COVID-19 vaccines don’t work as well against a variant that first emerged in South Africa as they do against other versions. In response, drug companies are already figuring out how to modify their vaccines.</p>
<p>Experts say that in the meantime, public health measures like social distancing and masks will reduce opportunities for the coronavirus to continue mutating and run rampant.</p>
<p>“Emerging of variants will occur,&#8221; Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation’s leading infectious disease expert, told NBC on Thursday. &#8220;The trick is when they do occur, to prevent them from spreading.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871628</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022521-ny-variant-e1614253382220.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/174084cf-8f15-44b1-b624-569d192d4109/9023ca58-1faa-41c2-a544-595a5896d923/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216630~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/174084cf-8f15-44b1-b624-569d192d4109/9023ca58-1faa-41c2-a544-595a5896d923/main.mp4*~hmac=68b125a4004a4e433e17190cb2f457b4583c7218c5a9acde4d1b5af76550e2c4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022521-ny-variant-e1614253382220.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022521-ny-variant-e1614253382220.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022521 ny variant</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Publix to begin offering COVID-19 vaccines in Miami-Dade and Broward</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/publix-to-begin-offering-covid-19-vaccines-in-miami-dade-and-broward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Publix will begin offering COVID-19 vaccines to eligible South Floridians in Miami-Dade and Broward counties. Starting Monday, all Publix pharmacies in the two counties, 136...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Publix will begin offering COVID-19 vaccines to eligible South Floridians in Miami-Dade and Broward counties.</p>
<p>Starting Monday, all Publix pharmacies in the two counties, 136 in total, will begin administering the vaccine to those 65 and over.</p>
<p>&#8220;It means a lot to me, you know, because that&#8217;s going to give me peace of mind,&#8221; Pierre Chery said.</p>
<p>Appointments can only be made online and will open up to the public on Friday at 7 a.m. Publix said appointments cannot be made by calling the store or the pharmacy.</p>
<p>The online reservation system typically opens every Monday, Wednesday and Friday morning for vaccine appointments at Florida Publix pharmacies, depending on the number of vaccines received from the state and federal governments.</p>
<p>The supermarket chain joins other retailers, such as Walmart and CVS y Mas, to offer COVID-19 vaccinations in South Florida.</p>
<p>Those who can get vaccinated at Publix pharmacies include individuals 65 years of age or older, health care personnel with direct patient contact, a resident of a long-term care facility or a staff member of a long-term care facility.</p>
<p>Cars lined up at a Walmart parking lot in Lauderdale Lakes to receive a vaccine on Thursday.</p>
<p>&#8220;Everybody should get it, protect ourselves and our children and our grandparents and everybody,&#8221; said Fay Tench, who waited in line for a vaccine.</p>
<p>With more vaccines on the way to pharmacies across the region, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis said more people will have the opportunity to get inoculated. The governor announced more permanent vaccination sites will come to South Florida, like the Overtown Youth Center, Oak Grove Park in North Miami Beach and Broward Community College North.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re looking at within the next four to six weeks that you&#8217;re going to see this, potentially, really turn a corner, just in terms of how ready access people have to it,&#8221; DeSantis said in Jacksonville on Thursday. &#8220;These sites will offer at least 200 vaccines a day. I would say without question, barring any problems with the vaccine distribution, you&#8217;re going to see the age lower sometime in March for sure.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Instead of telling people to be patient, we&#8217;ll need to start persuading the remaining people that haven&#8217;t been vaccinated that they need to be vaccinated,&#8221; Broward County Mayor Steve Geller said.</p>
<p>The Food and Drug Administration will review data from Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s single-dose COVID-19 vaccine on Friday. If it is granted emergency use authorization, federal officials said 3 to 4 million doses will be ready to go next week.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t know for sure how many vaccines that means for the state of Florida,&#8221; DeSantis said. &#8220;We think it&#8217;s gonna be tens of thousands. I mean, I hope it&#8217;s more than that, but at a minimum, we think it will be tens of thousands.&#8221;</p>
<p>Starting on Wednesday, Miami-Dade College&#8217;s North Campus will become a federal mass vaccination site.</p>
<p>&#8220;It will be administering 2,000 vaccines each day on site and an additional 1,000 per day through mobile units that will travel directly to harder to reach communities,&#8221; Miami-Dade County Mayor Daniella Levine Cava said.</p>
<p>Around 200 seniors in Miami received their second dose of the vaccine on Thursday thanks to the city&#8217;s mobile vaccination program.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re going to keep doing this, so that by the end of next week, beginning of the following, all those who were vaccinated for the first time would have had their second vaccination,&#8221; Miami Commissioner Joe Carollo said.</p>
<p>For more information or to make an appointment at Publix, <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine?utm_source=vanity&amp;utm_medium=direct&amp;utm_term=covidvaccine&amp;utm_campaign=PCN19449" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871222</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/publix5.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/15b34ec3-4d58-4b84-a0e8-07d89936e57e/d3932d4f-d5bd-4ec0-9dff-d354d9b2221c/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219639~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/15b34ec3-4d58-4b84-a0e8-07d89936e57e/d3932d4f-d5bd-4ec0-9dff-d354d9b2221c/main.mp4*~hmac=da03d369c6c42750e6c0cb2e46d903b46666f06ce0c84a48a1f656105537a20b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/publix5.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/publix5.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">publix5</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 6K new cases of COVID-19 on Thursday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-6k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-thursday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 19:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,478 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,478 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,892,301 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 6,640 from Wednesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 138 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 406,987 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 192,738 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 119,373, and 5,771 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 78,744 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871173</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
