<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Florida Gators &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/college/florida-gators/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:19:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Florida Gators &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Vols beat Florida 65-54, earn No. 4 seed in SEC tourney</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/vols-beat-florida-65-54-earn-no-4-seed-in-sec-tourney/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878145</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Victor Bailey Jr., John Fulkerson and Keon Johnson scored 14 points apiece and Tennessee rallied from a 14-point deficit to beat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Victor Bailey Jr., John Fulkerson and Keon Johnson scored 14 points apiece and Tennessee rallied from a 14-point deficit to beat Florida 65-54 on Sunday in the regular-season finale for both teams.</p>
<p>Tennessee (17-7, 10-7 SEC) secured the No. 4 seed and a bye into the Friday&#8217;s quarterfinals of the conference tournament.</p>
<p>Fulkerson added seven rebounds and four assists and Josiah-Jordan James had eight points and 10 boards for the Volunteers.</p>
<p>Florida used a 13-2 run to take a 31-17 lead with five minutes left in the first half but Tennessee scored 11 of the final 13 first-half points to trim its deficit to five at the break. Florida missed seven consecutive, and 9 of 10, from the field as the Vols ripped off a 21-4 spurt — including eight points by Bailey — to make it 53-43 with 7:33 to play.</p>
<p>Tyree Appleby had 17 points on 7-of-14 shooting and Colin Castleton added 11 points for Florida (13-9, 9-7).</p>
<p>The fifth-seeded Gators play the winner between No. 12 seed Texas A&amp;M and No. 13 seed Vanderbilt in Thursday&#8217;s second round.</p>
<p>After being outrebounded 18-16 in the first half, Tennessee was plus-11 on the glass in the second. Florida had just 21 points after the break, its lowest-scoring half of the season.</p>
<p>The Gators went into the game leading the SEC in free-throw percentage (.760, 37th NCAA), field-goal percentage (.472, 42nd NCAA) and 3-point field-goal percentage (.359, 78th NCAA). On Sunday, they shot 41.7% from the field, made 3 of 13 (23.1%) from behind the arc and hit 11 of 18 (61.1%) free throws.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878145</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida Gators edge Kentucky 71-67 for series split</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-gators-edge-kentucky-71-67-for-series-split/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872685</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LEXINGTON, Ky. (AP) — Tre Mann scored 14 of his 21 points in the second half and Florida pulled out a 71-67 victory over Kentucky...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LEXINGTON, Ky. (AP) — Tre Mann scored 14 of his 21 points in the second half and Florida pulled out a 71-67 victory over Kentucky on Saturday, winning its third straight game and avenging a blowout loss to the Wildcats.</p>
<p>Tyree Appleby&#8217;s wide-open 3-pointer with 3 1/2 minutes remaining put the Gators (13-6, 9-5 Southeastern Conference) ahead for good at 65-63 in a game that had 14 lead changes and nine ties, the vast majority coming in the second half when neither team led by more than four. Neither team scored again until Mann&#8217;s baseline jumper with 1:49 to go. The Gators cut the lead to two twice after that but two free throws by Mann with 10.5 seconds remaining sealed the win.</p>
<p>Florida, which lost to Kentucky 76-58 on Jan. 9, picked up just the fifth season split in the series&#8217; history, the last coming in 1998. The win was just the 11th for Florida at Lexington versus 52 losses.</p>
<p>Colin Castleton scored 14 points, Appleby added 11 and Anthony Duruji 10 for Florida, which shot 53% and made 7 of 15 from the arc, helping them to overcome a big disparity at the free-throw line where they made 14 of 16 to 25 of 29 for Kentucky.</p>
<p>Kentucky (8-14, 7-8) had a 10-point lead midway through the first half after an 8-0 run, gave up the lead, then reclaimed a 39-38 edge at halftime following baskets by Keion Brooks and Davion Mintz.</p>
<p>Mintz tied a career high with 21 points, Brandon Boston Jr. 13 and Isaiah Jackson and Jacob Toppin 11 apiece for Kentucky, which had a three-game win streak snapped. Jackson had three of Kentucky&#8217;s six blocks.</p>
<p>Florida is home against Missouri on Wednesday before concluding its regular season at Tennessee on March 7. Kentucky is at Mississippi on Tuesday and home against South Carolina next Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872685</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gators ride early eruption to down Georgia 70-63</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/gators-ride-early-eruption-to-down-georgia-70-63/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 23:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868436</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Colin Castleton scored 14 points and Tyree Appleby and Tre Mann each scored 13 and Florida led most of the way...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Colin Castleton scored 14 points and Tyree Appleby and Tre Mann each scored 13 and Florida led most of the way in a 70-63 win over Georgia on Saturday.</p>
<p>The win ended Florida&#8217;s two-game losing streak and marked the first win for the Gators (11-6, 7-5 Southeastern Conference) since Jan. 30. Contests against LSU and Texas A&amp;M were postponed due to COVID-19 protocols.</p>
<p>Florida used an early — and decisive — 13-0 run to build a 20-8 lead and never trailed again. Appleby and Mann scored 12 of Florida&#8217;s first 20 points. Later, Noah Locke buried a 3-pointer with 5:37 before halftime and Florida bloated its lead to 30-12.</p>
<p>Not until Florida removed its starters did Georgia (13-9, 6-9) draw within a single-digit deficit. Sahvir Wheeler made a pair of free throws with 1:44 to go to reduce the deficit to 66-58.</p>
<p>Castlejon made all five of his shot attempts off the bench and Ques Glover was 4-for-5 shooting off the bench. The Gators were 22-for-49 shooting and 20 for 25 from the foul line.</p>
<p>Wheeler led the Bulldogs with 27 points and Tye Fagan scored 14. Georgia missed 40 of its 64-shot attempts, including 16-missed 3s in 20 attempts.</p>
<p>The Bulldogs host LSU Tuesday. Florida heads to Auburn to face the Tigers Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868436</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida beats No. 11 WVU in Big 12-SEC Challenge 85-80</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-beats-no-11-wvu-in-big-12-sec-challenge-85-80/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 23:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=851306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MORGANTOWN, W.Va. (AP) — Colin Castleton led the way for Florida in the second half — on offense and defense. Castleton scored 15 of his...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MORGANTOWN, W.Va. (AP) — Colin Castleton led the way for Florida in the second half — on offense and defense.</p>
<p>Castleton scored 15 of his 21 points after halftime, and the Gators beat No. 11 West Virginia 85-80 on Saturday in the Big 12-SEC Challenge.</p>
<p>Castleton also led the defensive effort on West Virginia’s Derek Culver after he scored 21 in the first half. Culver finished with a career-high 28, but was bottled up late in the game and took fewer trips to the free-throw line.</p>
<p>“I thought Colin was really good defensively in the second half,” Florida coach Mike White said. “Much better. All of us were. Everyone that played, I thought, was a little bit more locked in defensively.”</p>
<p>Noah Locke had 19 points for Florida (10-4), which has won a season-high four straight. Tyree Applebee finished with 12.</p>
<p>“We let them get started. We didn&#8217;t guard them coming out of halftime,&#8221; West Virginia coach Bob Huggins said. “They&#8217;re good. They&#8217;ve got really good players. We just didn&#8217;t play with a lot of aggression.”</p>
<p>Culver made 7 of 11 field goals and 14 of 17 free throws. He also had 12 rebounds.</p>
<p>“Derek and I spent about an hour together yesterday after practice,” Huggins said. “All we did for an hour yesterday were the simple things with his post play and his free throws.”</p>
<p>The Gators went ahead to stay on Scottie Lewis’ tiebreaking 3-pointer with 4:05 remaining. Castleton followed with a three-point play, and he made two free throws to put the Gators up 83-80 with 1:36 remaining.</p>
<p>Castleton was called for an offensive foul with 59 seconds left, but West Virginia committed a shot-clock violation on the ensuing possession.</p>
<p>Appleby made two free throws with 28 seconds left for the final margin.</p>
<p>Castleton said Florida was “just being soft in the first half. We didn’t play hard enough. (Culver) got a bunch of easy buckets that he wasn’t supposed to. I kind of just zoned in on that in the second half and didn’t give him as much of easy looks as he had in the first half.”</p>
<p>Sean McNeil added 21 points and Taz Sherman scored 11 for the Mountaineers. Leading scorer Miles McBride, who had 24 points in an 88-87 win over No. 11 Texas Tech on Monday night, was held to nine.</p>
<p>“We gave up too many points in the paint. We’ve become too lackadaisical,” Culver said. “We got to get back to the drawing board.”</p>
<p>Florida improved to 7-3 since Southeastern Conference preseason player of the year Keyontae Johnson collapsed during a game in early December against Florida State. Johnson is back on the bench but only in a supporting role.</p>
<p>“We’ve revamped everything we’re doing offensively. So that’s taken time,” White said. “When we first came back, we were playing for Keyontae. We were playing on emotion as much as anything. We came back down to Earth a little bit. We’ve gotten to work and we’ve gotten better. We’ve got a ways to go, but we’re obviously better than we were a couple weeks ago.”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators shot 25 of 30 (83%) from the free-throw line. The real difference was in transition, where Florida outscored West Virginia 26-5 in fast-break points.</p>
<p>“Defense to a large degree is about heart and about competing,” Huggins said. “When you don&#8217;t compete, you get exposed. They&#8217;re just not as competitive as the guys we&#8217;ve had in the past. How do you not dive on the floor for a loose ball in a game like this?”</p>
<p>West Virginia: The Mountaineers faded down the stretch and now turn to their most grueling stretch of the season with eight games in three weeks, including five on the road. Six of those matchups are against ranked opponents.</p>
<p>NICHOLS BACK</p>
<p>Florida assistant coach Darris Nichols faced Huggins for the third time. The Gators beat West Virginia in the 2016 Big 12/SEC Challenge in Gainesville, Florida, and at the 2018 Jimmy V Classic. Nichols was a point guard at West Virginia in Huggins&#8217; first season in 2007-2008.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Despite beating No. 10 Texas Tech last Monday, Saturday&#8217;s loss could prevent West Virginia from moving into the top 10 of the AP poll.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts South Carolina on Wednesday.</p>
<p>West Virginia plays at Iowa State on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">851306</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smith scores career-high 27 to lead Mississippi State over Gators 72-69</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/smith-scores-career-high-27-to-lead-mississippi-state-over-gators-72-69/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 04:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=833615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[STARKVILLE, Miss. (AP) — Tolu Smith scored a career-high 27 points and grabbed 14 rebounds to lead Mississippi State to a 72-69 victory over Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>STARKVILLE, Miss. (AP) — Tolu Smith scored a career-high 27 points and grabbed 14 rebounds to lead Mississippi State to a 72-69 victory over Florida on Saturday.</p>
<p>The 6-foot-10 Smith was 11-of-13 shooting and posted his fifth double-double this season. His 6-11 frontline partner Abdul Abu added 11 points on 5-of-5 shooting with nine rebounds. Mississippi State (9-5, 4-2 Southeastern Conference) dominated the paint, outscoring the Gators 52-28.</p>
<p>The Bulldogs led 70-60 with just under a minute to go. Florida&#8217;s Tre Mann scored seven points from there before missing an awkward and contested 3-pointer at the buzzer.</p>
<p>Iverson Molinar added 13 points — he has scored in double figures in all 11 games he has played — and D.J. Stewart Jr. had 11 for the Bulldogs, who made only 1 of 8 3-pointers and 13 of 24 free throws. But their inside scoring and 47-26 rebounding advantage made the difference.</p>
<p>Tyree Appleby made all 11 of his free throws and scored 20 points for the Gators with Colin Castleton adding 16 points and six blocks after blocking seven in his previous game. He is the first SEC player with six-plus blocked shots in consecutive games since LSU’s Jordan Mickey in the 2014-2015 season.</p>
<p>Mann scored 14 points for the Gators (6-4, 3-3), who were missing starter Scottie Lewis (11 ppg) for the second straight game because of safety protocols.</p>
<p>The Bulldogs have won three straight over the Gators for the first time since the 1982-83 season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">833615</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brooks&#8217; return ignites Kentucky in 76-58 win over Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/brooks-return-ignites-kentucky-in-76-58-win-over-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 02:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=827186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — In his first game of the season, Keion Brooks Jr. scored 12 points on 6-for-8 shooting and Kentucky more closely resembled...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — In his first game of the season, Keion Brooks Jr. scored 12 points on 6-for-8 shooting and Kentucky more closely resembled its No. 10 pre-season ranking by throttling Florida 76-58 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Brooks is the only returning scholarship player who played last season, and only until last week was he medically cleared to return to competition after missing the first nine games of the season with a left leg injury.</p>
<p>Although he&#8217;d been conditioning and participating with the team in non-contact drills, Thursday was his first full practice since the injury.</p>
<p>Though topping 70 points for the third straight game, the Wildcats exerted high energy on the defensive end and held Florida to 37.5% shooting (21 for 56) and scored 25 points off 16 Gators turnovers.</p>
<p>The Wildcats (4-6, 3-0 Southeastern Conference) used a 16-4 run to start the second half after leading 35-29 at the break.</p>
<p>Brandon Boston Jr. and Davion Mintz each scored 13 for Kentucky and Olivier Sarr 10.</p>
<p>Anthony Duruji scored 15 for Florida (5-3, 2-2) and Tyree Appleby 10.</p>
<p>Kentucky has won three straight and will ready itself to play Alabama (9-3, 4-0) in an early-conference matchup for the top spot in the SEC on Tuesday.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Kentucky: Will get a chance to further test itself on Tuesday night against Alabama in Tuscaloosa.</p>
<p>Florida: Hosts Ole Miss Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">827186</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida, Mullen sanctioned for NCAA recruiting violations</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-mullen-sanctioned-for-ncaa-recruiting-violations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 17:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=807933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida received a year of probation and football coach Dan Mullen was sanctioned Tuesday after the school and the NCAA agreed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida received a year of probation and football coach Dan Mullen was sanctioned Tuesday after the school and the NCAA agreed to resolve an infractions case involving impermissible contact with recruits last year.</p>
<p>None of the infractions was deemed Level I, the most serious, but the NCAA said the head coach did not promote an atmosphere of compliance. It did not name Mullen, who has been Florida&#8217;s coach since 2018.</p>
<p>Many of the penalties, including reduced evaluation days and number of permissible phones calls to recruits, were implemented earlier this year.</p>
<p>“There is no evidence of systemic compliance issues at Florida, but when isolated circumstances occur they are addressed head on and we accept responsibility for our actions, as evidenced by this instance,&#8221; athletic director Scott Stricklin said. &#8220;It is important for our coaches and staff to remain diligent and take responsibility for compliance, and extricate themselves from potential NCAA violations.”</p>
<p>The case went through negotiated resolution, used when the school, individuals involved and NCAA enforcement staff agree on the violations and penalties. In this case, the group agreed infractions occurred between January and March of 2019.</p>
<p>The unidentified assistant coach and Mullen had impermissible in-person contact with a prospect at the prospect&#8217;s high school in Seattle, according to the report. The prospect had not yet completed his junior year, making it a Level II violation.</p>
<p>“Following the rules and being committed to doing things the right way is part of my history as a coach, at all levels, and I regret we didn’t do things the right way in this situation,&#8221; Mullen said in a statement. &#8220;Even though this is an isolated matter, I’m still disappointed in the violations outlined in the report. We’re going to learn from our mistakes and I’m confident this won’t happen again.”</p>
<p>Members of the Florida coaching staff also had impermissible contact with more than 100 prospects from “seven nonscholastic football teams” when they made an unofficial visit to Florida&#8217;s campus and toured the football facility on their way to a tournament in Tampa. The was deemed a Level III violation.</p>
<p>Mullen was hit with a one-year show cause order, during which he was prohibited from all off-campus recruiting activity this past fall. Because of the pandemic, the NCAA restricted off-campus recruiting for most of this year. Those restrictions will run through the end of the current school year.</p>
<p>Mullen also received a four-day, off-campus recruiting ban for fall 2021. Florida has banned Mullen from recruiting for the first 10 days of January.</p>
<p>Florida ended the recruitment of the prospect involved at the Seattle high school and will not recruit any prospects from the high school through the 2020-21 academic year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">807933</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dan mullen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida&#8217;s Johnson releases video message after collapse</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/floridas-johnson-releases-video-message-after-collapse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 23:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=803012</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida forward Keyontae Johnson thanked everyone for their support in a video message Friday, his first public appearance since collapsing on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida forward Keyontae Johnson thanked everyone for their support in a video message Friday, his first public appearance since collapsing on the court at Florida State nearly a week ago.</p>
<p>Johnson released a 25-second video on Twitter and Instagram and ended it by doing a Gator chomp that showed an IV line still connected to his right arm. He remains at UF Shands.</p>
<p>“Hey everybody, first and foremost, I would like to thank God,” Johnson said. &#8220;I know y’all have been sending your prayers out the last few weeks, and me and my parents are very grateful for the prayers that have been going out.</p>
<p>“To all the doctors and medical staff at Tallahassee Memorial and UF Shands, I just wants to say thank you for all the support y’all gave me, especially the lady that was in the gym at Florida State. To my Gator Nation and UF athletic family, I just want to thank you for all the prayers that y’all gave out to me. Go Gators!”</p>
<p>Johnson crumpled to the floor coming out of a timeout last Saturday and needed emergency medical assistance. He was moved to a stretcher and carried to a waiting ambulance as teammates, coaches, staff, fans and others watched in disbelief.</p>
<p>ESPN declined to show video of the incident. Witnesses said Johnson was standing near midcourt and suddenly fell forward and landed on his face.</p>
<p>He spent two nights at Tallahassee Memorial before being transferred to Gainesville via helicopter with his mother by his side.</p>
<p>Like many of his Florida teammates, Johnson tested positive for COVID-19 during the summer. Although the cause of Johnson’s collapse has not been revealed, the coronavirus can lead to myocarditis, a viral infection of the heart muscle. At its most severe, myocarditis can lead to sudden cardiac arrest and has been a documented cause of death for young, otherwise healthy athletes.</p>
<p>The SEC mandates strict protocols, including rigorous heart testing, before players can be cleared to return to play following positive COVID-19 tests.</p>
<p>Florida has postponed four basketball games since Johnson&#8217;s collapse. The team is next scheduled to next play Dec. 30 at Vanderbilt, the SEC opener for both schools.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">803012</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/121820-Keyontae-Johnson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/267ec425-9450-46db-b81a-728ce46fa829/ada93af8-d92d-4e96-883b-b1786d28e81d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216865~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/267ec425-9450-46db-b81a-728ce46fa829/ada93af8-d92d-4e96-883b-b1786d28e81d/main.mp4*~hmac=0892c76378cebe014a72d4633755c3e339baeb741fe64c41a2a39551575b6b1a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/121820-Keyontae-Johnson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/121820-Keyontae-Johnson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">121820 Keyontae Johnson</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mullen admits &#8216;it would be huge&#8217; to beat Saban in 10th try</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mullen-admits-it-would-be-huge-to-beat-saban-in-10th-try/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 19:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=802743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Dan Mullen’s impressive head coaching resume has a few glaring holes. He’s beaten national title-winning coaches Urban Meyer, Steve Spurrier, Les...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Dan Mullen’s impressive head coaching resume has a few glaring holes.</p>
<p>He’s beaten national title-winning coaches Urban Meyer, Steve Spurrier, Les Miles, Gene Chizik and Ed Orgeron. He upset Florida while he was at Mississippi State and won at Mississippi State in his first year with the Gators. He has topped Mark Stoops in a shootout and Gus Malzahn in a defensive battle.</p>
<p>Mullen’s done everything short of winning a championship during his dozen years in the league. Well, that and knock off Alabama under coach Nick Saban.</p>
<p>Mullen is 0-9 as a head coach against the Crimson Tide, losing every year during his near decade in Starkville. He gets another shot — his first with the 11th-ranked Gators (8-2) — in the Southeastern Conference title game Saturday night in Atlanta.</p>
<p>“It would be huge,” Mullen said Thursday. “At Mississippi State we had a couple times we were right there, had opportunities to win in close games with them, weren’t able to pull it out at the time.”</p>
<p>Indeed, Mullen and the Bulldogs nearly upset Alabama in 2014 and again three years later. Top-ranked Mississippi State, which was a nine-point underdog at No. 4 Alabama in 2014, rallied from a 12-point deficit to make it 25-20 before failing to recover an onside kick in the waning seconds.</p>
<p>The Crimson Tide was the one that needed a comeback in 2017. No. 2 Bama scored the final 14 points on the road, including a 26-yard touchdown pass to DeVonta Smith with 25 seconds remaining, and edged the 16th-ranked Bulldogs 31-24.</p>
<p>Two weeks later, Mullen left Starkville to take over in Gainesville. Now, he’s facing the SEC’s biggest bully again and still trying to close the gap on No. 1 Alabama (10-0) — on the recruiting trail and in the win column.</p>
<p>“He has done a great job of establishing the program, been there a long time,” said Mullen, who did beat Saban twice as Florida’s offensive coordinator (2006, ’08). “When you look at what he has been able to build, the program he has been able to establish through the years, the stability of it, the combination of a very well coached team on the field and they do an unbelievable job of getting great players in as well.”</p>
<p>It’s not like Mullen is alone in his pursuit of Saban. Alabama has won 27 in a row against teams from the SEC’s Eastern Division, every game since a 2010 loss to Spurrier’s South Carolina Gamecocks in 2010.</p>
<p>Coincidentally, Spurrier has an office one floor up from Mullen inside Florida’s football facility. And the Head Ball Coach often offers plays as well as praise. He delivered two mini bottles of wine to Mullen this season, one for beating rival Georgia in early November and another for clinching the East two weeks ago at Tennessee.</p>
<p>Maybe Spurrier might spring for a full-size bottle if Mullen upsets Alabama, now a 17-point favorite.</p>
<p>Mullen’s first step is to get his players to regroup after last week’s crushing loss to LSU and then convince them that Alabama is far from unbeatable, regardless of what the numbers say. His guys seem to be listening.</p>
<p>“I know a lot of times people can get caught up in names and uniforms and stuff like that,&#8221; said guard Stewart Reese, who spent four years at Mississippi State before joining Mullen in Gainesville. “So I tell them, ‘Just treat it like another game. There’s nothing to be afraid of.’</p>
<p>“We’re going for all the marbles; it’s the SEC championship. There’s nothing really to be worried about. If you lose, you lose. We’re not playing to lose, but at the end of the day, there’s really nothing to worry about.”</p>
<p>Added linebacker James Houston: “I’ve never really gone into a game thinking like this team is much more talented or this player is much better than me. … I know what I got. I know what we got. And I think we can go whip your butt.”</p>
<p>No one would love that more than the brash and borderline stubborn Mullen, whose season already has been a roller-coaster ride. Beating Saban for the first time in 10 tries surely would fill one gaping hole on his coaching resume.</p>
<p>“Yeah, you know what, it would be great,” Mullen said. “I don’t view it in terms of that. I view it (as) it would be great in terms of this year’s team for us to go win an SEC championship. It would be really special for all the work that these guys have put in over the course of this year.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">802743</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dan mullen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida&#8217;s Johnson &#8216;following simple commands&#8217; after collapse</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/floridas-johnson-following-simple-commands-after-collapse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 21:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=799813</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida forward Keyontae Johnson was “following simple commands” Monday after being transferred from Tallahassee Memorial to UF Health in Gainesville, the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida forward Keyontae Johnson was “following simple commands” Monday after being transferred from Tallahassee Memorial to UF Health in Gainesville, the school said.</p>
<p>Officials added that Johnson is undergoing further tests and remains in critical but stable condition two days after he collapsed on the court during a game at Florida State. Johnson was moved to Gainesville via helicopter with his mother by his side.</p>
<p>Coach Mike White and head athletic trainer Dave Werner, who stayed in Tallahassee for two nights, returned to Gainesville on the school’s jet with other family members Monday.</p>
<p>USA Today quoted Johnson&#8217;s grandfather, Larry DeJarnett, as saying the player had been in a medically induced coma.</p>
<p>The Southeastern Conference’s preseason player of the year crumpled to the floor coming out a timeout and received emergency medical attention. He was moved to a stretcher and carried to a waiting ambulance as teammates, coaches, staff, fans and others watched in disbelief Saturday.</p>
<p>ESPN declined to show any footage of the incident. According to witnesses, Johnson was standing and suddenly fell forward and landed on his face. His eyes were open and he had blood on his face and neck, according to photos obtained by The Gainesville Sun.</p>
<p>The Gators announced Johnson was in critical but stable condition less than an hour after his ordeal. The American Hospital Association defines patients in critical but stable condition as having “vital signs that are unstable and not within normal limits. Patient may be unconscious. Indicators are unfavorable.”</p>
<p>Florida sent a jet to Norfolk, Virginia, to get Johnson’s parents Saturday and take them to Tallahassee to be with their son.</p>
<p>Johnson’s teammates and coaches were visibly distraught before the game resumed. The Seminoles outscored Florida 80-60 after Johnson’s collapse and won 83-71 for their seventh straight victory in the series.</p>
<p>The Gators had been scheduled to host North Florida on Wednesday night, but the game was called off Monday evening. It&#8217;s unclear if it will be made up.</p>
<p>The school held a moment of silence for Johnson before its football game against LSU on Saturday night and again before a women&#8217;s basketball game Monday. Johnson&#8217;s girlfriend, forward Jordyn Merritt, played in that game and finished with six points and three rebounds in 17 minutes.</p>
<p>Johnson, a 6-foot-5 junior, averaged a team-high 14 points last season to go along with 7.1 rebounds. He also led the Gators with 38 steals.</p>
<p>Like many of his Florida teammates, Johnson tested positive for COVID-19 during the summer. Although the cause of Johnson’s collapse was not immediately known, the coronavirus can lead to myocarditis, a viral infection of the heart muscle. At its most severe, myocarditis can lead to sudden cardiac arrest and has been a documented cause of death for young, otherwise healthy athletes.</p>
<p>The Southeastern Conference mandates strict protocols, including rigorous heart testing, before players can be cleared to return to play following positive COVID-19 tests.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">799813</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">uf-gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 20 FSU tops Florida 83-71 after Johnson collapses early</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-20-fsu-tops-florida-83-71-after-johnson-collapses-early/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 21:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=797505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton told assistants and administrators that Florida could decide whether to continue after standout forward Keyontae Johnson...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton told assistants and administrators that Florida could decide whether to continue after standout forward Keyontae Johnson collapsed and was rushed to a nearby hospital.</p>
<p>Coach Mike White let his players make the call — not once, but twice. With tears in their eyes and their teammate&#8217;s condition uncertain, the Gators wanted to play.</p>
<p>They were obviously and understandably distracted the rest of the way.</p>
<p>Highly touted freshman Scottie Barnes scored 17 points and No. 20 Florida State extended its dominance against the Gators with an 83-71 victory Saturday that came after Florida suddenly lost its best player.</p>
<p>Johnson, the Southeastern Conference’s preseason player of the year, was taken off the floor on a stretcher in the opening minutes and transported to Tallahassee Memorial for evaluation. Florida officials said he was in critical but stable condition and would remain there overnight.</p>
<p>White canceled postgame interviews to join Johnson at the hospital as his players boarded a bus for the two-hour trip back to Gainesville. Johnson&#8217;s parents were flying in from Virginia to be with their son.</p>
<p>Whether the game should have resumed surely will be debated. White let his players chose both times — moments after Johnson left the court and then again at halftime.</p>
<p>“Whatever they thought was in the best interest of their team, then I would accept it,” Hamilton said. &#8220;My administration asked me and I told them we would be OK with whatever they decided. It was my understanding that they wanted to play.”</p>
<p>Johnson, a junior from Norfolk, Virginia, had just dunked in transition a couple of minutes before he crumpled to the hardwood as the team broke its huddle. The Gators were emotional wrecks as they watch the situation unfold, and a couple of them buried their faces in towels as White gathered his team in prayer.</p>
<p>Several Seminoles were in tears as well and took a knee to do the same.</p>
<p>“Those types of things can affect you in some adverse ways,” Hamilton said. &#8220;We’re just all hopeful and praying that he’s OK. If it affected our players in an emotional way, I can imagine what the situation was with his teammates.”</p>
<p>Officials gave both teams extra time to regroup before restarting. The Gators weren’t the same afterward.</p>
<p>Florida (3-1) was ahead 11-3 following Johnson’s dunk. The Seminoles (3-0) scored the next seven points and pulled away from there. They outscored the Gators 42-24 in the first half after Johnson was stricken.</p>
<p>The Seminoles led by as many as 18 in the second half. They ended up extending their winning streak against Florida to seven games, tying the longest by either team in the series. They also stretched their winning streak against nonconference opponents at home to 41 and won their 26th straight at home.</p>
<p>Barnes, Anthony Polite and M.J. Walker made this one look easy most of the day. Barnes, the top-rated recruit of Hamilton’s tenure in Tallahassee, had two thunderous dunks and was 7-of-10 shooting. It was a breakout game for the 6-foot-9 point guard many expect to be an NBA lottery pick.</p>
<p>“There’s no doubt that he showed potential,&#8221; Hamilton said. “He’s showing that he has the ability that we always knew he had. He made pretty good decisions with the ball and he did some athletic things. But as a team we have to get a little better all on the same page so that we could all be a little bit better in sync than we were.”</p>
<p>Polite hit three 3-pointers and finished with 14 points. Walker was perfect from the free-throw line, draining all 12 attempts, and ended up with 17 points.</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Scottie Lewis, who was clearly affected by Johnson’s ordeal, tied a career high with 19 points. Tre Mann added 17 points, eight rebounds and seven assists.</p>
<p>The Gators got little from anyone else. Johnson surely would have been a factor. He averaged a team-high 14 points last season to go along with 7.1 rebounds. He also led the Gators with 38 steals. He had five points in four minutes Saturday.</p>
<p>Like many of his teammates, Johnson tested positive for COVID-19 during the summer. The coronavirus can lead to myocarditis, a viral infection of the heart muscle, and it is common for athletes. At its most severe, myocarditis can lead to sudden cardiac arrest and has been a documented cause of death for young, otherwise healthy athletes.</p>
<p>The Southeastern Conference mandates strict protocols, including rigorous heart testing, before players can be cleared to return to play following positive COVID tests.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: It’s impossible to know how the Gators would have played with Johnson on the floor more than just a few minutes.</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles, who were ranked No. 4 in the country when the coronavirus pandemic ended the 2019-20 postseason, should be a factor in the Atlantic Coast Conference again this year. They have the fourth-biggest team in the country, a dynamic point guard in Barnes and an experienced leader in Walker.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: Hosts North Florida on Wednesday night. The Gators have won all nine meetings between the teams.</p>
<p>Florida State: Begins Atlantic Coast Conference play against Georgia Tech on Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">797505</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida cruises past Stetson 86-39 in home opener</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-cruises-past-stetson-86-39-in-home-opener/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=792532</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Keyontae Johnson scored 19 points, Scottie Lewis had 10 points, 10 rebounds and six assists and Florida beat Stetson 84-40 on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Keyontae Johnson scored 19 points, Scottie Lewis had 10 points, 10 rebounds and six assists and Florida beat Stetson 84-40 on Sunday in the Gators&#8217; home opener.</p>
<p>Johnson&#8217;s dunk started a 9-0 run to give Florida a 16-5 lead, and the Gators led by double figures for the rest of the game. Johnson finished the half with 12 points and Stetson scored 15. Florida scored the first 11 points of the second half for a 30-point lead, and the Gators led by as many as 47 points.</p>
<p>Noah Locke added 15 points and Tre Mann scored 10 for Florida (3-0). Locke was 5 of 6 from 3-point range as the Gators made 9 of 23 from behind the arc and 21 of 24 at the free-throw line. Mann scored a career-best 19 points in Florida’s opener against Army.</p>
<p>Johnson was coming off a 24-point, 12-rebound performance in a win over Boston College. He was 7 of 13 from the field against Stetson.</p>
<p>Rob Perry scored 13 points and Chase Johnston added 10 for Stetson (0-3), which was held to 10-of-51 shooting (19.6%) and turned it over 23 times.</p>
<p>Stetson&#8217;s second-year coach Donnie Jones coached at Florida for 11 seasons on Billy Donovan’s staff from 1996-07, helping lead the Gators to back-to-back national championships.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">792532</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 6 Florida Gators run past Tennessee 31-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-6-florida-gators-run-past-tennessee-31-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 01:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=792028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Kyle Trask threw for 433 yards and four touchdowns, and No. 6 Florida beat Tennessee 31-19 on Saturday to clinch a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Kyle Trask threw for 433 yards and four touchdowns, and No. 6 Florida beat Tennessee 31-19 on Saturday to clinch a spot in the SEC championship game.</p>
<p>Trask, a front-runner for the Heisman Trophy, put together another impressive performance. He completed 35 of 49 passes without committing a turnover. He even had a 32-yard punt late in the game.</p>
<p>Kyle Pitts had seven receptions for 128 yards, helping the Gators (8-1, No. 6 CFP) wrap up the SEC&#8217;s East Division. Kadarius Toney finished with eight catches for 108 yards and a TD.</p>
<p>The aerial performance by Trask and company took on added significance with Florida struggling to run the ball, finishing with just 21 yards on the ground.</p>
<p>Playing with a depleted roster, Tennessee (2-6) dropped its sixth consecutive game. The Vols were missing 16 players.</p>
<p>Freshman Harrison Bailey got the start at quarterback. He completed 14 of 21 passes for 111 yards and a 15-yard touchdown to Eric Gray. He was sacked five times.</p>
<p>Trask has 38 TD passes this season, moving him into sixth place in SEC history for a single season, ahead of Texas A&amp;M&#8217;s Johnny Manziel and Tim Couch of Kentucky. He has the most TD passes through a team&#8217;s first nine games.</p>
<p>Five plays into the second half, the outcome was all but decided. Florida stretched a 10-point halftime advantage to 24-7 with a 75-yard drive capped by an 8-yard pass from Trask to Trevon Grimes. The big play in the sequence was a 48-yard connection between Trask and Kyle Pitts.</p>
<p>Early in the fourth quarter, Florida upped the lead to 31-7 when Trask found Jacob Copeland for a 12-yard TD.</p>
<p>Quarterback J.T. Shrout came off the bench to lead the Vols to two late touchdowns. Ty Chandler ran the ball in from 7 yards, then Velus Jones, Jr., caught a 22-yard scoring pass.</p>
<p>Florida took a 17-7 lead into the locker room at intermission. Tennessee&#8217;s defense turned the Gators offense into a one-dimensional attack — but with Trask behind center, it was more than enough.</p>
<p>While the Gators generated just 1 net yard rushing in the first 30 minutes, Trask had plenty of success. He completed 21 of 28 passes for 251 yards and accounted for both touchdowns — a 4-yard toss to Grimes and a 2-yarder to Toney.</p>
<p>After a field goal on Florida&#8217;s first possession, Tennessee responded. Bailey engineered a 96-yard drive, most of which happened in the second quarter, and topped it off with a TD pass to Gray out of the backfield.</p>
<p>Florida answered with its first touchdown. Then it got interesting.</p>
<p>Down 10-7, the Vols were faced with fourth-and-5 on their own 30-yard line. Punter Paxton Brooks faked the punt and threw a pass to an open Jimmy Holiday. What would have been a first down was dropped by Holiday.</p>
<p>The mistake didn&#8217;t hurt, though. The Tennessee defense stiffened and forced the Gators into a field goal attempt from 53 yards. Evan McPherson missed wide right.</p>
<p>ROOKIE STARTERS</p>
<p>Sixteen Tennessee players missed the game. Freshman Cooper Mays got his first career start at center in place of senior Brandon Kennedy, who moved to left tackle. The Vols also turned to Bailey for his first start ahead of redshirt senior Jarrett Guarantano.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators reached the SEC championship game for the first time since 2016.</p>
<p>Tennessee: The Vols&#8217; six-game losing streak is the program&#8217;s longest since starting the 1988 season with six straight losses.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida closes out its regular season Saturday with a home game against LSU.</p>
<p>Tennessee will travel to Nashville for a meeting with rival Vanderbilt.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">792028</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mullen, No. 6 Florida can clinch SEC East title at Tennessee</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mullen-no-6-florida-can-clinch-sec-east-title-at-tennessee/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 19:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=790583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In his third season at Florida coach Dan Mullen has the Gators a win away from the Southeastern Conference championship game for the first time...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his third season at Florida coach Dan Mullen has the Gators a win away from the Southeastern Conference championship game for the first time since 2016.</p>
<p>Sixth-ranked Florida can clinch the East by beating Tennessee on Saturday, something they&#8217;ve done 14 of the last 15 games in this series.</p>
<p>“This is the game to clinch the East, this is the game to assert our dominance and tell everybody we’re going to the SEC championship, and yeah, I think everybody’s pretty excited,” Florida linebacker James Houston said. &#8220;I don’t think too many people need motivation for this game. We all know what’s at stake.”</p>
<p>Mullen has Florida (7-1, No. 6 CFP) clicking with five straight victories and one of the nation&#8217;s best offenses led by a Heisman Trophy favorite in Kyle Trask.</p>
<p>The quarterback was a freshman the last time Florida played for the SEC title, and winning the SEC East has been these Gators&#8217; first of many goals this season.</p>
<p>“We have a chance to do that on Saturday,” Trask said. &#8220;We’ll definitely be playing at our top level to get that done. It will mean everything to get back to Atlanta. I remember it just like it was yesterday, my freshman year we went in 2016. It goes by so fast. It would be cool to be back there and hopefully get a win.”</p>
<p>The Gators (7-1, No. 6 CFP) have been nearly impossible to stop, beating Kentucky 34-10 last week. As impressive as the performance was, it snapped a school-record streak of nine straight games scoring at least 35 points.</p>
<p>“The biggest emphasis on us is finding ways that we’ve got to improve as a team,” said Mullen who never won a division title coaching at Mississippi State.</p>
<p>While Florida is focused on fine-tuning, Tennessee (2-5) is just glad to play after COVID issues postponed their Nov. 16 game against Texas A&amp;M and last week&#8217;s game with Vanderbilt was postponed by the SEC.</p>
<p>The Vols also have lost five straight, the longest skid since the 1988 team lost its first six to open that season. They haven&#8217;t played since Nov. 21 when they lost 30-17 at No. 23 Auburn, and this skid has fans questioning whether Jeremy Pruitt is the right coach for the program in just his third season.</p>
<p>“We just want to go out here and flip the script, we want to get this train back on the tracks,” Tennessee running back Eric Gray said.</p>
<p>TRASK AND THE HEISMAN</p>
<p>The Florida quarterback has thrown his way into the Heisman Trophy conversation with 34 touchdown passes. That&#8217;s best in the country and tied David Klinger of Houston in 1990 and Dennis Shaw of San Diego State in 1969 for the third-highest total through eight games in FBS history. Trask is second nationally with 351.3 yards passing per game and fifth in passer rating.</p>
<p>COVID ISSUES</p>
<p>The Volunteers have been dealing with their biggest COVID-19 issues since fall practice. Pruitt said a couple tested positive when they came back from Auburn, and contact tracing took out “a lot” of players. Pruitt said they had a couple more positives Tuesday, involving one player.</p>
<p>A quarterback is among those affected, though Pruitt declined to identify who. Pruitt isn&#8217;t saying who will start against Florida.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;ll make the decision as we get closer to the game,” Pruitt said.</p>
<p>KEEPING IT TIGHT</p>
<p>Florida has featured tight ends all season, even without potential first-round draft pick Kyle Pitts.</p>
<p>Pitts has 29 receptions for 513 yards and 11 touchdowns in 5 ½ games this season. He missed 10 quarters because of a concussion and a broken nose sustained during a vicious hit against Georgia last month. In Pitts’ absence, backups Kemore Gamble and Keon Zipperer combined to catch 10 passes for 203 yards and five touchdowns.</p>
<p>Florida’s tight ends now have 43 catches for 755 yards and 16 scores in eight games, more production from the position than anyone in the country.</p>
<p>FAST STARTS</p>
<p>The Gators have scored on their opening possession in seven of eight games this season. Six touchdowns and a field goal, to be exact. They have first-drive TDs in each of their last three games, a streak they hope to continue in Knoxville.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">790583</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/dan-mullen-e1607025435436.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dan mullen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pitts scores 3 TDs in return, No. 6 Florida tops Kentucky</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/pitts-scores-3-tds-in-return-no-6-florida-tops-kentucky/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=787374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kyle Pitts was feeling a little jittery before his first game in three weeks. His chest “got hot&#8221; and his heart...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kyle Pitts was feeling a little jittery before his first game in three weeks.</p>
<p>His chest “got hot&#8221; and his heart started beating fast. Once he stepped on the field and saw one-on-one coverage, his eyes had to widen as well.</p>
<p>Pitts scored three touchdowns in his return from a concussion and a broken nose — all on perfect passes from Heisman Trophy front-runner Kyle Trask — and No. 6 Florida overcame a sluggish start to beat Kentucky 34-10 Saturday in the Swamp.</p>
<p>The Gators (7-1) avenged a home loss to the Wildcats (3-6) two years ago and put themselves on the verge of returning to the Southeastern Conference championship game for the first time since 2016. Pitts and Trask look every bit ready for the big stage.</p>
<p>“It was just getting back in the groove and playing how I’ve been playing,” Pitts said.</p>
<p>The junior tight end missed the last 10 quarters following a vicious hit against Georgia that knocked his helmet so sideways that his face mask fractured his septum. He had surgery and sat out two full games. Trask wasted little time reconnecting with his favorite and most talented target.</p>
<p>They misfired on Florida&#8217;s opening down but Trask <a href="https://twitter.com/SECNetwork/status/1332737128351084544">found Pitts for a 56-yard touchdown </a>four plays later. Pitts ran away from starting cornerback Kelvin Joseph on the score.</p>
<p>“He causes a lot of mismatches for defenses and chaos in the back end trying to guard him,” Trask said.</p>
<p>Pitts now has 11 touchdowns in 5 1/2 games.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s such a dynamic playmaker,” coach Dan Mullen said. &#8220;He can turn some smaller gains into some pretty explosive, big plays. I think he does an amazing job of doing that. He creates matchup problems for you. He’s hard to deal with one on one, and if you get him one on one, we can take advantage of it.”</p>
<p>Trask&#8217;s three TD passes gave him 34 on the season, moving him past 2007 Heisman Trophy winner Tim Tebow and into a tie for third on the school’s single-season list. Only Danny Wuerffel (39 in 1996, 35 in 1995) is ahead of him. Rex Grossman also threw 34 in 2001.</p>
<p>Trask did break one of Wuerffel’s records Saturday. He became the first player in school history with at least three TD passes in eight consecutive games, topping Wuerffel’s mark of seven set in 1996.</p>
<p>Trask is on pace to pass Wuerffel for TDs, too, and it could happen in his final two regular-season games. More importantly for Trask and the Gators, though, is clinching the East with a victory at Tennessee next week.</p>
<p>“The sky&#8217;s the limit,” Trask said. “We have huge goals for this team.”</p>
<p>The Wildcats (3-6) kept Florida’s high-scoring offense in check for the first half, thanks partly to a fumble and a dropped third-down pass.</p>
<p>Kadarius Toney turned the game by taking advantage of a huge mistake by All-American punter Max Duffy. Kicking from their own 10-yard line, the Wildcats called for a kick left, but Duffy shanked it right.</p>
<p>Kentucky’s coverage unit surrounded Xzavier Henderson on one side while Toney caught the ball on the other with no one around him. He went untouched for a 50-yard score that put the Gators up 14-10 with 42 seconds left.</p>
<p>“We didn’t execute good enough. We didn’t coach good enough. Tough loss,&#8221; Kentucky coach Mark Stoops said.</p>
<p>The Wildcats added to their self-inflicted woes with three straight penalties to start the third quarter, giving Florida 39 free yards and setting up Trask’s second TD pass to Pitts.</p>
<p>“There’s nothing more aggravating to a defense than when you have a chance for a sack or no-yard gain or lost yards gain and you have a 15-yard penalty,” Stoops said. “It just breaks your back.”</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Kentucky: The Wildcats played without leading rusher Chris Rodriguez for the second consecutive week and averaged 3.4 yards a carry. It was far from ideal for a team built to run the ball and stay in short-yardage situations on second and third downs.</p>
<p>Florida: Mullen will have plenty to address after a second straight ho-hum performance. The defense struggled early and offensive miscues put the Gators in a small hole. But Trask, Pitts and Toney helped mask many of the flaws.</p>
<p>TRASH TALK?</p>
<p>Pitts said several Kentucky defensive backs, including Joseph, were talking trash on social media before the game and said it gave him “that extra boost.&#8221; He even got a warning from officials — and Mullen — for yapping a little too much after his third score.</p>
<p>“If you&#8217;re going to trash talk, you better back it up,” Mullen said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Kentucky: Hosts South Carolina next Saturday. The Wildcats have won five of the last six meetings.</p>
<p>Florida: Can secure a spot in the title game in Atlanta by beating Tennessee for the 15th time in the last 16 years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">787374</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 6 Florida focused on much more than just Vanderbilt</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-6-florida-focused-on-much-more-than-just-vanderbilt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 19:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=782378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Dan Mullen sees no reason for sixth-ranked Florida to overlook winless Vanderbilt, not with what is on the line for the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Dan Mullen sees no reason for sixth-ranked Florida to overlook winless Vanderbilt, not with what is on the line for the Gators this season.</p>
<p>The Gators (5-1) sit atop the Southeastern Conference&#8217;s Eastern Division with a spot awaiting them in Atlanta on Dec. 19 in the league championship game and possibly a berth in the College Football Playoff — if they keep winning. They&#8217;re putting up the kind of offensive numbers seen when Florida won its first national title.</p>
<p>Mullen also remembers Vanderbilt holding a 21-3 lead the last time his Gators visited Nashville.</p>
<p>“If we want to be a great team, we have to get better,” Mullen said. “So not only you know, is that focus on your opponent, that focus is on yourself as well. If not, I guess I’ll put on a cheerleading outfit and get on the sidelines and start trying to motivate us that way.”</p>
<p>Playing only a 10-game schedule also should be more than enough to get players&#8217; attention on Saturday, even if the Gators have dominated the series against Vanderbilt. Florida is 41-10-2 against the Commodores with six straight wins.</p>
<p>“Shouldn’t need any more motivation than that,” Mullen said of the truncated schedule.</p>
<p>Vanderbilt (0-6) has never gone winless through an entire season, and these Commodores have a trio of one-possession losses. Coach Derek Mason said they know how dynamic the Gators are but have to focus on playing together themselves.</p>
<p>“The challenges are great, but the opportunity&#8217;s greater,” Mason said. “Definitely look forward to seeing this group on Saturday.”</p>
<p>DEFENDING TRASK</p>
<p>Florida quarterback Kyle Trask has an SEC-best 28 touchdown passes through six games, and he&#8217;s spreading the ball around for an offense that&#8217;s in the top six nationally averaging 371.7 yards passing and scoring 45.8 points a game.</p>
<p>Mason compared Trask to facing Heisman Trophy winner Joe Burrow with LSU a year ago. Vanderbilt gave up six TD passes to Burrow in a 66-38 loss, and the Commodores gave up 363 yards and three TDs to Trask last year in the Swamp in a 56-0 loss to Florida.</p>
<p>“I think he’s much better,” Mason said of Trask. &#8220;I think he’s got command of the offense. I think he knows where to go with the football. He’s probably got as talented a weapons crew as you’re going to see in the SEC”</p>
<p>NO GATOR TRAPS</p>
<p>Trask says the Gators heard the chatter that playing Arkansas last week could catch Florida off guard coming off a big win over Georgia to grab control of the SEC East. Trask says they did a good job ignoring the noise, and Florida routed Arkansas 63-35.</p>
<p>Now the challenge is keep it up in a stadium where only parents and family will be allowed. Florida will have up to 500 tickets.</p>
<p>“We haven’t really been used to having a lot of fans anyways, so we’ve been having to create our own energy for every single game,” Trask said. &#8220;It’s just going to be another week of creating our juice from the inside out.”</p>
<p>INJURED AND MISSING</p>
<p>Florida won&#8217;t have tight end Kyle Pitts or wide receiver Trent Whittemore, who broke a rib and punctured a lung last week. Mullen said linebacker James Houston is questionable.</p>
<p>Vanderbilt is getting right guard Drew Birchmeier back after he missed the past two games, and running back Ja&#8217;Veon Marlow, who has played only twice this season, also will be available. Running back Keyon Henry-Brooks was hurt in last week&#8217;s 38-35 loss at Kentucky. He leads the Commodores with 147.2 all-purpose yards a game.</p>
<p>JOB SECURITY</p>
<p>Mason is the longest-tenured black head coach in SEC history in his seventh season, and he&#8217;s two wins from tying for the fifth-most wins by an Vanderbilt coach with 27. But Vanderbilt has four games remaining to avoid the first winless season in school history. Mason said he hasn&#8217;t talked with anyone about his future.</p>
<p>“They understand week to week we&#8217;re going to put the best product out there that we can,” Mason said. “And I feel comfortable about like how I continue to lead this team and that&#8217;s what we&#8217;re going to do. &#8230; I haven&#8217;t had any other conversations other than our numbers and are we healthy and can we play this week.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">782378</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heisman front-runner? Trask, Gators thump Hogs 63-35</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heisman-front-runner-trask-gators-thump-hogs-63-35/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 03:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=779253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kyle Trask extended his school record for consecutive games with at least four touchdown passes to six and No. 6 Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kyle Trask extended his school record for consecutive games with at least four touchdown passes to six and No. 6 Florida overwhelmed Arkansas 63-35 on Saturday night in the Swamp.</p>
<p>Trask threw for 356 yards and six scores against the Razorbacks (3-4), who were without coach Sam Pittman and without much of a chance by halftime. It was the second time this season Trask tossed six TDs in a game. He&#8217;s the only player in school history to accomplish that feat.</p>
<p>Arkansas quarterback Feleipe Franks, a three-year starter for the Gators (5-1), was booed in his return to Florida Field and unable to do much to steal the spotlight from Trask.</p>
<p>Trask started a new streak by throwing at least four TD passes in the first half for the second straight week, quite possibly raising his stock from Heisman Trophy hopeful to Heisman front-runner. He had five in Florida’s first six drives and might have had another had the Gators not failed to convert a fourth-down play at the Arkansas 16.</p>
<p>Still, it was Trask&#8217;s most impressive half in two years as a starter and put him in elite company as the Gators won their 11th straight at home and moved a step closer to locking up a spot in the Southeastern Conference championship game.</p>
<p>The only negative for Florida: Its defense allowed a 47-yard TD pass, an 83-yard TD run and an 82-yard catch and run for another score.</p>
<p>Trask&#8217;s night certainly overshadowed those deficiencies.</p>
<p>He became the third player in school history with at least 25 touchdown passes in multiple years, joining Heisman Trophy winners Tim Tebow and Danny Wuerffel. Both of those guys have statues outside the stadium.</p>
<p>He also became the fourth in the Football Bowl Subdivision since 1996 to throw four or more TDs in six consecutive games in a single season. The list includes Colt Brennan (Hawaii, 9 in 2006), Graham Harrell (Texas Tech, 6 in 2007) and Logan Woodside (Toledo, 6 in 2016).</p>
<p>His six TDs against Arkansas went to four different receivers: Trevon Grimes (twice), Keon Zipperer (twice), Justin Shorter and Jacob Copeland as the Gators torched what had been the SEC’s second-ranked pass defense.</p>
<p>Trask had time in the pocket thanks to a complementary ground game and plenty of open options despite playing without dynamic tight end Kyle Pitts, who could miss multiple games because of concussion-related issues.</p>
<p>They showed no signs of a letdown following an emotional victory against rival Georgia. Franks’ return may have had a little to do with it.</p>
<p>Florida defenders wanted a piece of him and Trask surely wanted to prove coach Dan Mullen made the right call by sticking with him over Franks.</p>
<p>Franks <a href="https://twitter.com/ESPNCFB/status/1327771502356406272">completed a 47-yard touchdown pass on his opening drive and pointed to the Florida sideline</a> as he ran to celebrate with teammates. But he did little else the rest of the night and ended up in the locker room in the third quarter with a left hand/wrist injury.</p>
<p>He returned with it heavily tapped and wore a glove to help protect it. He could be seen looking into the stands, possibly reminiscing about his time in Gainesville, between the third and fourth quarters as the Gators played Tom Petty’s “I Won’t Back Down.”</p>
<p>Franks completed 15 of 19 passes for 250 yards and two scores.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Arkansas: The Razorbacks&#8217; impressive start to the season took an ugly turn in Gainesville, but they could rebound with winnable games against LSU and Missouri next.</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators have the offense to beat anyone and the defense to keep everyone in games.</p>
<p>PITTS UPDATE</p>
<p>Pitts is likely to miss a second consecutive game because of a concussion and related issues.</p>
<p>Pitts was knocked out of last week’s game against rival Georgia on a vicious hit over the middle. Mullen told ESPN earlier Saturday that Pitts probably would miss at least another game.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Arkansas: Is tentatively scheduled to host LSU next Saturday, but the Tigers are dealing with COVID-19 issues that prompted their game against No. 1 Alabama this weekend to be postponed. The Razorbacks have lost four straight against LSU.</p>
<p>Florida: Gets on an airplane for the first time since its travel-related COVID outbreak last month and faces Vanderbilt next Saturday. The Gators have won 28 of 29, including six in a row, in the series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">779253</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mullen&#8217;s message for Florida before Arkansas: don&#8217;t peak now</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mullens-message-for-florida-before-arkansas-dont-peak-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=777963</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida coach Dan Mullen had a message for his players this week: great teams don’t peak at the midpoint of the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida coach Dan Mullen had a message for his players this week: great teams don’t peak at the midpoint of the season.</p>
<p>The sixth-ranked Gators enjoyed their most significant victory in Mullen’s three-year tenure last Saturday, a 44-28 victory against rival Georgia in Jacksonville that gave them a stranglehold on the Southeastern Conference’s Eastern Division.</p>
<p>Florida (4-1) has enough cushion in the East that it could lose once and still make the league title game in Atlanta next month. But with the College Football Playoff still a possibility, Mullen wanted to make it clear how much his guys have in front of them.</p>
<p>“If you want to be a great team, great teams get better every single week,” Mullen said. “Great teams don’t peak at the midway point of the season. Great teams peak in early, mid-December, and early, mid-January.</p>
<p>“Those are your peak moments as a team. For us, that’s got to be our goal and our focus this week. If we don’t improve, last week was really irrelevant.”</p>
<p>Florida begins the second half of its season against surprising Arkansas (3-3) on Saturday night in the Swamp. Razorbacks quarterback Feleipe Franks will be a main storyline as he returns to Florida Field for the first time to face his former team.</p>
<p>“Just being the competitor I am, being able to be a part of those stories is awesome,” Franks said. “It’s a blessing at the end of the day.”</p>
<p>Franks was a three-year starter for the Gators before dislocating and fracturing his right ankle at Kentucky early last season. Faced with long odds of regaining the starting job over Trask, Franks chose to transfer.</p>
<p>He landed at Arkansas and has been instrumental in the team’s turnaround. He has 14 touchdown passes and three interceptions, including six scores and no picks in the last two games.</p>
<p>Friends and ex-teammates are eager for the reunion, some ready for a special greeting.</p>
<p>“In practice, you cannot touch that quarterback,” Florida linebacker James Houston said. “If you touch that quarterback, you’re going to be in trouble. It’s fun hitting someone that you couldn’t lay a finger on for four years.”</p>
<p>If 17 1/2-point underdog Arkansas is going to have a chance at pulling an upset, it probably has to get to Florida’s Kyle Trask. He already has 22 touchdown passes this season, including at least four in every game.</p>
<p>“We’re tough, physical, we don’t back down from any opponent,” Arkansas defensive lineman Eric Gregory said. “We’re going in like it’s any other game. We’re going to go play with a chip on shoulder.”</p>
<p>Florida, meanwhile, expects to heed Mullen’s message and avoid any kind of letdown after being Georgia for the first time since 2016.</p>
<p>“We can’t get complacent,” Houston said. “We know it was a big win, but we celebrated on Saturday and Sunday, and now it’s time to move on and get better so we can win out the rest of the season.”</p>
<p>MISSING MAN</p>
<p>Arkansas will be without coach Sam Pittman, who tested positive for COVID-19 earlier in the week and has been helping with the game plan virtually. Defensive coordinator Barry Odom will serve as interim coach, hoping to upset the Gators like he did as Missouri’s head coach in 2018.</p>
<p>“It’s really not a big loss because we have other great coaches,” Gregory said. “We consider it the best coaching staff in the SEC, so it’s not really a big drop-off.”</p>
<p>IN THE PITTS</p>
<p>Florida could be without star tight end Kyle Pitts because of a concussion. Pitts was knocked out of the Georgia game in the second quarter on Lewis Cine’s crushing blow over the middle. Cine was ejected for targeting. Pitts spent the rest of the game in the locker room and was listed as questionable for the game.</p>
<p>SWAMP STREAK</p>
<p>The Gators have won 10 in a row at home, a streak that started after Missouri’s 38-17 victory in Gainesville on Nov. 3, 2018. Odom was on the visiting sideline for that one, his only win against a ranked team in four years (2016-19) at Mizzou.</p>
<p>WEATHER WATCH</p>
<p>Tropical Storm Eta brought strong wind and heavy rain across northern Florida on Thursday, but the weakening system was expected to have no bearing on the game or any travel paths to Gainesville.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">777963</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">191002 dan mullen 2</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trask, Florida upend Georgia 44-28 in &#8216;Cocktail Party&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/trask-florida-upend-georgia-44-28-in-cocktail-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 02:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=775054</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kyle Trask started jumping up and down on the sideline. His Florida teammates took it to another level, running and leaping...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kyle Trask started jumping up and down on the sideline. His Florida teammates took it to another level, running and leaping into the stands.</p>
<p>Coach Dan Mullen wasn&#8217;t going to be left out off the fun. Mullen pulled himself onto the edge of the front row and celebrated wildly with fans.</p>
<p>Mullen clearly understood the magnitude of the victory. Everyone did.</p>
<p>Trask had another four-touchdown night, becoming <a href="https://twitter.com/CBSSports/status/1325204500500652034?s=20">the first quarterback in Southeastern Conference history to accomplish the feat </a>in five consecutive games, and the eighth-ranked Gators beat No. 5 and undermanned Georgia 44-28 on Saturday.</p>
<p>“You’ve got to enjoy it,&#8221; Mullen said. &#8220;I might be 48 years old, but I’m really young on the inside so I’ve still got to enjoy some of that stuff.”</p>
<p>The Gators (4-1) ended a three-game losing streak in the rivalry known as the “World’s Largest Outdoor Cocktail Party” — it was Mullen’s most significant victory in three years in Gainesville — and now have a stranglehold on the SEC’s East Division.</p>
<p>The Bulldogs (4-2), who entered the game as 3½-point favorites, were likely eliminated from College Football Playoff consideration and probably have a quarterback competition moving forward.</p>
<p>Florida, meanwhile, has a Heisman Trophy contender.</p>
<p>Trask completed 30 of 43 passes for a career-high 474 yards — 8 yards shy of Tim Tebow&#8217;s single-game school record — despite playing much of the night without standout tight end Kyle Pitts.</p>
<p>Pitts was knocked out of the game in the second quarter on Lewis Cine’s crushing hit over the middle. Cine was ejected for targeting, adding to Georgia’s already-thin defense.</p>
<p>The Bulldogs were without nose tackle Jordan Davis (elbow), safety Richard LeCounte (motorcycle accident) and defensive tackle Julian Rochester (knee) to start the game.</p>
<p>Trask and the Gators took advantage, burning Georgia repeatedly with wheel routes while overcoming a 14-0 deficit. Running backs Malik Davis, Nay&#8217;Quan Wright and Dameon Pierce combined to catch 10 passes for 212 yards.</p>
<p>“Kyle Trask does a great job,&#8221; Mullen said. &#8220;He’s not going to force the ball. If they’re going bracket and take away and double people, he’s going to go to who you’re not doubling or covering.”</p>
<p>Once Trask and Florida got going, the Bulldogs did little to stop them. The Gators scored on seven of eight possessions after a three-and-out to open the game and finished with 571 yards — the most allowed in Georgia coach Kirby Smart&#8217;s five seasons.</p>
<p>“We just can’t let this game define us,&#8221; Dawgs receiver Kearis Jackson said. &#8220;We’re not in the situation we want to be in right now, but we still have games to be played. There are still plays out there to be made.”</p>
<p>The Bulldogs had several chances to make it a one-possession game late, but D’Wan Mathis kept overthrowing open receivers. Mathis, who started the season opener, replaced Stetson Bennett in the third quarter.</p>
<p>Bennett left the game briefly in the first quarter with a shoulder injury and was ineffective after returning. He completed 5 of 16 passes for 78 yards, with a touchdown and an interception.</p>
<p>Bennett was without his top target, George Pickens (upper body), and lost Marcus Rosemy-Jacksaint to an apparent broken right leg on a 32-yard touchdown catch in the first quarter.</p>
<p>Replays showed the severity of Rosemy-Jacksaint’s injury as team trainers rushed to the end zone and quickly got an air cast on his leg. He was carted into the tunnel amid a standing ovation. Florida safety Brad Stewart hit Rosemy-Jacksaint just before he crossed the goal line.</p>
<p>The Dawgs led 14-0 after the freshman’s first career TD reception. Zamir White scored on the game’s first play from scrimmage, going untouched for 75 yards.</p>
<p>It looked like it would be a Georgia rout.</p>
<p>It ended up being Florida’s night to celebrate.</p>
<p>“I don’t make excuses,&#8221; Smart said, pointing out his team is 19-2 in its last 21 East games. “I don’t look at it as cause for concern. &#8230; I’m not going to say the sky’s falling or everything’s coming down. We’ve got to be better.&#8221;</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Georgia might have to move on from Bennett, a fourth-year junior who has completed 20 of 44 passes for 201 yards with one touchdown and five interceptions since the first half against Alabama. Mathis wasn&#8217;t any better against Florida, but he&#8217;s young and has potential. Southern California transfer JT Daniels or highly touted recruit Carson Beck also could get a shot.</p>
<p>Florida notched a signature win for Mullen, but likely can&#8217;t afford a slip-up down the stretch to remain in play for a CFP spot.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Georgia likely will fall out of top 10 of The Associated Press&#8217; college football poll for the first time this season. Florida surely will jump the Dawgs.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts Arkansas next Saturday, the return of quarterback Feleipe Franks to the Swamp. Franks left the Gators at the end of last season, landed with the Razorbacks and has played well.</p>
<p>Georgia plays at Missouri, which has lost six straight in the series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">775054</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida LB Cox gets shot at former team in &#8216;Cocktail Party&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-lb-cox-gets-shot-at-former-team-in-cocktail-party/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=773743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — There’s little doubt Brenton Cox has been waiting for this game. Counting down the days? Circled on the calendar? No one...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — There’s little doubt Brenton Cox has been waiting for this game.</p>
<p>Counting down the days? Circled on the calendar? No one knows for sure because Cox turned down multiple interview requests this week in an attempt to avoid the spotlight. But the Florida linebacker made his feelings clear last month when he said facing Georgia would “definitely be personal.” He also vowed to get a victory against his former team.</p>
<p>The eighth-ranked Gators (3-1) expect Cox to be at his best against the No. 5 Bulldogs (4-1) on Saturday in Jacksonville, a Southeastern Conference rivalry that likely will determine the East Division and who advances to the league title game next month. Florida has lost three straight in the series.</p>
<p>&#8220;The World’s Largest Outdoor Cocktail Party” won’t have the same fanfare as usual. Each school got 9,000 tickets — well shy of the 85,000 fans who usually cram into reconfigured TIAA Bank Field — and tailgating has been banned in stadium parking lots.</p>
<p>None of that matters to Cox, a five-star recruit from Stockbridge, Georgia, who picked the Bulldogs over more than two dozen other schools, including powerhouses Alabama, Clemson and Ohio State.</p>
<p>He played in 13 games as a freshman in 2018 and even started the Sugar Bowl against Texas. He finished with 20 tackles, including six against the Longhorns, and appeared poised to be the next great defender to come out of Athens.</p>
<p>But he was arrested on a misdemeanor charge of marijuana possession in April 2019 and abruptly left the team four months later. He spent a few days in the NCAA transfer portal before landing in Gainesville.</p>
<p>Florida coach <a href="https://apnews.com/article/145be17d5f414cedbe47e2cfef89e48e">Dan Mullen was hopeful Cox would get an NCAA waiver that would have allowed him to play</a> right away. But the request was denied, forcing Cox to sit out the 2019 season under NCAA transfer rules.</p>
<p>“He ended up being on the scout team,” Mullen said. “Had a great attitude, worked his tail off and all the work he put in last year not being able to play is showing this year.”</p>
<p>Cox handled it as well as could be expected.</p>
<p>“Sitting on the sideline was definitely hard for me because I’ve never done that before,” he said. “I had a lot of faith in Coach Mullen. But some things just don’t work out the way we planned. I’m just ready to go now.”</p>
<p>Cox has started every game for Florida this season, the first three out of position. With defensive tackle Kyree Campbell returning from a suspension last week against Missouri, it allowed Zach Carter to move back to defensive end and Cox to his more natural spot at outside linebacker.</p>
<p>He finished with five tackles against the Tigers, including one for a loss, to go along with three quarterback hurries and a fumble recovery that helped turn the game in the second quarter.</p>
<p>“He went out, put on a show and dominated like he’s supposed to,” Florida cornerback Jaydon Hill said. “That’s him, you know? That’s what he’s supposed to do.”</p>
<p>Cox is second on the team with 21 tackles and leads the Gators with two sacks. Facing Georgia, though, could raise his game to new heights.</p>
<p>“I feel like he knows he has something to prove and he wants to show his old team what he’s been doing, who he is,” Florida receiver Trevon Grimes said. “Just from seeing that, I know it’s going to be a big game for him, a big game for us, a big game for the team, and we’re looking forward to going out there and showing Georgia what we can do and who we are.”</p>
<p>The Gators weren’t very good defensively in their first three games but felt they turned a corner against Mizzou by allowing 248 yards, notching three sacks and forcing two turnovers.</p>
<p>Cox was at the center of Florida&#8217;s best defensive showing since thumping Florida State last November in the Swamp.</p>
<p>&#8220;Brenton’s playing really well,” Georgia coach Kirby Smart said. “He’s an explosive pass rusher, really good player like he was coming out of high school. He plays really hard. He’s hard to block. … What he’s really good at is rushing the passer like all the Florida guys they’ve had over the past. …</p>
<p>“He’s playing really well for them. He’s playing physical. He’s playing hard. He’ll create some issues for us Saturday and we’ve got to do a good job knowing where he’s at.”</p>
<p>There&#8217;s a good chance Cox will be the one staring, pointing and screaming at Georgia&#8217;s sideline.</p>
<p>“You have to be able to finish and do your job. You can’t be reckless in your approach,&#8221; Florida defensive coordinator Todd Grantham said. ”There’s a fine line in being aggressive and physical and not reckless. &#8230; I certainly expect him to be a guy that plays to his ability and executes the things he needs to do to be successful.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">773743</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC fines Florida&#8217;s Mullen $25K for role in brawl vs. Mizzou</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/sec-fines-floridas-mullen-25k-for-role-in-brawl-vs-mizzou/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 19:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=771776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — The Southeastern Conference fined Florida coach Dan Mullen $25,000 on Monday for his role in a benches-clearing brawl against Missouri. The...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — The Southeastern Conference fined Florida coach Dan Mullen $25,000 on Monday for his role in a benches-clearing brawl against Missouri.</p>
<p>The league also reviewed video of the fight and issued half-game suspensions for Missouri linebacker Chad Bailey, offensive lineman Dylan Spencer and defensive lineman Markell Utsey. Each of them will sit out the first half of Missouri’s next game, against No. 5 Georgia on Nov. 14.</p>
<p>Florida defensive lineman Zach Carter and linebacker Antwuan Powell, who were ejected from the game for fighting, will be suspended for the first half against the Bulldogs next week in Jacksonville. NCAA fighting rules mandate an automatic half-game suspension for the ensuing game.</p>
<p>Missouri linebacker Tre Williams was ejected for a flagrant unsportsmanlike conduct foul and will not be punished further.</p>
<p>“There is no place in college football for the kind of incident that took place at halftime of the Missouri at Florida game Saturday night,&#8221; SEC Commissioner Greg Sankey said. &#8220;Everyone involved is responsible for meeting sportsmanship standards throughout each game.</p>
<p>&#8220;Running on the field to confront a game official, the gathering of teams in an on-field confrontation and student-athletes throwing punches are all disappointing at any time, but even more so as we work to support healthy competition during a pandemic.”</p>
<p>The suspensions could be significant for the No. 8 Gators (3-1), who were without 15 players against Mizzou. Some of the absences stemmed from injuries, others because of COVID-19 test results and contact tracing. It’s unclear how many of them will return against the Bulldogs.</p>
<p>The melee started Saturday night when Missouri’s Trajan Jeffcoat delivered what looked like a high, late hit on Florida quarterback Kyle Trask on the final play of the first half. The Hail Mary pass fell incomplete, and Trask landed hard on his back. His linemen came to his defense. So did Mullen, who started screaming at officials and the opposing sideline.</p>
<p>Mullen clearly did more to inflame than extinguish the situation, and his team followed his lead.</p>
<p>“I respect the decision from the conference office,&#8221; Mullen said in a statement. &#8220;As the head coach, it is my responsibility to defuse these types of situations, and I didn’t live up to that standard.”</p>
<p>Players from both teams converged near Missouri’s side of the field, and wild punches could be seen flying and connecting. Only three players were ejected.</p>
<p>The SEC handed down more punishments.</p>
<p>It was the latest black eye for Mullen, who was already under fire for saying he hoped to pack 90,000 fans inside Florida Field for a home game during a pandemic and for criticizing an NCAA rule that prevents teams having meetings and practices on Election Day.</p>
<p>Florida’s faithful dismissed Mullen’s strong and somewhat questionable stances as typical brashness for an outspoken coach who’s focused on winning. They found themselves defending him again Saturday night.</p>
<p>Mullen had to be pulled away several times and was so irate by the end of the exchange that he came back out of the locker room tunnel for a curtain call. Fans chanted his name as he returned to the field for the start of the third quarter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">771776</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">191002 dan mullen 2</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gators coach Mullen joins players in testing positive for COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/gators-coach-mullen-joins-players-in-testing-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 02:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=762445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida coach Dan Mullen, who last week wanted 90,000 fans packed inside the stadium amid a pandemic, says he has tested positive for...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida coach Dan Mullen, who last week wanted 90,000 fans packed inside the stadium amid a pandemic, says he has tested positive for COVID-19.</p>
<p>Mullen made the announcement Saturday on Twitter, saying his initial positive result was confirmed by a second test. The 10th-ranked Gators had at least 21 players and coaches test positive earlier this week, an outbreak that prompted the Southeastern Conference to postpone Florida&#8217;s next two games.</p>
<p>With potentially dozens more quarantined because of contract tracing, Florida (2-1) would have had fewer than 50 scholarship players available to face the defending national champion Tigers (1-2) in the Swamp.</p>
<p>Two assistant coaches also tested positive for the highly contagious virus.</p>
<p>Mullen is the second SEC head coach, along with Alabama icon Nick Saban, to contract COVID-19 and the fifth overall known this season in major-college football, joining Florida State’s Mike Norvell, Arizona’s Kevin Sumlin and Kansas’ Les Miles.</p>
<p>Florida has started administering daily tests since it first suspected an outbreak following last week&#8217;s loss at Texas A&amp;M.</p>
<p>The 48-year-old Mullen says he has experienced “mild to no symptoms.”</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m continuing to self-isolate from my family, who all remain healthy, and am following all the guidelines set forth by UF Health, the CDC and our public health officials,” Mullen <a href="https://twitter.com/CoachDanMullen/status/1317582683392954368">tweeted</a>. “I am proud of how our players, staff and campus community have navigated this unprecedented time and hope all continue to be safe.”</p>
<p>The Gators believe their outbreak started with two players — one experiencing congestion and the other a headache late last week. Both suspected allergies and didn&#8217;t alert team doctors before getting on the team flight to Texas A&amp;M.</p>
<p>Mullen raised eyebrows after the loss to the Aggies by saying he wanted to pack the Swamp against LSU. When given a chance to back down, he doubled down. He was given another chance Monday and dug in more. He finally relented Wednesday and apologized if he offended anyone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">762445</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC postpones LSU-Florida game as Gators deal with outbreak</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/sec-postpones-lsu-florida-game-as-gators-deal-with-outbreak/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 03:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=760813</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — No. 10 Florida and defending national champion LSU are now scheduled to play in December. Unfortunately for coach Dan Mullen, the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — No. 10 Florida and defending national champion LSU are now scheduled to play in December. Unfortunately for coach Dan Mullen, the stadium still won&#8217;t be packed.</p>
<p>The Southeastern Conference postponed Saturday’s LSU-Florida game a day after Mullen had 19 players and coaches test positive for COVID-19. Florida athletic director Scott Stricklin said Wednesday the number is now up to 21 positives with considerably more in quarantine because of contract tracing.</p>
<p>Those players likely would have been unavailable against the Tigers, leaving Florida with fewer than 50 scholarship athletes and less than the SEC&#8217;s threshold (53) for holding games amid the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>The game was tentatively rescheduled for Dec. 12, the league&#8217;s built-in bye week before its annual championship. It&#8217;s the second SEC game bumped this week, following Missouri-Vanderbilt.</p>
<p>Florida hosts Missouri next, on October 24, and that game also could be in jeopardy.</p>
<p>“Hopefully we don’t have any more positives and we’re able to get on the other side of this and then we can get everyone back in a situation where you can go compete again,” Stricklin said.</p>
<p>Florida paused <a href="https://apnews.com/article/virus-outbreak-college-football-dan-mullen-health-gainesville-3bd542b05de9c0618993598bffa3ff43">team activities Tuesday after seeing a spike in positives. </a> Mullen said two assistant coaches also tested positive. The Gators have since moved to everyday testing and and halted meetings and practices indefinitely.</p>
<p>Stricklin suggested traveling to Texas A&amp;M may have been the root of the team&#8217;s outbreak, with two players who later tested positive telling team doctors they had symptoms before getting on a plane last Friday. One had a runny nose, the other a headache.</p>
<p>Neither told anyone, which Stricklin said would be addressed. He also hinted at potentially looking at tweaking travel protocols.</p>
<p>“I really think it could be as simple as not understanding symptoms,” Stricklin said, pointing to Florida having 10 positives over the previous 11 weeks. &#8220;I know people personally who have had the sniffles and a friend of theirs was COVID positive, so they went and got tested and found out they had it. They thought they just had something pretty common. &#8230;</p>
<p>&#8220;As a college student, you have those things and it’s not uncommon. But in a COVID environment, it’s so important that we are hypersensitive to being diligent on that front. I don’t know that this was a situation where someone goes, ‘I don’t feel well, but I’m going to power through it.’ I think this is a situation where someone felt like, ‘I’ve got a sniffle, I need a Kleenex and I’m ready to play a game.’”</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s shutdown came three days after Mullen’s comments about wanting to <a href="https://apnews.com/article/virus-outbreak-college-football-dan-mullen-gainesville-football-1e21c3bd07b05e4ea0ecd02fa9923679">pack 90,000 fans inside Florida Field to create a better home-field advantage</a> against the Tigers. Mullen didn’t double down Monday, but he didn’t back down, either.</p>
<p>He brushed aside criticism and praised his guys for how well they have handled COVID safety protocols.</p>
<p>He finally backtracked two days later, apologizing “if I offended people or anybody out there.”</p>
<p>“One of the things I want to encourage was whatever our local health officials come and out say, ‘This is the number of people that we’re going to allow at the game right now,&#8217;” Mullen said. “I want to encourage those people to come in, bring the energy, bring the excitement into the stadium and help our team to win and bring that energy that they bring of what makes the Swamp such a special place to go play in.”</p>
<p>Stricklin made it clear Wednesday that Mullen overstepped his area of expertise and added that the plan for the rest of 2020 would be to allow up to 17,000 fans (25% capacity) at Florida Field for home games.</p>
<p>“That number will change one day. I don’t know when they’ll change,” Stricklin said. &#8220;But until that changes, this is where we’re going to be.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">760813</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">uf-gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida halts meetings, practices amid 19 new COVID cases</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-halts-meetings-practices-amid-19-new-covid-cases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 01:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=760132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — No. 10 Florida paused all team activities Tuesday following “an increase in positive COVID tests among players,&#8221; putting Saturday&#8217;s home game...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — No. 10 Florida paused all team activities Tuesday following “an increase in positive COVID tests among players,&#8221; putting Saturday&#8217;s home game against defending national champion LSU in jeopardy.</p>
<p>The Gators had 19 positives following Tuesday morning testing, a person familiar with the situation told the Associated Press. The person spoke on the condition of anonymity because of privacy laws. The Independent Florida Alligator first reported the total number of positives.</p>
<p>Athletic director Scott Stricklin said the decision to halt meetings and practices was made “out of an abundance of caution.” Stricklin added that coach Dan Mullen has spoken with players and parents and that he told last week&#8217;s opponent, Texas A&amp;M, and Saturday&#8217;s opponent, the Tigers.</p>
<p>Stricklin said the situation “will be re-evaluated by UF Health and the athletic department’s sports medicine staff Wednesday.”</p>
<p>The shutdown came three days after Mullen&#8217;s eyebrow-raising comments <a href="https://apnews.com/article/virus-outbreak-college-football-dan-mullen-gainesville-football-1e21c3bd07b05e4ea0ecd02fa9923679">about wanting 90,000 fans at Florida Field</a> to create a better home-field advantage against the Tigers. Mullen didn&#8217;t double down Monday, but he didn&#8217;t back down, either.</p>
<p>He brushed aside criticism and praised his players for how well they have handled COVID safety protocols.</p>
<p>“I think if you look at what we’ve been able to do, the safety precautions we have that our players have followed, our coaches follow, our staff follows, you know, I think we’re a model of safety of what we’ve been doing during this time period,” Mullen said.</p>
<p>“So I’m really proud of how we’ve handled everything and how safe we’ve been with everything we’re doing and all the precautions we’ve had in place during this time.”</p>
<p>Texas A&amp;M AD Ross Bjork said the Aggies have reviewed contact tracing data deployed by the conference and found nothing yet.</p>
<p>“At this point, there has been no impact within our football program, but we will continue our regular testing regiment this week and stay diligent with all of our safety protocols,” Bjork said in a statement.</p>
<p>The Southeastern Conference already has postponed one game this week: Vanderbilt and Missouri was tentatively pushed to Dec. 12 because COVID-19 issues have left the Commodores without enough players. It was the first SEC game rescheduled due to coronavirus-related problems and the 28th in the Football Bowl Subdivision to be postponed or canceled since Aug. 26.</p>
<p>Florida reported five new COVID-19 positives earlier Tuesday, but those results stemmed from last week&#8217;s tests. The Gators test student-athletes three times a week, with football players getting tested Sunday at noon as well as Tuesday and Thursday mornings.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">760132</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/03/uf-gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">uf-gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spiller helps No. 21 A&#038;M top No. 4 Florida 41-38</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/spiller-helps-no-21-am-top-no-4-florida-41-38/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 04:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=758484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) — Jimbo Fisher got his first win against a top-five opponent since taking over at Texas A&#38;M. And just like that,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) — Jimbo Fisher got his first win against a top-five opponent since taking over at Texas A&amp;M.</p>
<p>And just like that, he started looking ahead to next weekend.</p>
<p>“This game shows you what you’re capable of,” the coach said. “Now I want to see what do you follow up with?”</p>
<p>Isaiah Spiller rushed for 174 yards and two touchdowns, and No. 21 Texas A&amp;M beat fourth-ranked Florida 41-38 on Seth Small’s 26-yard field goal as time expired Saturday.</p>
<p>Spiller helped get the Aggies get into position for Small’s decisive kick, sending A&amp;M to its first win over a top-five team since a 41-38 victory over No. 3 Auburn in 2014. It was the school&#8217;s first such victory at home since it toppled No. 1 Oklahoma 30-26 in 2002.</p>
<p>“I think this is a real big confidence-booster,” Spiller said. “I feel like we really gained our identity.”</p>
<p>Fisher brushed off the notion that it was a signature win or it meant more than anything he&#8217;s done in three seasons in College Station.</p>
<p>“It’s a good win,&#8221; he said. “It’s a big win &#8230; but they’re all big wins.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kellen Mond threw a 51-yard pass to Caleb Chapman for a tying TD with about 4½ minutes to go.</p>
<p>The Gators were driving when Buddy Johnson forced a fumble by Malik Davis, and it was recovered by DeMarvin Leal to set up the game-ending field goal.</p>
<p>“We had plenty of opportunities to put the game away,&#8221; quarterback Kyle Trask said. “So you can’t blame it all on one play because it shouldn’t even been close if we would have executed on the drives that we didn’t score on.”</p>
<p>Mond passed for 338 yards and three touchdowns to help the Aggies (2-1, 2-1 SEC) down the previously undefeated Gators (2-1, 2-1).</p>
<p>Unlike Fisher, Mond, who became Texas A&amp;M&#8217;s career leader in yards passing Saturday, raved about the importance of such a high-profile win.</p>
<p>“We’ve had some big wins (but) this is definitely huge,&#8221; he said. “This definitely I feel like can be a culture-changing win and only can give this team more confidence.&#8221;</p>
<p>Trask, who was named after Kyle Field by his A&amp;M-graduate parents, had 312 yards passing and four TDs. But the Gators were done in by the late mistake and another poor performance by their defense.</p>
<p>“We’re playing 10 SEC games in a row,&#8221; Florida coach Dan Mullen said. “We have to get over this one quick. It’s more like an NFL schedule.”</p>
<p>Mullen was disappointed that the Gators allowed A&amp;M to convert 12 of 15 third-down opportunities.</p>
<p>“We’re going to evaluate a lot of things defensively, and our ability to make plays and get off the field,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Chapman finished with nine receptions for 151 yards and two touchdowns as the Aggies bounced back from last week’s lopsided loss to No. 2 Alabama.</p>
<p>Leon O’Neal intercepted Trask on Florida’s first drive of the second half, but the play was wiped out by a hands-to-the-face penalty on Michael Clemons. There was a scuffle after a play later in the drive that resulted in unsportsmanlike conduct penalties for both teams.</p>
<p>Kadarius Toney grabbed his second TD reception on the next play, <a href="https://twitter.com/GatorsFB/status/1314993303369084928?s=20">a 37-yarder that made it 28-17</a> Gators with about 10 minutes left in the third.</p>
<p>Another unsportsmanlike conduct penalty on the Aggies, this one on Andre White, occurred on the ensuing kickoff and it looked as if Florida was in control of the game.</p>
<p>But then Spiller got going. Texas A&amp;M grinded it out on its next drive, passing just once on a 10-play possession capped by a <a href="https://twitter.com/AggieFootball/status/1314995838280708097?s=20">3-yard TD from Spiller</a>.</p>
<p>Florida led 28-24 early in the fourth when Spiller struck again, <a href="https://twitter.com/AggieFootball/status/1315000497204531201?s=20">running 19 yards for a touchdown</a> on a fourth-and-2 play. Spiller bounced off several defenders before waltzing into the end zone and then hitting the Florida fan section with a Gator chomp.</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Evan McPherson kicked a tying 53-yard field goal with about 9½ minutes remaining, setting the stage for a wild finish.</p>
<p>The game was tied when Ainias Smith fumbled after a reception and the ball was recovered by Marco Wilson. The Gators cashed in on the mistake when Trask threw a 1-yard touchdown pass to Dameon Pierce to make it 38-31 with about six minutes left.</p>
<p>Kyle Pitts gave the Gators an early lead when he leaped above two defenders <a href="https://twitter.com/GatorsFB/status/1314971598428934144?s=20">for a 5-yard touchdown reception</a> on the first drive. The Aggies tied it up when Mond connected with Chase Lane <a href="https://twitter.com/AggieFootball/status/1314976815878938625?s=20">on an 11-yard TD</a> on their first possession.</p>
<p>Trask’s second TD pass came on the next drive when he found Toney for an 11-yard grab.</p>
<p>Mond then orchestrated a 14-play, 94-yard drive capped by a touchdown pass to Chapman after that.</p>
<p>Florida regained the lead on Nay’Quan Wright’s 1-yard scoring run with about four minutes left in the second.</p>
<p>A field goal by the Aggies at the end of the second cut the lead to 21-17 at halftime.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Both teams showed off their offensive firepower, but will need to improve on defense after a game where the teams combined for more than 900 yards.</p>
<p>FULL HOUSE?</p>
<p>Mullen thought A&amp;M&#8217;s crowd played a factor in win, even though only 24,709 fans were allowed because of the coronavirus. Now that Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has lifted capacity restrictions at sporting events in the state, Mullen wants to see a much bigger crowd than he saw Saturday when the Gators are at home next week.</p>
<p>“I certainly hope our university administration follows the governor,&#8221; Mullen said. “The governor has passed a rule that we’re allowed to pack the Swamp and have 90,000 in the Swamp to give us the home-field advantage Texas A&amp;M had.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Gators allowed 17,000 fans for their home opener on Oct. 3.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>The Aggies should move up a few spots after knocking off the Gators, and Florida will certainly drop after losing to a team that didn’t really put up a fight against Alabama last week.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: Hosts No. 17 LSU next Saturday in the first of two straight home games.</p>
<p>Texas A&amp;M: Travels to visit Mississippi State next Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">758484</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 4 Florida looks to improve defense against No. 21 A&#038;M</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-4-florida-looks-to-improve-defense-against-no-21-am/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=757066</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Through two games, the fourth-ranked Florida Gators have done just about anything they wanted on offense. Their defensive performance is another story. They’ve given up...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Through two games, the fourth-ranked Florida Gators have done just about anything they wanted on offense.</p>
<p>Their defensive performance is another story. They’ve given up 942 yards and 59 points in two games this season, and they’re looking to fix that on Saturday when they visit No. 21 Texas A&amp;M.</p>
<p>“These past two weeks have been unacceptable for me, personally,” linebacker Amari Burney said. “You know, just talking with the coaches, my parents, watching film, it’s been unacceptable on my part just being a starter and not doing my job.”</p>
<p>The Gators (2-0) have been especially unhappy with their inability to get off the field consistently on third and fourth downs. Teams have converted 15 of 31 third-down attempts against them and 5 of 7 fourth-down opportunities.</p>
<p>“You can’t get complacent when the offense is scoring so many points and then we don’t stop them on defense,” Burney said. “The defense has to go out there and start making stops instead of just giving the team life back and let them score on us.”</p>
<p>Florida’s defense has allowed an average of 327.5 yards passing a game and will now face Texas A&amp;M&#8217;s veteran quarterback Kellen Mond, who is coming off a 318-yard passing performance in a loss to No. 2 Alabama.</p>
<p>“It starts with the quarterback, I mean, because we played this quarterback &#8230; when I was at Mississippi State,” defensive coordinator Todd Grantham said. “Just looking at the development of the quarterback and the way (coach) Jimbo (Fisher) has developed quarterbacks over the course of his career, you can see that they’ve really improved him from that standpoint.”</p>
<p>Mond and the Aggies (1-1) will try to get back on track after the 52-24 loss to the Crimson Tide. Fisher faced criticism for Texas A&amp;M’s poor performance against Alabama in his third season with the Aggies after signing a 10-year, $75 million contract.</p>
<p>“We feel the progress is there,” he said. “But until you win them all, you’re never satisfied.”</p>
<p>KYLE AT KYLE</p>
<p>Florida quarterback Kyle Trask has never been to an actual game at the place that bears his name. Trask’s parents, both Texas A&amp;M graduates, named their son after century-old Kyle Field.</p>
<p>Trask grew up in Manvel, about a two-hour drive from College Station. He played behind former Houston and current Miami standout D’Eriq King in high school and then waited four years to get his shot with the Gators.</p>
<p>“There’s always a chip on my shoulder just because … no one gave me a chance in recruiting,” said Trask, who didn’t get an offer from the Aggies. “I kind of just came in with a chip on my shoulder to whatever program I came into to just try to prove myself.”</p>
<p>FISHER VS. FLORIDA</p>
<p>This will be Fisher’s first meeting with Florida as Texas A&amp;M’s coach. But he has plenty of history against the Gators, going 7-1 against them in his time at Florida State.</p>
<p>He recalled the in-state rivalry this week.</p>
<p>“At times at Florida State when I played them, we were all ranked in the top 10 two or three times we played them,” Fisher said. “Florida has always had really good players, had some really good years when I was there. We had some success against them, and we had a really good team and had built our program up.”</p>
<p>CLOSING TIME?</p>
<p>Florida coach Dan Mullen wants the Gators to finish games better.</p>
<p>They could have put Ole Miss away in the opener but kicked three consecutive field goals in the second half, including two from inside the 20-yard line. Last week against South Carolina, Florida threw an interception and went three-and-out on back-to-back drives in the fourth.</p>
<p>“Finishing is a big thing for us,” pass rusher Brenton Cox said. “As the season goes on, we’ll connect, we’ll come together, we’ll come together for the win. I mean, the first two games, it’s always tough for any team. And I feel like we’ll get it together.”</p>
<p>MOND’S MILESTONE</p>
<p>Mond needs 125 yards passing on Saturday to pass Jerrod Johnson (8,011) for most yards passing in school history. The senior has already set Texas A&amp;M records for completions (655) and attempts (1,153). He has 23 wins in his career and a win on Saturday would tie him for fourth-most by a quarterback in school history.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">757066</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kyle Trask leads Florida into venue that inspired his name</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kyle-trask-leads-florida-into-venue-that-inspired-his-name/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 18:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=755688</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — When Florida quarterback Kyle Trask walks into Kyle Field this weekend, it surely will feel a little surreal. That&#8217;s because Trask...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — When Florida quarterback Kyle Trask walks into Kyle Field this weekend, it surely will feel a little surreal.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because Trask will come face to face with his namesake. Yes, Trask’s parents named their son after Texas A&amp;M&#8217;s century-old football stadium.</p>
<p>“That’s what I was told,” Trask said Monday.</p>
<p>He has no reason to question the story. After all, about half his family — including mom and dad — attended Texas A&amp;M. The school is about a two-hour drive from their hometown of Manvel, Texas. So Trask had plenty of loved ones around him rooting against the state’s flagship university in Austin.</p>
<p>“I was definitely raised to hate the Longhorns,” he said.</p>
<p>On Saturday, some of those relatives might be a little torn between their beloved and 21st-ranked Aggies (1-1) and Trask and the No. 4 Gators (2-0).</p>
<p>“A lot of excitement,” Trask said. “I’m definitely going to have to get a lot of tickets for this week for a lot of family making the drive up there. It will just be an exciting time to play against a team that I grew up watching.”</p>
<p>Trask never made it to a regular-season game at Kyle Field, but he did get to see a spring game featuring reigning Heisman Trophy winner Johnny Manziel in 2013. Trask was a freshman at Manvel High at the time, in the early stages of a seven-year stretch as a backup quarterback.</p>
<p>He played behind current Miami starter D’Eriq King in high school and never got a sniff from the nearby Aggies.</p>
<p>“Not that I remember,” he said. “Obviously, I wasn’t really highly recruited. I think they already had their quarterback for that class and I don’t think I really got any contact from them or any big-time schools for the most part.”</p>
<p>He landed at Florida in 2016 and then had to wait his turn behind Austin Appleby, Luke Del Rio, Feleipe Franks and Malik Zaire.</p>
<p>Now, he’s tearing it up as the Gators’ most entrenched starter since 2007 Heisman Trophy winner Tim Tebow.</p>
<p>A year after replacing Franks at Kentucky and finishing with the most TD passes (25) for a Florida quarterback since Tebow’s senior season in 2010, Trask leads the Southeastern Conference with 10 TD tosses in two games.</p>
<p>He’s completed 51 of 71 passes for 684 yards, with just two mistakes: an interception and a fumble in a 38-24 victory against South Carolina that helped the Gamecocks keep it close.</p>
<p>Errors aside, he’s given the Florida faithful a strong belief that the Gators can compete for the conference and national championships in Trask’s senior season.</p>
<p>“Obviously, he throws a very catchable ball,” offensive coordinator Brian Johnson said. “He has the ability to drive it, to touch it. But I think the biggest attribute is he plays with such a great sense of anticipation and understanding when things are supposed to come open.</p>
<p>“And he does a great job of playing with eyes and trusting what he sees. And guys have made plays around him.”</p>
<p>With the 6-foot-5 Trask leading the way, the Gators have scored 85 points in two games against two of the worst defensive teams in the league in 2019.</p>
<p>They expect a tougher test from the Aggies, who beat Vanderbilt 17-12 in the opener and then got blown out at No. 2 Alabama. The Tide’s Mac Jones threw for 435 yards and four touchdowns in the 52-24 drubbing.</p>
<p>Trask would love to put up similar numbers, especially in front of so many friends and family members and in the place that bears his name.</p>
<p>“I’m sure it will be a kind of homecoming for him,” receiver Trent Whittemore said. “And it’ll be special for him to play well.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">755688</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 5 Florida beats Ole Miss 51-35 in Kiffin&#8217;s debut</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-5-florida-beats-ole-miss-51-35-in-kiffins-debut/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=748470</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[OXFORD, Miss. (AP) — Kyle Pitts gives Florida an almost unfair advantage. The star tight end caught four of Kyle Trask’s six touchdown passes and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OXFORD, Miss. (AP) — Kyle Pitts gives Florida an almost unfair advantage.</p>
<p>The star tight end caught four of Kyle Trask’s six touchdown passes and No. 5 Florida spoiled the head coaching debut of Mississippi’s Lane Kiffin with a 51-35 victory Saturday.</p>
<p>Trask completed 30 of 42 passes for 416 yards including touchdown passes of 1, 16, 71 and 17 yards to Pitts. The star tight end had 170 yards receiving on eight catches.</p>
<p>Trask directed four consecutive touchdown drives that spanned the second and third quarters to build a 41-14 lead for the Gators (1-0 Southeastern Conference).</p>
<p>Trask modestly chose to deflect the attention to 6-foot-6, 240-pound Pitts, who consistently found seams in the Ole Miss secondary.</p>
<p>“He is a match up nightmare for defenses,” Trask said. “He’s too big for cornerbacks and too fast for linebackers so it gives defenses lots of trouble and that’s what you like to see.”</p>
<p>After an unusual offseason, filled with uncertainty because of the pandemic, just playing was a victory.</p>
<p>“You know what? the question of are we playing next week, when can we play, how long is training camp, when is this ever going to happen, when are we ever going to get to a game?&#8221; said Mullen, who coached nine years at Mississippi State and went 5-4 against the Rebels. &#8220;We got to a game. It’s a great day for us and a great win.”</p>
<p>Kiffin, the former Tennessee and USC head coach who came to Ole Miss from FAU, had the Rebels’ offense humming with Matt Corral at quarterback.</p>
<p>Corral completed 22 of 31 passes for 395 yards and three touchdowns passes, two to Dontario Drummond.</p>
<p>But they couldn’t stop the Gators. Ole Miss (0-1) tied it at 14 midway through the second quarter before yielding to the Trask-led Florida outburst.</p>
<p>“We had a lot of chances to make plays to change the outcome” Kiffin said.</p>
<p>“When you play the No. 5 team in the nation, you can’t make mistakes like we did if you want to win. We’re 0-1 and we’ve got to go on the road and find a way to get to 1-1.”</p>
<p>The teams combined for 1,255 yards of total offense, including 642 by the Gators.</p>
<p>Trevon Grimes and Kedarius Toney had touchdown receptions of 22 and 16 yards respectively, for Florida. Jerrion Ealy and Snoop Conner had touchdown runs and Kenny Yoboah added a touchdown reception for the Rebels.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Florida: The already high expectations for Mullen’s third team should only go up a notch. Along with the formidable offense, the kicking game was highlighted by three field goals by Evan McPherson, including a 55-yarder with room to spare. Brenton Cox Jr. led the defense that had 11 tackles for loss and a turnover,</p>
<p>Ole Miss: The Rebels featured a completely new coaching staff with scheme changes. Spring practice did not happen. An influx of newcomers and coronavirus testing protocols shuffled the depth charts. Expectations were cautiously optimistic for Kiffin’s home debut in front of an enthusiastic crowd of 16,010 and nearly 600 fan cutouts purchased at $55 apiece. The Rebels answered with an impressive offensive performance, led by Elijah Moore’s 227 yards receiving.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don’t care about individual stats, I care about winning,” said Moore, who finished with 10 receptions and had another touchdown catch erased on a holding penalty. “We didn’t win, so it doesn’t matter.”</p>
<p>STATEMENT</p>
<p>Before the opening kick, players from each team took a knee to acknowledge racial injustice in the United States.</p>
<p>Both teams put out statements on social media right before the game started.</p>
<p>“As members of the Florida and Ole Miss football teams, we recognize the impact of our personal platforms and are choosing to amplify the issues that directly impact us. Together we have chosen to take the opening series of today’s competition to acknowledge the unrest in our country surrounding the treatment of African Americans. We will continue to support social justice efforts as members of the Southeastern Conference and members of our respective communities.”</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Six SEC teams, including the fifth-ranked Gators, are among the top 10 teams in the poll. The impressive performance secures them a poll slot among the elite, but moving up will be difficult.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators host South Carolina Saturday. The home opener will be the second successive early morning kickoff for Florida.</p>
<p>Ole Miss: The Rebels visit No. 23 Kentucky Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">748470</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida opens practice short-handed, Mullen expects opt-outs</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-opens-practice-short-handed-mullen-expects-opt-outs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=713020</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida coach Dan Mullen had several players miss the team’s opening training camp practice Monday. Mullen declined to provide names, but...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida coach Dan Mullen had several players miss the team’s opening training camp practice Monday.</p>
<p>Mullen declined to provide names, but the Orlando Sentinel and Sports Illustrated reported that four guys — receivers Kadarius Toney, Trevon Grimes and Jacob Copeland and defensive end Zachary Carter — skipped the session.</p>
<p>“We had a couple guys not practice today, but we’ll see how that goes moving forward for us,” Mullen said during a Zoom call with reporters. “But, you know, I wouldn’t be surprised if you have guys opt out. I’m going to support them fully. Really wouldn’t be surprised if we had coaches opt out, to be honest with you. Coaches are at such high risk because of the age group that they’re in.</p>
<p>“But we’ll figure it out.”</p>
<p>It’s unclear if the players’ absences were related to the coronavirus pandemic. Toney and Copeland expressed concerns earlier this month about playing amid a global health crisis.</p>
<p>Toney wrote on Twitter that sitting out “might be the better decision.” Copeland responded that Toney might have the right idea and tweeted, “Health over football,” followed by a thumbs-up emoji.</p>
<p>Carter, meanwhile, has supported the #WeAreUnited campaign started by Pac-12 players earlier this month. His father, Frank Carter, told Rivals that his son has significant concerns.</p>
<p>“First of all, he’s my son and I support him,” Frank Carter told the recruiting website. “He told me he wants to play, but he just doesn’t feel safe right now. We’ve had a couple friends of the family who’ve passed away from the effects of COVID. Now some players in other conferences are having issues with their heart.</p>
<p>“I think all of that is kind of alarming to him. There’s really not enough research or data to give him information that can put his mind at ease, so he’s just taking the cautious route.”</p>
<p>The elder Carter also told Rivals something he said he hasn’t shared with his son.</p>
<p>“I went through it,” he said. “I was having those night sweats and I couldn’t consume enough liquid to keep me from being dehydrated, so I had to get rushed to the hospital because my wife said I was hallucinating. I didn’t tell Zach any of this stuff.”</p>
<p>Two hours after Mullen’s news conference, Grimes posted on Twitter, “Don’t believe everything you read.” He did not elaborate.</p>
<p>Florida is scheduled to open Sept. 26 at Mississippi, which is entering its first season under coach Lane Kiffin. The next five weeks will be critical in getting to the opener.</p>
<p>Two Power Five conferences — the Big Ten and the Pac-12 — already have postponed their football seasons because of coronavirus concerns.</p>
<p>The Gators had 21 players test positive for COVID-19 since returning to campus in late May. They’ve had no positives or anyone quarantined because of exposure over the past four weeks.</p>
<p>“Statistically speaking off of that, we’re — off of those numbers — you would think the safe place to be is practicing football and doing organized team activities because that’s where our numbers greatly decreased,” Mullen said. “That’s the information we have now. That’s why I feel comfortable.</p>
<p>“I can’t tell you what’s going to happen long-term, but our guys have handled everything really well. I think our medical staff, UF people that have helped our medical staff here within the athletic department, have done an amazing job creating a safe environment for our players and the coaches as well.”</p>
<p>The Gators will get another challenge this weekend when students start returning to campus.</p>
<p>“We’re going to adapt to whatever happens as we continue to move forward,” Mullen said. “I think it’s the team that’s able to adapt best to whatever situation — there’s a lot of moving parts — and the team that’s able to adapt will end up holding up that national championship trophy at the end of the season.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">713020</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen-2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">191002 dan mullen 2</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Univ. of Florida ends &#8216;gator bait&#8217; cheer, cites racism</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/univ-of-florida-ends-gator-bait-cheer-cites-racism/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 12:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=669388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — The University of Florida is ending its “gator bait” cheer at football games and other sports events because of its...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — The University of Florida is ending its “gator bait” cheer at football games and other sports events because of its racial connotations, the school&#8217;s president announced Thursday in a letter making several other similar changes on campus.</p>
<p>Florida president Kent Fuchs said <a href="http://statements.ufl.edu/statements/2020/june/another-step-toward-positive-change-against-racism.html">in a letter</a> to the university&#8217;s faculty, students and staff that the cheer has a “horrific historic racist imagery” involving African American people, especially children, being used as bait for alligators.</p>
<p>“Accordingly, university athletics and the Gator Band will discontinue the use of the cheer,&#8221; Fuchs wrote.</p>
<p>The university&#8217;s sports teams in the Southeastern Conference are nicknamed the Gators, for the ubiquitous Florida reptile. In the past, the school&#8217;s band would strike up a “gator bait” tune and fans would respond with their arms doing a chomping motion while shouting the slogan.</p>
<p>The link to racism is borne out by news articles in years past. For example, in 1923, Time Magazine published a story about how “colored babies were being used for alligator bait” in Chipley, Florida.</p>
<p>“The infants are allowed to play in the shallow water while expert riflemen watch from concealment nearby,&#8221; the article said. &#8220;When a saurian (alligator) approaches this prey, he is shot by the riflemen.” The Chipley Chamber of Commerce responded to the Time article by calling it a “silly lie, false and absurd.”</p>
<p>The letter from Fuchs outlined a number of other steps the university in Gainesville, Florida, is taking on racial issues following the death of George Floyd at the hands of Minneapolis police. Floyd&#8217;s death has sparked nationwide protests focused on police brutality against African Americans.</p>
<p>Among other things, Fuchs said the university will require students, faculty and staff to be trained on “racism, inclusion and bias” and will also bring a new focus on the African American experience in the upcoming academic year.</p>
<p>The University of Florida, one of the state&#8217;s largest universities with about 55,000 students, is expected to reopen in the fall semester with restrictions related to the coronavirus outbreak.</p>
<p>In his letter, Fuchs said the school will look into a number of other race-related topics. These include one task force to document the university&#8217;s history regarding race and ethnicity, and a second task force to examine the reasons behind honorary namings on campus.</p>
<p>“I am personally committed to removing any monuments or namings that UF can control that celebrate the Confederacy or its leaders,” Fuchs wrote.</p>
<p>Fuchs said that he is ending the university&#8217;s practice of using prison and jail inmates as farm labor in some of its agricultural programs. He also said the university will redouble its efforts to recruit and retain African American students, faculty and staff.</p>
<p>“It is past time for UF to commit and engage in this challenging, uncomfortable, transformational work,” Fuchs wrote in the letter. “We know that we cannot undo lifetimes of injustice and racism, but we believe we can make progress — in education, in advancing truth, reconciliation and justice, and in anti-racism, equality and working to eradicate inequities.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">669388</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/gator-fans-e1592568476160.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/gator-fans-e1592568476160.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/gator-fans-e1592568476160.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">gator fans</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>University of Florida ends &#8216;gator bait&#8217; cheer over racial connotations</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/university-of-florida-ends-gator-bait-cheer-over-racial-connotations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=668932</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) &#8212; The University of Florida is ending its &#8220;gator bait&#8221; cheer at football games and other sports events because of its...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) &#8212; The University of Florida is ending its &#8220;gator bait&#8221; cheer at football games and other sports events because of its racial connotations, the school&#8217;s president announced Thursday in a letter making several other similar changes on campus.</p>
<p>Florida president Kent Fuchs said in a letter to the university&#8217;s faculty, students and staff that the cheer has a &#8220;horrific historic racist imagery&#8221; involving African American people, especially children, being used as bait for alligators.</p>
<p>&#8220;Accordingly, university athletics and the Gator Band will discontinue the use of the cheer,&#8221; Fuchs wrote.</p>
<p>The university&#8217;s sports teams in the Southeastern Conference are nicknamed the Gators, for the ubiquitous Florida reptile. In the past, the school&#8217;s band would strike up a &#8220;gator bait&#8221; tune and fans would respond with their arms doing a chomping motion while shouting the slogan.</p>
<p>The letter outlined a number of other steps the university in Gainesville, Florida, is taking on racial issues following the death of George Floyd at the hands of Minneapolis police. Floyd&#8217;s death has sparked nationwide protests focused on police brutality against African Americans.</p>
<p>Among other things, Fuchs said the university will require students, faculty and staff to be trained on &#8220;racism, inclusion and bias&#8221; and will also bring a new focus on the African American experience in the upcoming academic year.</p>
<p>The University of Florida, the state&#8217;s largest with about 52,000 students, is expected to reopen in the fall semester with restrictions related to the coronavirus outbreak.</p>
<p>In his letter, Fuchs said the school will look into a number of other race-related topics. These include one task force to document the university&#8217;s history regarding race and ethnicity, and a second task force to examine the reasons behind honorary namings on campus.</p>
<p>&#8220;I am personally committed to removing any monuments or namings that UF can control that celebrate the Confederacy or its leaders,&#8221; Fuchs wrote.</p>
<p>Fuchs said that he is ending the university&#8217;s practice of using prison and jail inmates as farm labor in some of its agricultural programs. He also said the university will redouble its efforts to recruit and retain African American students, faculty and staff.</p>
<p>&#8220;It is past time for UF to commit and engage in this challenging, uncomfortable, transformational work,&#8221; Fuchs wrote in the letter. &#8220;We know that we cannot undo lifetimes of injustice and racism, but we believe we can make progress &#8212; in education, in advancing truth, reconciliation and justice, and in anti-racism, equality and working to eradicate inequities.&#8221;</p>
<p>Correction: University of Florida is one of the largest universities in Florida.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">668932</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/171024_university_of_florida_uf_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/171024_university_of_florida_uf_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/171024_university_of_florida_uf_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">171024_university_of_florida_uf_sign</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 6 Kentucky rallies from 18 down, stuns Florida 71-70</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-6-kentucky-rallies-from-18-down-stuns-florida-71-70/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 03:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=604664</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kentucky coach John Calipari went around the locker room at halftime and picked on just about everyone. His harshest criticism was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Kentucky coach John Calipari went around the locker room at halftime and picked on just about everyone. His harshest criticism was directed toward star forward Nick Richards.</p>
<p>“Nick, you are so bad right now,&#8221; Calipari recalled. &#8220;We&#8217;re not going away from you, so you can either be the player you&#8217;ve been all year or look like this.”</p>
<p>Richards chose option No. 1. The junior scored 17 of his 19 points in the second half, leading the way as the sixth-ranked Wildcats rallied from an 18-point deficit and stunned Florida 71-70 on Saturday.</p>
<p>The shorthanded Wildcats (25-6, 15-3 Southeastern Conference) needed the comeback to avoid losing consecutive games for the first time in nearly three months. They blew an 17-point lead against Tennessee on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Richards, Keion Brooks Jr. and EJ Montgomery provided the spark in this one, helping make up for the absence of point guard Ashton Hagans.</p>
<p>Hagans didn’t make the trip three days after arguing with Calipari on the bench against the Volunteers.</p>
<p>“Just personal,” Calipari said. “Here&#8217;s what I&#8217;ll tell you about these kids: In the last three years, this has totally changed. What is on these players. &#8230; The clutter that they got to deal with, the lists, what&#8217;s out there, not being able to stay in the moment, the anxiety of worrying a year from now, everyone around them.</p>
<p>&#8220;And then you&#8217;re at Kentucky, where every game is someone&#8217;s Super Bowl, every game is sold out and now all of a sudden you start struggling four of five games and now you don&#8217;t know how to deal with stuff.”</p>
<p>Calipari said he expects Hagans to return before next week&#8217;s SEC Tournament in Nashville, Tennessee. Kentucky is the No. 1 seed and opens play Friday following a double bye.</p>
<p>“Hopefully what you&#8217;ll see is an inspired young man,&#8221; Calipari said. &#8220;And if he doesn&#8217;t think he&#8217;s ready for that, then he&#8217;s not ready. We&#8217;re going to go without whoever we have.”</p>
<p>Kentucky showed a little depth without Hagans and guard Immanuel Quickley, who fouled out with about nine minutes remaining. Quickley finished with 12 points. Freshman guard Johnny Juzang scored 10 points while playing a season-high 32 minutes. But the frontcourt did most of the heavy lifting down the stretch.</p>
<p>Brooks hit a floater in the lane with 59 second remaining to cut the lead to 70-69. Florida answered with a shot-clock violation on the other end.</p>
<p>Brooks missed a driving baseline layup, and Montgomery&#8217;s tip-in was initially waived off as a cylinder violation. Officials reviewed it and gave Montgomery the basket with 11.8 seconds left for a 71-70 Wildcats&#8217; lead, their first of the game.</p>
<p>Richards missed the front end of a one-and-one, giving Florida a final chance to win it. But Andrew Nembhard&#8217;s 3-pointer bounced twice off the rim before missing, setting off Kentucky&#8217;s raucous celebration.</p>
<p>Richards was 1-for-6 shooting in the first half. He was 7 of 11 after the break.</p>
<p>“Coaches gave me the challenge to see if I could turn it around,” Richards said. “I took on that challenge. Obviously, we came out with a really big win.&#8221;</p>
<p>Scottie Lewis scored a career-high 19 for Florida (19-12, 11-7). Noah Locke added 14, and Keyontae Johnson 12. Florida led by 18 points with 11:48 left in the game.</p>
<p>The Gators played most of the second half with standout forward Kerry Blackshear Jr. Blackshear sprained his left wrist in the first half. He went to the locker room and returned with it heavily taped. He tried to play in the second half, but he ended up on the bench with it wrapped in ice.</p>
<p>Blackshear was scoreless for the first time all season. He had five rebounds. Without him, Kentucky had a much easier time in the paint.</p>
<p>“Obviously, that&#8217;s big for us, a big loss defensively and offensively,&#8221; Lewis said. &#8220;He&#8217;s someone that can go get an easy bucket for us.”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Kentucky: The Wildcats need Hagans back to make a deep postseason run. They&#8217;re simply not the same without arguably the league&#8217;s best perimeter defender and open-court playmakers.</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators have to wait and see their seeding. They will be either No. 4 or 5 depending on Mississippi State&#8217;s outcome tonight.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Kentucky: Gets an extended break before playing in the quarterfinals of the SEC Tournament on Friday in Nashville.</p>
<p>Florida: Awaits seeding in the SEC Tournament. Will begin play Thursday or Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">604664</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tennessee hold off Florida 63-58 behind Fulkerson</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tennessee-hold-off-florida-63-58-behind-fulkerson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 23:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=597998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — John Fulkerson knew the shot clock was winding down and Tennessee needed something to halt a furious Florida comeback. Fulkerson set...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — John Fulkerson knew the shot clock was winding down and Tennessee needed something to halt a furious Florida comeback.</p>
<p>Fulkerson set his feet and let a 3-point shot fly from near the top of the key. The junior forward had only attempted one other 3-pointer in his entire career, and missed.</p>
<p>But his second attempt hit nothing but net, and helped the Vols secure their biggest victory of the season.</p>
<p>Fulkerson scored 22 points, including his clutch 3 and a tip dunk down the stretch, as Tennessee held on to beat Florida 63-58 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Tennessee (16-13, 8-8 SEC) led by 19 points with nine minutes remaining, but saw the Gators claw back behind Tre Mann and Kerry Blackshear Jr.</p>
<p>Florida (18-11, 10-6) got as close as one point in the final three minutes, but Fulkerson&#8217;s 3-pointer stemmed the rally.</p>
<p>&#8220;I was talking to Kerry Blackshear down at the other end and I was like, &#8216;That was God right there,'&#8221; said Fulkerson, who missed his only other career 3-point attempt against Arkansas earlier this season. &#8220;He said &#8216;good shot,&#8217; and I was like, &#8216;I really can&#8217;t take credit for it.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The Vols defeated Florida for the fourth straight time, and have won five of the last six against the Gators.</p>
<p>Tennessee&#8217;s defense put the clamps on Florida in the first half, forcing turnovers, charges and a shot clock violation.</p>
<p>The Vols closed the half on a 16-3 run, highlighted by back-to-back 3-pointers from Jordan Bowden and Santiago Vescovi, to carry a 32-17 lead into halftime.</p>
<p>Florida had 11 turnovers, leading to 13 Tennessee points, and was 6 of 18 from the field and 1 for 7 from 3-point range through the first 20 minutes.</p>
<p>&#8220;I thought Tennessee was really disruptive and I thought they did a really good job with pressuring us, especially in the first half,&#8221; Florida head coach Mike White said. &#8220;We played unsettled and somewhat rattled in the first 25 minutes of the game. I think Tennessee had a lot to do with that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tennessee expanded its lead to 48-29 on a play that sent the crowd, which included former UT quarterback great Heath Shuler and basketball star Dale Ellis, into a tizzy.</p>
<p>Some good ball movement that started with a behind-the-head pass by Vescovi ended with a Fulkerson dunk with 11:44 remaining.</p>
<p>Mann and Blackshear Jr. sparked Florida&#8217;s comeback on offense while Scottie Lewis tightened the defense. The Gators embarked on a 25-7 run to cut Tennessee&#8217;s lead to 55-54 with under three minutes remaining.</p>
<p>But Fulkerson swished his 3-pointer and then soared above the rim for a putback dunk to keep the Vols barely in front for the remainder.</p>
<p>After Fulkerson&#8217;s emphatic flush, the Tennessee fans began chanting &#8220;Fulky, Fulky, Fulky.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;If someone asked me if I ever thought I would be playing in a Tennessee game and they would be chanting &#8216;Fulky,&#8217; I would have never guessed it in my wildest dreams,&#8221; Fulkerson said. &#8220;It is like a dream come true. I am so blessed to be in the position I am and to be able to make some good plays.&#8221;</p>
<p>White wasn&#8217;t surprised by the Fulkerson&#8217;s production.</p>
<p>&#8220;I thought he had the best motor in the league,&#8221; White said. &#8220;I think he plays as hard as anyone in the SEC.&#8221;</p>
<p>Freshman Josiah-Jordan James scored 12 points, including 10 in the first half, and added eight rebounds and six assists for Tennessee. Vescovi finished with 11 points and Bowden had 10.</p>
<p>The Vols shot 52.1% from the field (25 of 48), and had only nine turnovers after reaching double-digits in many games.</p>
<p>Blackshear Jr., a graduate senior who considered Tennessee when he transferred to Florida from Virginia Tech, finished with 20 points and nine rebounds to lead the Gators. Noah Locke had 15 points and Mann scored all nine of his points in the second half.</p>
<p>&#8220;I told the team, as much as a coach I would have liked to have a little bit more comfort at the end of the game, the way we won the game was probably better for us because we have lost so many like that,&#8221; Tennessee head coach Rick Barnes said.</p>
<p>ROCKY TOP HOMECOMING</p>
<p>Florida freshman guard Ques Glover returned home to play. The Knoxville native attended Bearden High, where he was teammates with Tennessee freshman Drew Pember.</p>
<p>Glover was 0 for 1 from the field in 19 minutes. Pember missed his second straight game while in concussion protocol.</p>
<p>Glover and Pember played Fortnite together during the week leading up to the game, but Glover said they didn&#8217;t engage in any trash talk.</p>
<p>Glover attended games at Thompson-Boling Arena when he was growing up, and had plenty of friends and family in the stands supporting him. To his disappointment, he said he didn&#8217;t receive an offer from Tennessee coming out of high school.</p>
<p>SWEET SURPRISE</p>
<p>Tennessee freshman guard Santiago Vescovi got a surprise from his family. His parents, Pablo and Laura, and his sister, Lucia, traveled from Montevideo, Uruguay, to Knoxville for the first time to watch him play. They snuck up behind Vescovi before the game, and the family shared a big group hug once he realized it was them. Vescovi was a mid-year enrollee, and arrived at Tennessee on Dec. 28.</p>
<p>BIC PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida seems safely in the NCAA Tournament with two regular-season games remaining, but the Gators didn&#8217;t help their resume with the road loss to a team nowhere near the NCAA bubble.</p>
<p>There is no NCAA Tournament in the future for Tennessee unless it makes a run and win the SEC tournament. But beating a rival is always good motivation. The Vols have two more chances with games against Kentucky and Auburn to close out the regular season.</p>
<p>Up Next</p>
<p>Florida: Gators are at Georgia on March 4 at 7 p.m. ET</p>
<p>Tennessee: Vols are at Kentucky on March 3 at 9 p.m. ET</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">597998</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quickley&#8217;s 26 points lift No. 10 Kentucky past Florida 65-59</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/quickleys-26-points-lift-no-10-kentucky-past-florida-65-59/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 04:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=593889</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LEXINGTON, Ky. (AP) &#8211; John Calipari praised Immanuel Quickley&#8217;s basketball savvy, but only after the Kentucky coach and an assistant first challenged the guard to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LEXINGTON, Ky. (AP) &#8211; John Calipari praised Immanuel Quickley&#8217;s basketball savvy, but only after the Kentucky coach and an assistant first challenged the guard to shoot the ball &#8211; or else.</p>
<p>&#8220;I said, &#8216;If you don&#8217;t shoot open shots, I&#8217;m putting Johnny (Juzang) in because I know he will shoot every shot,&#8221; Calipari said.</p>
<p>Quickley got the message and responded with a career game that helped the No. 10 Wildcats earn another hard-fought victory.</p>
<p>He scored a career-high 26 points, including 15 of Kentucky&#8217;s 17 during a decisive second-half stretch as the 10th-ranked Wildcats pushed past Florida 65-59 on Saturday night for their sixth consecutive win.</p>
<p>Quickley made 4 of 6 from 3-point range and 8 of 17 shots overall to surpass his previous high of 23 points at Auburn on Feb. 1. He scored all but four of his points in the second half. Tyrese Maxey had 13 points for first-place Kentucky (22-5, 12-2 Southeastern Conference), which leads No. 13 Auburn and LSU by two games and took a three-game lead over Florida (17-10, 9-5).</p>
<p>Kentucky&#8217;s leading scorer is on a 16-game run of double-digit scoring performances. Nonetheless, Quickley has taken some ribbing for failing to crack 25 points like teammates Nick Richards and Maxey. Against Florida, he was all but threatened to shoot instead of passing, as he did with open looks in the first half.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t want to say who it was, but one of the coaches yelled at me with some pretty choice words,&#8221; Quickley said. &#8220;For lack of a better term, he said, &#8216;You need to score.&#8217; So, that kind of got me.</p>
<p>&#8220;I didn&#8217;t think I was dribbling to pass, I thought I was just making plays. But it happens sometimes, coaches see one thing and a player sees another.&#8221;</p>
<p>A Rupp Arena crowd of 20,489 &#8211; including former Kentucky star John Wall of the Washington Wizards &#8211; eventually saw bigger things for Quickley, with fans chanting &#8220;MVP! MVP!&#8221; at him. He is building a case to be considered for SEC Player of the Year.</p>
<p>&#8220;He was the best player on the floor,&#8221; Gators coach Mike White said of Quickley. &#8220;I thought he did a great job finding space, searching. Hit huge shots, and complemented that with terrific defense on the perimeter.&#8221;</p>
<p>Keyontae Johnson had 19 points and Kerry Blackshear Jr. scored 18 for the Gators, who had won their previous three games and five of six.</p>
<p>A back-and-forth game featuring 11 lead changes and 10 ties swung Kentucky&#8217;s way midway through the second half thanks to Quickley, who knocked down three consecutive 3-pointers for a 50-44 lead with 11:20 remaining. The sophomore guard&#8217;s 3 with 1:34 left provided an eight-point cushion.</p>
<p>But Florida rallied within 61-59 on Scottie Lewis&#8217; tip of his missed free throw with 19 seconds left.</p>
<p>Maxey converted a 1-and-1, and Ashton Hagans made a steal that led to Quickley adding two free thows with 1.9 seconds left.</p>
<p>Florida outrebounded Kentucky 30-27 but committed 16 turnovers, leading to 20 points.</p>
<p>RELIEF ROLE</p>
<p>Hagans didn&#8217;t start after injuring his leg at LSU but entered the game early and finished with seven points, four assists and six turnovers in 34 minutes.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was dangerous what I did with Ashton because if he got hit right on that spot, he&#8217;s probably out three games,&#8221; Calipari said. &#8220;Not real smart. But he said, &#8216;I can do this, I&#8217;ll play.'&#8221;</p>
<p>TUNING OUT NOISE</p>
<p>Blackshear visited Kentucky last summer before eventually transferring to Florida, and Wildcats fans let him know with boos every time he touched the ball. He shot 6 of 14 and 2 of 6 from deep and helped keep Florida in the game.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: Blackshear&#8217;s perimeter shooting and Johnson&#8217;s work inside helped the Gators early. After taking their last lead at 44-41, the Gators made one of their next 11 from the field and struggled to stop Quickley. They were also outscored 36-26 in the paint.</p>
<p>Kentucky: A strong inside presence helped keep the Wildcats within range until Quickley caught fire. Two three-point plays got him started before his string of 3s made the difference in a game where every possession mattered.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts LSU on Wednesday night, aiming to avenge an 84-82 loss to the Tigers on Jan. 21.</p>
<p>Kentucky visits Texas A&amp;M on Tuesday night in the lone regular season matchup with the Aggies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">593889</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nembhard scores 24 as Gators beat Aggies 78-61</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nembhard-scores-24-as-gators-beat-aggies-78-61/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 04:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=589070</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) &#8212; Florida coach Mike White raved about his team&#8217;s performance on offense after the Gators routed Texas A&#38;M on Wednesday night....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) &#8212; Florida coach Mike White raved about his team&#8217;s performance on offense after the Gators routed Texas A&amp;M on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>&#8220;We really moved the ball well,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It was the best we&#8217;ve moved the ball all year. That&#8217;s as well as we&#8217;ve played offensively all year.&#8221;</p>
<p>Andrew Nembhard scored 24 points and Florida used a big run early in the second half to take control of the game and cruise to the 78-61 win.</p>
<p>Noah Locke added 21 points for the Gators (15-9, 7-4 Southeastern Conference), who bounced back from a close loss to Ole Miss in their last game.</p>
<p>&#8220;For us to come in here and score 78, obviously we did a lot well offensively,&#8221; White said. &#8220;With this team we&#8217;ve struggled at times against really good defenses, especially on the road. So that&#8217;s about as well as we&#8217;ve played.&#8221;</p>
<p>Texas A&amp;M (11-12, 5-6) cut its deficit to two points on a 3-pointer by Emanuel Miller early in the second half before the Gators used a 14-4 run to make it 53-41 with about 11 minutes to go. Keyontae Johnson scored six points during that span. The 6-foot-5 sophomore finished with 10 points, 10 rebounds &#8212; his second consecutive double-double &#8212; and a career-high six assists.</p>
<p>Texas A&amp;M&#8217;s only points in that stretch came on free throws as the Aggies went almost eight minutes without making a field goal.</p>
<p>&#8220;Their team is so good,&#8221; Texas A&amp;M coach Buzz Williams said. &#8220;They put stress on you in every possible way.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was Miller who finally made A&amp;M&#8217;s next basket, but it didn&#8217;t get the Aggies going and the Gators went on a 10-2 run after that to make it 63-45 with 7 1/2 minutes to go. Scottie Lewis and Tre Mann made 3-pointers to lead Florida in that run.</p>
<p>Locke made five 3-pointers for the Gators to give him at least one 3 in 22 straight games, which is tied for the 10th-longest streak in school history.</p>
<p>Miller had 19 points for the Aggies, who lost their second straight game and for the third time in four games.</p>
<p>Williams was disappointed that Florida got 14 offensive rebounds on 25 missed shots.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s hard for any team to overcome,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>THE BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators showed flashes of solid play, especially in the second half when they took over the game, but they will need to limit their mistakes and turnovers as they continue SEC play. They had 14 turnovers on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Texas A&amp;M: The Aggies have to find a way to be more effective on offense and simply can&#8217;t go minutes at a time without a basket if they hope to get on track.</p>
<p>BLACKSHEAR FACING BUZZ</p>
<p>Kerry Blackshear Jr. had eight points and three rebounds. Blackshear played for Williams at Virginia Tech last season before joining the Gators as a graduate transfer.</p>
<p>White said he asked Blackshear earlier in the week if he&#8217;d have any added emotion in facing his former coach and he told him he wasn&#8217;t even thinking about that.</p>
<p>&#8220;He said: `we need a `W&#8217; I&#8217;m more concerned about how we&#8217;re playing and how I can help this team win,'&#8221; White said. &#8220;He&#8217;s a really really good kid &#8230; and I don&#8217;t know where we&#8217;d be without him.&#8221;</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts Vanderbilt on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Texas A&amp;M hosts Georgia on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">589070</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tyree leads Ole Miss to win over Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tyree-leads-ole-miss-to-win-over-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 01:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=586927</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[OXFORD, Miss. (AP) &#8212; The second season, proclaimed by Mississippi coach Kermit Davis as the month of February, has been a rousing success after two...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OXFORD, Miss. (AP) &#8212; The second season, proclaimed by Mississippi coach Kermit Davis as the month of February, has been a rousing success after two games.</p>
<p>Breein Tyree scored 23 points as the Rebels won successive SEC games for the first time this season with a 68-51 win over Florida Saturday, snapping a two-game winning streak by the Gators.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve totally shifted our focus to February and our players have bought into that,&#8221; Davis said. &#8220;We never felt like we were not a good team, it just did not show on our record. We kept working and now we&#8217;ve built confidence with a couple of wins.&#8221;</p>
<p>Devontae Shuler and KJ Buffen scored 14 points apiece as Ole Miss (12-11, 3-7 Southeastern Conference) never trailed after the opening two minutes.</p>
<p>Buffen had a team-high nine rebounds, while Shuler added a game-high five assists.</p>
<p>Florida (14-9, 6-4 SEC) was led by Keyontae Johnson and Kerry Blackshear Jr. with 16 and 11 points, respectively. The Gators trailed 21-8 after nine minutes, 33-27 at halftime and did not cut the margin to single digits in the final 10 minutes.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s unfortunate we&#8217;re a team that puts ourselves in that position,&#8221; Florida coach Mike White said. &#8220;When you make these comebacks, you feel great about the results but not great about the whole 40 minutes. Tonight our goal was to play the whole 40 and it would&#8217;ve taken that to win. We played well for about 25.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ole Miss shot 26 of 55 (47.3%), 7 of 16 (43.8%) from 3-point range, including four by Tyree. Florida struggled offensively with 15 turnovers and shot 18 of 54 (33.3%) from the field and 5 of 23 (21%) from beyond the arc. The Rebels outscored Florida 16-7 off the turnovers.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators have won twice in SEC play by wiping out deficits of 20 points or more, but could not erase the 13-point deficit established in the opening nine minutes. It was an unhappy homecoming for White, a former Ole Miss captain and four-year starter at point guard, who led the Rebels to a pair of SEC West Division titles and three NCAA Tournament appearances.</p>
<p>&#8220;They defended better than us. They rebounded better than us. They coached better than us,&#8221; White said. &#8220;We&#8217;ve got to ask ourselves as a team why are we down 22? Why are we down like we were today? They played better than us.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ole Miss: After a frustrating January of near misses, the Rebels won consecutive SEC games after losing eight of the previous nine games. Tyree is arguably the league&#8217;s best offensive performer, but lately he has gotten help from an improved defense and scoring help from Shuler and Buffen, especially during a decisive 13-3 run that built an insurmountable 48-36 lead with 12:19 left.</p>
<p>&#8220;We defended today for 40 minutes; the best we&#8217;ve defended all year long,&#8221; Davis said. &#8220;We&#8217;re going to need that again because we are playing a really outstanding Mississippi State team in here on Tuesday night.&#8221;</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: Visits Texas A&amp;M on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Ole Miss: Hosts Mississippi State on Tuesday to complete a three-game home stand.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">586927</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida hands Vanderbilt its 26th straight SEC loss</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-hands-vanderbilt-its-26th-straight-sec-loss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=584150</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Keyontae Johnson and Noah Locke helped Florida end its three-game losing streak. Johnson scored 20 points and Locke added 17 as...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Keyontae Johnson and Noah Locke helped Florida end its three-game losing streak.</p>
<p>Johnson scored 20 points and Locke added 17 as the Gators beat Vanderbilt 61-55 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Florida coach Mike White said his team would have been lost without Johnson, who hit 7 of 11 from the floor and 4 of 5 from the foul line.</p>
<p>“I just thought Keyontae was as good as he’s played,” White said. “Offensively, defensively, you name it: energy, toughness. I think he got the last rebound of the game, which was pretty fitting.”</p>
<p>Florida (13-8, 5-3 Southeastern Conference) needed a win after dropping games to Mississippi State, Baylor and LSU.</p>
<p>“This game was real important,” Johnson said. “We tried to mainly focus on defense and we did good in the first half. Second half we slacked off just a little bit, but we managed to get big stops towards the end.”</p>
<p>Locke buried 5 of 8 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>“Everything fell our way toward the end,” Locke said. “We were trying to get back on track. Recently, we’ve been having a little bit of slippage.”</p>
<p>Vanderbilt (8-13, 08) suffered its 26th consecutive SEC loss, adding to the Commodores&#8217; dubious league record.</p>
<p>Florida took charge with a 10-0 run early against Vanderbilt, which had played well in a loss at Kentucky.</p>
<p>“The most that I’m disappointed by is how we started the game,” Vanderbilt Jerry Stackhouse said. “Great momentum from last game and we come out and we were just soft. In so many ways we were just soft. We’ve got to find a way to get away from that disposition.”</p>
<p>The Commodores committed 17 turnovers as they suffered their ninth straight loss overall.</p>
<p>Scotty Pippen Jr. led the Commodores with 15 points and Saben Lee added 11.</p>
<p>“Definitely, I feel like it’s one step forward and one foot back,” Pippen said. “We lost this game in the first couple of minutes. We started slow and although we fought at the end, it wasn’t enough.”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators led most of the way against the injury-plagued Commodores.</p>
<p>Vanderbilt: The Commodores continue to struggle without Aaron Nesmith (foot injury) and Clevon Brown (knee). Nesmith was leading the SEC in scoring when a stress fracture knocked him out of the lineup on Jan. 11.</p>
<p>LATE RUN</p>
<p>Vanderbilt got a roar from the crowd when it narrowed the deficit to 55-49 with just over 2 minutes left.</p>
<p>Lee’s layup through traffic cut the margin to 58-53 with 23.8 seconds left.</p>
<p>HONOREES</p>
<p>Vanderbilt honored its 1992-93 Sweet 16 team at halftime. The Commodores won their first SEC title since 1974 that year.</p>
<p>Eddie Fogler was named national coach of the year.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts Georgia (12-9, 2-6) on Wednesday. Georgia freshman Anthony Edwards is coming off a 29-point, 15-rebound game against Texas A&amp;M.</p>
<p>Vanderbilt hosts No. 22 LSU (17-4, 8-0), which has won 10 straight, on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">584150</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 1 Baylor stifles Florida 72-61 for 16th straight victory</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-1-baylor-stifles-florida-72-61-for-16th-straight-victory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 05:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=581101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; No. 1 Baylor was surprised to learn it was a slight underdog on the road against Florida. The Bears raised their...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; No. 1 Baylor was surprised to learn it was a slight underdog on the road against Florida.</p>
<p>The Bears raised their eyebrows, shook their heads, shrugged their shoulders and decided to treat it as bulletin-board material.</p>
<p>MaCio Teague and Devonte Bandoo scored 16 points apiece and Baylor extended its winning steak to 16 with a 72-61 victory over the Gators in the Big 12/SEC Challenge on Saturday night.</p>
<p>&#8220;One thing about this team, when things are out like that, we take it as motivation,&#8221; Bandoo said. &#8220;We just knew we were a great team and knew if we executed the game plan everything would come out right.&#8221;</p>
<p>Baylor (17-1) was a two-point underdog at tip-off, an odd line considering the team hadn&#8217;t lost in 2 1/2 months. Vegas surely didn&#8217;t do Florida (12-7) any favors, and those odds-makers probably won&#8217;t underestimate the Bears again.</p>
<p>Baylor&#8217;s stifling defense was on display &#8212; as usual &#8212; as it held the Gators to 44% shooting, including 23.5% from 3-point range. That much was expected.</p>
<p>&#8220;Baylor made it look ugly for us at times tonight,&#8221; Florida coach Mike White said.</p>
<p>The Bears added a twist by making nine 3-pointers, their most in nearly a month. They were shooting 30.5% from behind the arc in Big 12 play.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is one of our bad defensive games,&#8221; Florida&#8217;s Keyontae Johnson said. &#8220;They were more connected than we were. They shot the ball with confidence, knowing their shots were going to go in.&#8221;</p>
<p>Baylor improved to 6-1 in the annual inter-conference series &#8212; the best record of any team in either conference &#8212; and assured itself another week atop The Associated Press poll.</p>
<p>The Bears also gave the Big 12 an even split (5-5) in the daylong event.</p>
<p>Baylor overcame an eight-point deficit early and led by 19 points in the second half before Florida mounted a minor rally. The Gators had a chance to make it a single-digit game with a little more than 7 minutes to play, but they missed the front end of three consecutive one-and-ones. Kerry Blackshear Jr. misfired twice on back-to-back possessions and then Noah Locke did the same seconds later.</p>
<p>&#8220;My goodness, my good free throw shooters,&#8221; White said. &#8220;To beat the No. 1 team country, you have to make some of those.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida eventually whittled Baylor&#8217;s lead to 10 on Andrew Nembhard&#8217;s driving layup with 2:40 remaining. But the Bears answered on the other end thanks to their 13th offensive rebound and did little, if anything, wrong down the stretch.</p>
<p>Davion Mitchell finished with 12 points and six assists for Baylor. Jared Butler chipped in 10 points.</p>
<p>The Gators fell to 2-17 against the No. 1 team, including 10 consecutive losses.</p>
<p>Johnson led Florida with 20 points. Nembhard added 16 points and eight assists, but he missed more shots (8) than he made (6), including all four 3-pointers. The Gators missed 13 of 17 from behind the arc.</p>
<p>Baylor took control of the game with a 13-2 run to close the first half, turning a tie game into a double-digit lead. The Bears hit six 3-pointers in the opening 20 minutes &#8212; twice as many as Florida &#8212; and had seven offensive rebounds.</p>
<p>They got help from an unlikely source: Bandoo, who averages 7.5 points off the benched, scored 11 in the opening half. They also fed off the betting line.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve got a lot of guys that have been through the battles and wars, and they don&#8217;t get rattled as easy as someone that hasn&#8217;t,&#8221; Baylor coach Scott Drew said.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Baylor: The Bears matched their best 18-game start in school history. They also started 17-1 in 2011-12 and 2016-17. They landed No. 3 seeds in the NCAA Tournament after those regular seasons and were eliminated both times by SEC teams (Kentucky in &#8217;12, South Carolina in `17).</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators appeared to be taking strides while beating then-No. 4 Auburn last Saturday and nearly stunning LSU on the road earlier this week. But the team&#8217;s offensive woes returned against Baylor &#8212; no surprise given the Bears are one of the best defenses in the nation.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Baylor: Returns to Big 12 action and plays at Iowa State on Wednesday night. The Bears have won three of the last four in the series, but lost to the Cyclones in the conference tournament last March.</p>
<p>Florida: Returns to SEC play and hosts Mississippi State on Tuesday night. The Gators lost to the Bulldogs last year to end an eight-game winning streak in the series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">581101</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Williams, Mays help LSU hold on against Florida, 84-82</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/williams-mays-help-lsu-hold-on-against-florida-84-82/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 04:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=579111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — LSU guard Skylar Mays could afford to have a sense of humor after the Tigers nearly blew a 10-point lead...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — LSU guard Skylar Mays could afford to have a sense of humor after the Tigers nearly blew a 10-point lead in the final 1:11 against Florida, but escaped with yet another narrow victory.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;ve got to keep it close,” Mays said with a relieved smile. “It&#8217;s worked for us, so why not stick with it.”</p>
<p>Emmitt Williams scored 19 points, Mays capped an 18-point performance with two crucial free throws in the final 10 seconds, and LSU remained unbeaten in SEC play with an 84-82 victory over the Gators on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Keyontae Johnson had 16 points for Florida and briefly believed he&#8217;d forced overtime with a layup on a backdoor cut as time expired. But officials determined on video review that the half-second on the clock when the ball was put in play ran out before the ball left Johnson&#8217;s hand.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;ve seen crazier things happen in my time here, but that was just a great game,” Mays continued, applauding the Gators&#8217; effort. “Credit to them. They&#8217;re a quality team. They&#8217;re resilient, just like us. Luckily we were able to pull this one out.”</p>
<p>Javonte Smart scored 13 points and freshman Trendon Watford punctuated his 14-point night with a two-handed dunk on a baseline cut to give LSU (14-4, 6-0) a 79-69 lead with 1:20 to go. Marlon Taylor had 10 points and 11 rebounds for the Tigers, who&#8217;ve won five straight by four or fewer points.</p>
<p>Noah Locke scored 16 points for Florida (12-6, 4-2), which created a tense finish by scoring 13 points in the final 1:11 on Andrew Nembhard&#8217;s layup, Locke&#8217;s 3, two more 3s by Johnson and a layup by Kerry Blackshear.</p>
<p>“We probably shot the ball more confidently late, more than the first 35 minutes, unfortunately,” Florida coach Michael White said. “We could have just packed it in out there, but our guys fought to the bitter end.”</p>
<p>Nembhard and Balckshear each finished with 15 points.</p>
<p>LSU led for the final 14:08 and appeared primed to pull away when Mays hit a 3 with 4:02 remaining. He followed that with a steal from Nembhard and Days pushed the Tigers&#8217; lead to 73-62 when snagged the long rebound from his missed 3 and drove past scrambling defenders for a layup.</p>
<p>LSU coach Will Wade responded by calling a 30-second timeout to rest his defense and stomped onto the court triumphantly, pumping both fists and hollering approvingly at his players.</p>
<p>Little could Wade know how close the Gators would make it after that.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;ve been really good coming from behind in these situations. Now we&#8217;ve got to be a little better — make some better decisions — playing from ahead,” Wade said. “That was my fault.”</p>
<p>Florida briefly led by as many as eight points in the first half when Scottie Lewis&#8217; transition 3 capped a 12-6 surge and made it 25-17.</p>
<p>LSU responded by pressing defensively and scored nine straight, highlighted by sequence in which Taylor followed his 3 with a steal and fast-break dunk to put the Tigers in front 26-25.</p>
<p>The game remained tight for the remainder of the half, with Florida taking a 36-34 lead into the break on Lewis&#8217; jumper with 2 seconds on the clock.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s size and talent intermittently gave LSU fits. The Gators shot 50% and hit 11 3s. But untimely turnovers — 12 in all — and defensive breakdowns did them in. Florida allowed LSU to grab 15 offensive rebounds, leading to 11 second-chance points.</p>
<p>LSU made just two of 14 3-point shots, but dominated the paint, outrebounding Florida 38-28 and outscoring the Gators 24-9 at the foul line.</p>
<p>COACHING RIVALS</p>
<p>Wade and White could be seen giving each other long looks during just the latest of several close and intense games their teams have played in recent seasons. White said he grew up with LSU assistant Greg Heiar and noted that he coached with LSU assistant Bill Armstrong when both were on Mississippi&#8217;s staff.</p>
<p>“It may just be the familiarity with each other,&#8221; White said. &#8220;Maybe the coaching staffs just want to beat each other&#8217;s brains in. Who knows?”</p>
<p>Added Wade, “They do a tremendous, tremendous, job. I think my staff does as good a job as anybody in the league. So, strength-on-strength. &#8230; The talent level&#8217;s close. The staffs are close. Everything&#8217;s close, so they&#8217;re all close games.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts No. 1 Baylor on Saturday night in the Big12/SEC Challenge.</p>
<p>LSU visits Texas on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">579111</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Payne&#8217;s career game helps Florida beat No. 4 Auburn 69-47</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/paynes-career-game-helps-florida-beat-no-4-auburn-69-47/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 04:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=577660</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Omar Payne was an afterthought in Florida&#8217;s highly touted recruiting class, which featured high school All-Americans Scottie Lewis and Tre Mann....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Omar Payne was an afterthought in Florida&#8217;s highly touted recruiting class, which featured high school All-Americans Scottie Lewis and Tre Mann.</p>
<p>No one expected Payne to start, let along star, in any games this season. So his performance against Auburn was a bigger shock than the final score.</p>
<p>Payne had the best game of his college career, finishing with 19 points and 11 rebounds, as the Gators routed the fourth-ranked Tigers 69-47 on Saturday.</p>
<p>“Elite,” teammate and fellow big man Kerry Blackshear Jr. said. &#8220;Great on both ends of the floor. His energy was great. We fed off his energy. He was a big reason why we were able to get this win.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was Florida&#8217;s first victory against a top-five team since beating then-No. 2 Michigan State in 2009. It was the 14th time this season that an unranked team knocked off a top-five opponent.</p>
<p>It surely will bolster Florida&#8217;s NCAA Tournament resume considering coach Mike White&#8217;s team hadn&#8217;t beaten a top-40 team in the NCAA Evaluation Tool (NET) rankings.</p>
<p>Auburn (15-2, 3-2 Southeastern Conference), meanwhile, has lost two straight following a torrid start. This one ended with the program&#8217;s fourth-fewest points under sixth-year head coach Bruce Pearl.</p>
<p>“Obviously, there&#8217;s a pretty big price on our head,&#8221; Pearl said. “We&#8217;re ranked fourth in the country. Obviously, that&#8217;s not going to last much longer. I think we&#8217;ve got to respond to the step up that we saw this week from both Alabama and Florida.&#8221;</p>
<p>Pearl gave Payne, Blackshear and point guard Andrew Nembhard credit for continually breaking down his team&#8217;s defense. He also placed some blame on his starting backcourt of Samir Doughty and J&#8217;Von McCormick, who combined for 14 points, three rebounds, two assists and three turnovers. The duo was 2 for 10 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>Danjel Purifoy led the Tigers with 10 points.</p>
<p>Pearl conceded that his team&#8217;s lack of size outside center Austin Wiley will continue to be a weakness.</p>
<p>Florida exploited it, with Blackshear pulling Wiley outside and allowing Payne to crash the boards on both ends. Payne made all nine shots, scoring mostly on putbacks and tip-ins. He finished with seven offensive rebounds. It was a huge day for a guy who entered the game averaging 4.3 points and 4.1 rebounds.</p>
<p>“He just continues to improve,&#8221; White said. &#8220;He hasn&#8217;t had a bad practice in a long time. &#8230; He just brings it.”</p>
<p>Payne&#8217;s three-point play, which came after his final offensive rebound, put Florida (12-5, 4-1) up by 14 with a little more than 4 minutes to play.</p>
<p>The Gators sent the home crowd into a late frenzy — and to the exits — with a 14-0 run that included 3-pointers by Noah Locke, Keyontae Johnson and Blackshear. Fans chanted “over-rated” in the closing minutes.</p>
<p>Students stayed and chanted “Omar Payne” as he left the court following radio and TV interviews.</p>
<p>“When we come out with that (kind of energy), we look like we&#8217;re the best team out here,” Payne said. “We just got to do that every game.”</p>
<p>Locke and Blackshear finished with 11 points apiece for the Gators, who haven&#8217;t lost at home to Auburn since 1996. Blackshear added a season-high-tying 16 rebounds.</p>
<p>The Tigers struggled out of the gate, missing 15 of their first 16 shots. But Florida failed to take advantage of Auburn&#8217;s sluggishness, turning the ball over far too often for White&#8217;s liking.</p>
<p>Auburn kept it close thanks to those turnovers and being perfect (10 for 10) from the free throw line.</p>
<p>The Gators led by five at the break and quickly built a double-digit lead coming out of the locker room. Nembhard, Johnson and Blackshear made consecutive baskets and then Payne pushed the lead to 11 with a putback and a layup.</p>
<p>PLAYING SICK</p>
<p>Nembhard played despite missing three days of practice with the flu. Team officials moved him and roommates Locke and Johnson into hotel rooms for one night while their apartment was completely cleaned and sanitized.</p>
<p>“In my head, I was never not going to play today,&#8221; Nembhard said. &#8220;I felt better every day.”</p>
<p>Nembhard finished with six points, five rebounds, five assists and four turnovers in a season-low 25 minutes.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Auburn: The Tigers won&#8217;t win many, if any, games shooting like this. Purifoy made 3 of 11 shots and Doughty was 3 of 12 from the field.</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators finally look like a top-10 team. They opened the season ranked No. 6 but lost two of their first four games. White tweaked the offense, and the results are starting to show.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Auburn: Hosts South Carolina on Wednesday. The Tigers have lost four of the last six in the series.</p>
<p>Florida: Plays at LSU on Tuesday. The Gators have won four of the last five meetings, including two in overtime.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">577660</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hot-shooting Missouri routs Florida 91-75</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hot-shooting-missouri-routs-florida-91-75/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=574785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COLUMBIA, Mo. (AP) &#8212; Missouri has made scoring points look very hard this season. In Saturday&#8217;s 91-75 victory over Florida, the Tigers made it look...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>COLUMBIA, Mo. (AP) &#8212; Missouri has made scoring points look very hard this season. In Saturday&#8217;s 91-75 victory over Florida, the Tigers made it look easy.</p>
<p>&#8220;When you start seeing the ball go in for everybody, it&#8217;s easy to get rolling,&#8221; said Dru Smith, who finished with 22 points, six assists and five steals. &#8220;The crowd gets into it, and it gives you a little more energy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Missouri (9-6, 1-2 Southeastern Conference) entered the game next-to-last in the league in scoring at 66.7 points per game. The Tigers tied a season-high for points and shot 61.5% from the field and 63.2% from 3-point range. Mark Smith and Javon Pickett scored 14 points each, and Mitchell Smith added 10 points.</p>
<p>&#8220;As a staff, we felt helpless,&#8221; Florida coach Mike White said. &#8220;We couldn&#8217;t find a way to get stops. It wasn&#8217;t our best effort, but Mizzou had a lot to do with that. I thought Dru Smith was fantastic. That was one of the better performances of anyone we&#8217;ve played against this year.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kerry Blackshear led Florida (10-5, 2-1) with 22 points, Noah Locke scored 12 and Scottie Lewis finished with 11.</p>
<p>Mark Smith sank a 3-pointer on the game&#8217;s opening possession, and the Tigers were off and running. They led 51-36 at halftime. The second half started the same way, as Mitchell Smith sank a 3-pointer, causing White to call a timeout just 40 seconds after intermission.</p>
<p>The Gators cut an 18-point deficit to 10 when Tre Mann hit a 3-pointer with 14:50 left, but they couldn&#8217;t get enough defensive stops to get any closer.</p>
<p>Missouri has failed to reach 60 points four times this season, including their first two SEC games. The Tigers were noticeably more aggressive driving the ball than previously this season. Missouri had a 40-14 advantage in points in the paint.</p>
<p>Dru Smith was especially effective at muscling into the lane and finishing.</p>
<p>&#8220;He does a great job of shot-faking, and he knows how to use angles with bigger guys on him,&#8221; Missouri coach Cuonzo Martin said. &#8220;And he&#8217;s a good passer, so it gives him an advantage. So when he gets in the lane, he can make plays.&#8221;</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators lengthened the game and made a run early in the second half by beating a path to the free throw line. They had Missouri in so much foul trouble they were shooting free throws in the bonus at the 13:20 mark. Florida made 25 of 32 free throws.</p>
<p>Missouri: The Tigers pushed the pace more than usual against the Gators. Missouri created transition chances with 11 steals. For a team that often struggles to score in halfcourt sets, any easy basket is welcome. &#8220;Our first key written on the board before the game was, `Push the ball in transition,&#8221;&#8216; Dru Smith said.</p>
<p>THUNDEROUS DUNK</p>
<p>Missouri sophomore point guard Xavier Pinson said Martin had stern words for him after he struggled in Tuesday&#8217;s loss to Tennessee. Pinson responded against Florida, scoring eight points and dishing three assists with no turnovers.</p>
<p>&#8220;My whole anger and hunger today on the court was all because of him,&#8221; Pinson said of his coach. &#8220;I can&#8217;t thank him enough.&#8221;</p>
<p>Pinson drew one of the biggest roars of the season from the Mizzou Arena crowd when he led a fast break, faked a pass to the right corner and threw down a dunk over Omar Payne to give Missouri a 13-5 lead. Pinson called it one of his top five all-time dunks.</p>
<p>&#8220;To me, it was just getting the crowd involved, giving the crowd something worth their time for coming,&#8221; Pinson said.</p>
<p>MISSOURI SUSPENDS GUARD</p>
<p>Missouri announced before the game it has suspended freshman guard Mario McKinney indefinitely for undisclosed reasons. McKinney had played in seven games and was averaging 2.6 points.</p>
<p>EXTENDED STAY</p>
<p>The Gators usually fly back to Gainesville right after road games, but White decided before the trip to spend an extra night in Missouri because ice and snow was in the forecast. White said he was concerned that flight delays might cost his players valuable sleep.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators play Mississippi on Tuesday at home.</p>
<p>Missouri: The Tigers visit Mississippi State on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">574785</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida rallies from 21 points down to top Alabama in 2OT</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-rallies-from-21-points-down-to-top-alabama-in-2ot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 04:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=571868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Noah Locke and his Florida teammates knew what was coming. Alabama had run the same set on its previous two inbound...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Noah Locke and his Florida teammates knew what was coming. Alabama had run the same set on its previous two inbound plays.<br />
So the Gators defended it perfectly.</p>
<p>Locke stole John Petty Jr.&#8217;s inbound pass and hit a layup with 21 seconds remaining in regulation, helping Florida overcome a 21-point deficit and beat the Crimson Tide 104-98 in double overtime in the Southeastern Conference opener for both teams.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was just like we drew it up,&#8221; Locke said.</p>
<p>Florida (9-4) closed it out from the line in the final period, with Scottie Lewis, Andrew Nembhard and Kerry Blackshear Jr. hitting two free throws apiece in the final minute to cap the largest comeback in school history. The previous high was 18, accomplished against Alabama (2007) and South Carolina (1993).</p>
<p>Few saw this outcome coming, at least not after the way the Gators opened the game.</p>
<p>&#8220;We looked jittery, unsure, unconfident when we were shooting 2s, shooting 3s, when we were handling the ball,&#8221; coach Mike White said. &#8220;Just out of character.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida couldn&#8217;t make shots, couldn&#8217;t defend, had three times as many turnovers as assists and missed its first six shots from 3-point range. The Gators trailed by 21 &#8212; their largest deficit of the season &#8212; before scoring seven straight points to end the half. Nembhard hit a 3-pointer just before the buzzer to end the long-range drought.</p>
<p>The Gators hit two more treys after the break, huge shots that helped turn the game.</p>
<p>&#8220;Stuff that coaches lose sleep over definitely went the wrong way for us,&#8221; first-year Alabama coach Nate Oats said.</p>
<p>Oats pointed to Florida coach Mike White&#8217;s technical foul with 12 minutes to play in regulation. Oats said 15 of the next 20 calls went Florida&#8217;s way.</p>
<p>&#8220;When you&#8217;re up 21 on the road to open SEC play, you deserve to get a win,&#8221; Oats said.</p>
<p>But nothing was bigger than Locke&#8217;s steal. Alabama looked like it would withstand Florida&#8217;s late run, which came with clutch 3-pointers and a pair of three-point plays from Nembhard.</p>
<p>But the Tide seemed to get lax by running a set play that had worked previously. Florida read it, reacted and responded.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve got to give them better options coming out of timeouts,&#8221; Oats said.</p>
<p>White refused to take credit for expecting the play, saying he was &#8220;actually yelling for a timeout there&#8221; before the turnover.</p>
<p>Florida seemed to wear down the Crimson Tide (7-6) in the extra periods, especially after Herbert Jones, Galin Smith and Javian Davis fouled out.</p>
<p>Lewis had a breakout performance with 17 points, 10 rebounds and three blocked shots. Blackshear finished with 24 points and 16 boards despite picking up his fourth foul with 11:36 remaining in regulation.</p>
<p>Nembhard scored 25 points, Locke added 18 and Keyontae Johnson chipped in 10 points and 12 rebounds for Florida.</p>
<p>Petty led Alabama with 19 points. Kira Lewis Jr. finished with 17 points on 7-of-25 shooting. Lewis had a chance to win the game in regulation following Locke&#8217;s layup, but missed a 3-pointer on the other end.</p>
<p>Jones (15), Beetle Bolden (15), Alex Reese (14) and Jaden Shackelford (11) also scored in double figures for Alabama, which had its three-game winning streak halted.</p>
<p>&#8220;We were just about dead in the water a couple different times, mid-first half, mid-second half and just found a way,&#8221; White said. &#8220;Hopefully we can build upon it. It&#8217;s a good life lesson and a good lesson for the program.&#8221;</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Alabama: The Tide trailed just once &#8212; for less than a minute &#8212; until overtime. Despite the loss, Alabama still leads the conference in scoring and 3-point shooting.</p>
<p>Florida: The Gators continued their season of inconsistency even in victory. White revamped his offense following early season losses to Florida State and UConn, giving his players less freedom and more set plays, but Florida looked lost at times in its SEC opener.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Alabama: After opening SEC play on the road for the first time in three years, the Crimson Tide return home to host Mississippi State on Wednesday. Alabama has won five of the last six in the series.</p>
<p>Florida: Travels to play South Carolina on Tuesday. The Gamecocks won last year&#8217;s meeting on Chris Silva&#8217;s dunk following a full-court pass from Felipe Haase with 2.5 seconds remaining.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">571868</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Perine leads No. 6 Gators past Virginia 36-28 in Orange Bowl</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/perine-leads-no-6-gators-past-virginia-36-28-in-orange-bowl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=569907</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Lamical Perine scored on a 61-yard run in the opening minute and didn&#8217;t stop until he climbed onto a platform...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Lamical Perine scored on a 61-yard run in the opening minute and didn&#8217;t stop until he climbed onto a platform for the postgame ceremony to receive the Orange Bowl&#8217;s most valuable player trophy.</p>
<p>Perine totaled 181 yards rushing and receiving with three touchdowns Monday to help No. 6 Florida beat Virginia 36-28.</p>
<p>The win means the Gators (11-2) will likely finish in the Top 10 in consecutive seasons for the first time since 2008-09. Second-year coach Dan Mullen credited Perine and the rest of the senior class with leading the resurgence.</p>
<p>“They restored the Gator standards and are building what we want to build,” said Mullen, who improved to 21-5 at Florida.</p>
<p>“My sophomore year, we were 4-7,” Perine said. “We came back and had two double-digit win seasons. It’s great, man.”</p>
<p>Perine carried 13 times for a career-high 138 yards rushing at the end of a so-so senior season. He came into the game with only 538 yards rushing this year in the Gators&#8217; pass-oriented offense.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s one of the top running backs in the SEC,” Mullen said. “People say, ‘The stats say this, the stats say that.’ But every time we needed a big run this season, he came up with it.”</p>
<p>Perine was too quick and speedy for the Cavaliers, as his dash through their secondary on the first series showed. He also scored on a 10-yard run and caught a 16-yard touchdown pass from Kyle Trask.</p>
<p>The Cavaliers (9-5) lost their final two games but still posted their highest win total since 2007.</p>
<p>Trask capped a storybook junior season by throwing for 305 yards. He was lightly recruited and in late September became a starter for the first time since ninth grade.</p>
<p>“This game is huge for this program,” Trask said. “We just continued to grind every single week, and here we are winning the Orange Bowl. It’s pretty incredible.”</p>
<p>Florida totaled 549 yards, including a season-high 244 rushing, and didn&#8217;t punt until midway through the third quarter. The Gators exposed the weaknesses in a Virginia defense that allowed more than 23 points per game and gave up 62 to Clemson in an Atlantic Coast Conference title game loss.</p>
<p>“Tonight we faced a team that they decided they were going to stop the pass and drop a lot of guys into coverage,&#8221; Mullen said. &#8220;We were able to take what they were giving us.”</p>
<p>The Cavaliers&#8217; offense tried valiantly to keep up. Senior Bryce Perkins threw for 323 yards and four scores in the final game of his career.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m not into moral victories, but I&#8217;m proud of these guys and the culture we set,” Perkins said. “Next year, these guys are going to be a force to reckoned with.”</p>
<p>CLOSING IT OUT</p>
<p>Tanner Cowley&#8217;s 52-yard catch-and-run led to a Cavaliers touchdown that cut their deficit to 27-21 early in the fourth quarter. The Gators answered with a touchdown set up by Perine&#8217;s 23-yard run to the 1.</p>
<p>Virginia drove 75 yards for a touchdown with 38 seconds left, but Florida recovered the ensuing onside kick.</p>
<p>“We were a few plays short,” Cavaliers coach Bronco Mendenhall said.</p>
<p>HOME-FIELD ADVANTAGE</p>
<p>The Gators had the edge in crowd support playing in the Orange Bowl for the first time since 2001, when Steve Spurrier was their coach.</p>
<p>“Playing here at home in the state — I mean, we are the University of Florida,” Mullen told the crowd during the trophy ceremony. “It is our state.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Gators open next season on Sept. 5 against Eastern Washington. They’ll have to replace four senior wide receivers, plus their top cornerback and pass rushers.</p>
<p>The Cavaliers’ opener will be Monday, Sept. 7, against Georgia in Atlanta. “As many of these games as we can play, and we&#8217;ve earned the right to play in on the stage that we&#8217;re currently in, the faster the program accelerates,” Mendenhall said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">569907</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/lamical-perine-e1577797469653.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/lamical-perine-e1577797469653.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/lamical-perine-e1577797469653.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">lamical perine</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MDPD conducts security sweep at Hard Rock Stadium ahead of Orange Bowl</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mdpd-conducts-security-sweep-at-hard-rock-stadium-ahead-of-orange-bowl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Franco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 17:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=569687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Miami-Dade Police officers were out in full force to make sure the Hard Rock Stadium was secure hours before the big Orange Bowl game. A...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami-Dade Police officers were out in full force to make sure the Hard Rock Stadium was secure hours before the big Orange Bowl game.</p>
<p>A K-9 sniffed seats, locker rooms and even the field to make sure there were no explosives.</p>
<p>Officials said the sweep was also a practice run for the Super Bowl in February.</p>
<p>The Florida Gators will face off against the Virginia Cavaliers at 8 p.m., Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">569687</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/711_125.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/711_125.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/711_125.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">711_125</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cavs try to take &#8216;next step&#8217; in Orange Bowl against Gators</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/cavs-try-to-take-next-step-in-orange-bowl-against-gators/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 21:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=569425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — University of Virginia junior Charles Snowden recalls that when he first arrived on campus, new acquaintances were disappointed to learn he was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — University of Virginia junior Charles Snowden recalls that when he first arrived on campus, new acquaintances were disappointed to learn he was a linebacker rather than a power forward.</p>
<p>“I was 6-7 and 190 pounds, real skinny,&#8221; Snowden said. &#8220;And people would say, ‘Are you on the basketball team?’”</p>
<p>“&#8217;No, I&#8217;m on the football team.&#8217;”</p>
<p>“&#8217;Oh.&#8217;”</p>
<p>As in, “Oh, that&#8217;s too bad.”</p>
<p>But now that the Cavaliers (9-4, No. 24 CFP) are about to play No. 6-ranked Florida in the Orange Bowl, strangers are excited to meet a football player, Snowden said.</p>
<p>“That’s a twist, and it&#8217;s pretty cool,” he said. “I love it.”</p>
<p>Virginia&#8217;s trip to the Orange Bowl shows how far the program has come, and Monday night&#8217;s game will offer a gauge of where it might be headed.</p>
<p>“We understand the history Virginia has had,” Snowden said. “We were not a big name in college sports, so we hear a lot of what people say. A lot of us just kind of laughed it off. If I had heard the name Virginia a couple years ago, I&#8217;d have probably had the same reaction. So we&#8217;re going to go out there and prove it&#8217;s a new team and a new era.”</p>
<p>The Gators (10-2, No. 9 CFP) are on the rise, too. A victory would clinch Florida&#8217;s first 11-win season since 2012.</p>
<p>“We don&#8217;t get to play again until September,” coach Dan Mullen said. “That&#8217;s a long time to sit around. So if you have the opportunity to finish the season with a win, I think it really kind of bolts you into the next season.”</p>
<p>PROGRESSING PROGRAMS</p>
<p>The Cavaliers are making their Orange Bowl debut, and a win would be the biggest bowl victory in school history. They would crack the AP Top 25 and finish the season ranked for the first time since 2004.</p>
<p>“This is the next step for our program, and we can’t wait to capitalize,” coach Bronco Mendenhall said. “We are a program that is developing, rising, growing and becoming.”</p>
<p>Football still doesn&#8217;t match the popularity of a basketball team that won the national championship in April, but Mendenhall has revived a program that went 2-10 in his first season in 2016. This year the Cavaliers ended a streak of 15 consecutive losses to rival Virginia Tech and earned their third consecutive bowl berth.</p>
<p>The Gators, however, are 14 1/2-point favorites. A win would give them a second consecutive Top 10 finish under second-year coach Mullen, who has quickly returned Florida to supremacy in the football-crazed Sunshine State.</p>
<p>“That&#8217;s really huge for us,” quarterback Kyle Trask said. “Coach Mullen’s thing is that’s how it should be. That’s the Gators standard. We need to be the best team in the state every single year. This past couple of years is letting everybody know Florida is back on the map like it should be.”</p>
<p>MIDNIGHT JOGS</p>
<p>The lightly recruited Trask came off the bench to lead a comeback victory at Kentucky in September. The next week he made his first start since he was a high school freshman, and he quickly became the triggerman for a potent offense.</p>
<p>The junior&#8217;s passer rating of 159.24 is the highest at Florida since Tim Tebow led the nation at 164.2 in 2009. Center Nick Buchanan attributes Trask&#8217;s surprising success to hard work that dates to when both were freshmen.</p>
<p>“One of the first times I saw him, I was at one of the dorms coming in, and it&#8217;s like midnight,” Buchanan recalled. &#8220;I see Kyle and I&#8217;m like, ‘What you doing, bro?’ He&#8217;s like, ‘I just went on a two-mile jog.’ I&#8217;m like, ‘What?!’</p>
<p>“This kid is crazy. It&#8217;s amazing to see that work ethic. All he does is come to work. It&#8217;s amazing to see him come and leading us to victory week after week.”</p>
<p>MULTIPLE WEAPONS</p>
<p>The Cavaliers, who gave up 62 points to Clemson in their Atlantic Coast Conference title game loss, now face the challenge of dealing with Florida&#8217;s deep receiving corps.</p>
<p>For the first time since 1993, four Gators have at least 35 catches and four touchdowns. The 150-yard receiving mark for the season has been surpassed by nine players, the most at Florida since at least 1990.</p>
<p>“One of the first things that jumps off the film when you study Florida&#8217;s offense is just how many really good athletes are in space, and how frequently the ball is delivered accurately and effectively in well-designed plays,” Mendenhall said. “It&#8217;ll be a challenge for us and will require a lot of innovation, a lot of coaching on our part to try to neutralize that.”</p>
<p>GENERATING HEAT</p>
<p>Neither team has an All-American, but two of the nation&#8217;s best pass rushes will be on display.</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s 46 sacks rank fifth. Virginia ranks sixth with a school-record 45 sacks, and blitzes on almost every play.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s about switching up the patterns and being able to get the O-line a little bit twisted up,” linebacker Zane Zandier said. “It has been big for us this year.”</p>
<p>NFL FUTURE?</p>
<p>Now that Mullen is the first Gators coach to win at least 10 games in each of his first two seasons, speculation has begun regarding the possibility of an NFL team luring him away.</p>
<p>“Those are nice compliments,” Mullen said Sunday. “In the coaching profession, a lot of times they&#8217;re making comments on you one way or the other, right? They either need to get rid of you, or you&#8217;re going somewhere else. So it&#8217;s always better to be on the latter of those two.”</p>
<p>Mullen also said: “I think everybody knows how much I love being a Florida Gator.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">569425</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/11/171127_uf_gators_head_coach_dan_mullen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/11/171127_uf_gators_head_coach_dan_mullen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/11/171127_uf_gators_head_coach_dan_mullen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">171127_uf_gators_head_coach_dan_mullen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merrill&#8217;s 21 points help Utah State beat Gators 65-62</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/merrills-21-points-help-utah-state-beat-gators-65-62/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 04:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=566774</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Utah State didn&#8217;t give up a field goal in the first 10 minutes Saturday and still led by only four points,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Utah State didn&#8217;t give up a field goal in the first 10 minutes Saturday and still led by only four points, which was enough to make coach Craig Smith rub his jaw in disbelief.</p>
<p>“The start,” he said, “was a little bit of a root canal.”</p>
<p>Pain relief came soon enough for the Aggies. They shot 50 percent in the second half, including 5 for 12 from 3-point range, and held Florida without a field goal for six minutes down the stretch to win 65-62 in the Orange Bowl Classic.</p>
<p>“Early it was kind of a battle,” forward Justin Bean said. “No one was hitting many shots. It just took a lot of physicality from our guys, staying together, executing our sets and just knowing the shots would fall.”</p>
<p>The Aggies (12-2) improved to 3-0 in games decided by a one-possession margin. They won despite losing hard-luck center Neemias Queta to an undisclosed injury in the first half.</p>
<p>Florida (7-4) continued to struggle after being ranked sixth in the preseason. The Gators missed their first 14 shots, and missed seven in a row in the final minutes after taking a 55-54 lead.</p>
<p>But coach Mike White saw offensive progress.</p>
<p>“We got a little better today,” White said. “We had a chance to beat a really good team — as good a team as we’ll play this season.”</p>
<p>Sam Merrill led the Aggies with 21 points, nine rebounds and five assists. He went 5 for 10 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>“Sam Merrill was absolutely outstanding,” Smith said. “He set everything up for us.”</p>
<p>Diogo Brito&#8217;s basket with 4:15 left put the Aggies ahead to stay, and he went 4 for 4 from the free throw line in the final 25 seconds. Bean had 12 points, nine rebounds and four assists.</p>
<p>Senior Kerry Blackshear led Florida with 22 points and a career-high 14 rebounds. He went 15 for 17 from the free throw line.</p>
<p>The Gators out-rebounded the tallest team in the nation 41-33 but shot only 32 percent, including 4 for 17 from 3-point range. Eight players missed before Florida finally sank a shot.</p>
<p>“We got good looks,” Blackshear said. “You’ve got to keep shooting.”</p>
<p>REINJURED</p>
<p>Queta, who recently returned from a knee injury, limped to the locker room in the first half. He went to the floor hard and was shaken up when he collided with a Florida player and was called for an offensive foul.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s not the injury he was out with for a while,” said Smith, but he provided no further information.</p>
<p>Queta averaged 11.8 points and 8.9 rebounds last season as a freshman.</p>
<p>QUOTABLE</p>
<p>The Gators fell to 17-4 in the annual one-day Orange Bowl Classic. When someone complimented White on agreeing to a tough match-up with the defending Mountain West Conference champions, he said: “Wasn’t a very good decision, was it?”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>The Aggies were 34th in votes in the latest AP poll, and two wins this week might not be enough for them to crack the Top 25.</p>
<p>“They’re a team that could make a deep run in March,” White said.</p>
<p>Florida continues to be a puzzle with an offense that has failed to top 70 points seven times.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Gators play host to Long Beach State on Dec. 28, their final non-conference game before beginning Southeastern Conference play.</p>
<p>Utah State plays host to Eastern Oregon on Dec. 28.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">566774</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida-Virginia bowl matchup: &#8216;a lot of orange and blue&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-virginia-bowl-matchup-a-lot-of-orange-and-blue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=563296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOLLYWOOD, Fla. (AP) — Virginia coach Bronco Mendenhall finds it amusing his Cavaliers have been designated the home team in the Orange Bowl. They&#8217;re playing...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOLLYWOOD, Fla. (AP) — Virginia coach Bronco Mendenhall finds it amusing his Cavaliers have been designated the home team in the Orange Bowl.</p>
<p>They&#8217;re playing Florida, which ensures most of the crowd on Dec. 30 will be cheering for the “visitors.&#8221;</p>
<p>“This might be the most disproportionate home team-visiting team game ever,&#8221; Mendenhall said. “Based on the Gator responses I got all day here in the area recruiting, I&#8217;m not sure it&#8217;s home yet.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida coach Dan Mullen laughed at that but tried to stress what the teams have in common.</p>
<p>“There’s going to be a lot of orange and blue in that stadium,&#8221; Mullen said.</p>
<p>The two coaches appeared Wednesday at a kickoff event for the matchup. Both said the berth will help their program and specifically recruiting, especially in talent-rich South Florida.</p>
<p>“The exposure not only nationally but locally — for young people to see our program up close, it&#8217;s essential,&#8221; Mendenhall said. “We look forward to capitalizing the best we can.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida (10-2) is No. 9 in the College Football Playoff rankings, and Virginia (9-4) is No. 24. The Cavaliers will make their Orange Bowl debut, while the Gators are in the game for the first time since the 2001 season.</p>
<p>But Mullen has been a head coach in the Orange Bowl before — he led Mississippi State in a 39-34 loss to Georgia Tech in the December 2014 game. Despite the defeat, he has fond memories.</p>
<p>“Dan asked me if I had been to this game yet and I said no,&#8221; Mendenhall said. “He said, ‘Just wait,&#8217; and kind of lit like it was Christmas based on his experience.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mullen, a Pennsylvania native, said he considers the berth special in part because of his childhood.</p>
<p>“As a guy that grew up in the northeast, I&#8217;d finish shoveling all the snow out of the driveway, and get to come in and watch the Orange Bowl,&#8221; he said. “To be part of it is an unbelievable honor.&#8221;</p>
<p>The game will be Virginia&#8217;s first in a New Year’s Six game since 1998, and Cavaliers fans roared at news of the berth.</p>
<p>“There was an announcement made at the UVA-North Carolina basketball game at halftime,&#8221; Mendenhall said. “It was as if we won a national championship in basketball.&#8221;</p>
<p>So the game is expected to be a hot ticket in Charlottesville. Make room, Gators fans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">563296</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191002-dan-mullen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">191002 dan mullen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfamiliar rivals Florida, Virginia headed to Orange Bowl</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/unfamiliar-rivals-florida-virginia-headed-to-orange-bowl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=561825</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — There isn’t much of a history between Florida and Virginia. The schools met in the College World Series in 2015,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — There isn’t much of a history between Florida and Virginia.</p>
<p>The schools met in the College World Series in 2015, the Cavaliers ousting the Gators on the way to the national championship. They’ve played in the NCAA basketball tournament twice in recent years, the Gators winning in 26-point routs both times.</p>
<p>But the lone football matchup between the schools was 60 years ago.</p>
<p>That’s about to change.</p>
<p>Florida (10-2, No. 9 in the College Football Playoff rankings) will face Atlantic Coast Conference runner-up Virginia (9-4, No. 24 CFP) in the Orange Bowl on Dec. 30, with both teams still chasing something. For the Gators, it’s a chance at their first 11-win season since 2012. For the Cavaliers, it’s the second 10-win season in school history.</p>
<p>“South Florida is an important region for our program, and home for many Gators,&#8221; Florida athletic director Scott Stricklin said.</p>
<p>It’s the first Orange Bowl bid in Virginia history and the first New Year’s Six — the tag given to the Orange, Rose, Sugar, Cotton, Peach and Fiesta bowls — appearance for the Cavaliers since going to the Peach in 1998.</p>
<p>“Each year the bowl game quality and tier seems to be escalating, the stage that it&#8217;s on seems to be escalating,” Virginia coach Bronco Mendenhall said. “So my job is to advance our program and have it match those stages at a really high level.”</p>
<p>It’s an uncommon matchup: The only time the schools have played in football was 1959, a 55-10 win for the Gators at Florida Field.</p>
<p>But there are two common opponents in 2019 — Miami and Florida State. The Gators beat Miami 24-20 and Florida State 40-17; the Cavaliers lost to the Hurricanes 17-9 and beat the Seminoles 31-24 after rallying with two touchdowns in the final 6:02.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re 10-2. We played a tough non-conference schedule,” said Dan Mullen, the Florida coach who became the first in school history to start his Gators career with consecutive double-digit-win seasons. “We went out to aggressively schedule two Power 5 teams non-conference. I mean, there&#8217;s a lot of teams not doing that.”</p>
<p>Florida’s only losses were to CFP-bound and top-ranked LSU, along with SEC runner-up Georgia. Virginia lost to Notre Dame, Louisville, Miami and Saturday’s ACC championship game to Clemson in a 62-17 rout.</p>
<p>“That wasn&#8217;t us,&#8221; Virginia wide receiver Hasise Dubois said. &#8220;That was us playing, but we&#8217;re a better team than we showed.&#8221;</p>
<p>This Orange Bowl trip was a long time coming for the Cavaliers — almost 70 years in the making.</p>
<p>Virginia turned down a chance to play in the Orange Bowl after the 1951 season, because the school at the time didn’t want to be part of major college football. The Cavaliers didn’t go to their first bowl game until 1984.</p>
<p>“I’m just so happy for our players,&#8221; Virginia athletic director Carla Williams said. “This type of accolade, they’re the result of a lot of hard work over a long period of time.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Gators are in the Orange Bowl for the fourth time, having won each of their previous three appearances. They also won the BCS national championship game after the 2008 season, a game hosted by the Orange Bowl Committee.</p>
<p>Florida is in a New Year’s Six game for the second straight year, after beating Michigan in the Peach Bowl last season. Virginia topped South Carolina in the 2018 Belk Bowl and is making a third straight bowl appearance since a run of four in a row from 2002 through 2005.</p>
<p>“This team had to deal with so much adversity, so many injuries, so many other things,” Mullen said. “I think we were a better team at the end of the year, so it was a very successful year. We got another game.”</p>
<p>Clemson coach Dabo Swinney said Virginia shouldn’t be written off because of the one-sided ACC title game.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;ll tell you what, man, they&#8217;ve got some good players,” Swinney said. “Those guys are well positioned. They&#8217;re incredibly well-coached.”</p>
<p>Florida cornerback CJ Henderson, one of the Gators’ top players, will not be in the Orange Bowl. He’s already announced his intention to forgo his senior season and enter the NFL draft.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">561825</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 24 Butler tops Florida 76-62 behind balanced scoring</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-24-butler-tops-florida-76-62-behind-balanced-scoring/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 01:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=561675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[INDIANAPOLIS (AP) &#8212; Aaron Thompson believes unselfish play is a major part of Butler&#8217;s success. Thompson and Sean McDermott each scored 16 points to lead...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INDIANAPOLIS (AP) &#8212; Aaron Thompson believes unselfish play is a major part of Butler&#8217;s success.</p>
<p>Thompson and Sean McDermott each scored 16 points to lead No. 24 Butler to a 76-62 win over Florida on Saturday.</p>
<p>&#8220;Nobody cares who scores, we&#8217;re just trying to get the best shot on that possession,&#8221; Thompson said. &#8220;As long as we are getting good shots, everyone is happy.&#8221;<br />
Thompson made 6 of 7 shots and delivered seven assists for Butler (9-0).</p>
<p>McDermott missed his first four 3-point shots and then four of his final five. He contributed a team-high seven rebounds.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t know if we have a harder working player than Sean McDermott,&#8221; Butler coach LaVall Jordan said. &#8220;He&#8217;s made more of an effort to become a more complete player. Obviously, his strength is shooting the basketball, but he&#8217;s able to defend better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jordan Tucker added 13 points off the bench for the Bulldogs. Kamar Baldwin, who was averaging a team-high 17.5 points for Butler, scored 12 points.</p>
<p>Baldwin picked up two fouls in the first 3-plus minutes of the game and was limited to 11 minutes in the first half. The senior guard finished with three fouls.</p>
<p>&#8220;When Kamar got into foul trouble early, the next man was up and ready to go,&#8221; Jordan said.</p>
<p>Kerry Blackshear Jr. led Florida (6-3) with 17 points. Andrew Nembhard and Noah Locke each scored 11.</p>
<p>The Bulldogs shot 52% percent while holding the Gators to 44%. Butler made 9 of 20 3-pointers while Florida was 6 of 21. Each team had 10 turnovers.</p>
<p>The Gators, who trailed by nine at halftime, narrowed the deficit to six points twice before the Bulldogs pulled away. Butler&#8217;s largest lead was 19 points at 61-42 with 7:33 remaining.</p>
<p>Butler finished the first half with a 19-5 run to take a 35-26 lead at halftime. Trailing 21-16, the Bulldogs had an 11-0 run.</p>
<p>Florida coach Mike White said Butler was &#8220;more disciplined than us and that&#8217;s on me.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Gators start three sophomores, a freshman and Blackshear, a graduate transfer from Virginia Tech.</p>
<p>THE BEAT GOES ON</p>
<p>Butler owns the nation&#8217;s longest streak of consecutive non-conference home victories at 56.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida: After a solid start on the road, the Gators&#8217; four-game winning streak end with a thud. Entering the game with a 30% average from 3-point range, Florida shot 23%.</p>
<p>Butler: The Bulldogs won their third meeting with an SEC opponent in the last four games, previously beating Missouri 63-52 in the Hall of Fame Classic on Nov. 24 and host Mississippi 67-58 Tuesday.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: Home game against another Big East opponent Providence on Dec. 17.</p>
<p>Butler: Travels to No. 18 Baylor on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">561675</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 15 Florida falls to UConn 62-59 on the road</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-15-florida-falls-to-uconn-62-59-on-the-road/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=554291</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[STORRS, Conn. (AP) &#8212; Christian Vital scored 15 points and made a key steal at the end of the game as UConn upset No. 15...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>STORRS, Conn. (AP) &#x2014; Christian Vital scored 15 points and made a key steal at the end of the game as UConn upset No. 15 Florida 62-59 on Sunday.<p>Tyler Polley also scored 15 points and Josh Carlton added 13 for the Huskies (2-1) who led by five points at halftime and never trailed after intermission.</p><p>A layup by Florida&#x2019;s Keyontae Johnson with just over a minute to go cut the lead to 60-59, but those would be the last points the Gators scored.</p><p>Vital hit two free throws with 17 seconds left and Florida had a chance to tie. But Alterique Gilbert tipped the ball out of Johnson&#x2019;s hands and Vital grabbed it and dribbled away, securing the win.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/GatorsMBK/status/1196195680525570049?s=20</embed></div><p>Kerry Blackshear Jr. had 15 points and eight rebounds for Florida (2-2), falling two boards shy of a fourth straight double-double. But he fouled out with 4:37 left in the game and his team trailing 53-49.</p><p>Andrew Nembhard scored Florida&#x2019;s next four points, including a 3-pointer that brought the Gators within a point at 54-53.</p><p>Blackshear scored the game&#x2019;s first two baskets, but the Gators made just four of their first 13 attempts from the floor.</p><p>But UConn had a tougher start, going without a basket for the first six minutes.</p><p>Vital got the UConn crowd into the game with a 3-pointer, a dunk and a jumper on consecutive trips down the court that gave the Huskies an 11-6 lead.</p><p>The Huskies held Florida to two Blackshear free throws over the final 4:17 of the first half and led 25-20 at halftime.</p><p>BIG PICTURE</p><p>The loss ends a rough seven days for the Gators. Florida was No. 6 coming into the season but lost to Florida State a week ago and beat Towson by just six points on Thursday. The Gators offense came into the game averaging just 63.7 points per game, while giving up 60.7.</p><p>UConn: Highly touted freshman guard James Bouknight has finished serving his three-game suspension following his arrest on charges including evading police in a September car accident. Bouknight, who is due in court on Monday, is expected to suit up for the Huskies in this week&#x2019;s Charleston Classic, where it&#x2019;s possible the Huskies could again face either Saint Joseph&#x2019;s or Florida, depending on how the early rounds pan out.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Florida: The Gators face Saint Joseph&#x2019;s in the Charleston Classic on Thursday.</p><p>UConn: The Huskies also travel to Charleston and face Buffalo in the first round of the tournament on Thursday.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">554291</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
