<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Sports &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:43:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Sports &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site><item>
	<title>Trocheck, Reimer help Hurricanes blow past Panthers 4-2</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/trocheck-reimer-help-hurricanes-blow-past-panthers-4-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878143</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Vincent Trocheck and James Reimer continued to torment their former team, lifting the Carolina Hurricanes to their fifth straight victory with...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Vincent Trocheck and James Reimer continued to torment their former team, lifting the Carolina Hurricanes to their fifth straight victory with a 4-2 win over the Florida Panthers on Sunday night.</p>
<p>Trocheck, who was traded to Carolina just over a year ago, scored for the fourth time this season against the Panthers. Nino Niederreiter, Sebastian Aho and Warren Foegele also had goals for the Hurricanes, who have won eight of 10 home games (8-1-1) this season.</p>
<p>“We didn’t really have any lulls in the game,” Hurricanes coach Rod Brind’Amour said. “I like the fact that we hung in there. Didn’t get frustrated, just kept playing.”</p>
<p>Reimer, who made 21 saves, came to Carolina less two years in ago in a trade from Florida. He’s 3-0-0 since against the Panthers.</p>
<p>MacKenzie Weegar and Mason Marchment scored for Florida, which had a five-game points streak snapped. Chris Dreidger made 22 saves for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Trocheck scored just eight seconds into the Hurricanes’ first power play of the game. At that point with 4:05 to play in the opening period, Carolina had as many goals as the Panthers did shots on goal.</p>
<p>“We played a full 60 minutes,” Trocheck said. “I think this one was the best of the last four.”</p>
<p>Trocheck has four goals during his five-game points streak.</p>
<p>“He has found a home,” Brind’Amour said. “It’s no different than any job. When you’re feeling good about and where you fit, you have success. You don’t expect him to score at this rate, but we’ll take it for as long as we can.”</p>
<p>Niederreiter took a pass from Martin Necas and beat Dreidger, who had been under siege early in the second period. Niederreiter has 11 goals, posting at least one against every Central Division team except for Tampa Bay.</p>
<p>Carolina is 3-0-1 against the Panthers this season. This was the first meeting decided in regulation.</p>
<p>“They’re a well-structured team,” Panthers left wing Jonathan Huberdeau said. “It’s always tough to play against them.”</p>
<p>The Panthers got on the scoreboard when Weegar blasted the puck between Reimer’s pads with 9:19 left in the second period.</p>
<p>Aho posted the team’s second short-handed goal of the season 38 seconds into the third period. Foegele extended the lead to 4-1 slightly more than three minutes later.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes took advantage of special teams situations.</p>
<p>“You’ve got to make quick plays,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. “We had some good looks. We didn’t have enough of them. Not enough clean possession time.”</p>
<p>Florida won 6-2 at Nashville on Saturday, while the Hurricanes hadn’t played since Thursday night.</p>
<p>MILESTONE MOMENT</p>
<p>Panthers defenseman Keith Yandle appeared in his 1,000th career game. He’s in his 15th season in the league and his fourth season with the Panthers.</p>
<p>His accomplishment was recognized with an announcement during a break in the first period.</p>
<p>Yandle has played 890 consecutive games for the longest active streak in the league and the third-longest stretch in NHL history.</p>
<p>HIM AGAIN</p>
<p>Trocheck has scored in each of Carolina&#8217;s four matchups with Florida this season.</p>
<p>He’s the first player in the Carolina (and former Hartford) organization to score in his first four games against his ex-team following a trade since the NHL began tracking that information in 1991-92.</p>
<p>“I think it’s just the luck of the draw on that one,” Trocheck said of the topic. “Obviously it’s nice to get one against the former team. There’s motivation every night.”</p>
<p>Trocheck, who has a goal in four of the last five games, has a team-leading 13 goals this season. Florida doesn’t have a player with a double-digit goal total.</p>
<p>MORE TIME OFF</p>
<p>Hurricanes winger Teuvo Teravainen missed the game for undisclosed reasons. He had returned from a seven-game absence because of a concussion to play Thursday night in a victory against Detroit. He logged 14½ minutes in that game.</p>
<p>Brind’Amour said the latest time off might be related to the previous injury.</p>
<p>“Whenever you have those kinds of injuries, nobody really knows,” he said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Play at Columbus on Tuesday and Thursday.</p>
<p>Hurricanes: Stay home for games Tuesday and Thursday vs. Nashville.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878143</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Vols beat Florida 65-54, earn No. 4 seed in SEC tourney</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/vols-beat-florida-65-54-earn-no-4-seed-in-sec-tourney/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Gators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878145</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Victor Bailey Jr., John Fulkerson and Keon Johnson scored 14 points apiece and Tennessee rallied from a 14-point deficit to beat...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Victor Bailey Jr., John Fulkerson and Keon Johnson scored 14 points apiece and Tennessee rallied from a 14-point deficit to beat Florida 65-54 on Sunday in the regular-season finale for both teams.</p>
<p>Tennessee (17-7, 10-7 SEC) secured the No. 4 seed and a bye into the Friday&#8217;s quarterfinals of the conference tournament.</p>
<p>Fulkerson added seven rebounds and four assists and Josiah-Jordan James had eight points and 10 boards for the Volunteers.</p>
<p>Florida used a 13-2 run to take a 31-17 lead with five minutes left in the first half but Tennessee scored 11 of the final 13 first-half points to trim its deficit to five at the break. Florida missed seven consecutive, and 9 of 10, from the field as the Vols ripped off a 21-4 spurt — including eight points by Bailey — to make it 53-43 with 7:33 to play.</p>
<p>Tyree Appleby had 17 points on 7-of-14 shooting and Colin Castleton added 11 points for Florida (13-9, 9-7).</p>
<p>The fifth-seeded Gators play the winner between No. 12 seed Texas A&amp;M and No. 13 seed Vanderbilt in Thursday&#8217;s second round.</p>
<p>After being outrebounded 18-16 in the first half, Tennessee was plus-11 on the glass in the second. Florida had just 21 points after the break, its lowest-scoring half of the season.</p>
<p>The Gators went into the game leading the SEC in free-throw percentage (.760, 37th NCAA), field-goal percentage (.472, 42nd NCAA) and 3-point field-goal percentage (.359, 78th NCAA). On Sunday, they shot 41.7% from the field, made 3 of 13 (23.1%) from behind the arc and hit 11 of 18 (61.1%) free throws.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878145</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/gators.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Gators</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Hubb scores 22 as Notre Dame beats No. 11 Florida State</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hubb-scores-22-as-notre-dame-beats-no-11-florida-state/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877594</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — This time, Notre Dame made enough plays to knock off a ranked team. It had been a while. Prentiss Hubb...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — This time, Notre Dame made enough plays to knock off a ranked team.</p>
<p>It had been a while.</p>
<p>Prentiss Hubb scored 22 points, Dane Goodwin had 15 and Notre Dame beat No. 11 Florida State 83-73 on Saturday.</p>
<p>The Seminoles s (15-5, 11-4 squandered a chance for a second straight Atlantic Coast Conference title, losing out on the title when No. 21 Virginia beat Louisville later Saturday to win the regular-season championship.</p>
<p>The Fighting Irish (10-14, 7-11) had five players score in double figures in the program&#8217;s first win against a ranked team since a 67-66 victory over Wichita State in November 2017. They had dropped 28 such games in a row.</p>
<p>“I thought we had some edge about us to get loose balls and stick our nose in there and take charges, and that helped us,” coach Mike Brey said. “You’re not gonna really run anything pretty against an athletic, switching defense, (but) I thought we did a good job the last two days of practice talking about just opening the floor up and cutting more.”</p>
<p>Cormac Ryan, Nikola Djogo and Nate Laszewski had 11 points apiece for Notre Dame, which had dropped four in a row. Juwan Durham had nine points and nine rebounds.</p>
<p>The Fighting Irish went 28 for 34 at the free-throw line, compared to 15 for 20 for the Seminoles.</p>
<p>“I thought Notre Dame did a better job of being extremely aggressive and hitting the open shots and challenging our defensive discipline by making the extra pass,” Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton said. “Then at the end, they hit their free throws.”</p>
<p>Scottie Barnes led Florida State with 17 points. RaiQuan Gray added 15 points and 10 rebounds. M.J. Walker had 12 points on 4-for-16 shooting.</p>
<p>Notre Dame led by as many as 20 on its way to a 47-31 halftime lead. Florida State closed to 74-70 on Anthony Polite&#8217;s 3-pointer with 2:34 left. But Laszewski hit four foul shots down the stretch to help the Irish close it out.</p>
<p>WORTH NOTING</p>
<p>Hubb passed 1,000 career points, becoming the 65th player in program history to reach the milestone.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles are comfortably in the NCAA Tournament and only fighting for seeding position as they head into the ACC Tournament.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish got Brey a sorely needed victory near the end of a challenging season.</p>
<p>TITLE TALK</p>
<p>Florida State got its first ACC regular-season title last year during its 29th year in the league. A repeat seemed likely entering Saturday.</p>
<p>“Part of the journey of our team is being in a position mentally and emotionally to handle this moment, the pressure to want to play well and win a championship,” Hamilton said. “The will of Notre Dame wanting to be successful against a Top 25 opponent, their will was a little stronger than ours today.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida State: The Seminoles enter the ACC tourney as either the No. 1 or No. 2 seed, pending the outcome of Virginia’s game. Either way, FSU will have a double bye into Thursday’s quarterfinals.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish, as the ACC’s No. 11 seed, face 14th-seeded Wake Forest on Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877594</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Butler takes over, Heat top Pelicans 103-93</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-takes-over-heat-top-pelicans-103-93/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 04:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876379</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#8217;s absence to beat the...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>NEW ORLEANS (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#x2019;s absence to beat the New Orleans Pelicans 103-93 on Thursday night.<p>With a repertoire of strong inside moves and accurate mid-range shooting, Butler made 10 of 14 shots and eight of nine free throws to help the Heat keep the Pelicans at bay. Butler added a late step-back 3 to give him 10 points during an 11-2 run that put Miami up 98-87 with 2:50 to go.</p><p>Kelly Olynyk hit his first four 3-point shots and finished with 18 points and 10 rebounds, and Goran Dragic scored nine of his 13 points in the second half for Miami.</p><p>Brandon Ingram scored 17 points and Steven Adams scored 15 for New Orleans. Nickeil Alexander-Walker scored 13 and Josh Hart 12 for the Pelicans.</p><p>Hart, normally a reserve, was inserted in the starting lineup after Williamson was scratched because of a toe injury.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/TheMozKnowz/status/1367691307582423041?s=20</embed></div><p>While the Pelicans struggled mightily to make shots during the first three quarters, Miami was unable to put New Orleans away early.</p><p>When Hart made a half-court shot as the horn sounded to signal the end of the third period, the Heat&#x2019;s lead was just 77-70.</p><p>Alexander-Walker then pulled the Pelicans to 77-73 with a 3 to open the fourth quarter, which was largely competitive until Butler began asserting himself more in the final five minutes.</p><p>TIP-INS</p><p>Heat: Andre Iguodala scored 10 points, highlighted by a late driving dunk that virtually sealed the victory. &#x2026; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra is now 16-17 against Pelicans coach Stan Van Gundy, his longtime friend and mentor. &#x2026; This is the fourth time in the last seven seasons that the Heat haven&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t been better than .500 at the All-Star break. But during Spoelstra&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s 12-year tenure, Miami has won 62% of its games after the break. Only San Antonio and Houston have better post-break records in the Spoelstra era. &#x2026; Miami shot 49.3% (36 of 73) but missed 20 of 30 3-point shots.</p><p>Pelicans: In addition to being without Williamson, New Orleans also played without JJ Redick, who was bothered by a sore right heel. &#x2026; The Pelicans shot just 39.8% (33 of 83) and missed 33 of 43 3-point shots. &#x2026; Rookie Kira Lewis Jr. scored 11 points in 17 minutes off the bench. &#x2026; Lonzo Ball scored 10 but missed nine of 11 shots from deep.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Heat: Hosts Orlando on March 11.</p><p>Pelicans: Host Minnesota on March 11.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876379</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Noel Acciari gets hat trick as Panthers beat Predators 6-2</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/noel-acciari-gets-hat-trick-as-panthers-beat-predators-6-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877581</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The Florida Panthers are playing so well that someone who hadn&#8217;t scored a point this season can turn in a hat...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The Florida Panthers are playing so well that someone who hadn&#8217;t scored a point this season can turn in a hat trick.</p>
<p>The Nashville Predators couldn&#8217;t be much more frustrated right now, struggling despite having so many key players who won a Presidents&#8217; Trophy just three seasons ago.</p>
<p>Noel Acciari scored three goals for his third career hat trick, and the Panthers beat the Nashville Predators 6-2 on Saturday for their second straight victory.</p>
<p>Acciari, who began the day with no points in 14 games this season, scored twice in a three-goal second period as the Panthers took the lead for good. He finished off the hat trick with an unassisted goal with 3:02 left.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s a great feeling,” Acciari said. “I was just hoping to get one &#8230; just to get my first of the season. But to get the other two was definitely exciting, and a lot of guys are putting pressure on me about tomorrow.”</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because the last time Acciari had a hat trick, he became the second in Florida history to turn in a hat trick in consecutive games on Dec. 16-20, 2019. Florida coach Joel Quenneville said the fourth-line forward either scores none or he scores three at a time.</p>
<p>“Pretty impressive,” Quenneville said. &#8220;He gets flurries and nice to see him score. I think around the net he&#8217;s been pressing a little bit. He doesn&#8217;t get a ton of chances, but he&#8217;s usually pretty nifty and tonight they were going in.”</p>
<p>Aaron Ekblad, Jonathan Huberdeau and Frank Vatrano each had a goal and an assist as the Panthers improved to 8-1-1 on the road this season. Keith Yandle had two assists. Sergei Bobrovsky made 28 saves.</p>
<p>Eeli Tolvanen and Viktor Arvidsson scored for Nashville, which lost its third straight and dropped to 1-9 combined against the Central Division&#8217;s top three teams. Filip Forsberg had two assists, including the 200th of his career.</p>
<p>Nashville captain Roman Josi was so frustrated he nearly cursed talking to media after the game. He said the Predators have an identity for parts of games but not the full 60 minutes.</p>
<p>“We need to find a way to get out of this together,” Josi said. “It’s obviously not the way we want to play right now.”</p>
<p>The Predators took the first 10 shots and didn&#8217;t allow a Florida shot until midway through the first period. When Grigori Denisenko tripped Forsberg, the Predators scored 7 seconds into the man advantage with <a href="https://twitter.com/PredsNHL/status/1368281375040823299">Tolvanen easily beating Bobrovsky</a> with a slap shot to the far side of the net.</p>
<p>They appeared poised to take just their fourth lead after the first period this season until the final seconds. That&#8217;s when Ekblad, coming off a four-point game, tied it with 12.6 seconds left in the first with a snap shot from the high slot at the right circle. It was all Panthers from there.</p>
<p>Huberdeau put the Panthers up 2-1 just 1:15 into the second with Patric Horqnvist getting his 500th career NHL point on the assist. Hornqvist got the puck in the Nashville offensive zone and passed to Huberdeau, who had <a href="https://twitter.com/NHL/status/1368295895608008707">enough time to deke out Rinne</a> before flipping the puck over the goalie&#8217;s right pad.</p>
<p>Acciari padded the lead at 11:17 of the second, finishing off a 2-on-1 with a wrist shot from the right circle. He got his second with 1:14 left in the period with a backhand past Rinne for a power-play goal.</p>
<p>TOO LITTLE TOO LATE</p>
<p>Nashville came in tied for the NHL lead with 30 goals in the third period this season. Arvidsson made it 31 with a wrist shot in front 19 seconds into the third.</p>
<p>But the Predators couldn&#8217;t put one past Bobrovsky the rest of the period. Vatrano got his eighth of the season before Acciari capped the scoring.</p>
<p>ROAD WARRIORS</p>
<p>The Panthers already had the best road record through the first nine games in franchise history, and they won their fourth straight in Nashville. Florida also is 5-1-0 over the last six road games. Montreal is the only other NHL team with only one regulation road loss this season.</p>
<p>DUCHENE OUT</p>
<p>Nashville center Matt Duchene was placed on injured reserve. He is expected to be sidelined for three to five weeks with a lower-body injury. The veteran has eight points in 23 games this season with a minus-11 rating.</p>
<p>WHAT&#8217;S NEXT</p>
<p>After dropping two to the Hurricanes in Florida, the Panthers continue their road trip Sunday in Carolina.</p>
<p>The Predators start an eight-game road swing Sunday night in Dallas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877581</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>McGusty scores 27, rallies Miami over Boston College 80-76</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mcgusty-scores-27-rallies-miami-over-boston-college-80-76/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877116</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Kameron McGusty scored a season-high 27 points and led a late rally as Miami defeated Boston College 80-76 on Friday...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Kameron McGusty scored a season-high 27 points and led a late rally as Miami defeated Boston College 80-76 on Friday in a regular-season finale.</p>
<p>Boston College (4-15, 2-11 Atlantic Coast Conference) erased Miami&#8217;s largest lead of the game of nine points with a 11-0 run while the Hurricanes (8-16, 4-15) went scoreless for over 4 1/2 minutes to trail 68-66 with 3:40 left. McGusty ended the drought with a bucket, scoring the first seven points of a 9-0 run that gave Miami a 75-68 lead with 1:49 remaining. Boston College got within three on a 3-pointer by Frederick Scott with 6.4 seconds to go but an Isaiah Wong free throw ensured the win.</p>
<p>McGusty was 9-of-12 shooting with four 3-pointers and five assists. Nysier Brooks scored a career-high 21 points on 8-of-11 shooting and Anthony Walker added 17 points, seven rebounds and four assists. Miami, injury-plagued all season, had just six scholarship athletes available but were able to snap a six-game losing streak.</p>
<p>James Karnik scored 15 points, hitting all nine of his free throws, to lead the Eagles. Makai Ashton-Langford added 13 points, Frederick Scott and Kamari Williams scored 11 points each and JC Felder had 10 points and a career-high six blocks. Jay Heath, the Eagles&#8217; leading scorer who had 25 points in BC&#8217;s 84-62 win over Miami on Jan. 13, finished with 10 points on 4-of-16 shooting. The Eagles, who made a season-high 18 3-pointers in that January win, had nine on Friday.</p>
<p>The teams started the day with the same winning percentage (.167) so they were playing to avoid becoming the lowest seed for the conference tournament that runs March 9-13 in Greensboro, North Carolina.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877116</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>NFL picks its first Black female game official</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nfl-picks-its-first-black-female-game-official/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876973</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Maia Chaka will make history when the new National Football League season starts this year. The NFL said Friday it has added Chaka...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Maia Chaka will make history when the new National Football League season starts this year.</p>
<p>The NFL said Friday it has added Chaka to its roster of game officials for 2021, making her the league&#8217;s first Black woman named to the position.</p>
<p>Chaka, a Virginia educator and erstwhile college football game official, says she&#8217;s honored to be selected, but that this is also &#8220;bigger than a personal accomplishment.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;It is an accomplishment for all women, my community, and my culture,&#8221; Chaka said in a<a href="https://nflcommunications.com/Pages/MAIA-CHAKA-ADDED-TO-NFL-OFFICIATING-ROSTER.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> statement released by the league</a>.</p>
<p>Chaka, previously a game official in the NCAA&#8217;s Pac-12 Conference and Conference USA, also officiated in the short-lived Alliance of American Football in 2019. She entered the NFL&#8217;s Officiating Development Program in 2014.</p>
<p>The league says the program offers top officiating prospects in the collegiate ranks &#8220;exposure to in-game experiences that NFL officials face, to determine if they have the ability to succeed.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Maia&#8217;s years of hard work, dedication and perseverance &#8212; including as part of the NFL Officiating Development Program &#8212; have earned her a position as an NFL official,&#8221; Troy Vincent Sr., NFL executive vice president of football operations, <a href="https://nflcommunications.com/Pages/MAIA-CHAKA-ADDED-TO-NFL-OFFICIATING-ROSTER.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said.</a></p>
<p>&#8220;As we celebrate Women&#8217;s History Month, Maia is a trailblazer as the first Black female official and inspires us toward normalizing women on the football field,&#8221; Vincent said.</p>
<p>Off the football field, Chaka is a health and physical education teacher in the Virginia Beach public school system.</p>
<p>Her selection by the NFL comes six years after the league made Sarah Thomas its first permanent female game official.</p>
<p>Thomas became the first female to officiate an NFL playoff game in 2019, and the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/19/us/sarah-thomas-to-ref-super-bowl-trnd/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first female on a Super Bowl officiating crew this year</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876973</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_af673e9dc3e41ab0dc7c92049c71aae1-h_7eb93f2fb0630cf6537368219d1624a3.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/afe54f1b-4721-428a-b14d-919fc5a8d980/8f06c8a0-9c3b-40b7-a310-2a76f8d54da3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218067~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/afe54f1b-4721-428a-b14d-919fc5a8d980/8f06c8a0-9c3b-40b7-a310-2a76f8d54da3/main.mp4*~hmac=2e96e863fd1cc9e192759066a12030403dbf402a928930adf6a0ddd164568357' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_af673e9dc3e41ab0dc7c92049c71aae1-h_7eb93f2fb0630cf6537368219d1624a3.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_af673e9dc3e41ab0dc7c92049c71aae1-h_7eb93f2fb0630cf6537368219d1624a3.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Salt Lake Stallions v San Diego Fleet</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Butler takes over, Heat top Pelicans 103-93</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-takes-over-heat-top-pelicans-103-93/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 04:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876379</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#8217;s absence to beat the...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>NEW ORLEANS (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#x2019;s absence to beat the New Orleans Pelicans 103-93 on Thursday night.<p>With a repertoire of strong inside moves and accurate mid-range shooting, Butler made 10 of 14 shots and eight of nine free throws to help the Heat keep the Pelicans at bay. Butler added a late step-back 3 to give him 10 points during an 11-2 run that put Miami up 98-87 with 2:50 to go.</p><p>Kelly Olynyk hit his first four 3-point shots and finished with 18 points and 10 rebounds, and Goran Dragic scored nine of his 13 points in the second half for Miami.</p><p>Brandon Ingram scored 17 points and Steven Adams scored 15 for New Orleans. Nickeil Alexander-Walker scored 13 and Josh Hart 12 for the Pelicans.</p><p>Hart, normally a reserve, was inserted in the starting lineup after Williamson was scratched because of a toe injury.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/TheMozKnowz/status/1367691307582423041?s=20</embed></div><p>While the Pelicans struggled mightily to make shots during the first three quarters, Miami was unable to put New Orleans away early.</p><p>When Hart made a half-court shot as the horn sounded to signal the end of the third period, the Heat&#x2019;s lead was just 77-70.</p><p>Alexander-Walker then pulled the Pelicans to 77-73 with a 3 to open the fourth quarter, which was largely competitive until Butler began asserting himself more in the final five minutes.</p><p>TIP-INS</p><p>Heat: Andre Iguodala scored 10 points, highlighted by a late driving dunk that virtually sealed the victory. &#x2026; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra is now 16-17 against Pelicans coach Stan Van Gundy, his longtime friend and mentor. &#x2026; This is the fourth time in the last seven seasons that the Heat haven&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t been better than .500 at the All-Star break. But during Spoelstra&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s 12-year tenure, Miami has won 62% of its games after the break. Only San Antonio and Houston have better post-break records in the Spoelstra era. &#x2026; Miami shot 49.3% (36 of 73) but missed 20 of 30 3-point shots.</p><p>Pelicans: In addition to being without Williamson, New Orleans also played without JJ Redick, who was bothered by a sore right heel. &#x2026; The Pelicans shot just 39.8% (33 of 83) and missed 33 of 43 3-point shots. &#x2026; Rookie Kira Lewis Jr. scored 11 points in 17 minutes off the bench. &#x2026; Lonzo Ball scored 10 but missed nine of 11 shots from deep.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Heat: Hosts Orlando on March 11.</p><p>Pelicans: Host Minnesota on March 11.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876379</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Hawks win McMillan&#8217;s debut as interim coach, top Heat 94-80</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hawks-win-mcmillans-debut-as-interim-coach-top-heat-94-80/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874785</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Trae Young took over late and made sure Nate McMillan would win his debut as interim coach of the Atlanta Hawks. Young...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Trae Young took over late and made sure Nate McMillan would win his debut as interim coach of the Atlanta Hawks.</p>
<p>Young scored 18 points, including 13 straight for his team in the fourth quarter, and the Hawks snapped Miami’s six-game winning streak by beating the Heat 94-80 on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>John Collins scored 17 for Atlanta, which lost at Miami on Sunday and fired coach Lloyd Pierce on Monday. Kevin Huerter scored 16 for the Hawks and Clint Capela had 10 points and 17 rebounds.</p>
<p>“Losing Coach Pierce, we all had to do better,&#8221; McMillan said. “And that was the challenge to this team tonight. He took a hit because we didn&#8217;t do what we were supposed to be doing out there. And I thought tonight, they did better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Duncan Robinson and Goran Dragic each scored 14 for Miami, which missed a chance to get over .500 for the first time this season. Bam Adebayo scored 11 for the Heat, who shot 37% — their fourth-worst showing of the season.</p>
<p>“We had been trending much better offensively,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “It just was a flat offensive game. It was not a fluid game for us on that side of the floor.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tony Snell added 11 for the Hawks.</p>
<p>“Ugly game, but in the end you win a lot of games giving up 80 points,&#8221; Huerter said. “Great bounceback from the last 24 hours. And now we&#8217;ve got to finish the first half of the season strong tomorrow in Orlando.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami was outrebounded 47-26, by far its worst margin of the season, and was held to a season-low in points. The Heat were again without Jimmy Butler, who missed his second consecutive game with right knee inflammation.</p>
<p>Miami shot 29% in the opening quarter and 36% in the half, including a 2-for-15 start from 3-point range. But by limiting Young for the second consecutive game — he had just two points by halftime and five points after three quarters — the Heat hung around, trailing 44-37 at the break and leading 66-63 going into the fourth.</p>
<p>Then Young got hot in the fourth, when the Heat shot just 5 for 18, and just like that what had been the NBA’s longest active winning streak entering the night was finished.</p>
<p>It was Miami&#8217;s lowest point total in its home building since scoring 79 against Milwaukee on Jan. 19, 2016. The Heat were held to 85 or fewer points for the fifth time this season, by far the most in the NBA — with Butler missing four of those five games.</p>
<p>“Defenses are going to be disruptive and do different things to try to guard us,&#8221; Robinson said. “But there are always counters and ways to be effective. We just have to find solutions.&#8221;</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Hawks: Bogdan Bogdanovic returned after missing 25 games with an avulsion fracture in his right knee. He had five points in 16 minutes. &#8230; Atlanta had 23 turnovers to Miami’s nine and won anyway. “You&#8217;re not going to win many games with that amount,&#8221; McMillan said.</p>
<p>Heat: Tyler Herro has a 3-pointer in 32 straight games, tying for the fifth-longest streak in team history. He’s one shy of matching Tim Hardaway — who had two separate 33-game streaks. &#8230; Robinson is four away from 400 career 3-pointers. He’s played 123 games; Young is the fastest to make 400 3s in NBA history, and it took him 159 games.</p>
<p>SLOW FIRST</p>
<p>Just as he did Sunday in Miami, Young went scoreless in the first quarter. The last time he was blanked in the opening quarter of consecutive games was Dec. 10 and 11, 2019, against the Heat and Chicago.</p>
<p>The Hawks had lost 13 consecutive games when he was scoreless in first quarters.</p>
<p>SLOW HALF</p>
<p>The 81 combined points at the half were the fourth fewest by halftime in an NBA game this season. Miami-Dallas had 77 on Jan. 1, New York-Cleveland on Jan. 29 had 80 and Toronto-Minnesota on Feb. 19 also had 80.</p>
<p>The 37 points allowed matched Atlanta’s best first-half defensive effort in its last 145 games. The last time they gave up that few was Jan. 6, 2019 — also against Miami.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Hawks: Visit Orlando on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Heat: Visit New Orleans on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874785</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>AP source: NBA set to remove restriction on 2-way deals</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ap-source-nba-set-to-remove-restriction-on-2-way-deals/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874783</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The NBA has moved closer to a deal where players on two-way contracts would be eligible to appear on the active roster...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The NBA has moved closer to a deal where players on two-way contracts would be eligible to appear on the active roster for as many games as their teams would like this season, a person with knowledge of the situation said Tuesday.</p>
<p>The proposal to lift what was a 50-game limit on the active roster for two-way players got overwhelming support Tuesday and is likely to be passed by the NBA’s board of governors, said the person who spoke to The Associated Press on condition of anonymity because that final approval is pending. The approval is expected later this month.</p>
<p>No team has used two-ways more this season than Miami, with Gabe Vincent and Max Strus having a combined 42 appearances this season entering Tuesday’s game against Atlanta. Vincent has also been a part-time starter for the Heat, and Miami was one of the teams concerned that those 50-game appearance limits on the active roster was fast approaching.</p>
<p>“We all appreciate that they see that each team is in a different place,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “We felt that we’ve competed in this season with great honor and respect to the league. &#8230; Our two-ways are playing for us. There are a few other teams that are in that circumstance. It’s just an uneven and unpredictable year for so many teams. Not even all the teams are in the same range of amount of games played up to this point, with all the postponements.”</p>
<p>The NBA relaxed the rule on two-way players for this season in anticipation of postponements and rosters being taxed by virus-related issues. The rule in past years has been that two-way players could spend 45 days with the NBA club and the rest of the time with a franchise’s G League team. But with a shortened G League season this year, and not all teams having clubs in that league this season, there were obvious reasons to change things.</p>
<p>Players on two-way deals are earning $449,155 this season.</p>
<p>“It just makes all the sense in the world to not have to even think about that or concern yourself with days, particularly when we are playing them,” Spoelstra said of the looming change. “It’s what’s fair to the teams. It’s what makes the most sense and is fair to the players. We are just glad that it was seen that way, objectively, because not everybody is in the same circumstance.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874783</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180621_NBA_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Heat top Hawks for 6th straight win, get back to .500</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-top-hawks-for-6th-straight-win-get-back-to-500/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 05:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873224</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat are back at .500, not even a couple weeks removed from being near the very bottom of the Eastern...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat are back at .500, not even a couple weeks removed from being near the very bottom of the Eastern Conference.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn scored 24 points, Bam Adebayo had 16 points and 13 rebounds, and the Heat extended the NBA’s longest current winning streak to six games by beating the Atlanta Hawks 109-99 on Sunday night.</p>
<p>“That was a big-time game for us,” Nunn said. “Took a step in the right direction.”</p>
<p>Previous Achiuwa had 14 points in 12 minutes for Miami, which used a 10-0 run late in the fourth quarter to pull away from a game that was tied at 95 with 3:00 left. Tyler Herro had 12 of his 14 points for Miami in the fourth and Goran Dragic scored 13 for the Heat (17-17).</p>
<p>John Collins led all scorers with 34 points for Atlanta, plus grabbed 10 rebounds. Clint Capela finished with 20 points and 14 rebounds for the Hawks, while Trae Young added 15 points, nine assists and eight rebounds.</p>
<p>But Young shot just 3 for 14.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s seen the pressure,&#8221; Hawks coach Lloyd Pierce said. “He knows teams are going to throw different defenses at us. A lot of it&#8217;s focused on taking the ball out of his hands. And we have ways to punish, but again, if you don&#8217;t make shots there&#8217;s nothing really we can do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Huerter scored 13 for the Hawks, who were just 8 for 35 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>The teams play again Tuesday in Miami when the Heat — who have won 10 of their last 13 — will try to get over .500 for the first time all season. Miami played Sunday without Jimmy Butler, sidelined by right knee inflammation.</p>
<p>“With Jimmy out, I thought guys really stepped up and filled in in a lot of different places,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>Miami led 54-44 at the half, a big part of that because of their defense on Young. He was scoreless until 2:53 remained in the half, the deepest he’s gone into a game this season without a point.</p>
<p>Collins was 4 for 4 in the second quarter, helping keep the Hawks within striking distance.</p>
<p>He stayed dominant in the third. Collins had 19 in that quarter alone — the second-most any player has had in a quarter against Miami this season, one shy of the 20 that Philadelphia’s Joel Embiid had in the third quarter of the 76ers’ win over the Heat on Jan. 12.</p>
<p>Capela added 10 in the third quarter and the Hawks briefly recaptured the lead before going into the fourth down just 78-77. Collins and Capela were 13 for 18 in the third; the rest of the Hawks were 1 for 8 and Young — just as he was in the first quarter — was scoreless.</p>
<p>“JC was really setting the tone by being aggressive,&#8221; Capela said.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Hawks: Young’s scoreless first quarter was his fifth of the season. The Hawks are 0-5 in those games this season and 0-13 in those games since the finale of his rookie year. &#8230; Rajon Rondo’s last seven games in Miami have come with him playing for seven different teams: Boston, Dallas, Sacramento, Chicago, New Orleans, the Lakers and now Atlanta.</p>
<p>Heat: The six straight wins is Miami&#8217;s longest such regular-season streak since a seven-game run midway through the 2017-18 season. The Heat had a seven-game win streak in last season&#8217;s playoffs as well. &#8230; Among those in the crowd of about 3,000 was celebrity chef Guy Fieri. &#8230; Adebayo now has six consecutive double-doubles, tying a career-best.</p>
<p>BUTLER’S KNEE</p>
<p>The Heat are listing Butler as day-to-day. Spoelstra said Butler was with the team for shootaround Sunday morning and the knee “didn’t loosen up the way he wanted it to.” Spoelstra added that he believes the issue is minor.</p>
<p>FLORIDA MEN</p>
<p>This game was the first of four consecutive the Hawks will play in Florida — they’re at Miami again Tuesday, at Orlando on Wednesday and vs. Toronto in Tampa to start the second half on March 11. They are scheduled to play four straight in California from March 20-26, and have had only one four-game stretch in Georgia so far this season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873224</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Butler, Dragic carry Heat past NBA-best Jazz, 124-116</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-dragic-carry-heat-past-nba-best-jazz-124-116/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 03:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872208</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Jimmy Butler and the Miami Heat got their most significant win of the season and took down the team with the NBA’s...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Jimmy Butler and the Miami Heat got their most significant win of the season and took down the team with the NBA’s best record in the process.</p>
<p>Butler scored a season-high 33 points, reserve Goran Dragic tied his season-best with 26 and the Heat held on to beat Utah 124-116 on Friday night — handing the Jazz (26-7) just their third loss in their last 25 games.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo scored 19 points and grabbed 11 rebounds for Miami, which has won a season-best five straight games. Duncan Robinson scored 15 and Kendrick Nunn added 12 for the Heat.</p>
<p>Donovan Mitchell scored 30 for the Jazz, who got 17 from Bojan Bogdanovic and 15 from Rudy Gobert. Mike Conley scored 14 for Utah, which got 13 apiece from Jordan Clarkson and Joe Ingles.</p>
<p>Miami outrebounded Utah 49-36 and held the Jazz to 15-for-46 shooting from 3-point range.</p>
<p>The Heat had to dig deep time and again in the fourth to pull out the win.</p>
<p>Dragic found Andre Iguodala for an open 3-pointer, then made another himself on the next Heat possession for a 114-107 lead.</p>
<p>Bogdanovic’s 3-pointer with 3:39 left started the last Jazz flurry, Conley got a layup on the next Utah possession and Gobert made two free throws on the next. Just like that, the Jazz were within 116-115.</p>
<p>But they got no closer, with Dragic taking a charge to erase what would have been a basket by Conley with 1:58 left. The Jazz wound up missing their last six shots.</p>
<p>The Jazz are shooting 41.2% on 3-pointers in the first halves of games this season against everyone other than Miami, and only 22.2% in the opening half of their two games against the Heat. They were 7 for 24 before the break on Friday, part of the reason why Miami went into intermission up 57-53.</p>
<p>There were six ties, six lead changes, and neither team led by more than six in that first half. And Miami held on for a 96-94 lead after three quarters — the prerequisite for beating the Jazz this season. Utah came into Friday 24-0 when leading after three quarters, 2-6 when trailing.</p>
<p>They’re 2-7 now.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Jazz: Derrick Favors played in his 607th career regular-season game with Utah, breaking a tie with Rickey Green for ninth on the team’s all-time list. Next up: Bryon Russell, 628. &#8230; Gobert had a free throw 1:53 into the game for his 6,000th career point.</p>
<p>Heat: Adebayo was listed as questionable coming into the game because of a knee issue. &#8230; Tyler Herro (bruised hip) missed his third straight game with that injury and 11th missed game this season overall. &#8230; It was the sixth game in Heat history in which both teams had at least 94 points through three quarters. Three of those have come since Feb. 26, 2020.</p>
<p>FUNDAMENTALS</p>
<p>The teams were a combined 14 for 14 from the foul line in the first half. It was the second time the Jazz had been part of a game in which both teams shot 100% from the line in the opening 24 minutes this season, and the first such game for the Heat since a “home” game in the bubble last season against Toronto.</p>
<p>RAINING 3’S</p>
<p>Utah has more 3-pointers through 33 games, 559, than any other NBA team has ever made through not just 33 games — but even 35 games. Houston had 554 3’s made through the first 35 games of the 2017-18 season. The previous 33-game mark was 522, by those 2017-18 Rockets.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Jazz: Visit Orlando on Saturday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host Atlanta on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872208</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Trocheck, Reimer help Hurricanes blow past Panthers 4-2</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/trocheck-reimer-help-hurricanes-blow-past-panthers-4-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878143</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Vincent Trocheck and James Reimer continued to torment their former team, lifting the Carolina Hurricanes to their fifth straight victory with...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Vincent Trocheck and James Reimer continued to torment their former team, lifting the Carolina Hurricanes to their fifth straight victory with a 4-2 win over the Florida Panthers on Sunday night.</p>
<p>Trocheck, who was traded to Carolina just over a year ago, scored for the fourth time this season against the Panthers. Nino Niederreiter, Sebastian Aho and Warren Foegele also had goals for the Hurricanes, who have won eight of 10 home games (8-1-1) this season.</p>
<p>“We didn’t really have any lulls in the game,” Hurricanes coach Rod Brind’Amour said. “I like the fact that we hung in there. Didn’t get frustrated, just kept playing.”</p>
<p>Reimer, who made 21 saves, came to Carolina less two years in ago in a trade from Florida. He’s 3-0-0 since against the Panthers.</p>
<p>MacKenzie Weegar and Mason Marchment scored for Florida, which had a five-game points streak snapped. Chris Dreidger made 22 saves for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Trocheck scored just eight seconds into the Hurricanes’ first power play of the game. At that point with 4:05 to play in the opening period, Carolina had as many goals as the Panthers did shots on goal.</p>
<p>“We played a full 60 minutes,” Trocheck said. “I think this one was the best of the last four.”</p>
<p>Trocheck has four goals during his five-game points streak.</p>
<p>“He has found a home,” Brind’Amour said. “It’s no different than any job. When you’re feeling good about and where you fit, you have success. You don’t expect him to score at this rate, but we’ll take it for as long as we can.”</p>
<p>Niederreiter took a pass from Martin Necas and beat Dreidger, who had been under siege early in the second period. Niederreiter has 11 goals, posting at least one against every Central Division team except for Tampa Bay.</p>
<p>Carolina is 3-0-1 against the Panthers this season. This was the first meeting decided in regulation.</p>
<p>“They’re a well-structured team,” Panthers left wing Jonathan Huberdeau said. “It’s always tough to play against them.”</p>
<p>The Panthers got on the scoreboard when Weegar blasted the puck between Reimer’s pads with 9:19 left in the second period.</p>
<p>Aho posted the team’s second short-handed goal of the season 38 seconds into the third period. Foegele extended the lead to 4-1 slightly more than three minutes later.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes took advantage of special teams situations.</p>
<p>“You’ve got to make quick plays,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. “We had some good looks. We didn’t have enough of them. Not enough clean possession time.”</p>
<p>Florida won 6-2 at Nashville on Saturday, while the Hurricanes hadn’t played since Thursday night.</p>
<p>MILESTONE MOMENT</p>
<p>Panthers defenseman Keith Yandle appeared in his 1,000th career game. He’s in his 15th season in the league and his fourth season with the Panthers.</p>
<p>His accomplishment was recognized with an announcement during a break in the first period.</p>
<p>Yandle has played 890 consecutive games for the longest active streak in the league and the third-longest stretch in NHL history.</p>
<p>HIM AGAIN</p>
<p>Trocheck has scored in each of Carolina&#8217;s four matchups with Florida this season.</p>
<p>He’s the first player in the Carolina (and former Hartford) organization to score in his first four games against his ex-team following a trade since the NHL began tracking that information in 1991-92.</p>
<p>“I think it’s just the luck of the draw on that one,” Trocheck said of the topic. “Obviously it’s nice to get one against the former team. There’s motivation every night.”</p>
<p>Trocheck, who has a goal in four of the last five games, has a team-leading 13 goals this season. Florida doesn’t have a player with a double-digit goal total.</p>
<p>MORE TIME OFF</p>
<p>Hurricanes winger Teuvo Teravainen missed the game for undisclosed reasons. He had returned from a seven-game absence because of a concussion to play Thursday night in a victory against Detroit. He logged 14½ minutes in that game.</p>
<p>Brind’Amour said the latest time off might be related to the previous injury.</p>
<p>“Whenever you have those kinds of injuries, nobody really knows,” he said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Play at Columbus on Tuesday and Thursday.</p>
<p>Hurricanes: Stay home for games Tuesday and Thursday vs. Nashville.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878143</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Noel Acciari gets hat trick as Panthers beat Predators 6-2</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/noel-acciari-gets-hat-trick-as-panthers-beat-predators-6-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877581</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The Florida Panthers are playing so well that someone who hadn&#8217;t scored a point this season can turn in a hat...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The Florida Panthers are playing so well that someone who hadn&#8217;t scored a point this season can turn in a hat trick.</p>
<p>The Nashville Predators couldn&#8217;t be much more frustrated right now, struggling despite having so many key players who won a Presidents&#8217; Trophy just three seasons ago.</p>
<p>Noel Acciari scored three goals for his third career hat trick, and the Panthers beat the Nashville Predators 6-2 on Saturday for their second straight victory.</p>
<p>Acciari, who began the day with no points in 14 games this season, scored twice in a three-goal second period as the Panthers took the lead for good. He finished off the hat trick with an unassisted goal with 3:02 left.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s a great feeling,” Acciari said. “I was just hoping to get one &#8230; just to get my first of the season. But to get the other two was definitely exciting, and a lot of guys are putting pressure on me about tomorrow.”</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because the last time Acciari had a hat trick, he became the second in Florida history to turn in a hat trick in consecutive games on Dec. 16-20, 2019. Florida coach Joel Quenneville said the fourth-line forward either scores none or he scores three at a time.</p>
<p>“Pretty impressive,” Quenneville said. &#8220;He gets flurries and nice to see him score. I think around the net he&#8217;s been pressing a little bit. He doesn&#8217;t get a ton of chances, but he&#8217;s usually pretty nifty and tonight they were going in.”</p>
<p>Aaron Ekblad, Jonathan Huberdeau and Frank Vatrano each had a goal and an assist as the Panthers improved to 8-1-1 on the road this season. Keith Yandle had two assists. Sergei Bobrovsky made 28 saves.</p>
<p>Eeli Tolvanen and Viktor Arvidsson scored for Nashville, which lost its third straight and dropped to 1-9 combined against the Central Division&#8217;s top three teams. Filip Forsberg had two assists, including the 200th of his career.</p>
<p>Nashville captain Roman Josi was so frustrated he nearly cursed talking to media after the game. He said the Predators have an identity for parts of games but not the full 60 minutes.</p>
<p>“We need to find a way to get out of this together,” Josi said. “It’s obviously not the way we want to play right now.”</p>
<p>The Predators took the first 10 shots and didn&#8217;t allow a Florida shot until midway through the first period. When Grigori Denisenko tripped Forsberg, the Predators scored 7 seconds into the man advantage with <a href="https://twitter.com/PredsNHL/status/1368281375040823299">Tolvanen easily beating Bobrovsky</a> with a slap shot to the far side of the net.</p>
<p>They appeared poised to take just their fourth lead after the first period this season until the final seconds. That&#8217;s when Ekblad, coming off a four-point game, tied it with 12.6 seconds left in the first with a snap shot from the high slot at the right circle. It was all Panthers from there.</p>
<p>Huberdeau put the Panthers up 2-1 just 1:15 into the second with Patric Horqnvist getting his 500th career NHL point on the assist. Hornqvist got the puck in the Nashville offensive zone and passed to Huberdeau, who had <a href="https://twitter.com/NHL/status/1368295895608008707">enough time to deke out Rinne</a> before flipping the puck over the goalie&#8217;s right pad.</p>
<p>Acciari padded the lead at 11:17 of the second, finishing off a 2-on-1 with a wrist shot from the right circle. He got his second with 1:14 left in the period with a backhand past Rinne for a power-play goal.</p>
<p>TOO LITTLE TOO LATE</p>
<p>Nashville came in tied for the NHL lead with 30 goals in the third period this season. Arvidsson made it 31 with a wrist shot in front 19 seconds into the third.</p>
<p>But the Predators couldn&#8217;t put one past Bobrovsky the rest of the period. Vatrano got his eighth of the season before Acciari capped the scoring.</p>
<p>ROAD WARRIORS</p>
<p>The Panthers already had the best road record through the first nine games in franchise history, and they won their fourth straight in Nashville. Florida also is 5-1-0 over the last six road games. Montreal is the only other NHL team with only one regulation road loss this season.</p>
<p>DUCHENE OUT</p>
<p>Nashville center Matt Duchene was placed on injured reserve. He is expected to be sidelined for three to five weeks with a lower-body injury. The veteran has eight points in 23 games this season with a minus-11 rating.</p>
<p>WHAT&#8217;S NEXT</p>
<p>After dropping two to the Hurricanes in Florida, the Panthers continue their road trip Sunday in Carolina.</p>
<p>The Predators start an eight-game road swing Sunday night in Dallas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877581</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Ekblad&#8217;s four points leads Panthers over Predators 5-4</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ekblads-four-points-leads-panthers-over-predators-5-4/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876377</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad had two goals and two assists to lead the Florida Panthers to a 5-4 victory over the Nashville Predators...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad had two goals and two assists to lead the Florida Panthers to a 5-4 victory over the Nashville Predators on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Carter Verhaeghe, Mason Marchment and Jonathan Huberdeau also scored for Florida, which snapped a two-game losing streak. Aleksander Barkov had three assists and Sergei Bobrovsky made 31 saves for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Mattias Ekholm, Filip Forsberg, Colton Sissons and Ryan Johansen scored for Nashville, which has lost two straight. Viktor Arvidsson had three assists and Pekka Rinne made 33 saves.</p>
<p>The teams finish their two-game series Saturday at Bridgestone Arena.</p>
<p>Both of Ekblad’s goals came via the power play. It was his first career four-point game.</p>
<p>Ekblad pushed Florida’s lead to 4-1 with 1:16 left in the second period with a power-play goal, but Forsberg answered 50 seconds later to pull Nashville back within two.</p>
<p>Nashville appeared to draw within one, two minutes into the third on a goal by Rocco Grimaldi, but Florida challenged the play for offside and a video review erased the goal.</p>
<p>Ekblad’s second of the game and eight of the season came at 9:07 of the third to make it 5-2.</p>
<p>Sissons again brought Nashville within two with at 12:40 and Johansen made it 5-4 with 1:13 remaining in the third with Rinne pulled for an extra attacker.</p>
<p>Verhaeghe scored the game’s first goal at 6:29 of the opening period. It was his eighth.</p>
<p>Marchment made it 2-0 at 9:01 with his first NHL goal. Coming off of the right half wall, Marchment cut into the faceoff circle and snapped a wrist shot between Rinne’s pads.</p>
<p>Huberdeau’s goal 59 seconds into the second gave Florida a 3-0 advantage. Former Predator Patric Hornqvist skated behind the Nashville net and found an unchecked Huberdeau in front where his wrist shot deflected off of Rinne’s chest and into the net on the glove side for his ninth.</p>
<p>Ekholm got Nashville on the board at 12:23 of the second on a one-timer from the right point off of a pass from Arvidsson. Ekholm has four goals in the four games he has played since missing six games with a lower-body injury.</p>
<p>FEELS LIKE THE FIRST TIME</p>
<p>Marchment’s first period goal was the second time in two games that Rinne allowed an opponent’s first career goal. In Tuesday’s game against the Carolina Hurricanes, it was Steven Lorentz.</p>
<p>MILESTONE</p>
<p>Florida defenseman Radko Gudas played his 500th career NHL game.</p>
<p>SAROS TO IR</p>
<p>Predators goaltender Juuse Saros was placed on injured reserve Thursday, two days after leaving Tuesday night’s game against the Carolina Hurricanes. Early in the first period Tuesday, Carolina’s Nino Niederreiter collided head-to-head with Saros behind the Nashville net as Saros was playing a puck. Saros finished the first period but was replaced by Rinne to start the second.</p>
<p>Kasimir Kaskisuo was elevated from the team’s taxi squad Thursday and served as Rinne’s backup.</p>
<p>JOHANSEN RETURNS</p>
<p>Johansen returned to the Nashville lineup Thursday. He missed Tuesday’s game after being placed on the NHL’s COVID-19 protocol list. Prior to missing the one game on the COVID-19 list, Johansen had played four games since missing the previous seven with an upper-body injury.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876377</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Necas&#8217; shootout goal lifts Hurricanes past Panthers 4-3</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/necas-shootout-goal-lifts-hurricanes-past-panthers-4-3/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 05:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872681</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Martin Necas scored the winning goal in a shootout, and the Carolina Hurricanes beat the Florida Panthers 4-3 on Saturday night....]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Martin Necas scored the winning goal in a shootout, and the Carolina Hurricanes beat the Florida Panthers 4-3 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Vincent Trocheck, Jake Bean and Warren Foegele scored in regulation for Carolina, which snapped a three-game skid.</p>
<p>Jonathan Huberdeau, Frank Vatrano, and Patric Hornqvist scored for Florida.</p>
<p>Hornqvist scored his ninth goal of the season with 1:54 remaining in the third period as Florida rallied for the second time in the contest and forced the OT.</p>
<p>Foegele had given Carolina a 3-2 lead with just under six minutes remaining.</p>
<p>“I like how we bounced back from the negative kind of things that (happen) in a game,” Carolina coach Rod Brind’Amour said. “We have a lot of good options on the shootout. So that’s very, very positive. It’s coming through this year obviously.”</p>
<p>James Reimer had 28 saves for the Hurricanes. Sergei Bobrovsky turned back 30 of 33 shots for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Florida also surged back from a 2-0 deficit within a two-minute span of the third before Foegele’s goal.</p>
<p>Carolina capitalized on its first of many power-play chances when Trocheck beat Bobrovsky with 2:21 left in the first period. It was Trocheck’s 10th goal.</p>
<p>Minutes earlier, Trocheck was honored with a tribute on the video scoreboard during a timeout.</p>
<p>“It was awesome to see the tribute they gave me,” said Trocheck, who spent seven seasons with the Panthers. “It was very classy of them. Obviously a little emotional &#8230; I played here for a long time and a lot of good memories here.”</p>
<p>The Hurricanes extended their lead to 2-0, again on the man advantage when Bean scored his first goal just 1:30 into the third period. Brett Pesce and Necas assisted on the goal.</p>
<p>Florida had cut the deficit with 11:47 remaining as Hornqvist stuffed one past Reimer on the power play for his ninth goal. The Panthers then tied the game when Vatrano converted a perfect feed from Mason Marchment for his sixth goal.</p>
<p>Carolina’s Brock McGinn and Necas had consecutive breakaways on Panthers giveaways in the neutral zone. Bobrovsky made a sprawling save on McGinn, and Alex Wennberg surged in from behind and poke-checked the puck away from Necas.</p>
<p>Florida outshot the Hurricanes, 10-2, early on before Carolina’s late flurry, including Trocheck’s goal with Kevin Connauton in the box for tripping.</p>
<p>Florida coach Joel Quenneville liked the way his team battled from behind with another third-period comeback.</p>
<p>“We chipped away and all of a sudden we get a lot of momentum back,” Quenneville said. “The nice thing that’s positive about coming back is that we’re scoring some hard goals and that’s where the rewards are.”</p>
<p>DIFFERENT OUTCOME</p>
<p>The 4-3 result was the second in as many games between the two Central Division rivals. Florida edged the Hurricanes, 4-3, in overtime at the PNC Center earlier this season.</p>
<p>A MUCH-NEEDED ’W”</p>
<p>Trocheck and his teammates were relieved that the Hurricanes were able to end their losing streak.</p>
<p>“We needed to get the win here. Obviously good teams don’t lose back-to-backs and we lost three in a row, so coming in tonight against a good team we needed to get that win.”</p>
<p>Carolina did not record its first shot until just past the midway point of that period. Florida had the game’s first five shots.</p>
<p>REUNION TIME</p>
<p>Along with Trocheck, James Reimer was back in Sunrise as a former Panther. It was Reimer’s second visit, with the last coming on Oct. 8, 2019.</p>
<p>Trocheck, who skated in 420 games for the Panthers and registered 282 points between 2014-20, also scored against his former teammates in Carolina’s overtime loss to Florida.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>The contest was witnessed by 4,281 fans at the BB&amp;T Center.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts Carolina on Monday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872681</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Panthers stun Stars 3-2 with late rally</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-stun-stars-3-2-with-late-rally/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 03:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871497</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Frank Vatrano scored the go-ahead goal with 3:10 remaining and the Florida Panthers stunned the Dallas Stars 3-2 with a late...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Frank Vatrano scored the go-ahead goal with 3:10 remaining and the Florida Panthers stunned the Dallas Stars 3-2 with a late comeback Thursday night.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov and Anton Stralman also scored in the final 6 1/2 minutes as the Panthers overcame a 2-0 deficit. Sergei Bobrovsky made 37 saves.</p>
<p>Joe Pavelski and Jamie Benn had the goals for Dallas. Rookie netminder Jake Oettinger stopped 32 shots.</p>
<p>Florida scored three times in 3:11 after a nine-minute delay to repair a section of the boards.</p>
<p>Barkov poked in a loose puck that bounced behind Oettinger and sat in the paint near the goal line with 6:21 left. Stralman tied the score on a drive from the right circle. Vatrano put the Panthers ahead with a shot from the slot.</p>
<p>Pavelski scored the game’s first goal 2:10 into the second period on the power play when he swept in the puck from the left side of the crease. Pavelski leads the Stars with 10 goals in 15 games.</p>
<p>John Klingberg’s shot from the high slot was redirected by Benn into the net to make it 2-0 with 2:11 left in the second.</p>
<p>The Panthers, who lost 3-0 to Dallas on Wednesday, are 6-0-0 following a loss.</p>
<p>IRONMAN STREAK</p>
<p>Florida defenseman Keith Yandle played in his 885th consecutive regular-season game dating to March 26, 2009, passing Steve Larmer (1982–93) for sole possession of the third-longest streak in NHL history.</p>
<p>ROSTER MOVES</p>
<p>Panthers D Radko Gudas was scratched with an upper-body injury. &#8230; Florida recalled forward Mason Marchment and defenseman Kevin Connauton from the taxi squad. D Markus Nutivaara has been placed on injured reserve.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>A crowd of 3,844 was on hand. The Panthers cap attendance at 5,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871497</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Waiting game for Marlins as heralded young hitters struggle</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/waiting-game-for-marlins-as-heralded-young-hitters-struggle/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875581</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Marlins outfield prospect Monte Harrison says he surprised himself when he made his major league debut last year. It wasn&#8217;t just...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Marlins outfield prospect Monte Harrison says he surprised himself when he made his major league debut last year.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t just that he didn&#8217;t hit; it was how he reacted when he didn&#8217;t hit.</p>
<p>“I said I was not going to be that guy who gets called up to the big leagues and struggles mentally,” Harrison said. “And then when I got to the big leagues, I struggled mentally. That’s very humbling.”</p>
<p>Harrison&#8217;s experience wasn&#8217;t isolated in Miami last season; several other Marlins prospects also scuffled in their first crack at the majors. In fact, while the farm system rebuilt under CEO Derek Jeter brims with young talent, it has yet to produce a hitter who busts out in the majors.</p>
<p>With pitching it&#8217;s different. The Marlins have stockpiled young arms so successfully their rotation is expected to be the strength of this year&#8217;s team, with no starter older than 26.</p>
<p>Development of hitters lags. That&#8217;s baseball.</p>
<p>“There are a few young guys who don’t struggle; the majority do,” Marlins manager Don Mattingly said Wednesday. “There are very few Sotos, Griffey Jrs. and Acunas of the world who are instantly stars. It doesn’t happen that often.”</p>
<p>For the Jeter regime, instant success hasn&#8217;t happened at all. Four of the Marlins&#8217; top 12 prospects made their MLB debuts last year, and none batted above .170.</p>
<p>Harrison went 8 for 47 with 26 strikeouts. Outfielder Jesús Sánchez went 1 for 25 with 11 strikeouts. First baseman Lewin Díaz went 6 for 39 with 12 strikeouts. Infielder Jazz Chisholm went 9 for 56 with 19 strikeouts.</p>
<p>Other heralded youngsters, including second baseman Isan Díaz and outfielder Magneuris Sierra, also have been unable to win a starting job.</p>
<p>Outfielder Lewis Brinson feels their pain. A prospect acquired in the Christian Yelich trade with Milwaukee, Brinson has a .189 career average in 761 at-bats, although he did show progress in 2020 and might have a role on this year&#8217;s team.</p>
<p>His advice for scuffling young hitters?</p>
<p>“Embrace that struggle,” Brinson said. &#8220;Embrace getting slapped, getting humbled a little bit.</p>
<p>“We’ve killed it in the minors; when you get to the big leagues it’s a different ballgame. You can&#8217;t succeed without failing sometimes. You’ve got to take your lumps.”</p>
<p>Mattingly said he doesn&#8217;t believed the Marlins have been calling up youngsters too soon. Instead, he thinks the game has changed since 1984, when he won the American League batting title at age 23 by hitting .343.</p>
<p>“There is a bigger separation now between Triple-A and the big leagues,” Mattingly said. &#8220;It almost always takes that getting slapped, as Lew would say, and then going back and working on your game, and the next time it’s usually a little better.</p>
<p>“We’re seeing it with Lew. He&#8217;s making strides, and it has taken a little bit. Hopefully it’s not going to take two or three years with guys, but sometimes that’s what it takes.”</p>
<p>Or, as Mattingly noted, success may never come. But that&#8217;s where the Marlins&#8217; depth of young talent helps their chances of building on last year&#8217;s surprising run to their first playoff berth since 2003.</p>
<p>The Marlins remain high on their 2020 rookie class, and even if the entire group flops, there are more young prospects on the way. That includes outfielders JJ Bleday, Kameron Misner, Peyton Burdick and Connor Scott, and shortstop Jose Devers.</p>
<p>The improved depth of the farm system has been evident during the first week of spring training games, Mattingly said.</p>
<p>“You see it clear as day,” he said. “There is just no doubt our quality has been up, and you see that depth coming.”</p>
<p>In the meantime, last year&#8217;s rookies battle to win roster spots.</p>
<p>Harrison, for one, embraces getting slapped last year. A dynamic player and personality, he failed to make the roster out of camp last summer, and saw only spot duty after later joining the Marlins.</p>
<p>“I think the best thing that ever happened to me was in that time period where I got sent down and called back up and I had to sit on the bench,” Harrison said. &#8220;The best of Monte will come out. I can&#8217;t wait for the fans of Miami to see that, and the world.”</p>
<p>The Marlins remain confident, too, that they won&#8217;t continue to strike out with their young hitters.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875581</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Marlins logo on flag</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Lefty Gio González agrees to minor league deal with Marlins</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/lefty-gio-gonzalez-agrees-to-minor-league-deal-with-marlins/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 04:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875580</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Veteran left-hander Gio González has agreed to terms on a minor league contract with the Miami Marlins and will take part in...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Veteran left-hander Gio González has agreed to terms on a minor league contract with the Miami Marlins and will take part in their major league camp.</p>
<p>González, a South Florida native, pitched in 12 games last year for Chicago White Sox with four starts and had an ERA of 4.83. He has a career record of 131-101 with a 3.70 ERA in 13 seasons for four teams.</p>
<p>At 35, González provides experienced depth for the Marlins&#8217; talented young rotation. He is a two-time All-Star, with Oakland in 2011 and Washington in 2012.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875580</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Alcantara leads young staff that should be Marlins&#8217; strength</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/alcantara-leads-young-staff-that-should-be-marlins-strength/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874784</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — At 25, Sandy Alcantara says he&#8217;s old enough to be the Miami Marlins&#8217; ace. The Marlins agree. Alcantara has pitched less than...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — At 25, Sandy Alcantara says he&#8217;s old enough to be the Miami Marlins&#8217; ace.</p>
<p>The Marlins agree.</p>
<p>Alcantara has pitched less than 300 innings and has a career record of 11-19, but Miami is counting on him to lead a parade of talented young starting pitchers who are considered the team&#8217;s strength.</p>
<p>“That’s what the Marlins are looking for from me, and that&#8217;s what I want,” said the Dominican right-hander, who pitched two scoreless innings against the Mets in his first spring training start Monday. “There are a lot of young guys behind me. I have to show them they can be like me.</p>
<p>“It doesn’t matter how young I am. I have experience. I&#8217;ve been in the big leagues for four years now.”</p>
<p>On Miami&#8217;s staff, that&#8217;s a lot. The other right-handers expected to help make up the rotation include Pablo López, Elieser Hernández and Sixto Sánchez. Four pitchers are contending for the last spot — left-hander Trevor Rogers and Daniel Castano, and right-handers Nick Neidert and Braxton Garrett.</p>
<p>Among the eight pitchers, Castano is the oldest at 26, and their combined career record is 36-54.</p>
<p>Even so, the Marlins believe starting pitching can lead them back to the playoffs after they made a surprising run last year to their first postseason berth since 2003.</p>
<p>“We hang our hat on pitching,” manager Don Mattingly said. “We feel like that is going to be our thing. Every time we put a starter out there, you feel like you’ve got a guy who can keep you in the game.”</p>
<p>Relying on young pitching is nothing new for the Marlins, due to their perennially small payrolls. But the depth of 25-and-under talent might be the franchise&#8217;s best since 2002, when the rotation included Josh Beckett, Brad Penny, A.J. Burnett and Ryan Dempster.</p>
<p>A year later, the Marlins won the World Series.</p>
<p>“We have arms that are able to shut any lineup down,” López said. “Electric arms. It’s a very exciting rotation.”</p>
<p>The Marlins have stockpiled the young pitchers as a foundation for CEO Derek Jeter&#8217;s rebuilding project, now entering Season 4. One of Jeter&#8217;s first moves was to acquire Alcantara in the 2017 trade that sent outfielder Marcell Ozuna to the Cardinals.</p>
<p>The 6-foot-5 Alcantara made his first major league start the following year. In 2019 he became an All-Star and pitched two shutouts, most in the majors.</p>
<p>Alcantara was sidelined early last season by the Marlins&#8217; COVID-19 outbreak, but returned and finish with a 3.00 ERA in seven starts, and then beat the Cubs in his playoff debut.</p>
<p>“You see the wannabe, which is huge,” Mattingly said. “His stuff can be as good as anybody&#8217;s, and he wants to be great.”</p>
<p>Even so, the starter who created the most buzz last year was Sánchez, acquired in the trade two years ago that sent catcher J.T. Realmuto to the Philadelphia Phillies. The highly touted 22-year-old performed so well he was able to trade in uniform number 73 for 45, the number worn by his hero and fellow Dominican, Pedro Martínez.</p>
<p>“It means a lot,” Sánchez said in Spanish. “I used to watch Pedro pitch. I want to accomplish many things he did.”</p>
<p>He&#8217;s off to a good start. Called up in August, Sánchez went 3-2 with a 3.46 ERA in seven starts, and he pitched five shutout innings against the Cubs in the playoffs.</p>
<p>“Sixto came as advertised,” Mattingly said. “There really wasn’t anything not to like.”</p>
<p>Perhaps Miami&#8217;s most promising pitching prospect is another 22-year-old, right-hander Edward Cabrera. He was expected to contend for a rotation spot but is sidelined indefinitely with an inflamed nerve in his right biceps.</p>
<p>That still leaves plenty of pitching depth in camp.</p>
<p>&#8220;We have a lot of young guys,” Alcantara said. “And when they get opportunity, they’re going to be good.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874784</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-488-Sandy-Alcantara-1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-488-Sandy-Alcantara-1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-488-Sandy-Alcantara-1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210218 Pitchers &#38; Catchers 488 - Sandy Alcantara 1</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Marlins unveil COVID-19 protocols for fans wanting to attend games</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-unveil-covid-19-protocols-for-fans-wanting-to-attend-games/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870734</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins have revealed their COVID-19 protocols that will be enforced for fans who attend home games at Marlins Park during the 2021 MLB...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins have revealed their COVID-19 protocols that will be enforced for fans who attend home games at Marlins Park during the 2021 MLB season.</p>
<p>In a release sent out on Wednesday, the Marlins announced face coverings will be mandatory for all guests above 2 years old. However, they may be temporarily removed to consume a beverage or eat a meal.</p>
<p>Also, Marlins officials said tickets will be digital for 2021, and guests can access them through the MLB Ballpark App. Ticketed fans will receive a time and gate location to enter the ballpark on their ticket, and officials encourage them to adhere to the staggered entry.</p>
<p>Miami plans to have around <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-will-allow-fans-with-capacity-at-about-25-percent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">25% capacity</a> at the ballpark to begin the season and may increase capacity as the season progresses.</p>
<p>The team became the second MLB team to <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-enroll-in-covid-19-safety-rating-plan-to-have-fans-for-opening-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enroll in the WELL Health-Safety Rating</a> prior to the season. The rating was created in response to the coronavirus pandemic, and it incorporates guidance from the World Health Organization, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and other health agencies.</p>
<p>They also partnered with RB, the makers of Lysol, to have ample disinfecting products around the ballpark. According to the Marlins, they will have frequently touched surfaces and objects regularly disinfected, and they will have hand sanitizing stations throughout the stadium.</p>
<p>Officials encourage all fans to pay for items using a credit or debit card at all concession and retail spots.</p>
<p>Bags will not be allowed inside of Marlins Park unless it is for medical or infant purposes, Marlins officials said.</p>
<p>Miami will play the Tampa Bay Rays on Opening Day at Marlins Park on April 1 to begin their 2021 season.</p>
<p>For a full list of changes to attend a game in the 2021 season, click <a href="https://www.mlb.com/marlins/ballpark/health-and-safety" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870734</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021821-marlins-park-interior.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021821-marlins-park-interior.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021821-marlins-park-interior.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021821 marlins park interior</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Marlins killer Adam Duvall is now on their side and in RF</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-killer-adam-duvall-is-now-on-their-side-and-in-rf/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870732</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Adam Duvall gave the Miami Marlins fits last year, and they solved the problem by bringing him over to their side. Duvall...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Adam Duvall gave the Miami Marlins fits last year, and they solved the problem by bringing him over to their side.</p>
<p>Duvall hit five homers for Atlanta in nine games against Miami and had an OPS of 1.201. The Marlins were especially mindful of his three-homer, nine-RBI game in the midst of the playoff race when they signed him to a $5 million, one-year deal two weeks ago.</p>
<p>“They talked about how I had had some success against them,” Duvall said with a laugh Wednesday.</p>
<p>His signing changes the Marlins&#8217; outlook as full-squad spring training workouts begin in Jupiter, Florida. They&#8217;re planning to plug him into right field and the middle of lineup, where he provides a significant power upgrade for an offense that ranked fifth-worst in MLB in homers in 2020.</p>
<p>Duvall hit 16 for the Braves, five more than Marlins leader Brian Anderson.</p>
<p>“Adam has solidified right field for us,” manager Don Mattingly said. “He&#8217;s a guy who is big and strong and capable of hitting the ball out of the ballpark, and it doesn’t really matter what ballpark. He&#8217;s one of those true power guys, and you do want danger in there.”</p>
<p>Duvall, 32, has been much more dangerous since the Braves demoted him to Triple-A for much of the 2019 season. He returned to post a career-high .882 OPS with 10 homers for Atlanta in 41 games that year.</p>
<p>Last season, only two National League players hit more homers.</p>
<p>“He definitely has closed some holes up,” Mattingly said.</p>
<p>Duvall said he bonded in the minors with batting coach Bobby Magallanes, who became a mentor.</p>
<p>“It was a blessing in disguise,” Duvall said. “I like the growth I&#8217;ve had in the past two years.</p>
<p>“I really enjoy learning the game. I enjoy trying to get every edge I can, and that’s one thing that has helped me progress as I get older. Every little piece of the game, I enjoy learning about and talking about.”</p>
<p>Duvall believes that makes him a good fit with the Marlins, who made the playoffs last year for the first time since 2003 with a young team that appears to be trending upward.</p>
<p>“We have a group of guys that are hungry and want to learn,” Duvall said. “That’s going to be fun.”</p>
<p>Duvall said he&#8217;s still learning, too. He&#8217;s solid defensively and was an offensive force last year, but he batted only .237 with an on-base percentage of .301. His career batting average is .233, with a strikeout rate of one per game.</p>
<p>“I want to be the best hitter I can be,&#8221; he said. &#8220;That’s going to be driving the ball, but I want to be better in other aspects as far as walking and just getting base hits when they&#8217;re needed.”</p>
<p>Duvall&#8217;s deal includes a $2 million salary this year and a $7 million mutual option for 2022 with a $3 million buyout.</p>
<p>Mattingly said Duvall has looked good in the cage in camp. But the manager said he doesn&#8217;t need any convincing that Duvall can hit.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;ve seen enough of him the last couple of years,” Mattingly said with a smile.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870732</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Marlins logo on flag</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Butler takes over, Heat top Pelicans 103-93</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/butler-takes-over-heat-top-pelicans-103-93/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 04:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876379</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#8217;s absence to beat the...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>NEW ORLEANS (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Jimmy Butler had 29 points and nine assists, and the Miami Heat took advantage of Zion Williamson&#x2019;s absence to beat the New Orleans Pelicans 103-93 on Thursday night.<p>With a repertoire of strong inside moves and accurate mid-range shooting, Butler made 10 of 14 shots and eight of nine free throws to help the Heat keep the Pelicans at bay. Butler added a late step-back 3 to give him 10 points during an 11-2 run that put Miami up 98-87 with 2:50 to go.</p><p>Kelly Olynyk hit his first four 3-point shots and finished with 18 points and 10 rebounds, and Goran Dragic scored nine of his 13 points in the second half for Miami.</p><p>Brandon Ingram scored 17 points and Steven Adams scored 15 for New Orleans. Nickeil Alexander-Walker scored 13 and Josh Hart 12 for the Pelicans.</p><p>Hart, normally a reserve, was inserted in the starting lineup after Williamson was scratched because of a toe injury.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/TheMozKnowz/status/1367691307582423041?s=20</embed></div><p>While the Pelicans struggled mightily to make shots during the first three quarters, Miami was unable to put New Orleans away early.</p><p>When Hart made a half-court shot as the horn sounded to signal the end of the third period, the Heat&#x2019;s lead was just 77-70.</p><p>Alexander-Walker then pulled the Pelicans to 77-73 with a 3 to open the fourth quarter, which was largely competitive until Butler began asserting himself more in the final five minutes.</p><p>TIP-INS</p><p>Heat: Andre Iguodala scored 10 points, highlighted by a late driving dunk that virtually sealed the victory. &#x2026; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra is now 16-17 against Pelicans coach Stan Van Gundy, his longtime friend and mentor. &#x2026; This is the fourth time in the last seven seasons that the Heat haven&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t been better than .500 at the All-Star break. But during Spoelstra&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s 12-year tenure, Miami has won 62% of its games after the break. Only San Antonio and Houston have better post-break records in the Spoelstra era. &#x2026; Miami shot 49.3% (36 of 73) but missed 20 of 30 3-point shots.</p><p>Pelicans: In addition to being without Williamson, New Orleans also played without JJ Redick, who was bothered by a sore right heel. &#x2026; The Pelicans shot just 39.8% (33 of 83) and missed 33 of 43 3-point shots. &#x2026; Rookie Kira Lewis Jr. scored 11 points in 17 minutes off the bench. &#x2026; Lonzo Ball scored 10 but missed nine of 11 shots from deep.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Heat: Hosts Orlando on March 11.</p><p>Pelicans: Host Minnesota on March 11.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876379</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>AP source: NBA set to remove restriction on 2-way deals</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ap-source-nba-set-to-remove-restriction-on-2-way-deals/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874783</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The NBA has moved closer to a deal where players on two-way contracts would be eligible to appear on the active roster...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The NBA has moved closer to a deal where players on two-way contracts would be eligible to appear on the active roster for as many games as their teams would like this season, a person with knowledge of the situation said Tuesday.</p>
<p>The proposal to lift what was a 50-game limit on the active roster for two-way players got overwhelming support Tuesday and is likely to be passed by the NBA’s board of governors, said the person who spoke to The Associated Press on condition of anonymity because that final approval is pending. The approval is expected later this month.</p>
<p>No team has used two-ways more this season than Miami, with Gabe Vincent and Max Strus having a combined 42 appearances this season entering Tuesday’s game against Atlanta. Vincent has also been a part-time starter for the Heat, and Miami was one of the teams concerned that those 50-game appearance limits on the active roster was fast approaching.</p>
<p>“We all appreciate that they see that each team is in a different place,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “We felt that we’ve competed in this season with great honor and respect to the league. &#8230; Our two-ways are playing for us. There are a few other teams that are in that circumstance. It’s just an uneven and unpredictable year for so many teams. Not even all the teams are in the same range of amount of games played up to this point, with all the postponements.”</p>
<p>The NBA relaxed the rule on two-way players for this season in anticipation of postponements and rosters being taxed by virus-related issues. The rule in past years has been that two-way players could spend 45 days with the NBA club and the rest of the time with a franchise’s G League team. But with a shortened G League season this year, and not all teams having clubs in that league this season, there were obvious reasons to change things.</p>
<p>Players on two-way deals are earning $449,155 this season.</p>
<p>“It just makes all the sense in the world to not have to even think about that or concern yourself with days, particularly when we are playing them,” Spoelstra said of the looming change. “It’s what’s fair to the teams. It’s what makes the most sense and is fair to the players. We are just glad that it was seen that way, objectively, because not everybody is in the same circumstance.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874783</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/180621_nba_logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180621_NBA_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Heat top Hawks for 6th straight win, get back to .500</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-top-hawks-for-6th-straight-win-get-back-to-500/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 05:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873224</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat are back at .500, not even a couple weeks removed from being near the very bottom of the Eastern...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Heat are back at .500, not even a couple weeks removed from being near the very bottom of the Eastern Conference.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn scored 24 points, Bam Adebayo had 16 points and 13 rebounds, and the Heat extended the NBA’s longest current winning streak to six games by beating the Atlanta Hawks 109-99 on Sunday night.</p>
<p>“That was a big-time game for us,” Nunn said. “Took a step in the right direction.”</p>
<p>Previous Achiuwa had 14 points in 12 minutes for Miami, which used a 10-0 run late in the fourth quarter to pull away from a game that was tied at 95 with 3:00 left. Tyler Herro had 12 of his 14 points for Miami in the fourth and Goran Dragic scored 13 for the Heat (17-17).</p>
<p>John Collins led all scorers with 34 points for Atlanta, plus grabbed 10 rebounds. Clint Capela finished with 20 points and 14 rebounds for the Hawks, while Trae Young added 15 points, nine assists and eight rebounds.</p>
<p>But Young shot just 3 for 14.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s seen the pressure,&#8221; Hawks coach Lloyd Pierce said. “He knows teams are going to throw different defenses at us. A lot of it&#8217;s focused on taking the ball out of his hands. And we have ways to punish, but again, if you don&#8217;t make shots there&#8217;s nothing really we can do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Huerter scored 13 for the Hawks, who were just 8 for 35 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>The teams play again Tuesday in Miami when the Heat — who have won 10 of their last 13 — will try to get over .500 for the first time all season. Miami played Sunday without Jimmy Butler, sidelined by right knee inflammation.</p>
<p>“With Jimmy out, I thought guys really stepped up and filled in in a lot of different places,&#8221; Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>Miami led 54-44 at the half, a big part of that because of their defense on Young. He was scoreless until 2:53 remained in the half, the deepest he’s gone into a game this season without a point.</p>
<p>Collins was 4 for 4 in the second quarter, helping keep the Hawks within striking distance.</p>
<p>He stayed dominant in the third. Collins had 19 in that quarter alone — the second-most any player has had in a quarter against Miami this season, one shy of the 20 that Philadelphia’s Joel Embiid had in the third quarter of the 76ers’ win over the Heat on Jan. 12.</p>
<p>Capela added 10 in the third quarter and the Hawks briefly recaptured the lead before going into the fourth down just 78-77. Collins and Capela were 13 for 18 in the third; the rest of the Hawks were 1 for 8 and Young — just as he was in the first quarter — was scoreless.</p>
<p>“JC was really setting the tone by being aggressive,&#8221; Capela said.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Hawks: Young’s scoreless first quarter was his fifth of the season. The Hawks are 0-5 in those games this season and 0-13 in those games since the finale of his rookie year. &#8230; Rajon Rondo’s last seven games in Miami have come with him playing for seven different teams: Boston, Dallas, Sacramento, Chicago, New Orleans, the Lakers and now Atlanta.</p>
<p>Heat: The six straight wins is Miami&#8217;s longest such regular-season streak since a seven-game run midway through the 2017-18 season. The Heat had a seven-game win streak in last season&#8217;s playoffs as well. &#8230; Among those in the crowd of about 3,000 was celebrity chef Guy Fieri. &#8230; Adebayo now has six consecutive double-doubles, tying a career-best.</p>
<p>BUTLER’S KNEE</p>
<p>The Heat are listing Butler as day-to-day. Spoelstra said Butler was with the team for shootaround Sunday morning and the knee “didn’t loosen up the way he wanted it to.” Spoelstra added that he believes the issue is minor.</p>
<p>FLORIDA MEN</p>
<p>This game was the first of four consecutive the Hawks will play in Florida — they’re at Miami again Tuesday, at Orlando on Wednesday and vs. Toronto in Tampa to start the second half on March 11. They are scheduled to play four straight in California from March 20-26, and have had only one four-game stretch in Georgia so far this season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873224</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Heat pull away to beat Thunder 108-94 in finale of road trip</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-pull-away-to-beat-thunder-108-94-in-finale-of-road-trip/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 05:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869572</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Duncan Robinson scored 22 points and made six 3-pointers, leading the Miami Heat to a 108-94 victory over the Oklahoma City...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Duncan Robinson scored 22 points and made six 3-pointers, leading the Miami Heat to a 108-94 victory over the Oklahoma City Thunder on Monday night in the finale of their seven-game road trip.</p>
<p>Kendrick Nunn added 20 points and nine assists, Bam Adebayo had 19 points and 13 rebounds, and they hooked up on an alley-oop dunk during Miami’s 15-0 run to start the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Robinson ended it with a 3-pointer that gave the Heat a 94-77 lead midway through the final period. The Heat did it all with five-time NBA All-Star Jimmy Butler on the sideline for the last 12 minutes.</p>
<p>“It was great, just the enthusiasm,” Heat coach Erik Spoelstra said. “I think those guys wanted to play well while he was on the bench and see if we could push the lead.</p>
<p>“Then, when we took that first timeout, I looked at Jimmy, and Jimmy was in the huddle and he said, ’Hey guys, keep going. Let’s give it another two or three minutes and see how it goes.&#8217;”</p>
<p>Spoelstra said Butler’s comments energized the group, which kept its double-digit margin and won the final three games of its trip to finish 4-3.</p>
<p>Shai Gilgeous-Alexander scored 27 points for the Thunder, who were outscored 63-40 after halftime.</p>
<p>“I give them a lot of credit. They came out of halftime really focused and we had to earn everything on both ends of the floor in the second half,” Thunder coach Mark Daigneault said. “They just outplayed us. … We definitely enjoy competing against a team like them, because we learn a lot about ourselves. They just outlasted us tonight.”</p>
<p>The Heat made five of their first eight 3-point attempts. Max Strus capped the hot start with one with 4:19 remaining in the first quarter.</p>
<p>Miami missed its next 12 3-point shots. Robinson finally ended the drought with a 31-foot jumper with 43 seconds left until the break.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Thunder shot 54% from the floor through the first 24 minutes. Gilgeous-Alexander fueled Oklahoma City’s 54-45 halftime advantage, scoring 18 points on 6-of-7 shooting. His only miss of the half came via a 27-foot stepback as time expired in the first period.</p>
<p>Miami responded with 34 points in the third quarter to take a 79-72 lead with under a minute left. Gilgeous-Alexander rattled off five points in the final 31.6 seconds to bring the Thunder within two entering the final period before Miami promptly blew it open.</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Tyler Herro (right hip contusion) was ruled out ahead of Monday’s game. He is day to day, according to Spoelstra. … The Heat haven’t played at home since a Feb. 9 win over the New York Knicks. … Jimmy Butler played in his 600th career game.</p>
<p>Thunder: Al Horford (rest) was not available for Oklahoma City’s second game in as many nights. Isaiah Roby started in Horford’s place. … The Thunder fell to 2-4 when playing the second game of a back-to-back. … Darius Bazley finished with 13 points on 5-of-9 shooting and five rebounds.</p>
<p>END OF THE ROAD</p>
<p>The Heat lost three consecutive games before beating the Sacramento Kings on Feb. 18, the Los Angeles Lakers on Saturday and the Thunder on Monday. Adebayo attributes the team’s time on the road to the group’s strong finish and strengthened bond within the locker room.</p>
<p>“We got better,” Adebayo said. “I feel like it was one of those situations, it felt like the bubble again where we got a chance to be cohesive and feel like brothers again. … When we’re at home, we can’t really hang out with each other. So, being able to be in the hotel and be safe, it feels like the bubble.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Thunder: Host the San Antonio Spurs on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Heat: Host the Toronto Raptors on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869572</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Heat hold off depleted Lakers 96-94 in NBA Finals rematch</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/heat-hold-off-depleted-lakers-96-94-in-nba-finals-rematch/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 05:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868596</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES (AP) — Although the Miami Heat&#8217;s road trip started slowly, Kendrick Nunn thinks they are picking up steam because of a team chemistry...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Although the Miami Heat&#8217;s road trip started slowly, Kendrick Nunn thinks they are picking up steam because of a team chemistry that is growing at every stop.</p>
<p>The Heat even kept it together to pull out a win over the defending NBA champions despite a fourth quarter that nearly went wrong.</p>
<p>Nunn scored 27 points, Jimmy Butler had 24 points and eight rebounds, and Miami held off the Los Angeles Lakers 96-94 Saturday night in an NBA Finals rematch.</p>
<p>Bam Adebayo had 16 points and 10 rebounds for the Heat in the teams’ first meeting since the Lakers won their 17th championship with a six-game victory over Miami in the Florida bubble four months ago. The Heat scored only 15 points in the fourth quarter, but they held the Lakers to 17 and hung on when Alex Caruso missed a long jumper at the buzzer.</p>
<p>“You can tell that the chemistry is building,” said Nunn, who hit five 3-pointers. “We’ve been together for a week and a half, and it just gives us more of a feel for each other. We’re moving in the right direction now. We dropped a couple early, but we’re starting to give ourselves the best chance at the end of the game.”</p>
<p>The victory was Miami&#8217;s second straight following a three-game skid during this seven-game road trip. The defending Eastern Conference champions (13-17) have been under .500 since Jan. 12, but their confidence is growing.</p>
<p>“We’re seeing progress the last few weeks,” coach Erik Spoelstra said. “I think our defensive mental toughness was better in this game to get some stops when we weren’t able to knock down some shots in the fourth quarter.”</p>
<p>LeBron James had 19 points, nine assists and nine rebounds as the champs lost their second straight game without starters Anthony Davis and Dennis Schröder.</p>
<p>James stole the Heat&#8217;s inbounds pass with 8.4 seconds left to create one last chance for the Lakers, but the 17-time All-Star passed out of a double team to Caruso, who capped his scoreless 20-minute night by missing.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re figuring out how to play without one of our creators in Dennis and one of our stars in AD,” Caruso said. “That&#8217;s going to take a little time, and obviously we don&#8217;t have practice time.”</p>
<p>Davis missed his third straight game after aggravating his strained right calf last weekend, and Schröder missed his second straight under the NBA’s health and safety protocols.</p>
<p>Kyle Kuzma scored 23 points while hitting four 3-pointers, and Montrezl Harrell had 18 points and 10 rebounds for the Lakers.</p>
<p>The injury absences don&#8217;t account for the Lakers&#8217; shooting woes over the last 10 games, including a 39% performance against Miami. LA missed five of its last six shots, including Wesley Matthews&#8217; rushed, off-balance 3-pointer with 15 seconds left.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re going to continue to work on our habits and be great for each other,” James said. “We all put in the work, so it’s not that. The law of averages will even itself out. We had lapses last season, and we had them during the playoffs. We know they’ll even them out over the course of the year.”</p>
<p>TIP-INS</p>
<p>Heat: Avery Bradley, a starter for the Lakers last season who missed their playoff run after opting out of the NBA restart, missed this game for Miami with a calf strain. &#8230; Goran Dragić missed his eighth straight game with a sprained left ankle.</p>
<p>Lakers: Schröder will miss at least two more games in quarantine, coach Frank Vogel said. The Lakers hope he&#8217;ll return Friday against Portland.</p>
<p>HERRO HURT</p>
<p>Tyler Herro left after playing less than 14 minutes due to a hip pointer. He will be re-evaluated Sunday, Spoelstra said.</p>
<p>“We’re used to it,” Spoelstra said of the Heat&#8217;s latest injury. “Every game there’s going to be something. This is developing a level of toughness in our group.&#8221;</p>
<p>Max Strus missed eight 3-pointers in Herro’s place.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Heat: At Thunder on Monday.</p>
<p>Lakers: Host Wizards on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868596</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-heat.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miami Heat logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>5-inning games, 2-out innings? Odd MLB spring look on deck</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/5-inning-games-2-out-innings-odd-mlb-spring-look-on-deck/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 03:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872209</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Colorado Rockies infielder Ryan McMahon figures players can find plenty to do with any extra time they could get at the end of days if...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Colorado Rockies infielder Ryan McMahon figures players can find plenty to do with any extra time they could get at the end of days if spring training games don&#8217;t go nine innings.</p>
<p>“Maybe slide out for some golf. If not, head home, hit the couch and watch some basketball right now,” McMahon said.</p>
<p>Or maybe even some extra batting practice.</p>
<p>“It could be, right? Depending on the day and depending on how things went, there’s a lot of different ways that you could go with it,” McMahon said. &#8220;The days are different every day, that’s for sure.”</p>
<p>Things certainly could look different when spring training games begin Sunday, with managers allowed to mutually determine in advance how many innings their teams need or want to play.</p>
<p>“What we’re finding is it’s going to provide some flexibility,&#8221; Milwaukee Brewers manager Craig Counsell said. “I think teams are viewing this differently. My early read on it is we’ll have some different game lengths daily, based on teams’ available pitching.&#8221;</p>
<p>Some games may not even make it to a seventh-inning stretch, since they can be as few as five innings through March 13. Even after that, until the end of spring training, games can be scheduled for only seven innings.</p>
<p>“It’s a very reasonable decision by MLB to be flexible,” said White Sox skipper Tony La Russa, managing again a decade after his game with the St. Louis Cardinals, and 35 years after he was last Chicago’s skipper.</p>
<p>The potentially shorter spring training games, and the ability to end innings before three outs, come on the heels of 2020, when teams had to alter workouts and the season was shortened to 60 games because of the coronavirus pandemic that is still ongoing. COVID-19 health and safety protocols remain in place while Major League Baseball prepares for what it hopes will be a full 162-game regular season this year.</p>
<p>Cincinnati Reds manager David Bell said he had already been in touch with Cleveland&#8217;s Terry Francona by midweek about their spring training opener Sunday. Teams have to confirm with MLB the previous day on how many innings they intend to play.</p>
<p>“It’s just going to be communication between the managers. It’s all new to us but it should be pretty seamless once we get into it,” Bell said.</p>
<p>Miami Marlins manager Don Mattingly expects his team&#8217;s first three games to go seven innings.</p>
<p>“After that, we&#8217;re good for nine,” Mattingly said.</p>
<p>While the number of innings have to declared in advance, all of those innings don&#8217;t initially have to be three outs.</p>
<p>Through March 13, defensive managers can end an inning before three outs following any completed plate appearance, provided the pitcher has thrown at least 20 pitches.</p>
<p>“Fans may not like it in the beginning,” Atlanta Braves manager Brian Snitker said. &#8220;You’ve got two outs and the bases loaded and you yell over there ‘Last hitter. We’re rolling him.’ But in the long run I think it’s a smart move to help, especially now as we’ll be trying to stretch pitchers out.”</p>
<p>Washington Nationals manager Dave Martinez said the ability to roll innings over, instead of trying to extend pitchers or use more pitchers to get out of an inning, will have managers on board to play nine full innings more often than not.</p>
<p>“It’s all about trying to keep everybody healthy. We’ve got guys out there to start the inning. You want them to get their work in, 20-25 pitches, some of these guys will be the maximum,” Martinez said. “After the shortened season, I put a lot of thought into keeping these guys healthy, getting them ready in a very controlled environment and building them up, which is really, really good.&#8221;</p>
<p>MANNY&#8217;S LASER FIX</p>
<p>Padres slugger Manny Machado said he had offseason laser eye surgery to deal with the lights.</p>
<p>“I hope it helps me hit better. I was dealing with some stuff last year with the lights, just night games. I still have the same vision,&#8221; he said. &#8220;We’ll just see when the lights turn on in San Diego, make that little adjustment there, if it helps me out or not. Vision’s fine, same thing, nothing major, nothing different, but hopefully it helps me see the ball a little better and I can hit .320, .330.”</p>
<p>Before the surgery, Machado hit .304 with 16 home runs in the pandemic-shortened 2020 season and was third in NL MVP balloting.</p>
<p>ARIZONA RELIEF</p>
<p>Veteran right-hander Tyler Clippard has done just about everything in the bullpen in 14 years and with 10 teams as a big league reliever. He should be able to do whatever is needed in Arizona.</p>
<p>“I understand the value in being a bridge guy, maybe covering multiple innings or coming in with guys on base in the sixth,” Clippard said Friday, four days after agreeing to terms on a $2.25 million, one-year contract. &#8220;I can do a lot of different things so I understand the value in that. So there’s no urgency to say I want to do this or that.”</p>
<p>The 36-year-old Clippard, a two-time All-Star with 777 career appearances and a 3.13 ERA, had a career-high 32 saves with the Nationals in 2012 and 17 saves with the Athletics in 2015.</p>
<p>But most of his best seasons have come as a setup man who can pitch longer stints if needed. He pitched in 40 games for the Diamondbacks in 2016 before being traded to the New York Yankees.</p>
<p>JESSE&#8217;S TEAM</p>
<p>Veteran right-hander Jesse Chavez is re-signing with the Los Angeles Angels on a minor league deal, and will join them in spring training after clearing intake protocols.</p>
<p>With experience as a starter, long reliever and late-inning pitcher, Chavez could provide experience and versatility for a pitching staff lacking depth.</p>
<p>Chavez appeared in 38 games for the Angels in 2017, including 21 starts. The Los Angeles-area native left for Texas as a free agent after one season, and he excelled after being traded in July 2018 to the Chicago Cubs, where he was managed by current Angels skipper Joe Maddon, then was with the Rangers again the past two years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872209</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-206.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-206.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-206.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Cutting grass</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Former MLB player Johnny Damon arrested for DUI in Florida</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/former-mlb-player-johnny-damon-arrested-for-dui-in-florida/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 16:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=867703</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[WINDERMERE, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; Former MLB player Johnny Damon has been arrested for driving under the influence in Florida. According to Orange County jail records,...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINDERMERE, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; Former MLB player Johnny Damon has been arrested for driving under the influence in Florida.</p>
<p>According to Orange County jail records, Damon was arrested by Windermere Police on charges of driving under the influence and resisting an officer without violence.</p>
<p>He is currently being held on $1,000 bond. However, no additional details about his arrest have been released.</p>
<p>Damon played in the MLB from 1995 to 2012. In that time, he played for the Kansas City Royals, Oakland Athletics, Boston Red Sox, New York Yankees, Detroit Tigers, Tampa Bay Rays and Cleveland Indians.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">867703</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/johnny-damon.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/johnny-damon.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/johnny-damon.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">johnny damon</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Players return to COVID protocols as spring training opens</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/players-return-to-covid-protocols-as-spring-training-opens/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866739</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[One year later, players and managers say they have a better understanding of what it takes to play baseball through a pandemic. Pitchers and catchers...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One year later, players and managers say they have a better understanding of what it takes to play baseball through a pandemic.</p>
<p>Pitchers and catchers around the game reported to spring training Wednesday saying they appreciate what’s at stake as they try to make sure the season starts on time. The protocols have been tightened even further from what they experienced during the abbreviated 2020 season.</p>
<p>“We’ve all gone through a year of this, of living through this,” New York Yankees manager Aaron Boone said. “And so I think we’re a little, much better equipped of how to handle ourselves, how to conduct ourselves, how to make good use of our time.”</p>
<p>New standards agreed to by Major League Baseball and the players’ association require players, staffers and other team personnel to wear electronic tracing wristbands for ballpark access. Players underwent a five-day at-home quarantine before reporting, with exceptions for essential activities and approved outdoor workouts and exercise.</p>
<p>They’ll need to stay in their living quarters throughout spring training except for baseball activities, medical care, grocery shopping, takeout food pickups and outdoor physical activity. Outdoor dining will only be allowed if they get permission beforehand.</p>
<p>“Between the players&#8217; union and MLB, the agreement I think is pretty rock-solid when it comes to player safety, staff safety,” Chicago White Sox pitcher Lucas Giolito said Tuesday. “There’s going to be a few things that are a little more, what’s the word for it, given more importance. I think some of the workouts are going to be in smaller groups, a lot more on point with mask wearing and things like that. I don’t think it will affect our work too much. We’ll certainly be able to get done what we need to get done.”</p>
<p>But the restrictions will make it more challenging to get ready for the season.</p>
<p>Catcher James McCann faces hurdles this spring trying to bond with an entirely new pitching staff after signing a $40 million, four-year deal with New York Mets. Normally, the veteran backstop would invite pitchers to dinner, set up play dates for their kids, go out and grab a drink — anything to help develop those relationships.</p>
<p>Forget the off-field meetups. Under MLB’s protocols, even getting together at the team’s Florida complex is more difficult. Gathering in places like the video room — usually a convenient spot for 3-4 players to meet — is a no-no.</p>
<p>“Nobody likes to wear a mask and sit and talk 6 feet away from each other,” McCann said. “A lot of different things I guess we took for granted.”</p>
<p>MLB is hoping to have a full season after playing a 60-game schedule last year that included no fans in the stands until the postseason. The Miami Marlins and St. Louis Cardinals both dealt with COVID-19 outbreaks that resulted in multiple postponements.</p>
<p>“We’re the lucky sport to have 162 games, but with that obviously comes a lot of thoughtfulness and dedication and commitment,” new Marlins general manager Kim Ng said. “To play this game, you have to be absolutely committed, especially this team with them going through what they went through last year. People understand how it can decimate.”</p>
<p>Cardinals pitcher Carlos Martinez battled COVID-19 last summer and says he wasn’t the same the rest of the season.</p>
<p>“After that, I was not comfortable with my body,” said Martinez, who added that he feels great now.</p>
<p>Oakland right-hander Frankie Montas was quarantining at home in Scottsdale, Arizona, on Wednesday with COVID-19. Manager Bob Melvin said Montas is “several days into it” after testing positive prior to reporting day.</p>
<p>Two other players were added to the COVID-19-related injured list Wednesday, which doesn&#8217;t necessarily mean they&#8217;ve tested positive: Boston Red Sox catcher Kevin Plawecki and Chicago Cubs left-hander Kyle Ryan.</p>
<p>One of the first things Cardinals president John Mozeliak did upon arriving in Jupiter, Florida, was to request a list from the medical staff of players and coaches who tested positive for COVID-19 antibodies.</p>
<p>Mozeliak believes knowing which players already have at least some measure of protection from the coronavirus can help in preventing an outbreak during spring training.</p>
<p>“I believe we had about 15 or 18 people with antibodies in this camp,” Mozeliak said, “so that was encouraging.”</p>
<p>Mozeliak also expressed hope that some staff and players could begin receiving the COVID-19 vaccine by opening day.</p>
<p>“But I certainly understand, collectively, you’re dealing with a pretty healthy group of young people,” he said, “and when you’re looking across our country, there are people more deserving of that opportunity than this group. But clearly if you were vaccinated, it would ease up a lot of the protocols we have in a sense of where you can go and where you can’t.”</p>
<p>For now, players say they are ready to follow the protocols while looking forward to the day they’re playing in full stadiums again.</p>
<p>“Thankful it’s going to be, not quite normal, but closer to it,” Arizona Diamondbacks pitcher Madison Bumgarner said. “I think we’re on the path back to that, so hopefully it all happens sooner rather than later.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866739</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MLB logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Black MLB players, executives strive to diversify baseball</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/black-mlb-players-executives-strive-to-diversify-baseball/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 23:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866117</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Michele Meyer-Shipp doesn&#8217;t have to travel far to realize the challenge of growing the sport of baseball in the Black community. She just sits down...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michele Meyer-Shipp doesn&#8217;t have to travel far to realize the challenge of growing the sport of baseball in the Black community.</p>
<p>She just sits down at the dinner table.</p>
<p>Meyer-Shipp, who is Major League Baseball&#8217;s chief people and culture officer, has three sons who love sports. They know all about some of baseball&#8217;s Black legends like Hank Aaron, the sport&#8217;s one-time home run king who recently died at age 86.</p>
<p>But today&#8217;s Black baseball stars? Not so much.</p>
<p>“When I listen to my boys talk about sports, they&#8217;re always talking about the Black football player. Always,” Meyer-Shipp said. &#8220;And I&#8217;m like, ‘You know, there are Black baseball players.’ They talk about Black basketball players as well. But those are the guys you always see on commercials, on TV.</p>
<p>“We need our guys from baseball out there building a brand for Black talent in the game. I think that would really make a difference.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marketing the game&#8217;s best Black players was one of many topics discussed by a five-person panel of current MLB players, executives and coaches. The conversation, which was streamed Tuesday on MLB.com, is part of MLB&#8217;s Diversity, Equity &amp; Inclusion program.</p>
<p>Dodgers manager Dave Roberts, Marlins outfielder Lewis Brinson, former Astros manager Bo Porter and Red Sox coach Bianca Smith were also on the panel. The 26-year-old Brinson said he started playing baseball in south Florida when he was 4 years old and immediately grew to love it, but as he got older, he eventually realized not many Black kids were playing baseball.</p>
<p>He said he only had two Black teammates from tee ball through high school.</p>
<p>“I got made fun of for playing baseball — ‘Oh you’re playing that white sport. What are you doing playing that, man?” Brinson said. “But obviously I didn&#8217;t really care because I loved it.”</p>
<p>The number of Black players in MLB has been dwindling for years, hovering around 8% of the league in recent seasons.</p>
<p>Brinson said that&#8217;s one reason he&#8217;s proud to be in the The Players Alliance, which is a group of more than 100 Black current and former professional baseball players. The goal is for their platform to lead to “increased opportunities for the Black community in every aspect of our game and beyond.”</p>
<p>Brinson said going into poor areas of cities, providing baseball equipment and giving back was important. He added that it&#8217;s also good for the sport when children see players who look like them.</p>
<p>“Having those Black kids see us, touch us and talk to us, knowing that ‘Man, they look like me. I could be in their shoes,'&#8221; Brinson said. “I think more than anything, us actually going ourselves into the community and showing these kids, ‘Listen, you could be where I’m at.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The panel also discussed how to diversify the upper levels of the game, especially among managers and front office staff. Porter was the manager of the Astros in 2013 and &#8217;14 and is now a consultant for MLB.</p>
<p>Porter said he remains optimistic about baseball&#8217;s progress in diversity, but said it&#8217;s important that executives work to find ways to broaden their hiring pool so they have a more diverse group of candidates.</p>
<p>“We have to open up the access gate because they don&#8217;t know what they don&#8217;t know,” Porter said. “A lot of these general managers, presidents of baseball operations, if they were to open the access gate and have conversations when these jobs come available, I guarantee you the hiring process will get better and it will change.</p>
<p>“As Black people, we&#8217;re not looking for a handout. What we want is an opportunity.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866117</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180325_lewis_brinson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180325_lewis_brinson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180325_lewis_brinson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180325_Lewis_Brinson</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>NL Cy Young winner Bauer joins World Series champion Dodgers</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nl-cy-young-winner-bauer-joins-world-series-champion-dodgers/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=858314</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES (AP) — Trevor Bauer is coming home to pitch for the World Series champion Los Angeles Dodgers. The reigning NL Cy Young Award...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Trevor Bauer is coming home to pitch for the World Series champion Los Angeles Dodgers.</p>
<p>The reigning NL Cy Young Award winner announced his decision on Friday in a two-minute video posted to his Twitter account. Bauer narrated the piece, which ended with him saying, &#8220;This season is about making sure history remembers us as we wish to be remembered. This season is about adding to our legacy. And I can’t wait, Dodger fans.”</p>
<p>The video was titled “MY NEW HOME!!!” and the credits said it was written by Bauer, who wore a Dodgers jersey and cap. He tossed a baseball from one hand to the other.</p>
<p>Bauer, who turned 30 last month, was born in North Hollywood, went to high school in Santa Clarita and played baseball at UCLA.</p>
<p>The right-handed free agent also was negotiating with the New York Mets. Bauer&#8217;s agent, Rachel Luba, tweeted, “So excited for your next chapter with the @Dodgers, Trevor Bauer.”</p>
<p>For the second straight year, the Dodgers had a mostly quiet offseason before making a blockbuster deal in February. In 2020, they traded for outfielder Mookie Betts and pitcher David Price, who opted out last season because of the pandemic. Price is expected back this year.</p>
<p>Bauer joins a Dodgers rotation that had a major league-best 3.02 ERA during the abbreviated 60-game season last year, when the franchise won its first championship since 1988.</p>
<p>He gives the club a third Cy Young winner, joining three-time winner Clayton Kershaw and 2012 winner Price. According to the Elias Sports Bureau, the Dodgers are the first team to have three former Cy Young winners in their rotation since the Detroit Tigers in 2014 had Justin Verlander, Max Scherzer and Price.</p>
<p>With the upcoming season expanding from 60 games to a full 162-game schedule, the Dodgers can go seven-deep in their rotation, which includes Julio Urias, Dustin May and Tony Gonsolin.</p>
<p>Bauer is 75-64 with a 3.90 ERA in nine major league seasons that included a career-best 17-9 with a 4.19 ERA for Cleveland in 2017. He was an All-Star the following year, going 12-6 with a 2.21 ERA.</p>
<p>Bauer was 5-4 in his second season with Cincinnati and his 1.73 ERA was second in the major leagues among qualified pitchers behind only Cleveland’s Shane Bieber at 1.63. Bauer earned $6,481,481 in prorated pay from a $17.5 million salary.</p>
<p>Arizona drafted Bauer with the third overall pick in the 2011 amateur draft. He made his big league debut with the Diamondbacks the following year and went 1-2 in four starts, then was traded to Cleveland in December 2012 with pitchers Matt Albers and Bryan Shaw as part of a three-team trade that brought shortstop Didi Gregorius and pitcher Tony Sipp to Arizona, outfielder Drew Stubbs to Cleveland and outfielder Shin-Soo Choo to Cincinnati.</p>
<p>He was traded to Cincinnati in July 2019 in another three-team deal, one with Cleveland and San Diego that brought pitcher Logan Allen and outfielders Franmil Reyes and Yasiel Puig to the Indians.</p>
<p>Bauer has caused controversy on social media. A female college student claimed to USA Today in 2019 that Bauer harassed her on Twitter, accusing him of retweeting an old tweet of her referring to drinking alcohol before her 21st birthday. USA Today said there were 80 tweets of Bauer that mentioned her and 20 of her that mentioned the pitcher. Bauer tweeted the woman “was obsessed with me.”</p>
<p>He took after baseball owners for the sport’s economics last May during bargaining to start the pandemic-delayed season.</p>
<p>“There’s so many ways to hide the money,” he said, adding owners could reduce ticket prices and at the same time charge more for parking garages they control through different entities that do not benefit the club.</p>
<p>“If I’m going to have to trust my salary to Rob Manfred marketing the game to make more money for the game, I am out on that,” Bauer said. “Let me market the game and we’ll all make more money.”</p>
<p>Los Angeles’ other offseason moves include re-signing reliever Blake Treinen to a $17.5 million, two-year contract, and agreeing to a $4.75 million, two-year deal with reliever Tommy Kahnle, who is rehabbing from Tommy John surgery in August.</p>
<p>Because Bauer turned down an $18.9 million qualifying offer, Los Angeles will forfeit its second-highest pick in the July amateur draft and $500,000 of international signing bonus allocation.</p>
<p>Cincinnati will receive an extra draft pick after competitive balance round B, approximately No. 60, as compensation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">858314</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MLB logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item></channel>
</rss>
