<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Florida Panthers &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-panthers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Florida Panthers &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Trocheck, Reimer help Hurricanes blow past Panthers 4-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/trocheck-reimer-help-hurricanes-blow-past-panthers-4-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878143</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Vincent Trocheck and James Reimer continued to torment their former team, lifting the Carolina Hurricanes to their fifth straight victory with...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Vincent Trocheck and James Reimer continued to torment their former team, lifting the Carolina Hurricanes to their fifth straight victory with a 4-2 win over the Florida Panthers on Sunday night.</p>
<p>Trocheck, who was traded to Carolina just over a year ago, scored for the fourth time this season against the Panthers. Nino Niederreiter, Sebastian Aho and Warren Foegele also had goals for the Hurricanes, who have won eight of 10 home games (8-1-1) this season.</p>
<p>“We didn’t really have any lulls in the game,” Hurricanes coach Rod Brind’Amour said. “I like the fact that we hung in there. Didn’t get frustrated, just kept playing.”</p>
<p>Reimer, who made 21 saves, came to Carolina less two years in ago in a trade from Florida. He’s 3-0-0 since against the Panthers.</p>
<p>MacKenzie Weegar and Mason Marchment scored for Florida, which had a five-game points streak snapped. Chris Dreidger made 22 saves for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Trocheck scored just eight seconds into the Hurricanes’ first power play of the game. At that point with 4:05 to play in the opening period, Carolina had as many goals as the Panthers did shots on goal.</p>
<p>“We played a full 60 minutes,” Trocheck said. “I think this one was the best of the last four.”</p>
<p>Trocheck has four goals during his five-game points streak.</p>
<p>“He has found a home,” Brind’Amour said. “It’s no different than any job. When you’re feeling good about and where you fit, you have success. You don’t expect him to score at this rate, but we’ll take it for as long as we can.”</p>
<p>Niederreiter took a pass from Martin Necas and beat Dreidger, who had been under siege early in the second period. Niederreiter has 11 goals, posting at least one against every Central Division team except for Tampa Bay.</p>
<p>Carolina is 3-0-1 against the Panthers this season. This was the first meeting decided in regulation.</p>
<p>“They’re a well-structured team,” Panthers left wing Jonathan Huberdeau said. “It’s always tough to play against them.”</p>
<p>The Panthers got on the scoreboard when Weegar blasted the puck between Reimer’s pads with 9:19 left in the second period.</p>
<p>Aho posted the team’s second short-handed goal of the season 38 seconds into the third period. Foegele extended the lead to 4-1 slightly more than three minutes later.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes took advantage of special teams situations.</p>
<p>“You’ve got to make quick plays,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. “We had some good looks. We didn’t have enough of them. Not enough clean possession time.”</p>
<p>Florida won 6-2 at Nashville on Saturday, while the Hurricanes hadn’t played since Thursday night.</p>
<p>MILESTONE MOMENT</p>
<p>Panthers defenseman Keith Yandle appeared in his 1,000th career game. He’s in his 15th season in the league and his fourth season with the Panthers.</p>
<p>His accomplishment was recognized with an announcement during a break in the first period.</p>
<p>Yandle has played 890 consecutive games for the longest active streak in the league and the third-longest stretch in NHL history.</p>
<p>HIM AGAIN</p>
<p>Trocheck has scored in each of Carolina&#8217;s four matchups with Florida this season.</p>
<p>He’s the first player in the Carolina (and former Hartford) organization to score in his first four games against his ex-team following a trade since the NHL began tracking that information in 1991-92.</p>
<p>“I think it’s just the luck of the draw on that one,” Trocheck said of the topic. “Obviously it’s nice to get one against the former team. There’s motivation every night.”</p>
<p>Trocheck, who has a goal in four of the last five games, has a team-leading 13 goals this season. Florida doesn’t have a player with a double-digit goal total.</p>
<p>MORE TIME OFF</p>
<p>Hurricanes winger Teuvo Teravainen missed the game for undisclosed reasons. He had returned from a seven-game absence because of a concussion to play Thursday night in a victory against Detroit. He logged 14½ minutes in that game.</p>
<p>Brind’Amour said the latest time off might be related to the previous injury.</p>
<p>“Whenever you have those kinds of injuries, nobody really knows,” he said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Play at Columbus on Tuesday and Thursday.</p>
<p>Hurricanes: Stay home for games Tuesday and Thursday vs. Nashville.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878143</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Noel Acciari gets hat trick as Panthers beat Predators 6-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/noel-acciari-gets-hat-trick-as-panthers-beat-predators-6-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The Florida Panthers are playing so well that someone who hadn&#8217;t scored a point this season can turn in a hat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The Florida Panthers are playing so well that someone who hadn&#8217;t scored a point this season can turn in a hat trick.</p>
<p>The Nashville Predators couldn&#8217;t be much more frustrated right now, struggling despite having so many key players who won a Presidents&#8217; Trophy just three seasons ago.</p>
<p>Noel Acciari scored three goals for his third career hat trick, and the Panthers beat the Nashville Predators 6-2 on Saturday for their second straight victory.</p>
<p>Acciari, who began the day with no points in 14 games this season, scored twice in a three-goal second period as the Panthers took the lead for good. He finished off the hat trick with an unassisted goal with 3:02 left.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s a great feeling,” Acciari said. “I was just hoping to get one &#8230; just to get my first of the season. But to get the other two was definitely exciting, and a lot of guys are putting pressure on me about tomorrow.”</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because the last time Acciari had a hat trick, he became the second in Florida history to turn in a hat trick in consecutive games on Dec. 16-20, 2019. Florida coach Joel Quenneville said the fourth-line forward either scores none or he scores three at a time.</p>
<p>“Pretty impressive,” Quenneville said. &#8220;He gets flurries and nice to see him score. I think around the net he&#8217;s been pressing a little bit. He doesn&#8217;t get a ton of chances, but he&#8217;s usually pretty nifty and tonight they were going in.”</p>
<p>Aaron Ekblad, Jonathan Huberdeau and Frank Vatrano each had a goal and an assist as the Panthers improved to 8-1-1 on the road this season. Keith Yandle had two assists. Sergei Bobrovsky made 28 saves.</p>
<p>Eeli Tolvanen and Viktor Arvidsson scored for Nashville, which lost its third straight and dropped to 1-9 combined against the Central Division&#8217;s top three teams. Filip Forsberg had two assists, including the 200th of his career.</p>
<p>Nashville captain Roman Josi was so frustrated he nearly cursed talking to media after the game. He said the Predators have an identity for parts of games but not the full 60 minutes.</p>
<p>“We need to find a way to get out of this together,” Josi said. “It’s obviously not the way we want to play right now.”</p>
<p>The Predators took the first 10 shots and didn&#8217;t allow a Florida shot until midway through the first period. When Grigori Denisenko tripped Forsberg, the Predators scored 7 seconds into the man advantage with <a href="https://twitter.com/PredsNHL/status/1368281375040823299">Tolvanen easily beating Bobrovsky</a> with a slap shot to the far side of the net.</p>
<p>They appeared poised to take just their fourth lead after the first period this season until the final seconds. That&#8217;s when Ekblad, coming off a four-point game, tied it with 12.6 seconds left in the first with a snap shot from the high slot at the right circle. It was all Panthers from there.</p>
<p>Huberdeau put the Panthers up 2-1 just 1:15 into the second with Patric Horqnvist getting his 500th career NHL point on the assist. Hornqvist got the puck in the Nashville offensive zone and passed to Huberdeau, who had <a href="https://twitter.com/NHL/status/1368295895608008707">enough time to deke out Rinne</a> before flipping the puck over the goalie&#8217;s right pad.</p>
<p>Acciari padded the lead at 11:17 of the second, finishing off a 2-on-1 with a wrist shot from the right circle. He got his second with 1:14 left in the period with a backhand past Rinne for a power-play goal.</p>
<p>TOO LITTLE TOO LATE</p>
<p>Nashville came in tied for the NHL lead with 30 goals in the third period this season. Arvidsson made it 31 with a wrist shot in front 19 seconds into the third.</p>
<p>But the Predators couldn&#8217;t put one past Bobrovsky the rest of the period. Vatrano got his eighth of the season before Acciari capped the scoring.</p>
<p>ROAD WARRIORS</p>
<p>The Panthers already had the best road record through the first nine games in franchise history, and they won their fourth straight in Nashville. Florida also is 5-1-0 over the last six road games. Montreal is the only other NHL team with only one regulation road loss this season.</p>
<p>DUCHENE OUT</p>
<p>Nashville center Matt Duchene was placed on injured reserve. He is expected to be sidelined for three to five weeks with a lower-body injury. The veteran has eight points in 23 games this season with a minus-11 rating.</p>
<p>WHAT&#8217;S NEXT</p>
<p>After dropping two to the Hurricanes in Florida, the Panthers continue their road trip Sunday in Carolina.</p>
<p>The Predators start an eight-game road swing Sunday night in Dallas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877581</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ekblad&#8217;s four points leads Panthers over Predators 5-4</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ekblads-four-points-leads-panthers-over-predators-5-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad had two goals and two assists to lead the Florida Panthers to a 5-4 victory over the Nashville Predators...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad had two goals and two assists to lead the Florida Panthers to a 5-4 victory over the Nashville Predators on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Carter Verhaeghe, Mason Marchment and Jonathan Huberdeau also scored for Florida, which snapped a two-game losing streak. Aleksander Barkov had three assists and Sergei Bobrovsky made 31 saves for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Mattias Ekholm, Filip Forsberg, Colton Sissons and Ryan Johansen scored for Nashville, which has lost two straight. Viktor Arvidsson had three assists and Pekka Rinne made 33 saves.</p>
<p>The teams finish their two-game series Saturday at Bridgestone Arena.</p>
<p>Both of Ekblad’s goals came via the power play. It was his first career four-point game.</p>
<p>Ekblad pushed Florida’s lead to 4-1 with 1:16 left in the second period with a power-play goal, but Forsberg answered 50 seconds later to pull Nashville back within two.</p>
<p>Nashville appeared to draw within one, two minutes into the third on a goal by Rocco Grimaldi, but Florida challenged the play for offside and a video review erased the goal.</p>
<p>Ekblad’s second of the game and eight of the season came at 9:07 of the third to make it 5-2.</p>
<p>Sissons again brought Nashville within two with at 12:40 and Johansen made it 5-4 with 1:13 remaining in the third with Rinne pulled for an extra attacker.</p>
<p>Verhaeghe scored the game’s first goal at 6:29 of the opening period. It was his eighth.</p>
<p>Marchment made it 2-0 at 9:01 with his first NHL goal. Coming off of the right half wall, Marchment cut into the faceoff circle and snapped a wrist shot between Rinne’s pads.</p>
<p>Huberdeau’s goal 59 seconds into the second gave Florida a 3-0 advantage. Former Predator Patric Hornqvist skated behind the Nashville net and found an unchecked Huberdeau in front where his wrist shot deflected off of Rinne’s chest and into the net on the glove side for his ninth.</p>
<p>Ekholm got Nashville on the board at 12:23 of the second on a one-timer from the right point off of a pass from Arvidsson. Ekholm has four goals in the four games he has played since missing six games with a lower-body injury.</p>
<p>FEELS LIKE THE FIRST TIME</p>
<p>Marchment’s first period goal was the second time in two games that Rinne allowed an opponent’s first career goal. In Tuesday’s game against the Carolina Hurricanes, it was Steven Lorentz.</p>
<p>MILESTONE</p>
<p>Florida defenseman Radko Gudas played his 500th career NHL game.</p>
<p>SAROS TO IR</p>
<p>Predators goaltender Juuse Saros was placed on injured reserve Thursday, two days after leaving Tuesday night’s game against the Carolina Hurricanes. Early in the first period Tuesday, Carolina’s Nino Niederreiter collided head-to-head with Saros behind the Nashville net as Saros was playing a puck. Saros finished the first period but was replaced by Rinne to start the second.</p>
<p>Kasimir Kaskisuo was elevated from the team’s taxi squad Thursday and served as Rinne’s backup.</p>
<p>JOHANSEN RETURNS</p>
<p>Johansen returned to the Nashville lineup Thursday. He missed Tuesday’s game after being placed on the NHL’s COVID-19 protocol list. Prior to missing the one game on the COVID-19 list, Johansen had played four games since missing the previous seven with an upper-body injury.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876377</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Necas&#8217; shootout goal lifts Hurricanes past Panthers 4-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/necas-shootout-goal-lifts-hurricanes-past-panthers-4-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 05:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Martin Necas scored the winning goal in a shootout, and the Carolina Hurricanes beat the Florida Panthers 4-3 on Saturday night....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Martin Necas scored the winning goal in a shootout, and the Carolina Hurricanes beat the Florida Panthers 4-3 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Vincent Trocheck, Jake Bean and Warren Foegele scored in regulation for Carolina, which snapped a three-game skid.</p>
<p>Jonathan Huberdeau, Frank Vatrano, and Patric Hornqvist scored for Florida.</p>
<p>Hornqvist scored his ninth goal of the season with 1:54 remaining in the third period as Florida rallied for the second time in the contest and forced the OT.</p>
<p>Foegele had given Carolina a 3-2 lead with just under six minutes remaining.</p>
<p>“I like how we bounced back from the negative kind of things that (happen) in a game,” Carolina coach Rod Brind’Amour said. “We have a lot of good options on the shootout. So that’s very, very positive. It’s coming through this year obviously.”</p>
<p>James Reimer had 28 saves for the Hurricanes. Sergei Bobrovsky turned back 30 of 33 shots for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Florida also surged back from a 2-0 deficit within a two-minute span of the third before Foegele’s goal.</p>
<p>Carolina capitalized on its first of many power-play chances when Trocheck beat Bobrovsky with 2:21 left in the first period. It was Trocheck’s 10th goal.</p>
<p>Minutes earlier, Trocheck was honored with a tribute on the video scoreboard during a timeout.</p>
<p>“It was awesome to see the tribute they gave me,” said Trocheck, who spent seven seasons with the Panthers. “It was very classy of them. Obviously a little emotional &#8230; I played here for a long time and a lot of good memories here.”</p>
<p>The Hurricanes extended their lead to 2-0, again on the man advantage when Bean scored his first goal just 1:30 into the third period. Brett Pesce and Necas assisted on the goal.</p>
<p>Florida had cut the deficit with 11:47 remaining as Hornqvist stuffed one past Reimer on the power play for his ninth goal. The Panthers then tied the game when Vatrano converted a perfect feed from Mason Marchment for his sixth goal.</p>
<p>Carolina’s Brock McGinn and Necas had consecutive breakaways on Panthers giveaways in the neutral zone. Bobrovsky made a sprawling save on McGinn, and Alex Wennberg surged in from behind and poke-checked the puck away from Necas.</p>
<p>Florida outshot the Hurricanes, 10-2, early on before Carolina’s late flurry, including Trocheck’s goal with Kevin Connauton in the box for tripping.</p>
<p>Florida coach Joel Quenneville liked the way his team battled from behind with another third-period comeback.</p>
<p>“We chipped away and all of a sudden we get a lot of momentum back,” Quenneville said. “The nice thing that’s positive about coming back is that we’re scoring some hard goals and that’s where the rewards are.”</p>
<p>DIFFERENT OUTCOME</p>
<p>The 4-3 result was the second in as many games between the two Central Division rivals. Florida edged the Hurricanes, 4-3, in overtime at the PNC Center earlier this season.</p>
<p>A MUCH-NEEDED ’W”</p>
<p>Trocheck and his teammates were relieved that the Hurricanes were able to end their losing streak.</p>
<p>“We needed to get the win here. Obviously good teams don’t lose back-to-backs and we lost three in a row, so coming in tonight against a good team we needed to get that win.”</p>
<p>Carolina did not record its first shot until just past the midway point of that period. Florida had the game’s first five shots.</p>
<p>REUNION TIME</p>
<p>Along with Trocheck, James Reimer was back in Sunrise as a former Panther. It was Reimer’s second visit, with the last coming on Oct. 8, 2019.</p>
<p>Trocheck, who skated in 420 games for the Panthers and registered 282 points between 2014-20, also scored against his former teammates in Carolina’s overtime loss to Florida.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>The contest was witnessed by 4,281 fans at the BB&amp;T Center.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida hosts Carolina on Monday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872681</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers stun Stars 3-2 with late rally</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-stun-stars-3-2-with-late-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 03:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871497</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Frank Vatrano scored the go-ahead goal with 3:10 remaining and the Florida Panthers stunned the Dallas Stars 3-2 with a late...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Frank Vatrano scored the go-ahead goal with 3:10 remaining and the Florida Panthers stunned the Dallas Stars 3-2 with a late comeback Thursday night.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov and Anton Stralman also scored in the final 6 1/2 minutes as the Panthers overcame a 2-0 deficit. Sergei Bobrovsky made 37 saves.</p>
<p>Joe Pavelski and Jamie Benn had the goals for Dallas. Rookie netminder Jake Oettinger stopped 32 shots.</p>
<p>Florida scored three times in 3:11 after a nine-minute delay to repair a section of the boards.</p>
<p>Barkov poked in a loose puck that bounced behind Oettinger and sat in the paint near the goal line with 6:21 left. Stralman tied the score on a drive from the right circle. Vatrano put the Panthers ahead with a shot from the slot.</p>
<p>Pavelski scored the game’s first goal 2:10 into the second period on the power play when he swept in the puck from the left side of the crease. Pavelski leads the Stars with 10 goals in 15 games.</p>
<p>John Klingberg’s shot from the high slot was redirected by Benn into the net to make it 2-0 with 2:11 left in the second.</p>
<p>The Panthers, who lost 3-0 to Dallas on Wednesday, are 6-0-0 following a loss.</p>
<p>IRONMAN STREAK</p>
<p>Florida defenseman Keith Yandle played in his 885th consecutive regular-season game dating to March 26, 2009, passing Steve Larmer (1982–93) for sole possession of the third-longest streak in NHL history.</p>
<p>ROSTER MOVES</p>
<p>Panthers D Radko Gudas was scratched with an upper-body injury. &#8230; Florida recalled forward Mason Marchment and defenseman Kevin Connauton from the taxi squad. D Markus Nutivaara has been placed on injured reserve.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>A crowd of 3,844 was on hand. The Panthers cap attendance at 5,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871497</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Khudobin helps Stars end 6-game skid in 3-0 win vs. Panthers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/khudobin-helps-stars-end-6-game-skid-in-3-0-win-vs-panthers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870809</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Anton Khudobin made 43 saves for his second shutout of the season, leading the Dallas Stars to a 3-0 victory over...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Anton Khudobin made 43 saves for his second shutout of the season, leading the Dallas Stars to a 3-0 victory over the Florida Panthers on Wednesday night that ended their six-game winless streak.</p>
<p>Defensemen John Klingberg, Esa Lindell and Joel Kiviranta scored for the Stars, who are 1-3-3 in their last seven. They hadn&#8217;t won since beating Columbus on the road 6-3 on Feb. 2.</p>
<p>Khudobin has shut out Florida three times in nine career starts. He has 10 career shutouts overall. Khudobin blanked Nashville 7-0 for his 100th career win on Jan. 22 to open the season.</p>
<p>“There have been good games in my career, there have been bad games in my career,” Khudobin said. “So maybe this is one of the best. I don’t know, I’m not looking at that. I’m just looking at the win.”</p>
<p>Chris Driedger made his fifth start in Florida’s last six games and stopped 23 shots in the loss.</p>
<p>The teams complete a three-game series in Florida on Thursday night.</p>
<p>The goaltending pairing of Khudobin and Driedger was a rematch from Monday, when the Panthers had 52 shots on goal. That included 29 shots in the second period — a franchise record for one frame — and Khudobin matched his career best with 49 saves in Florida’s 3-1 win.</p>
<p>“He played great tonight, he played great the other night,” Dallas coach Rick Bowness said. “We were still in the game because of Anton. He’s been very good both nights.”</p>
<p>Dallas opened the scoring when Klingberg wound up and fired in the game’s first shot just 53 seconds in while on a delayed penalty. The teams played a testy remainder of the period.</p>
<p>Khudobin was exceptional in the second, stopping MacKenzie Weegar on an odd-man rush at 6:54. He also turned back Carter Verhaeghe’s wrister from the low slot at 10:07 to maintain the Stars’ slim lead.</p>
<p>Lindell’s second goal came 2:17 into the third to make it 2-0. Kiviranta’s empty-netter sealed the win.</p>
<p>The Panthers were shut out for the first time this season.</p>
<p>“We broke through in the second period last game, but were unable to do it today,&#8221; Florida coach Joel Quenneville said. “We had some great looks. We were aggressive around his net and challenging him. Give him some credit.”</p>
<p>Added Florida&#8217;s Brett Connolly: “They played a lot of better, and we didn’t bring our best. We got what we deserved.”</p>
<p>BUSY STARS</p>
<p>The league reworked 11 games involving the Stars on Tuesday, including two each at home against Nashville and Tampa Bay that were postponed last week due to severe weather in Texas.</p>
<p>In all, they will play their remaining 42 games in 75 days and finish the campaign with seven straight on the road.</p>
<p>The club will play eight times against Tampa Bay, six more with the Panthers and four versus Carolina – the top teams in the division.</p>
<p>“Hockey is not meant to be played four (games) in six (nights), let alone what we’re going to do,” Bowness said before the game after he learned of the new schedule. “This is going to be incredibly taxing on our players.”</p>
<p>BACK WHERE IT ALL BEGAN</p>
<p>Dallas right wing Denis Gurianov skated in his 100th career NHL game in the win.</p>
<p>The native of Togliatti, Russia, who has 25 career goals, was a first-round selection (12th overall) by the Stars in the draft held in the Panthers’ arena on June 26, 2015.</p>
<p>FANS IN THE STANDS</p>
<p>The Panthers drew 3,324 fans for the matinee contest, which had a 5 p.m. ET puck drop.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870809</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ekblad, Yandle lift Panthers over struggling Stars 3-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ekblad-yandle-lift-panthers-over-struggling-stars-3-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 05:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad and Keith Yandle scored, Chris Driedger made 24 saves and the Florida Panthers beat the slumping, rusty Dallas Stars...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad and Keith Yandle scored, Chris Driedger made 24 saves and the Florida Panthers beat the slumping, rusty Dallas Stars 3-1 on Monday night.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov scored an empty-net goal to seal the Panthers’ sixth win in eight games.</p>
<p>Blake Comeau scored for Dallas, and Anton Khudobin stopped 49 of 51 shots. The Stars lost their sixth in a row and eighth of nine overall while playing their first game since Feb. 13 due to the weather conditions in Dallas.</p>
<p>“Yep. There was a lot of shots,” Khudobin said. “It doesn’t matter how I felt. We didn’t get there.”</p>
<p>The Stars’ season was twice interrupted — first by a coronavirus outbreak in training camp and then by last week’s winter storm in Texas.</p>
<p>Dallas was supposed to open the season at Florida for two games and then at Tampa Bay for two more, but close to 20 COVID-19 positive cases prompted the postponement of those games. This week, the Stars were scheduled to host the Lightning on Thursday and Saturday, but those games were called off because of power outages in the Dallas area.</p>
<p>Stars coach Rick Bowness wasn’t using the break as an excuse.</p>
<p>“Were we rusty? Yep. Did we play through it? No. In the second period we let them do whatever they wanted,” Bowness said. “It was a winnable game, one shot away. We wasted a great goaltending performance. That’s an 8-1 game without Anton.”</p>
<p>Trailing 1-0, the Panthers picked up the pace in a furious second period with a franchise-record 29 shots on goal, while the Stars only managed five.</p>
<p>“It was a pleasure to watch,” Driedger said. “The guys went to work in the second. I haven’t seen a period that dominant in a long time.”</p>
<p>Ekblad tied it at 1 at 8:41 of the second. Ekblad has six goals, tied with Jeff Petry (Montreal) and Darnell Nurse (Edmonton) for most goals by defensemen this season.</p>
<p>Yandle put the Panthers ahead 2-1 on his shot from the point with 1:42 left in the second.</p>
<p>“The first (period) we were off to a little bit of a bumpy start, but we found our legs in the second and it showed,” Panthers defenseman MacKenzie Weegar said. “We just kept coming at them and at them.”</p>
<p>Comeau gave the Stars a 1-0 lead when he poked in a loose puck at 4:29 of the first. Jason Robertson stretched his scoring streak to five games with an assist on the goal.</p>
<p>NOTES</p>
<p>Dallas’ Mark Pysyk spent the past four seasons with Florida, playing 292 games for the Panthers, and returned for the first time. The Panthers acknowledged Pysyk with a tribute on the scoreboard. &#8230; Panthers F Noel Acciari (upper body) was scratched.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The two teams meet again on Wednesday and close out the three-game set Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869575</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Wings hold off Panthers 2-1 after Brome&#8217;s 1st NHL goal</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/red-wings-hold-off-panthers-2-1-after-bromes-1st-nhl-goal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 01:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DETROIT (AP) — Mathias Brome scored his first NHL goal late in the second period, and the Detroit Red Wings held on for a 2-1...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DETROIT (AP) — Mathias Brome scored his first NHL goal late in the second period, and the Detroit Red Wings held on for a 2-1 victory over the Florida Panthers on Saturday.</p>
<p>Patrik Nemeth also scored his first goal of the season for the Red Wings, who won for only the second time in seven games. Detroit rebounded from a 7-2 loss to the Panthers the previous night.</p>
<p>Alex Wennberg scored for Florida in the first period, but the Panthers allowed two goals in the second.</p>
<p>With the score tied at 1, Dylan Larkin got open in the slot for Detroit. Goalie Sergei Bobrovsky stopped his shot, but Brome was there to put away the rebound. It was the rookie forward&#8217;s first career point in his 18th NHL game.</p>
<p>Detroit&#8217;s Anthony Mantha hit the post on a breakaway with just under four minutes remaining in the third, but the Red Wings didn&#8217;t end up needing the insurance goal.</p>
<p>Florida opened the scoring on the power play. Wennberg was left alone in front and had time to stickhandle a bit. The puck eventually bounced back to him off goalie Jonathan Bernier’s stick, and Wennberg was able to slam it in for his fifth goal of the season.</p>
<p>Nemeth tied it in the following period, beating Bobrovsky to the glove side with a wrist shot from the left circle.</p>
<p>It was the first regulation loss on the road for the Panthers this season. They&#8217;d been 6-0-1.</p>
<p>Bernier made 38 saves.</p>
<p>NOTES: The Red Wings assigned D Alex Biega to the taxi squad. &#8230; There was a moment of silence before the game after the death of Sergei Tchekmarev, a longtime team masseur for the Red Wings. &#8230; Detroit went 0 for 2 on the power play, its 12th straight game without scoring with the man advantage.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Host the Dallas Stars on Monday night.</p>
<p>Red Wings: Host the Nashville Predators on Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868471</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Patric Hornqvist scores twice, Panthers rout Red Wings 7-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/patric-hornqvist-scores-twice-panthers-rout-red-wings-7-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 04:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DETROIT (AP) — Patric Hornqvist scored in the first and third periods to help the Florida Panthers start and finish strong in a 7-2 victory over the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DETROIT (AP) — <a href="https://twitter.com/FlaPanthers/status/1362950634367045632">Patric Hornqvist </a>scored in the first and third periods to help the Florida Panthers start and finish strong in a 7-2 victory over the the Detroit Red Wings on Friday night.</p>
<p>Juho Lammikko and MacKenzie Weegar had goals on consecutive shots in the opening period, and Hornqvist made it 3-0 in a four-shot stretch that doomed a Detroit team averaging an NHL-low 1.9 goals a game.</p>
<p>“We were all over them in the first period and we were rewarded,&#8221; Hornqvist said. “We were on top of them all night.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Chris Driedger made 30 saves, including <a href="https://twitter.com/FlaPanthers/status/1362937179689930752">a spectacular stop</a> by lunging with his stick to deny Darren Helm in the second period.</p>
<p>“I don’t really know what happened I was so out of position,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>The Central Division-leading Panthers, set to face Detroit again Saturday night, matched a season high with three straight victories, giving them 11 wins in 15 games.</p>
<p>“When we’re playing the right way, we’re as good as anyone and that’s what we’re showing right now,&#8221; Hornqvist said.</p>
<p>Detroit’s Thomas Greiss gave up four goals and stopped nine shots in the first period. Jonathan Bernier replaced Greiss and had 23 saves over the last two periods for the Red Wings, who matched a season high by allowing seven goals.</p>
<p>After winning an NHL-low 17 games last season, the Red Wings are among the league&#8217;s worst teams with 15 losses in 19 games.</p>
<p>“On the road, I thought we figured out what we needed to do to have success, but this wasn’t it,&#8221; Detroit center Frans Nielsen said. “This was unacceptable.”</p>
<p>When the Red Wings briefly had positive moments Friday night, they didn&#8217;t last long.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov restored the Panthers&#8217; three-goal cushion a little more than a minute after Detroit’s Bobby Ryan scored late in the first period.</p>
<p>Valtteri Filppula was credited with a goal for the Red Wings on a shot that went off Florida forward Anthony Duclair&#8217;s stick, separating the teams by three goals for the third time in the game.</p>
<p>“On the ice, I told (Driedger), `My bad,’” Duclair recalled and added his postgame joke. “After the game, I told him he should’ve saved that.”</p>
<p>Florida quickly responded again with Hornqvist scoring a few minutes later.</p>
<p>“It’s a 3-1 game with a lot of hockey left, so the worst thing we could do was to give up a goal right away,&#8221; Nielsen said.</p>
<p>Duclair made up for redirecting a shot into his own net with a goal midway through the third to put the Panthers ahead 7-2.</p>
<p>“We were getting beat up the ice and beaten in the corners of our own end,&#8221; Nielsen said.</p>
<p>FAVORABLE SCHEDULE</p>
<p>Five of Florida&#8217;s 15 games have been against the lowly Red Wings, who have become even more of a common opponent because the Panthers have had series canceled because of COVID-19 issues. The Panthers have won four of five in the eight-game series.</p>
<p>Last month, the Panthers won at Detroit 3-2 on consecutive days. Florida also beat the Red Wings by one goal at home, but also allowed them to earn a rare win and end an eight-game losing streak earlier this month.</p>
<p>The Panthers have won six straight on the road against the Red Wings and 11 of last 13 games overall against them.</p>
<p>HOT START</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Jonathan Huberdeau has 22 points, the most by a player in franchise history through 15 games.</p>
<p>TAKE A SEAT</p>
<p>Greiss was benched after giving up four goals on 13 shots in the first period. Bernier was in net over the final two periods and was 21.5 seconds away from holding the Panthers scoreless in the second period, but Ekblad scored to put them ahead 5-1. He gave up two more goals in the third.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868126</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huberdeau scores in OT, lifts Panthers past Hurricanes 4-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/huberdeau-scores-in-ot-lifts-panthers-past-hurricanes-4-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 02:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Jonathan Huberdeau scored his second goal of the game with 2:31 remaining in overtime as the Florida Panthers rallied to beat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Jonathan Huberdeau scored his second goal of the game with 2:31 remaining in overtime as the Florida Panthers rallied to beat the Carolina Hurricanes 4-3 on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Huberdeau outraced Carolina players for a breakaway on the winning goal. He opened the scoring for Florida and added an assist before his seventh goal of the season sealed the win. Alex Wenneberg and Juho Lammikko also scored for the Panthers.</p>
<p>“Sticking with it when we were down 2-0, when it looked like it completely got away from us,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. “(This) is one of those games that we’ll remember.”</p>
<p>Jordan Staal and Sebastian Aho scored in the first period and Vincent Trocheck added a goal in the third for the Hurricanes, who lost for the first time in five home games.</p>
<p>“Probably got fortunate to even get a point out of it,” Hurricanes coach Rod Brind’Amour said. “… That second half of the game we just didn’t get to work. We just let the other team back in.”</p>
<p>Panthers goalie Chris Driedger made 32 saves. Carolina’s Alex Nedeljkovic stopped 33 shots.</p>
<p>Lammikko scored his first career goal with 7:54 remaining in regulation, giving Florida its first lead. Just 1:33 later, the Hurricanes tied the game on Trocheck’s goal against his former team.</p>
<p>The Panthers improved to 5-0-1 in road games, extending their best start in away games in franchise history. Two nights earlier, they handed the Tampa Bay Lightning their first home loss.</p>
<p>Staal’s first-period goal was his fifth score in four games. Twenty-two seconds later, Aho deflected in a pass from Brett Pesce.</p>
<p>The Panthers converted on a power play in the second period when Huberdeau scored with a shot from the left side. Then, Huberdeau’s pass set up Wenneberg’s tying goal early in the third period.</p>
<p>“That pass was the highlight for me,” Quenneville said. “I told him it has been a long time since I’ve seen something that special.”</p>
<p>Huberdeau wasn’t finished. He made the Hurricanes pay for a breakdown on the game’s final sequence.</p>
<p>“It was just a continuation of our second and third (periods),” Staal said, referring to sloppy play.</p>
<p>VIEW FROM THE TOP</p>
<p>The Panthers hold first place in the Central Division a quarter of the way through the schedule.</p>
<p>“Obviously, it’s a lot more fun when you win,” Huberdeau said. “We’re playing as a team and everyone is having fun.”</p>
<p>Widespread contributions are what makes it encouraging for Quenneville.</p>
<p>“I think internally there’s expectations that are growing,” he said. “A different night, it could be someone else doing it. We’re just not relying on one line or one guy.”</p>
<p>FAMILIAR FACES</p>
<p>The Panthers had defenseman Gustav Forsling back in the lineup after a nine-game absence with an upper-body injury.</p>
<p>He was a member of the Carolina organization from June 2019 until claimed off waivers on Jan. 9.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes acquired Trocheck from the Panthers in a Feb. 24, 2020, trade. This was his first appearance against his former team.</p>
<p>“He has been good the whole year,” Brind’Amour said. “So it’s not just tonight.”</p>
<p>GOOD TO SEE YA</p>
<p>The game was the first meeting of the season between the Panthers and Hurricanes because last month’s two-game set, which was to include Carolina’s home opener, was postponed due to the Hurricanes’ coronavirus issues.</p>
<p>The game was considered a make-up for one of those contests.</p>
<p>Carolina’s 35 wins against the Panthers at PNC Arena are its most against any opponent in the building. The Hurricanes entered the game 9-2-1 in the series since 2016-17.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Florida goes to Detroit for games Friday and Saturday.</p>
<p>Hurricanes: Carolina hosts the Chicago Blackhawks on Friday night to open a two-game set on consecutive nights.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866811</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers close in on Central-leading Lightning with 6-4 win</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-close-in-on-central-leading-lightning-with-6-4-win/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 04:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=865677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Jonathan Huberdeau scored and led a balanced attack that included goals from six players, and the Florida Panthers gained on Central...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Jonathan Huberdeau scored and led a balanced attack that included goals from six players, and the Florida Panthers gained on Central Division-leading Tampa Bay with a 6-4 victory over the Lightning on Monday night.</p>
<p>Florida won two of the three games between the teams in a five-day span and pulled within a point of the Lightning in the standings.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov, Anton Stralman, Owen Tipppett, Anthony Duclair and Frank Vatrano also scored for Florida, which recorded its first win in Tampa Bay since March 26. 2016, a span of eight games.</p>
<p>“Going into the season and the amount of games you’re playing against each other. It’s going to be a tight race throughout,’’ Stralman said. “It’s a good response for our team and taking four points out of six. It’s big for our team.’’</p>
<p>Chris Driedger finished with 27 saves and Florida improved to 4-0 in games following a loss this season.</p>
<p>Alex Volkov scored twice for Tampa Bay, which had its six-game home winning streak halted. Steven Stamkos and Tyler Johnson also scored for the Lightning. Curtis McElhinney made 15 saves in his second start of the season.</p>
<p>Stamkos, back in the lineup after missing the two previous games, scored his team-leading eight of the season to put Tampa Bay in front at 6:24 of the first period. Ondrej Palat won the puck below the goal line and found Erik Cernak in the slot. Cernak fed a pass to Stamkos, who dropped to a knee for a one-timer.</p>
<p>The lead didn’t last long as Huberdeau pulled the Panthers even 1:32 later. McElhinney left the crease to play the puck as it moved around the boards, but it slowed down coming around the bench and McElhinney was beaten to the puck by Patric Hornqvist, who fed Huberdeau alone in front of the vacated net for his fifth of the season.</p>
<p>The Panthers started to pull away in the second period with three goals in 5:24.</p>
<p>Tippett finished off a cross-ice pass from Eetu Luostarinen after a turnover by Jan Rutta at 4:59. Vatrano converted a penalty shot at 8:39 to give him goals in three consecutive games before Duclair finished a wrap around at 10:23 for a 4-1 lead.</p>
<p>“They didn’t do anything, really, to us,’’ Lightning head coach Jon Cooper said. “It was all self-inflicted. Like the first one, self-inflicted. The second one, self-inflicted. We had full control of the puck and we just hand it over to them. The third and fourth one, we turned it over at the blue line, self-inflicted. Terrible.’’</p>
<p>Volkov cut the deficit to two goals with a wrist shot from the left dot at 11:42, but Barkov answered that 54 seconds later with his fifth of the season and 420th career point, passing Olli Jokinen for second place on the Panthers’ all-time scoring list.</p>
<p>The Lightning pulled within one again on goals by Volkov and Johnson in a 48-second span. Volkov netted his second of the game after Pat Maroon’s backhander glanced off Volkov’s stick at 15:50, and Johnson finished off a Joseph pass on a 2-on-1 with 3:22 left in the second period.</p>
<p>Stralman scored his first of the season 59 seconds into the third period to regain a two-goal lead for Florida.</p>
<p>“They had all the momentum,’’ Florida head coach Joel Quenneville said. “We stabilized it a little with that (penalty) kill in the third. Huge goal (from Stralman), down Main Street with a great shot. We got our composure back.’’</p>
<p>CENTER OUT: Florida will be without C Noel Acciari for the full road trip after head coach Joel Quenneville announced Acciari suffered an undisclosed upper-body injury. Acciari, who scored 20 goals in 66 games last season, has yet to register a point through 12 games this season.</p>
<p>ROSTER SHUFFLING: With Lightning C Anthony Cirelli out week to week, Tampa Bay recalled forwards Alex Barre-Boulet and Ross Colton from Syracuse of the American Hockey League and assigned them to the taxi squad. In addition, G Spencer Martin was transferred from the taxi squad to Syracuse, while D Cal Foote was transferred from the active roster to the taxi squad.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: At Carolina Hurricanes on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Tampa Bay: At Dallas Stars on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">865677</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tyler Johnson scores twice, Lightning rout Panthers 6-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tyler-johnson-scores-twice-lightning-rout-panthers-6-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 05:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=864787</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Tyler Johnson scored two of Tampa Bay&#8217;s four goals in the second period and the Lightning avenged a loss to Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Tyler Johnson scored two of Tampa Bay&#8217;s four goals in the second period and the Lightning avenged a loss to Florida earlier in the week with a 6-1 victory over the Panthers on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Ondrej Palat, Mathieu Joseph and Barclay Goodrow scored, Alexander Volkov added his first NHL goal and the Lightning strengthened their hold on first place in the Central Division with a 3-1-0 road trip.</p>
<p>The Lightning (10-2-1) killed off four Florida power plays on the way to the win.</p>
<p>“I like everything,&#8221; said Tampa Bay coach Jon Cooper. &#8220;It was a little humbling experience the other night. Guys did an exceptional job. The guys who stepped in delivered.”</p>
<p>The rematch featured another matchup between Tampa Bay’s Andrei Vasilevskiy and Florida’s Sergei Bobrovsky, who started two nights earlier in the Panthers’ 5-2 victory.</p>
<p>Vasilevskiy stopped 33 shots and ran his record to 9-2-1. A third-period goal by Frank Vatrano spoiled his shutout bid.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s a big goalie, and when he gets in that rhythm and groove he’s as good as there is in the game,&#8221; Florida coach Joel Quenneville said. “You’ve got to find a way to get traffic in front of him &#8230; get in his face a little bit. We were a little on the outside today.”</p>
<p>Bobrovsky made 22 saves and fell to 5-1-1.</p>
<p>The Lightning owned the NHL’s top-ranked road power play entering the game and struck at 4:11 of the second on their second man advantage with Palat’s blast from the right circle in the second period.</p>
<p>The tempo picked up from there, with Tampa Bay withstanding a strong push by the Panthers and turning to its defense to push the lead to 2-0 after Joseph blocked a shot near the blue line and scored on a breakaway.</p>
<p>Gemel Smith’s steal along the boards resulted in Johnson’s first goal. Johnson backhanded in a rebound as the Lightning built a 4-0 lead.</p>
<p>“It definitely wasn’t our best effort (Thursday),&#8221; Johnson said. &#8220;We talked about it. The biggest thing was effort, working hard and staying within our structure.”</p>
<p>MacKenzie Weegar said the Panthers just didn&#8217;t show up in the finale of the two-game home series.</p>
<p>“They’ve got a lot of skill up front, a lot of speed,&#8221; the defenseman said. &#8220;(But) we just didn’t come to compete. It was on us tonight.”</p>
<p>91 MOVES</p>
<p>In Thursday’s first meeting, the Panthers and Lightning played without first-line forwards Anthony Duclair and Steven Stamkos, respectively, who both wear No. 91 and were added to the NHL’s COVID-19 list.</p>
<p>However, Duclair, who has been held without a goal but has six assists, returned to the Panthers’ lineup Saturday. Stamkos was added to the list Friday and missed his second consecutive game.</p>
<p>Tampa Bay also played without second-line center Anthony Cirelli (upper body). The club announced he was week to week and would miss significant time after being injured in the third period on Thursday.</p>
<p>MOMENT OF SILENCE</p>
<p>Before the anthem, the Panthers organization honored the 17 lives lost in the 2018 school shooting at nearby Stoneman Douglas High School in Parkland on Valentine’s Day.</p>
<p>In the darkened arena, fans displayed the lights on their phones as the 17 names scrolled on the big screen above center ice.</p>
<p>SATURDAY SPECIAL</p>
<p>The Panthers sported their new reverse retro jerseys for the first time. They will be a regularl sight during Saturdays at home. The blue-themed ensemble features their original leaping panther logo and red trim.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The intra-state rivals meet for the third consecutive time on Monday night at Tampa’s Amalie Arena.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">864787</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers beat Lightning 5-2 to open 2-game set</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-beat-lightning-5-2-to-open-2-game-set/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 02:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=863642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad and Alex Wennberg each had a goal and an assist and the Florida Panthers beat the Tampa Bay Lightning...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Aaron Ekblad and Alex Wennberg each had a goal and an assist and the Florida Panthers beat the Tampa Bay Lightning 5-2 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Frank Vatrano, Carter Verhaeghe and Brett Connolly also scored, and Sergei Bobrovsky made 19 saves.</p>
<p>Braden Point scored twice for Tampa Bay, and Andrei Vasilevskiy made 24 saves. The Lighting had won six straight.</p>
<p>The teams will meet again Saturday night in Sunrise.</p>
<p>With captain Steven Stamkos out of the lineup with a lower-body injury, Tampa Bay lacked its usual firepower while Florida was highly effective in its offensive end.</p>
<p>The Panthers opened the scoring midway through the first period when Vatrano took a feed from Owen Tippett behind the net and put a one-timer past Vasilevskiy. Wennberg made it 2-0 at 8:31 of the second, with Jonathan Huberdeau getting his 300th NHL assist on the play.</p>
<p>Point cut it to 2-1 on a power play at 10:55 of the second, and Ekblad and Verhaeghe countered quickly with goals in a 2:01 span in the period. Point scored again on a power play 54 seconds into the third.</p>
<p>Connolly scored into an empty net.</p>
<p>STAMKOS OUT</p>
<p>Stamkos, who is listed as day to day, had played in all 11 games for Tampa Bay, logging seven goals and seven assists. He was also key on the Lightning’s power-play unit having scored four times.</p>
<p>The Tampa Bay captain did not play the final 5:26 of a 6-1 victory at Nashville on Tuesday nihht. In that contest, he scored two goals and added an assist.</p>
<p>REUNION TIME</p>
<p>Verhaeghe, who won the Stanley Cup as a rookie with Tampa Bay last season, agreed to a two-year contract with Florida on Oct. 9 and has scored nine points (six goals, three assists) in 10 games.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">863642</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bobrovsky shines as Panthers edge Red Wings 2-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/bobrovsky-shines-as-panthers-edge-red-wings-2-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=862859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Sergei Bobrovsky made 31 saves and Patric Hornqvist was credited with the eventual winning goal when a teammate’s shot bounced off...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Sergei Bobrovsky made 31 saves and Patric Hornqvist was credited with the eventual winning goal when a teammate’s shot bounced off his shoulder and into the net as the Florida Panthers beat the Detroit Red Wings 2-1 on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Bobrovsky improved to 4-0-1 this season. Alex Wennberg also scored for the Panthers.</p>
<p>Hornqvist’s winner and sixth goal of the season came on a power play when a shot by Aaron Ekblad deflected off his shoulder and over the head of Thomas Greiss at 8:04 of the second period, making the score 2-1. Hornqvist also had an assist.</p>
<p>“It always hurts a little less when the puck goes in,” Hornqvist said. “All 20 guys out there were really good. It felt like we had control of the puck the whole night. It was a close game, but it didn’t feel like that.”</p>
<p>Bobrovsky allowed an early goal but was able to stop the Red Wings the rest of the way.</p>
<p>“I was feeling good. It was nice to be back, to play, to see the puck,” Bobrovsky said. “I wanted to go out and keep up my pace and have a higher intensity. It was a good win for us.”</p>
<p>Filip Zadina scored for the Red Wings.</p>
<p>Greiss stopped 20 shots in his eighth straight appearance.</p>
<p>The Panthers are 10-1-1 over their last 12 games against Detroit. The Red Wings have lost nine of 10.</p>
<p>“We have to find ways to win these games,” coach Jeff Blashill said. “We had some chances on the power play, but we need to score.”</p>
<p>Zadina put the Red Wings ahead 1-0 at the 3:31 mark of the first.</p>
<p>“We started good, won the battles, and scored the goal and felt pretty good,” Zadina said. “We need to score more than one goal.”</p>
<p>Dylan Larkin’s assist on Zadina’s goal, his first point in four games, gives him 20 points (nine goals, 11 assists) in 22 games against the Panthers.</p>
<p>“We need results and we need them now with the hole we’ve dug for ourselves,” Larkin said. “We just couldn’t get it by Bobrovsky.”</p>
<p>Huberdeau’s assist on the goal by Wennberg was his 450th NHL point.</p>
<p>BACK ON THE ICE</p>
<p>Red Wings F Anthony Mantha returned after being a healthy scratch Sunday.</p>
<p>Panthers F Ryan Lomberg played for the first time since opening night.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>The Panthers allow up to 5,000 fans. Attendance was 3.477.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Panthers host the Tampa Bay Lightning on Thursday.</p>
<p>The Red Wings visit the Nashville Predators on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">862859</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smith, Red Wings win for 1st time in 9 games, beat Panthers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/smith-red-wings-win-for-1st-time-in-9-games-beat-panthers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 01:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=860381</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Givani Smith had a goal and an assist as Detroit Red Wings won for the first time in nine games, beating...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Givani Smith had a goal and an assist as Detroit Red Wings won for the first time in nine games, beating the Florida Panthers 4-1 on Sunday.</p>
<p>Marc Staal scored for the first time with Detroit, Robby Fabbri and Vladislav Namestnikov added goals and Troy Stecher had two assists. Goaltender Thomas Greiss stopped 36 shots.</p>
<p>“Losing is never fun. We made some steps last game against Tampa that we carried over into tonight right off the hop and I think the biggest thing was we kept it going for 60 minutes,&#8221; Detroit coach Jeff Blashill said. “That’s the biggest thing. That’s how we’re going to win games and beat teams is to outwork them, outwill them and we proved that tonight.”</p>
<p>Greiss, who moved to 1-7-2, stopped a three-on-one Florida break with the Red Wings ahead 2-1 in the third period.</p>
<p>“He’s done that a lot this year &#8230; we just haven’t been able to capitalize off a great save like that, sort of nice to get one tonight,&#8221; Blashill said.</p>
<p>Alex Wennberg scored for the Panthers. Florida (6-1-2) became the last NHL team to lose in regulation.</p>
<p>Acquired from the New York Rangers in a trade last September after a 13-year career, Staal put Detroit up 1-0 at 2:58 of the second period with his backhander in close. Sam Gagner notched his first assist with the Red Wings on the goal.</p>
<p>Blashill made the decision to scratch Anthony Mantha, but Smith stepped up with a big goal.</p>
<p>Bobby Ryan’s steal near goaltender Chris Driedger set up Smith’s score at 17:02 for a 2-0 lead.</p>
<p>“The only thing I can really do is every time I’m in the lineup, just to work my hardest, work my best and hopefully it can pay off in the long run,&#8221; Smith said.</p>
<p>Trailing to begin the third period for the first time this season, the Panthers got within a goal at 2:09 when Wennberg scored his first for Florida on a deflection.</p>
<p>“(It was good) to get this first one off and build off that and get some confidence,&#8221; said Wennberg, a free-agent acquisition who previously played for Columbus.</p>
<p>Fabbri’s second goal at 9:11 regained Detroit’s two-goal lead.</p>
<p>Greiss&#8217; big stop on the three-on-one was a turning point in the game.</p>
<p>“We had a three-on-one with all the right guys on the ice with it, and the next thing you know it’s 3-1 instead of 2-2,” Florida coach Joel Quenneville said.</p>
<p>FLORIDA FIRST</p>
<p>Newcomer Mason Marchment was recalled from the taxi squad and made his debut for the Panthers by registering 7:56 of ice time and being minus-1.</p>
<p>After getting into four games for the Toronto Maple Leafs last season, Marchment played left wing on the fourth line with right wing Noel Acciari and center Juho Lammikko.</p>
<p>BIG HITS</p>
<p>The aggressive play was intense over the first 20 minutes, and Florida’s Radko Gudas delivered the biggest on Luke Glendening, who stayed down on the ice for a couple of minutes along the side boards.</p>
<p>The training staff assisted Glendening off the ice and into the dressing room after the hard contact, and the forward didn’t return.</p>
<p>ON THE MEND</p>
<p>Red Wings forward Tyler Bertuzzi was injured when Florida visited Detroit last week and is expected to miss a few more games.</p>
<p>The left wing suffered an upper-body injury when the teams met last Saturday and didn’t play the next day’s contest. Sunday marked his fourth straight game out of the club’s lineup.</p>
<p>NUMBERS GAME</p>
<p>The Panthers drew 3,706 fans for the Super Bowl Sunday matinee contest.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The two clubs conclude their two-game series on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">860381</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Florida_Panthers_logo.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida_Panthers_logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Forsberg shines as Predators beat Panthers 6-5 in overtime</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/forsberg-shines-as-predators-beat-panthers-6-5-in-overtime/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=857629</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Filip Forsberg scored in regulation and overtime, and the Nashville Predators beat the Florida Panthers 6-5 on Thursday night. Forsberg also...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Filip Forsberg scored in regulation and overtime, and the Nashville Predators beat the Florida Panthers 6-5 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Forsberg also had three assists as Nashville stopped a two-game slide. Matt Duchene scored twice, and Roman Josi and Calle Jarnkrok had the other goals for the Predators.</p>
<p>Nashville was down 5-3 before Josi scored with 2:06 left in the third. Duchene then tied it with his second of the season with 56.8 seconds left in regulation.</p>
<p>Forsberg skated in on a breakaway in overtime and beat Sergei Bobrovsky through the goaltender’s legs at 4:00. Bobrovsky finished with 35 saves.</p>
<p>“It was obviously a great comeback,” Forsberg said. “We’re working really hard. Obviously had to battle back in the third and we did that.”</p>
<p>Juuse Saros started for Nashville and allowed five goals on 24 shots. Pekka Rinne finished the game, making 12 saves.</p>
<p>“We were going to drive that third period the way that we wanted to play and it’s nice to see you guys do it and get rewarded,” coach John Hynes said. “For (Rinne) to come in and play the way he played, he held the fort for us. And it allowed us to be able to get up and get going and get moving. So I think that’s the big reason why we found the way to win.”</p>
<p>Jonathan Huberdeau had three goals and two assists for the Panthers. It was his first career hat trick.</p>
<p>Huberdeau’s second goal, scored in the first period, was originally given to Markus Nutivaara, then to Patric Hornqvist, before finally being credited to Huberdeau between the second and third period.</p>
<p>“I’m happy to get it out of the way, first one. But it would have been just nice to get a win tonight,” Huberdeau said. “I think we should’ve won that one, a tough one to lose. We’re back it tomorrow, but a tough one tonight.”</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov had a goal and an assist. He moved into second place in Panthers franchise history with his 158th goal, passing Scott Mellanby.</p>
<p>The Panthers unsuccessfully challenged Josi’s goal for a high stick, and that forced them into a penalty situation.</p>
<p>“Definitely disappointed the way things transpired,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said.</p>
<p>The Panthers (6-0-2) have not lost a game in regulation this season. They are the only remaining team in the NHL without a regulation loss.</p>
<p>Aaron Ekblad also scored for the Panthers in the opener of a six-game homestand.</p>
<p>SHOWING HIS MOVES</p>
<p>Barkov had a nifty assist on Ekblad’s power-play goal when he slid the puck between the skates of the defender in the left circle before passing to Ekblad in front.</p>
<p>MILESTONE</p>
<p>The 32-year-old Bobrovsky, who has won the Vezina Trophy twice, made his 500th NHL start.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The teams play again on Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">857629</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Surging Panthers hold off reeling Red Wings 3-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/surging-panthers-hold-off-reeling-red-wings-3-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 05:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=852556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DETROIT (AP) — Patric Hornqvist, Aaron Ekblad and Carter Verhaeghe scored and the Florida Panthers held off the Detroit Red Wings for a 3-2 win...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DETROIT (AP) — Patric Hornqvist, Aaron Ekblad and Carter Verhaeghe scored and the Florida Panthers held off the Detroit Red Wings for a 3-2 win Sunday night.</p>
<p>Anthony Mantha scored with 1:48 remaining to pull the Red Wings within a goal after Detroit pulled Thomas Greiss to add an extra skater. Detroit pulled its goaltender again, but couldn&#8217;t get another shot past Chris Driedger to extend the game.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/FOXPanthers/status/1356017651793989639">Hornqvist</a> pulled Florida into a 1-all tie on a power play early in the second. Ekblad took advantage of having an extra skater and with Hornqvist providing a distracting screen when his one-timer from the top of the left circle got past Greiss’ glove with 4:56 left in the second period.</p>
<p>Verhaeghe gave the Panthers a two-goal lead midway through the third, and they ended up needing the cushion when Detroit made a late charge.</p>
<p>Driedger finished with 32 saves for the Panthers, whose only loss this season was in a shootout.</p>
<p>“I think there’s a new vibe around here,” coach Joel Quenneville said. “Getting off to a good start enhances that attitude.”</p>
<p>Greiss stopped 27 shots for the Red Wings, who have dropped six straight.</p>
<p>Dylan Larkin scored to put the Red Wings ahead early in the game with a backhander after skating in front of Driedger on a goal set up by a short, slick pass from Givani Smith. Earlier in the day, Smith was recalled from the taxi squad because forward Tyler Bertuzzi is out indefinitely with an upper-body injury.</p>
<p>“We had a great start, but we didn’t generate enough in the second period and it killed our momentum,&#8221; Larkin said.</p>
<p>Both teams failed to take advantage of two power plays in the opening period as Detroit outshot Florida 13-6. The Panthers outshot the Red Wings 17-9 in the second period as they took control.</p>
<p>On Saturday night, Florida defeated Detroit 3-2 in overtime when Aleksi Heponiemi scored 2:15 into the extra period in his NHL debut.</p>
<p>OPPOSITE DIRECTIONS</p>
<p>Florida is 5-0-1, losing in a shootout Thursday night at Columbus, and its six-game, season-opening point streak is the second longest in franchise history. The 1996-97 team opened the season with a 12-game point streak.</p>
<p>“It feels like a fresh start for me and all of the guys in the room and we’re only going to get better,” Florida captain Aleksander Barkov said.</p>
<p>Detroit has lost six in a row after a 2-2 start, which briefly generated some optimism about a team that was easily the NHL&#8217;s worst last season.</p>
<p>SCORING PUNCH</p>
<p>Larkin’s goal gave him six points in seven games. He has provided desperately needed scoring for an offensively challenged team that was without Bertuzzi, who leads the team with five goals.</p>
<p>Larkin, the team&#8217;s captain, has been playing through an undisclosed injury since he was hurt last week against Dallas.</p>
<p>“I feel like I can still help us win, so I’m going to be out there,&#8221; he said. “If that changes, I’ll have to make a decision.&#8221;</p>
<p>HELPERS</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Jonathan Huberdeau and Keith Yandle each had an assist on Ekblad&#8217;s and Hornqvist&#8217;s goals.</p>
<p>PANDEMIC PLAY</p>
<p>The Red Wings were without Adam Erne, Robby Fabbri, Sam Gagner, Jon Merrill and Filip Zadina due to the NHL&#8217;s COVID-19 protocols, while Florida didn&#8217;t have anyone on the league&#8217;s list.</p>
<p>“I don’t know the exact dates, but we should have most of them available for Wednesday,&#8221; Detroit coach Jeff Blashill said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida returns home for a relative break before hosting Nashville on Thursday night, the start of a six-game, 10-day homestand that also includes games against Detroit and Tampa Bay.</p>
<p>The Red Wings play the Lighting on the road Wednesday night.</p>
<p>“This is going to be a great challenge on Wednesday against the Stanley Cup champions, but we sat for 11 months,&#8221; Blashill said. “We’re excited about these challenges.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">852556</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texier&#8217;s shootout goal lifts Blue Jackets over Panthers 3-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/texiers-shootout-goal-lifts-blue-jackets-over-panthers-3-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 05:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=849186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Alexandre Texier slickly beat Chris Driedger five-hole in the fourth round of a shootout to lift the Columbus Blue Jackets over the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Alexandre Texier <a href="https://twitter.com/NHL/status/1354987572267724804">slickly beat Chris Driedger five-hole</a> in the fourth round of a shootout to lift the Columbus Blue Jackets over the Florida Panthers 3-2 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Texier skated slowly in on Chris Driedger and poked the puck between his pads with the back of his stick. Columbus&#8217; Elvis Merzlikins sealed it by denying Patric Hornqvist, who scored the winning goal in a shootout between the teams Tuesday night.</p>
<p>“I mean, it’s like gambling,&#8221; said Merzlikins, who improved to 2-1-1. “Either you’re lucky or you’re not, so tonight luck was on my side, so I&#8217;m happy about that. I like (shootouts) when I win. When I lose, I hate them.”</p>
<p>Besides getting the shootout winner, Texier has started strong with four goals and two assists in the first eight games.</p>
<p>“Probably our most consistent guy,” coach John Tortorella said. “He turns one over and it costs us a goal (in the second period). I’m glad he got an opportunity to redeem himself. It was a great goal (in the shootout).”</p>
<p>Florida&#8217;s Eetu Luostarinen <a href="https://www.nhl.com/video/luostarinen-nets-tying-goal/t-320685290/c-7357327">tied it in the third period</a>, and Carter Verhaeghe also had a goal for the Panthers. Driedger finished with 29 saves.</p>
<p>Mikko Koivu and Max Domi scored and Merzlikins had 33 saves as Columbus dealt the Panthers their first loss in four games this season. Columbus rebounded after giving up a tying goal with 3 seconds left in regulation Tuesday night and then losing the shootout in the fifth round.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/BlueJacketsNHL/status/1354952306316472320">Koivu got his first goal as a Blue Jacket</a> late in the first period. Eric Robinson got to the loose puck behind the net, brought it around and set up Koivu with a pass across the crease.</p>
<p>Verhaeghe took the puck away from Texier in Florida&#8217;s zone late in the second and ended up poking it in from the doorstep past the glove of a falling Merzlikins.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nhl.com/video/domis-first-with-blue-jackets/t-320685290/c-7357148">Domi got his first goal of the season</a> — also his first as a Blue Jacket — when he beat Driedger on a power play at 6:19 of the third period. The Panthers tied it again at 12:56 when Luostarinen tapped in a rebound that had trickled into the blue paint.</p>
<p>The Blue Jackets showed more jump after managing just 22 shots in the first game against Florida.</p>
<p>“That was a gritty effort there,&#8221; Dreidger said. &#8220;They came out harder than they did (Tuesday). They definitely upped their game.”</p>
<p>SAVE YOUR ENERGY</p>
<p>Tortorella said that it’s been difficult to work on problem areas because with the way the games are bunched together in the 54-game schedule, he can’t afford to sap the players’ energy with strenuous practices. The coaching staff has to rely mostly on showing video clips in meetings to make adjustments. Consistency has been an issue for the Blue Jackets early, along with a struggling power play.</p>
<p>“We’re trying to stabilize ourselves and not go up and down — one good game and a lousy game,” Tortorella said.</p>
<p>QUOTABLE</p>
<p>“I don’t think we’re walking out of here licking our wounds by any means,” Florida defenseman Aaron Ekblad said. &#8220;But we obviously have to know that we can beat a team like this and know (we) can take the lead in games. But there’s a lot to work on, no doubt.”</p>
<p>ICE CHIPS</p>
<p>Panthers: F Brett Connolly played in his 500th NHL game. &#8230; Verhaeghe has four goals in the last three games and has points in all four of Florida&#8217;s games. &#8230; Longtime Blue Jacket Markus Nutivaara had the secondary assist on Luostarinen&#8217;s goal. &#8230; F Anthony Duclair has five assists in the last three games.</p>
<p>Blue Jackets: Jack Roslovic, who grew up in Columbus rooting for the Blue Jackets, made his debut with the team after coming in the trade with Winnipeg for Pierre-Luc Dubois. &#8230; Koivu, who is playing his first season in Columbus after 15 in Minnesota, has points in the last two games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Move on to Detroit for a two-game set on Saturday and Sunday before heading home for a string of six.</p>
<p>Blue Jackets: Play at Chicago on Friday and Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">849186</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hornqvist&#8217;s shootout goal lifts Panthers over Blue Jackets</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hornqvists-shootout-goal-lifts-panthers-over-blue-jackets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 04:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=846466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Patric Hornqvist scored the tying goal with 3 seconds left in regulation and had the game winner in a shootout as...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Patric Hornqvist scored the tying goal with 3 seconds left in regulation and had the game winner in a shootout as the Florida Panthers beat the Columbus Blue Jackets 4-3 on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Hornqvist beat Joonas Korpisalo in the fifth round of the shootout to end it after Columbus&#8217; Mikhail Grigorenko&#8217;s try went into the pads of Panthers&#8217; stopper Sergei Bobrovsky.</p>
<p>Hornqvist, the 14-year NHL veteran who joined the Panthers after six seasons with Pittsburgh, had tapped in the tiebreaker from the doorstep late during a 6-on-5 scramble after the Panthers had played from behind for most of the third period.</p>
<p>The Panthers stayed unbeaten in their third game of the season after having two series canceled because of COVID-19 issues with the other teams.</p>
<p>“Our start has been really good,” said Hornqvist, who has four goals and an assist. “We won the first two home games with the little ups and downs, and then today we play our best hockey so far. We were down the whole game and we find a way to win. So just keep going, keep coming to the rink happy and try to get better.”</p>
<p>Carter Verhaeghe and Aleksander Barkov also scored in regulation, and Bobrovsky, the former Blue Jacket, stopped 19 shots for Florida.</p>
<p>Kevin Stenlund, Alexandre Texier and Cam Atkinson scored, and Joonas Korpisalo — formerly Bobrovsky&#8217;s backup — had 28 saves.</p>
<p>The Panthers won for just the second time in their last 11 games against Columbus. They hadn’t prevailed at Nationwide Arena since 2007.</p>
<p>“From start to finish we deserved that win tonight,” Florida coach Joel Quenneville said. “We did a lot of great things. I liked our pace; I liked their purpose.”</p>
<p>The Blue Jackets weren&#8217;t sharp offensively in the first two periods, but scored on their first two shots on goal. They had just one more shot in the entire first period, and six in the second but managed to stay in the game and go ahead early in the third on a short-handed breakaway goal by Atkinson.</p>
<p>“Good teams find a way to win, even when you’re not playing your best,” Columbus captain Nick Foligno said. “We had a chance to win it tonight and we didn’t. That’s what’s disappointing.”</p>
<p>Columbus coach John Tortorella put it this way: “(We&#8217;ll) take the point and sprint out of the building.”</p>
<p>NEW FACES IN COLUMBUS</p>
<p>A blockbuster trade for Columbus last weekend sent unhappy Pierre Luc-Dubois to Winnipeg for Patrik Laine and Jack Roslovic. Laine is still trying to get visa issues worked out, and Roslovic is taking more time to get into game shape. He could be in the lineup Thursday. Koivu, a center who signed a one-year contract with Columbus after 15 seasons with the Minnesota Wild, played for the first time after coming off the COVID list. He missed a shot in the shootout.</p>
<p>SQUEEZE THEM IN</p>
<p>Because of COVID postponements of series against Dallas and Carolina, the Panthers will have to play 53 games in the next 101 days.</p>
<p>NO POWER PLAY</p>
<p>The Blue Jackets were 0 for 6 on the power play, and Foligno was tired of talking about the team&#8217;s inability to capitalize on the man-advantage. They were just 1 for 13 in the first six games.</p>
<p>“That’s on the group to get it done,&#8221; he said. &#8220;We have to come together as a group and know the answer is in there. There’s enough skill on that power play to score goals.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The teams play again Thursday night at Nationwide Arena. The Blue Jackets play five of the next seven games at home. The Panthers have three more on the road before heading back to South Florida.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">846466</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yandle gets 100th NHL goal, Panthers beat Blackhawks 5-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/yandle-gets-100th-nhl-goal-panthers-beat-blackhawks-5-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=834279</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Keith Yandle got his 100th career goal, Chris Driedger made 23 saves and the Florida Panthers beat the Chicago Blackhawks 5-2...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Keith Yandle got his 100th career goal, Chris Driedger made 23 saves and the Florida Panthers beat the Chicago Blackhawks 5-2 on Sunday night.</p>
<p>Eetu Luostarinen scored his first NHL goal, and Aaron Ekblad, Patric Hornqvist, and Jonathan Huberdeau also scored for Florida, which had three goals in the third period to pull away in its delayed opener. The Panthers were to have played Dallas last week twice, games that were called off because of a COVID-19 outbreak among the Stars.</p>
<p>Alex DeBrincat and Connor Murphy scored for the Blackhawks. Collin Delia stopped 24 shots.</p>
<p>As late as last Friday, it seemed as if Yandle was going to be scratched from this game and break his string of playing in 866 consecutive regular-season games, the longest active streak in the NHL. Instead, Yandle scored the goal and extended his streak to 867.</p>
<p>“Getting a win is the biggest thing but my 100th goal, it took a long time to get it and I’m happy,” Yandle said. “For me it was just being ready to go and scoring that goal solidified that work.”</p>
<p>Yandle, whose status on Florida’s active roster was a hot topic during camp, scored in the second period. His goal made it 2-0, and he celebrated wildly afterward — a bit of an uncharacteristic reaction for the veteran defenseman.</p>
<p>“Anytime I score I’m pretty excited and that was a special one,” Yandle said. “Anytime you get to put on a, you know, NHL jersey and be able to represent your team it’s a special thing.”</p>
<p>The move paid off for the Yandle and the Panthers.</p>
<p>“We have an understanding that everyone wants to play and play in certain situations,” coach Joel Quenneville said. “Yans gives us one of the best power plays in the league, and he’s been a significant piece on it.”</p>
<p>The Blackhawks have given up 15 goals in three games.</p>
<p>“I think around our net is a big part of it. I don’t think, right now, we have the right intensity that we need, and that includes all of us on defense,” Chicago&#8217;s Connor Murphy said.</p>
<p>SLOW START</p>
<p>The Blackhawks are 0-3-0, the first time they have not managed even one point in the season’s first three games since 1997-98. This is only the 10th time it has happened in the franchise’s 94 seasons.</p>
<p>“We know we have to be better, we’ve got to get a win. We didn’t give ourselves enough of a chance,” coach Jeremy Colliton said. “No one likes losing but you show who you are by responding.”</p>
<p>STILL GOING</p>
<p>Yandle’s streak of games played is the fourth-longest in NHL history. He trails Doug Jarvis (964 games from 1975 through 1987), Garry Unger (914 games from 1968 through 1979) and Steve Larmer (884 games from 1982 through 1993) on the all-time list. Yandle has not missed a game since March 22, 2009, when he was with the Arizona Coyotes.</p>
<p>KANE MILESTONE</p>
<p>Patrick Kane’s assist on Chicago’s first goal was his 634th career regular-season assist. That tied Neal Broten for eighth place on the NHL’s all-time list among U.S.-born players.</p>
<p>NEW FACES</p>
<p>Of the 22 players on the opening night roster, only 10 played a game with Florida in 2019-20.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>The Panthers were 29th in the 31-team league in attendance last season but are the early leaders this season. They drew 4.147 for the opener; that’s more than the 2,329 that the Arizona Coyotes averaged in their first two home games. The Panthers and Coyotes are the only teams so far to have fans. Dallas, which is scheduled to open Friday, is also planning to have fans.</p>
<p>The Panthers currently allow up to 25% capacity at games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The teams finish their two-game set on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">834279</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Driedger will get the opening-night start in net for Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/driedger-will-get-the-opening-night-start-in-net-for-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 04:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=833609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Chris Driedger will be Florida’s starting goaltender when the Panthers play their delayed season-opener Sunday night against the Chicago Blackhawks. Driedger...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Chris Driedger will be Florida’s starting goaltender when the Panthers play their delayed season-opener Sunday night against the Chicago Blackhawks.</p>
<p>Driedger becomes the 11th opening-night starter in Panthers history. Regular starter Sergei Bobrovsky, who missed most of Panthers’ training camp, is in line to start Florida’s second game against Chicago on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Driedger went 7-2-1 for Florida last season, starting 11 of his 12 appearances.</p>
<p>“He had a great run for us,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. “He did a great job of giving us a chance. The guys got a little bit familiar with him around the net. I thought he had some poise, some patience &#8230; he kept the game very simple.”</p>
<p>Sam Montembeault will be the backup for Florida on Sunday, Quenneville said. Bobrovsky probably could have played Sunday, but the Panthers felt it best to take a cautious approach.</p>
<p>“We’re doing things probably the right way, knowing he does need some time to help with his conditioning as well,” Quenneville said.</p>
<p>The Panthers will become the next-to-last NHL team to open the season. They were supposed to open Thursday and Friday with home games against Dallas, but the Stars could not play after a COVID-19 outbreak among players and coaches.</p>
<p>Dallas is now scheduled to open Friday against Nashville. Some teams will have played five times before the Stars get onto the ice this season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">833609</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers get goalie Sergei Bobrovsky back on the ice</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-get-goalie-sergei-bobrovsky-back-on-the-ice/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 18:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=830401</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — The Florida Panthers got goaltender Sergei Bobrovsky back Wednesday, the two-time Vezina Trophy winner joining the club on the ice for...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — The Florida Panthers got goaltender Sergei Bobrovsky back Wednesday, the two-time Vezina Trophy winner joining the club on the ice for the first time since training camp started.</p>
<p>Bobrovsky had been on the team’s “unfit to play” list since camp began Jan. 3. That term covers anyone who didn’t participate in camp for any reason, whether it was injury or something related to COVID-19 — either a positive test or potential exposure.</p>
<p>Whatever the reason, Bobrovsky is cleared now. He was on the ice well before the morning practice started, going through some drills and technique work, then remained with teammates for the full-squad session.</p>
<p>“It’s great to be back and I felt good,” Bobrovsky said. “Just a few more practices and I’ll be ready to go.”</p>
<p>Bobrovsky spent more than 90 minutes on the ice, and Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said he was surprised to see how much work his goalie was able to handle after the layoff.</p>
<p>“I was impressed that he was able to sustain it,” Quenneville said.</p>
<p>Florida was scheduled to begin the season at home Thursday against Dallas, a two-game set that was postponed because the Stars were dealing with a COVID-19 outbreak — 17 positive cases, forcing them to close their facility.</p>
<p>The Panthers’ opener has since been pushed back to Sunday against Chicago, so Bobrovsky has a few more days to get ready and a determination will be made in part after the team sees how well he feels Thursday. If he can’t go Sunday, Florida would likely have Chris Driedger or Sam Montembeault in net for the opener against the Blackhawks.</p>
<p>“I think he’s more than excited to get the season going and do what he has to do,” Quenneville said. “He’s approached it the right way.”</p>
<p>Bobrovsky struggled last season, his save percentage of .900 being the second worst of his career and his 3.23 goals-against average was three-quarters of a goal higher than his career rate entering the 2019-20 season. He allowed nearly as many goals in 50 games last season (151) as he did in 62 games with Columbus in the previous season (153).</p>
<p>But getting him back with the club was a lift Wednesday, Quenneville said, and Bobrovsky said he was relieved that his wait was finally over.</p>
<p>“It’s definitely not easy, knowing your teammates are working hard and hustling and getting ready and you are kind of out of action,” Bobrovsky said. “It’s not easy but I’m glad that it’s behind me. I’m very excited to be here and it was a great practice.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">830401</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida Panthers host Christmas tree giveaway for military families</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/florida-panthers-host-christmas-tree-giveaway-for-military-families/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=798375</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Florida Panthers hosted a Trees for Troops drive-thru event at the BB&#38;T Center in Sunrise. The team partnered with Twin Peaks and Truly Hard...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Florida Panthers hosted a Trees for Troops drive-thru event at the BB&amp;T Center in Sunrise.</p>
<p>The team partnered with Twin Peaks and Truly Hard Seltzer to distribute 40 Christmas trees to military families, Sunday.</p>
<p>Some attendees said they admire what the Panthers organization does on and off the ice.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m a fan of the Panthers, because of everything that they do for the community and how involved they do get,&#8221; said veteran Lisa Deutch. &#8220;It&#8217;s unbelievable how much it helps.&#8221;</p>
<p>Veterans and their families also received a tree stand, lights, ornaments and a Walmart gift card for the holiday season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">798375</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201213_Panthers_tree_giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0ce21384-7af1-4308-8ec8-0c35fe6aa9a0/11b4bb30-84bd-4916-b9a6-5ed7118560f8/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219913~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0ce21384-7af1-4308-8ec8-0c35fe6aa9a0/11b4bb30-84bd-4916-b9a6-5ed7118560f8/main.mp4*~hmac=34d7b8d196bffb06f648e372389d63653c8b42b937c8b025a4739fbf17618895' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201213_Panthers_tree_giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201213_Panthers_tree_giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201213_Panthers_tree_giveaway</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers hire Peterson, NHL&#8217;s first Black assistant GM</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-hire-peterson-nhls-first-black-assistant-gm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 19:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=781700</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Florida Panthers on Tuesday hired Brett Peterson as an assistant general manager, making him the first Black executive to hold that position in the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Florida Panthers on Tuesday hired Brett Peterson as an assistant general manager, making him the first Black executive to hold that position in the NHL.</p>
<p>Peterson&#8217;s hiring comes days after the nearby Miami Marlins hired Kim Ng as the first female GM in Major League Baseball. The NFL&#8217;s Miami Dolphins have a Black GM, Chris Grier, and coach, Brian Flores.</p>
<p>“I don’t think they’re just going out to get people — I think they’ve identified people that are good at what they do and hard-working and excited,” Peterson said on a conference call with reporters. “It just so happens to be that a couple of us are African-American and one of us is a woman and that shouldn’t matter. We want the best candidates.”</p>
<p>Among its recent anti-racism and diversity initiatives, the NHL formed an executive inclusion council that aims to increase minority participation in front offices and on coaching staffs. Peterson said his hiring is a milestone that he called “hard to put into words.”</p>
<p>“I’m just happy that now there can be a second and a third,” Peterson said. “It’s going to be exciting times because I think other people will realize that things are possible and they should be. There’s never really been a hard stop, but there hasn’t been this type of opportunity yet, so I’m happy that we can hopefully create some more.”</p>
<p>The 39-year-old Peterson has a background as a player agent just like GM Bill Zito and fellow assistant Paul Krepelka. He was previously vice president of hockey for Wasserman Media Group and has been an NHLPA certified agent since 2009.</p>
<p>&#8220;It’s a great move by the Florida Panthers, and Wasserman Hockey will certainly miss him,&#8221; Wasserman Hockey senior vice president Judd Moldaver said in a phone interview. “He played the game at a high level. He treats people the right way. He’s extremely smart. Players love him, respect him.&#8221;</p>
<p>Peterson played five pro seasons in the minors after winning a national title during his time at Boston College. The Northborough, Massachusetts, native also advises and consults for a nonprofit organization that provides mentoring and hockey programs for underprivileged youth and underserved communities.</p>
<p>“His substantive hockey experience as a player, significant developmental and evaluation skills and business acumen as a negotiator combine to form an elite skill set that is very difficult to find in our sport,” Zito said in a release sent by the Panthers. “There are many who can excel in one of those disciplines but few who excel in all three.”</p>
<p>The Panthers said Peterson will take an active role in their foundation’s community programs aimed at making the sport more inclusive in South Florida.</p>
<p>“I have worked with Brett for a number of years, and it’s not surprising that his skills were coveted by a front office,” said Wasserman Hockey executive VP Markus Lehto, who took over many of Zito’s clients at Acme World Sports when Zito became assistant GM of the Columbus Blue Jackets.</p>
<p>“I expect that many of the same qualities that made him a successful agent — his character, his respect within the industry, and his understanding of all levels of the game — will also make him a successful executive.”</p>
<p>Boston College coach Jerry York called Zito the day after he took the Panthers GM job to recommend Peterson, who the Hockey Hall of Famer thinks could&#8217;ve gone into any line of work he wanted after graduating. He opted to go the agent route, and now he has made history with the potential for more.</p>
<p>&#8220;First person of color that’s been an assistant general manager in the NHL — that’s breaking barriers,&#8221; York said. “I’d love to see him stay in that endeavor for a while and after five, six years or whatever, he could become a general manager seamlessly.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">781700</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>2021 NHL All-Star Weekend at BB&#038;T Center postponed</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/2021-nhl-all-star-weekend-at-bbt-center-postponed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=765508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The NHL&#8217;s 2021 All-Star Weekend, which was set to be hosted by the Florida Panthers at the BB&#38;T Center in Sunrise in January has been...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The NHL&#x2019;s 2021 All-Star Weekend, which was set to be hosted by the Florida Panthers at the BB&amp;T Center in Sunrise in January has been postponed due to the coronavirus.<p>The NHL made the announcement Thursday. They also announced the postponement of the 2021 Bridgestone NHL Winter Classic in Minnesota.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/FlaPanthers/status/1319362655698694145</embed></div><p>The All-Star Weekend was originally supposed to take place Jan. 29-30 and the Winter Classic was set to take place on Jan 1.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Fan participation, both in arenas and stadiums as well as in the ancillary venues and events that we stage around the Winter Classic and All-Star Weekend, is integral to the success of our signature events,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; said NHL Senior Executive Vice President Steve Mayer. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Because of the uncertainty as to when we will be able to welcome our fans back to our games, we felt that the prudent decision at this time was to postpone these celebrations until 2022 when our fans should be able to enjoy and celebrate these tentpole events in-person, as they were always intended.&#x201D;</p><p>The NHL said they plan to return to both Minnesota and Florida for the signature events in the near future.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">765508</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/nhl-logo.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/nhl-logo.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/nhl-logo.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">NHL LOGO</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dale Tallon, after 10 seasons, out as Florida Panthers&#8217; GM</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dale-tallon-after-10-seasons-out-as-florida-panthers-gm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=708093</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Florida Panthers will have a new general manager next season, making the announcement early Monday that Dale Tallon is leaving the franchise after 10...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Florida Panthers will have a new general manager next season, making the announcement early Monday that Dale Tallon is leaving the franchise after 10 years.</p>
<p>Tallon’s contract as president of hockey operations and general manager expired July 1, and was extended by Panthers owner Vincent Viola to get through the remainder of a season that was stretched out by the coronavirus pandemic. The Panthers were eliminated from the playoffs on Friday, falling to the New York Islanders in four games.</p>
<p>That ouster, the end of yet another season of high expectations that didn’t deliver as planned, sealed Tallon’s fate. The team said it was a mutual decision for Tallon to leave.</p>
<p>“For the last decade, Dale raised the team’s profile, attracted key players to South Florida and brought character and class to our franchise,” Viola said. “When we purchased the Panthers in 2013, we did so with a singular goal — to win a Stanley Cup. We have not seen our efforts come to fruition. We will now begin an organizational search for the next General Manager.”</p>
<p>The Panthers&#8217; decision to seek a new GM came one day after the NHL first-round playoff matchups were set, and hours before the league was holding the second phase of its draft lottery — with Florida being one of the eight teams with an equal shot at the No. 1 overall pick and chance to draft prized winger Alexis Lafreniere.</p>
<p>“I would like to thank the South Florida fans and community for the last 10 years, and the Viola family for the last seven with this franchise,” Tallon said. “I have had the opportunity to work with a group of first-class individuals, including a mentor of mine, the late William A. Torrey and I’ve had the privilege of watching the development of the organization’s young talent who have become great players and even better people.”</p>
<p>It’s believed that the Panthers will look outside the organization for a new GM. Senior vice president of hockey operations and assistant general manager Eric Joyce will likely continue to oversee the team’s AHL club.</p>
<p>And Roberto Luongo, the longtime Panthers goalie whose jersey was retired by the club earlier this year, is expected to remain with Florida. Luongo was brought on this season as a special advisor to Tallon, but is not believed to be a GM candidate.</p>
<p>Tallon had been with Florida since May 17, 2010, coming in at a time when the Panthers were 10 years removed from what had been their most recent playoff appearance. They went to the postseason three times in the decade that Tallon spent with the club, though still haven’t won a playoff series since the franchise’s lone run to the Stanley Cup Final in 1996.</p>
<p>Tallon had successes, such as drafting Jonathan Huberdeau, Aleksander Barkov and Aaron Ekblad — now cornerstones of the team. He brought Luongo back to Florida in a trade, swung a deal in 2015 that added Jaromir Jagr to the club, assembled the 2015-16 that set team records for wins (47) and points (103), and last year was instrumental in the talks that lured his close friend Joel Quenneville to take over as coach of the Panthers.</p>
<p>Oddly, history is repeating itself on that front.</p>
<p>Tallon, then in Chicago, hired Quenneville to coach the Blackhawks in 2008 and wound up watching him win three Stanley Cups there in a six-year span. Tallon wasn’t there for those Chicago titles; he was fired less than a year after delivering Quenneville.</p>
<p>And if Quenneville turns the Panthers into a winner, once again Tallon will be watching from elsewhere.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">708093</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/dale-tallon.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/dale-tallon.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/dale-tallon.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Dale Tallon</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NHL commissioner: &#8216;We need to do more&#8217; to promote racial diversity</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nhl-commissioner-we-need-to-do-more-to-promote-racial-diversity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=675350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The commissioner of the National Hockey League said more needs to be done to open the game to everyone regardless of race, and it must...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The commissioner of the National Hockey League said more needs to be done to open the game to everyone regardless of race, and it must be done in an environment where players feel safe anytime they&#8217;re on the ice.</p>
<p>In a recent Zoom interview with 7Sports Xtra, NHL Commissioner Gary Bettman said more than 90% of current players in the league are white.</p>
<p>&#8220;We have had the Hockey Is for Everyone [initiative], but whatever we&#8217;ve done, that&#8217;s behind us,&#8221; he said. &#8220;We need to be better, and we need to do more.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bettman went into detail about the league&#8217;s current efforts to foster inclusion and diversity. He said a new executive council has been set up with team owners, general managers and players.</p>
<p>Bettman said the NHL has made it clear that physical abuse and racist language cross the line will not be tolerated.</p>
<p>&#8220;We need to do more in terms of having actions and institutionalizing policies and procedures that ensure that it&#8217;s more than just words,&#8221; he said, &#8220;to make sure that racism is not just something we talk about but something we do something about.&#8221;</p>
<p>For a long time, NHL goalie Kevin Weekes once played for the Florida Panthers. He is working with the commissioner to help ensure any form of racism is eliminated from the game.</p>
<p>In 2002, Weekes was playing against the Carolina Hurricanes during an Eastern Conference finals game in Montreal. He said he saw firsthand the ugliness of bigotry.</p>
<p>&#8220;That moment, when that knucklehead threw that banana down after we lost that game in overtime and I was in the net, just getting out of the net, it couldn&#8217;t have been any more egregious,&#8221; said Weekes. &#8220;It couldn&#8217;t have been more embarrassing for the knucklehead who did it, and I didn&#8217;t really want to dignify that person and allow that to become a distraction from what we were doing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Weekes retired in 2009. Since then, he has been on a mission, working hand-in-hand with the NHL to promote the game on all levels, for all races.</p>
<p>&#8220;I will never allow myself to go through some of the things I did as a player. I&#8217;ll never allow that to happen to me as a human being or in the media. I&#8217;ll never allow that to happen,&#8221; he said, &#8220;and I don&#8217;t want to see those things happen to any girls or boys. We don&#8217;t want to lose any more kids or any more people as a result of the knuckleheads. We want all the knuckleheads out of the game.&#8221;</p>
<p>The recent protests have also compelled professional players to speak out. Over 100 NHL players have voiced their opinions on racial inequality, and Zdeno Chára, the captain of the Boston Bruins, recently marched in a protest.</p>
<p>&#8220;This has been more than just a wake-up call,&#8221; said Bettman. &#8220;There are players who are extremely focused, and this is an important issue for them as well.&#8221;</p>
<p>Willie O&#8217;Ree, the NHL&#8217;s first Black player, is working with the league&#8217;s new inclusion and diversity program. He is in the NHL Hall of Fame.</p>
<p>Jarome Iginla is in this year&#8217;s Hall of Fame class. He&#8217;ll become the fourth Black player inducted.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">675350</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/200629_gary_bettman.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/35950208-7f56-4868-8520-eaedfc22fbfc/50c0ccb0-2482-4aa5-8495-1443cfc805de/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218372~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/35950208-7f56-4868-8520-eaedfc22fbfc/50c0ccb0-2482-4aa5-8495-1443cfc805de/main.mp4*~hmac=af60afbcafd26f5d07259eb30ba397628de9e192a6d5c4193db0eb47a5ea5164' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/200629_gary_bettman.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/200629_gary_bettman.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200629_Gary_Bettman</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers, Marlins distribute meals throughout Broward, Miami-Dade</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-marlins-distribute-meals-throughout-broward-miami-dade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 22:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=644874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two South Florida sports teams distributed several hundred meals to front line workers and families throughout Miami-Dade and Broward counties. The Florida Panthers and the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two South Florida sports teams distributed several hundred meals to front line workers and families throughout Miami-Dade and Broward counties.</p>
<p>The Florida Panthers and the Miami Marlins passed out food to those in need on Tuesday.</p>
<p>The Panthers helped take care of front line workers at Broward Health Coral Springs, who have been taking care of so many during the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>Panthers Senior Vice President Shawn Thornton was on hand for the occasion.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are happy we can put some smiles on some faces,&#8221; he said. &#8220;This has been a fairly long ordeal already, and we don&#8217;t know how long it&#8217;s going to continue, but just to come by for an hour or so to put smiles on some faces, we are happy to do it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The team distributed over 400 box lunches to the front line workers.</p>
<p>&#8220;Without a doubt, every single day they put on a brave face, come to work and try and help others,&#8221; Thornton said. &#8220;There isn&#8217;t enough we can do for them. Like I said, this is just a small gesture.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Having the Florida Panthers come out today and serving lunches to our entire hospital, it allows our care givers a chance to take their minds off everything that&#8217;s happening right now, to just take a little moment to relax and get a nice perspective. It&#8217;s so refreshing,&#8221; hospital CEO Jared Smith said.</p>
<p>The Miami Marlins, along with Miami-Dade County Mayor Carlos Gimenez, teamed up with DeliverLean to provide non-perishable items at a drive-thru food distribution at Marlins Park in Miami.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is the community helping each other in this time of need,&#8221; Gimenez said. &#8220;Once more, thank you, DeliverLean, for your contribution. I want to thank the Miami-Dade Fire Department for their work and also the Miami Marlins.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">644874</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/051220-florida-panther-meal-delivery.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/051220-florida-panther-meal-delivery.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/051220-florida-panther-meal-delivery.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">051220 florida panther meal delivery</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Connolly, Driedger lead Panthers to 2-1 win over the Blues</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/connolly-driedger-lead-panthers-to-2-1-win-over-the-blues/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 14:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=606704</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS (AP) — Brett Connolly scored early in the third period and Chris Driedger stopped 26 shots, leading the Florida Panthers to a 2-1...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ST. LOUIS (AP) — Brett Connolly scored early in the third period and Chris Driedger stopped 26 shots, leading the Florida Panthers to a 2-1 victory over the St. Louis Blues on Monday night.</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman also scored for Florida and Aleksi Saarela assisted on both Panthers goals, the first assists of his career. He has played in nine regular-season games for the Panthers.</p>
<p>“He had an incredible night. Two apples from him,” Driedger said about Saarela. &#8220;I joke with him and tell him he&#8217;s a goal scorer and he tells me he&#8217;s a playmaker. He&#8217;s a talented kid and he showed it tonight.&#8221;</p>
<p>Driedger made his third consecutive start after being held out of the lineup for almost two months with a lower-body injury. He is 2-0-1.</p>
<p>Colton Parayko scored for St. Louis. Jordan Binnington recorded 32 saves for the Blues and fell to 6-2 in his last eight starts.</p>
<p>“I think, you know, we can win these games,” Binnington said. “They&#8217;re winnable games and it&#8217;s a time of year where you know you can&#8217;t make excuses and you got to find ways to win, and we didn&#8217;t do that tonight.”</p>
<p>Florida moved within one point of the idle Carolina Hurricanes for the final playoff spot in the East.</p>
<p>Panthers coach Joel Quenneville, who formerly coached the Blues, said he was happy to leave with two points.</p>
<p>“I like it here a lot. You know, I&#8217;m happy that they won a championship,” Quenneville said. “They&#8217;re a dangerous team. That was a huge two points for us in a real game that that puts us in a good position. This was a game where you handicap it and you would hope to get something out of it. We got two points and that&#8217;s huge.”</p>
<p>The Blues entered the game in first place in the Central Division, two points ahead of Colorado, which played late at Los Angeles. St. Louis ended a five-game home winning streak and fell to 9-2 in its last 11 games.</p>
<p>“We weren&#8217;t that bad in the game,” St. Louis coach Craig Berube said. &#8220;If we execute on some plays, we probably win the game.&#8221;</p>
<p>This game was originally scheduled to played Tuesday, but was moved up to accommodate the rescheduling of the Blues&#8217; game against the Anaheim Ducks, which was postponed last month after Jay Bouwmeester had a cardiac episode. The Blues will play at Anaheim on Wednesday.</p>
<p>This was the first meeting between the Blues and Panthers this season. The clubs will meet again in Florida on March 21.</p>
<p>The Blues swept the Panthers last season and have won 10 of their last 15 against them.</p>
<p>Connolly scored his 19th goal at 4:23 of the third period. He got a pass from Saarela and beat Binnington from the left of the net.</p>
<p>“This obviously was a huge win for our team,” Connolly said. “This is the best time of the year. There is lots of pressure now. You work hard to put yourself to get into the postseason. We&#8217;ve got to keep building. Just block out all the noise from everybody and play our best and see what happens.”</p>
<p>Each team scored in the second period.</p>
<p>Parayko wound up and smoked a slap shot from the top of the right circle at 11:20. A cross-ice pass from Robert Thomas caught Parayko in stride and he scored his 10th goal of the season, matching his career high set last year.</p>
<p>Defensemen have scored four of St. Louis&#8217; last five goals. Blues defenders have combined for 43 goals this season to tie for second in the NHL with the Rangers and Wild. The Flyers are first with 44.</p>
<p>Florida tied it on a power-play goal from Hoffman at 16:12. Hoffman scored his 29th goal on a wrist shot from inside the right circle. He has scored in eight of Florida&#8217;s last 11 games.</p>
<p>NOTES: Florida G Sergei Bobrovsky (lower body) and D Riley Stillman (upper body) both were scratched. &#8230; The Blues announced they are closing their locker room to media access until further notice due to concerns over the spread of the coronavirus. Every locker room in the NBA, NHL, Major League Baseball and Major League Soccer will be closed starting Tuesday. &#8230; Florida D Keith Yandle, the NHL&#8217;s active &#8220;Iron Man,&#8221; played in his 866th consecutive regular-season game. &#8230; Blues C Oskar Sundqvist played in his 200th career game.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: At Dallas on Thursday.</p>
<p>Blues: At Anaheim on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">606704</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers snap 8-game home skid with 4-1 win over Canadiens</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-snap-8-game-home-skid-with-4-1-win-over-canadiens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 04:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=604731</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Backup goalie Chris Driedger stopped 33 shots, Mike Hoffman had a goal and an assist, and the Florida Panthers broke their...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Backup goalie Chris Driedger stopped 33 shots, Mike Hoffman had a goal and an assist, and the Florida Panthers broke their eight-game home losing streak Saturday with a 4-1 win over the Montreal Canadiens.</p>
<p>On a night when Roberto Luongo&#8217;s number was retired, the former Florida goalie gave the team a pep talk during a pregame ceremony — and the Panthers took it to heart.</p>
<p>“We have to believe in ourselves right now and enjoy the moment. Work your hearts out,” the 40-year-old Luongo told players, sitting behind him on the home bench, shortly before his No. 1 became the first Panthers jersey displayed in the arena’s rafters.</p>
<p>Lucas Wallmark, MacKenzie Weegar and Jonathan Huberdeau also scored for Florida. Aaron Ekblad had two assists for the Panthers, who are 6-10-3 since the All-Star break.</p>
<p>The win moved Florida three points behind idle Toronto for third place in the Atlantic Division – with the Panthers owning a game in hand. They are also three points out of a wild-card spot.</p>
<p>“I thought we had a workmanlike type of game, more businesslike than we&#8217;ve had recently,” coach Joel Quenneville said. &#8220;We took that awful stretch we&#8217;ve had here and turned it into a different situation when you look at where we&#8217;re sitting.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jake Evans scored and Charlie Lindgren made 28 saves, but the Canadiens lost their second straight.</p>
<p>Making just his 14th NHL appearance, Driedger (6-2-1) made his best save by denying Max Domi on a breakaway at 4:37 of the second period.</p>
<p>“I think he was trying to cut back there, and I just sort of read that he was going to cut back. He ended up stuffing it into my stick there,” said Driedger, adding he was a fan of Luongo&#8217;s growing up.</p>
<p>“One hundred percent. I was five or six in his first year as a pro, so I’ve watched him my entire life being a goalie. He’s definitely been a role model for me,&#8221; said the 25-year-old goalie, who has a .936 save percentage.</p>
<p>Just after an unproductive Florida power play ended in the second, Wallmark broke the scoreless tie when Ekblad’s stretch pass was chipped near the offensive zone diagonally by Noel Acciari to Wallmark. The third-line center skated in unimpeded, faked a slap shot and roofed in a backhand for his 12th goal at 10:22.</p>
<p>Obtained from Carolina at the trade deadline, Wallmark notched his first goal for the Panthers in his sixth game. Ekblad’s helper gave him 10 assists in his last 12 matches.</p>
<p>Florida’s penalty kill gave the team a big boost when it killed off 2:50 of a four-minute, double-minor penalty by Dominic Toninato. Ekblad’s ensuing high-sticking infraction gave Montreal 1:10 of a 5-on-3 advantage, but the Panthers killed all three penalties.</p>
<p>“I don’t know if it was the turning point, but we could have done a much better job,&#8221; Canadiens coach Claude Julien said. &#8220;5-on-3, for some reason we were shooting from far out. It would have made probably a difference in the game.”</p>
<p>Just after a Florida power play that carried over into the third period expired, Weegar fired home his seventh marker from above the left circle 41 seconds into the third period.</p>
<p>Huberdeau pushed it to 3-0 with his 23rd – a tap-in right in front of Lindgren – off a slick pass from the goal line by Erik Haula at 4:13, but Evans scored his second at 8:04 to cut it to 3-1.</p>
<p>Hoffman stole the puck in the defensive zone with Montreal’s net empty and blindly whipped in his 28th at 18:06 for the final margin.</p>
<p>NOTES: NHL Commissioner Gary Bettman spoke to the media during warmups about the coronavirus. “The locker room is an intimate environment. It may be best to have media accessibility at a podium for everybody’s health and safety, not just the players’ but yours,” he responded when asked about teams possibly closing locker rooms to the media. … Canadiens LW Tomas Tatar (upper body), the club’s top point producer, traveled back to Montreal and missed his second consecutive game. … Montreal wore No. 16 stickers to honor Canadiens great Henri Richard, who died at age 84 on Friday. Richard played his entire 20-season career with Montreal, won an NHL-record 11 Stanley Cups and was elected into the Hockey Hall of Fame in 1979. … The teams’ No. 1 goalies – Montreal’s Carey Price and Florida’s Sergei Bobrovsky – did not play. Price (coach’s decision) missed just his second game in the past 15, while Bobrovsky (lower body) was out for his second straight.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">604731</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Krug scores in OT, Bruins rally past Panthers 2-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/krug-scores-in-ot-bruins-rally-past-panthers-2-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 03:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=603315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla (AP) — Torey Krug scored 4:08 into overtime, Patrice Bergeron also had a goal and the Boston Bruins beat the Florida Panthers 2-1...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla (AP) — Torey Krug scored 4:08 into overtime, Patrice Bergeron also had a goal and the Boston Bruins beat the Florida Panthers 2-1 Thursday night for their fourth straight win.</p>
<p>Moments before he scored, Krug led a 2-on-1 rush with David Pastrnak that was disrupted by MacKenzie Weegar&#8217;s poke check. Pastrnak recovered the puck in the corner and passed to Krug, who wheeled into the high slot and slapped the winner past Chris Driedger.</p>
<p>Jaroslav Halak stopped 32 shots for the NHL-leading Bruins.</p>
<p>Driedger made 25 saves and Weegar scored, but Florida dropped a franchise-worst eighth straight home game and lost its fourth game in a row overall.</p>
<p>This was Driedger&#8217;s first start since being recalled from AHL Springfield on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Bruins defenseman Brandon Carlo was elbowed in the face by Evgenii Dadonov in the second period. It was initially ruled a major penalty, then reduced to a minor on review. Carlo did not return to the game.</p>
<p>Weegar put the Panthers ahead when his shot from the high slot slipped by a screened Halak 6:55 into the second period.</p>
<p>Bergeron tied it on the power play four minutes later, getting his 30th of the season by redirecting Krug&#8217;s shot. Bergeron has scored at least 30 goals in three straight seasons.</p>
<p>NOTES: Panthers G Sergei Bobrovsky missed his second game with a lower-body injury. &#8230; C Lucas Wallmark, acquired from Carolina on Feb. 24, recorded his first point with the Panthers with an assist on Weegar’s goal.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Bruins: Host Tampa Bay on Saturday.</p>
<p>Panthers: Host Montreal on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">603315</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Talbot makes 38 saves, Flames beat Panthers 3-0</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/talbot-makes-38-saves-flames-beat-panthers-3-0/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 05:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=598634</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Cam Talbot made 38 saves, Johnny Gaudreau had a goal and an assist, and the Calgary Flames beat the Florida Panthers...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Cam Talbot made 38 saves, Johnny Gaudreau had a goal and an assist, and the Calgary Flames beat the Florida Panthers 3-0 Sunday.</p>
<p>TJ Brodie and Milan Lucic also scored for the Flames, and Mark Giordano had three assists.</p>
<p>&#8220;I felt pretty good from the get-go, got a good warm-up in this morning,&#8221; Talbot said. &#8220;Guys let me see the shots, kept them to the outside for the first little bit. It gets the confidence up early and able to get into a groove.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Flames finished 3-1-1 on the five-game road trip.</p>
<p>&#8220;We played a real, real good road period, maybe our best one of the whole trip in order to end it off,&#8221; coach Geoff Ward said. &#8220;Good response by our guys and a well-earned win.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sam Montembault stopped 25 shots for the Panthers, who have tied a franchise record with seven straight home losses. The Panthers are 5-11-2 since the All-Star break.</p>
<p>Gaudreau gave the Flames a 1-0 lead on his power-play goal at 6:21 of the first. Gaudreau&#8217;s shot from the left circle beat Montembeault on the glove side.</p>
<p>The Flames went ahead 2-0 when Derek Ryan passed from behind the net to Lucic in front, who banked it off the post and in at 3:10 of the second.</p>
<p>Calgary stretched its lead to 3-0 on Brodie&#8217;s shot from just inside the blue line 1:09 into the third.</p>
<p>&#8220;At the end, we didn&#8217;t have a push. That&#8217;s unacceptable,&#8221; Panthers captain Aleksander Barkov said. &#8220;We just have to regroup right now.&#8221;</p>
<p>The home crowd began to boo in the closing minutes of the second period and also at the end of the game.</p>
<p>&#8220;Obviously disappointed, we&#8217;ve put ourselves in a really tough spot,&#8221; Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. &#8220;Let&#8217;s find a way to bring some excitement in our team game and get the building going in our favor.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gaudreau was awarded a penalty shot with 7:43 left in the first after being hooked by MacKenzie Weegar, but Montembeault blocked it.</p>
<p>NOTES: Flames C Elias Lindholm recorded his 200th career assist on the goal by Gaudreau. &#8230; Panthers G Sergei Bobrovsky tweaked something in his lower-body in warm-ups and was replaced by Montembeault. &#8220;I don&#8217;t think it was serious, we&#8217;ll see,&#8221; Quenneville said. &#8230; The Panthers are 4 for 35 on the power play over their last 13 games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Flames: Host the Columbus Blue Jackets on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Panthers: Host the Boston Bruins on Thursday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598634</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kane, Toews lead Blackhawks over Panthers 3-2 in shootout</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kane-toews-lead-blackhawks-over-panthers-3-2-in-shootout/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 05:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=598145</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Patrick Kane and Jonathan Toews each scored in the shootout to lift the Chicago Blackhawks over the Florida Panthers 3-2 on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Patrick Kane and Jonathan Toews each scored in the shootout to lift the Chicago Blackhawks over the Florida Panthers 3-2 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Toews also had a goal and an assist in regulation, and Drake Caggiula also scored for the Blackhawks. Corey Crawford made 38 saves and stopped both of Florida&#8217;s shots in the shootout.</p>
<p>&#8220;Would have loved to close it out in regulation,&#8221; Blackhawks coach Jeremy Colliton said. &#8220;That would have been easier on everyone.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman had a goal and an assist, and Mike Matheson also scored for the Panthers. Sergei Bobrovsky stopped 27 shots.</p>
<p>The Panthers have lost six straight home games. Their last home win was a 4-3 victory against the Los Angeles Kings on Jan. 16. The Panthers are 0-5-1 at home in February. They salvaged a much needed point.</p>
<p>&#8220;Tough loss, but we&#8217;ll take the point and move in the other direction,&#8221; coach Joel Quenneville said.</p>
<p>The Panthers are five points behind Toronto and three behind Columbus in the wild card race in the Eastern Conference.</p>
<p>Down 2-1, the Panthers tied it when Matheson scored on a wrist shot from the right circle with 1:28 left in the third.</p>
<p>&#8220;We felt good about our odds going into overtime,&#8221; Matheson said. &#8220;We created a lot of chances going into overtime. It&#8217;s frustrating not to see them go in.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Blackhawks are 4-4 in overtime.</p>
<p>&#8220;You never want to give up one late and have to take it to overtime,&#8221; Crawford said. &#8220;We had some chances, off the bar, kind of went back and forth, but it was nice to get that win in the shootout.&#8221;</p>
<p>Caggiula broke a 1-all tie after he deflected a shot by Connor Murphy from the blue line and into the net at 6:21 of the second.</p>
<p>The Panthers took a 1-0 lead when Hoffman skated in on a breakaway and backhanded the puck past Crawford 4:07 in. Hoffman leads the Panthers with 27 goals.</p>
<p>The Blackhawks tied it at 1 when Toews redirected a shot from above the right circle by Adam Boqvist and into the net at 12:54 of the first.</p>
<p>NOTES: Blackhawks F Brandon Hagel was recalled from AHL Rockford on an emergency basis. &#8230; The game was Panthers coach Quenneville&#8217;s second against his former team. Florida won 4-3 in Chicago on Jan. 21.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Blackhawks: host Anaheim on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Panthers: host Calgary on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598145</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nylander leads Maple Leafs over Panthers, 5-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nylander-leads-maple-leafs-over-panthers-5-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=597147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla (AP) — William Nylander scored the go-ahead goal midway in the third period to lift the Toronto Maple Leafs over the Florida Panthers...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla (AP) — William Nylander scored the go-ahead goal midway in the third period to lift the Toronto Maple Leafs over the Florida Panthers 5-3 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Auston Matthews, Kasperi Kapanen, Zach Hyman and Justin Holl also scored for Toronto, who came back from a 3-1 deficit. Frederik Andersen stopped 24 shots in his sixth straight start.</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman, Noel Acciari and Mark Pysyk scored for the Panthers, while Sergei Bobrovsky made 24 saves.</p>
<p>With the score tied at 3, Nylander put the Maple Leafs ahead when he grabbed a loose puck in front and put it past Bobrovsky with 11 minutes left in the third.</p>
<p>“(Kyle) Clifford was battling there in front and it just ended up on my stick,” Nylander said. “I turned and just threw it at the net. Luckily it went in, but we&#8217;ll take it.”</p>
<p>Holl’s empty-net goal with 20.8 seconds remaining stretched the lead to 5-3.</p>
<p>Toronto has won three of their past four games. The Panthers have lost three of four. The Maple Leafs are four points ahead of the Panthers for third place in the Atlantic Division.</p>
<p>“It was a disappointing game,&#8221; Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said. “At home, you have to find a way to get something out of this game.”</p>
<p>The Panthers play their next four games at home and hope to gain some ground in their playoff push.</p>
<p>“One game at a time,&#8221; Quenneville said. &#8220;Let’s recapture some confidence here at home and get two points and go from there. There’s lots of hockey left.”</p>
<p>The Maple Leafs return home for a game against Vancouver, then go on a three-game West Coast swing.</p>
<p>“We did our part here in terms of getting off the mats and we want to build on this. We&#8217;re excited to get back home,&#8221; coach Sheldon Keefe said.</p>
<p>Each team scored three goals in a wild first period.</p>
<p>Trailing 3-1, the Maple Leafs closed to 3-2 when Kapinen’s shot from the left circle beat Bobrovsky with 2:17 left in the first. Matthews tied it when he poked in a rebound with 1:02 left.</p>
<p>“When we got down early in the first, we just tried to keep our composure.” Matthews said. “Go out there and take it one shift at a time and claw our way back.”</p>
<p>With the score tied at 1, Hoffman put the Panthers ahead 2-1 when he found a rebound in front and shot it into the open net at 7:25. Acciari’s shot from the right circle hit the post on the far side and went in at 12:36 and made it 3-1.</p>
<p>The Panthers took a 1-0 lead when Pysyk one-timed a pass from Aaron Ekblad from the right circle 2:23 in.</p>
<p>The Maple Leafs answered 1:09 later after Hyman poked a rebound past Bobrovsky to tie it at 1.</p>
<p>“It was a big game for us and unfortunately we are on the wrong side,&#8221; Bobrovsky said.</p>
<p>NOTES: Maple Leafs C Denis Malgin, acquired from the Panthers on Feb. 19, was a healthy scratch. &#8230; Toronto D Jake Muzzin will miss four weeks with a broken hand sustained in a 4-3 win at Tampa Bay on Thursday. &#8230; Florida&#8217;s Joel Quenneville became the 2nd NHL head coach to reach 1,700 games. Scotty Bowman coached 2,499 NHL games. &#8230; Ekblad’s assist on Pysyk’s goal gave him a career-high 39 points. &#8230; Panthers F Erik Haula played his 400th NHL game.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Maple Leafs: host Vancouver on Saturday.</p>
<p>Panthers: host Chicago on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">597147</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Golden Knights win 5th straight with 5-3 win over Panthers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/golden-knights-win-5th-straight-with-5-3-win-over-panthers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 22:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=594315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS (AP) &#8212; Reilly Smith scored two goals, Marc-Andre Fleury made 31 saves and the Vegas Golden Knights defeated the Florida Panthers 5-3 on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LAS VEGAS (AP) &#8212; Reilly Smith scored two goals, Marc-Andre Fleury made 31 saves and the Vegas Golden Knights defeated the Florida Panthers 5-3 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>The Golden Knights completed a five-game homestand 5-0-0 and catapulted to the top of the Pacific Division, where they lead Vancouver by two points and Edmonton by three. The Canucks and Oilers have two games in hand on Vegas, which faces Edmonton three more times and Vancouver twice.</p>
<p>&#8220;Every night there&#8217;s someone new stepping up and I think that&#8217;s a big key to that homestand and picking up a lot of wins,&#8221; said Smith, whose empty-net goal with a little more than a minute remaining was his career-high tying 25th goal, which he originally set during the 2015-16 season, when he played with the Panthers. &#8220;Those are things that really give our team a boost. When we&#8217;re rolling with all four lines we&#8217;re a tough team to beat.&#8221;</p>
<p>William Carrier and Max Pacioretty also scored, while Tomas Nosek had a goal and an assist for the Golden Knights, who had 10 players with points.</p>
<p>Vegas improved to 9-3-2 under coach Peter DeBoer, who replaced fired Gerard Gallant on Jan. 15. The Golden Knights&#8217; five-game win streak is their highest of the season.</p>
<p>Vegas&#8217; analytics have improved dramatically under DeBoer, as the Golden Knights rank No. 1 with 36.4 shots per game, have the second-fewest shots allowed per game (27.3), the second-most goals per game average (3.64), the third-most goals scored (51) and have the fifth-most points (20) since his first game as coach on Jan. 16.</p>
<p>The other thing they&#8217;ve done well, something they struggled with prior to DeBoer&#8217;s arrival, is staying focused and calm when falling behind in games. It&#8217;s a small sample size compared to the Golden Knights under Gallant, but their win percentage was just .296 (8-14-5) before the coaching change after allowing the first goal and is .500 (3-2-1) under DeBoer after allowing the first goal.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s (been) building confidence in your group and the only way to do that is to have success,&#8221; DeBoer said. &#8220;We&#8217;ve started well, there&#8217;s been some other games we&#8217;ve gotten behind. There&#8217;s been a real calmness to the group, but they know that we can put some pressure on the other team and we&#8217;re not out of games. They have that ability to score and get back in games pretty quickly.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Panthers, meanwhile, are four points out of the Eastern Conference wild-card race after dipping to 3-7-0 in their last 10.</p>
<p>&#8220;We started fine, but once the game kept going, they got the momentum,&#8221; Florida captain Aleksander Barkov said. &#8220;They outskated us, they out chanced us, put pucks on the net. You need a full 60-minute effort. They worked really hard. We just need to match their work ethic.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman, Evgenii Dadonov and Aleksi Saarela scored for the Panthers. Sam Montembeault, making just his 24th career start, made 34 saves.</p>
<p>Florida took an early 1-0 lead when Hoffman kicked a rebound to his stick and knocked it past Fleury just 3:28 into the game. It was Hoffman&#8217;s 24th of the season, second-highest on the team. Nosek tied the game when he gathered a loose puck in the slot and sent a wrist shot under Montembeault&#8217;s pads midway through the first.</p>
<p>Dadonov gave the Panthers a 2-1 lead just 42 seconds into the second period with his team-high 25th goal. With a beautiful display of passing, Barkov took Keith Yandle&#8217;s pass and fed Dadonov, who chipped it past Fleury for the 200th point of his career.</p>
<p>Carrier got his seventh goal of the season when he lasered a wrist shot from the circle that caromed into the net off of Montembeault&#8217;s glove. Later, with 52 seconds left in the second, Shea Theodore stole the puck from Aaron Ekblad and raced in on a 2-on-0 rush with Pacioretty, who fired a shot off the side of Montembeault&#8217;s torso, making it three straight goals that went off Florida&#8217;s goalie.</p>
<p>Smith matched his jersey number by scoring 19 seconds into the third period, as he buried Jonathan Marchessault&#8217;s pass top shelf for his 24th goal of the campaign.</p>
<p>Saarela cut into Vegas&#8217; lead when he punched in a shot over a cluster of players in the crease. Vegas coach Peter DeBoer challenged the goal, thinking Hoffman interfered with Fleury. But after review, it was ruled Hoffman was pushed into Fleury by Vegas defenseman Nick Holden.</p>
<p>Smith iced the game with his career-high tying goal into an empty net.</p>
<p>NOTES: Alec Martinez is one game shy of playing in the 600th of his career. &#8230; Las Vegas-native Gage Quinney became the first Nevada-born hockey player to play in an NHL game when he made his debut in the starting lineup. &#8230; Theodore&#8217;s assist on Pacioretty&#8217;s goal was his 41st point, tying the franchise record for points by a defenseman originally set by Colin Miller during the team&#8217;s inaugural season in 2017-18.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Florida: Visits Arizona on Tuesday</p>
<p>Vegas: Visits Anaheim on Sunday</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">594315</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saarela&#8217;s first NHL goal helps Panthers top Ducks 4-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/saarelas-first-nhl-goal-helps-panthers-top-ducks-4-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 12:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=592123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ANAHEIM, Calif. (AP) — The Florida Panthers showed a little rebounding prowess, getting a pair of friendly bounces off the end boards to deliver a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ANAHEIM, Calif. (AP) — The Florida Panthers showed a little rebounding prowess, getting a pair of friendly bounces off the end boards to deliver a key 4-1 victory over the Anaheim Ducks on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Vincent Trocheck and Aleksi Saarela each scored second-period goals off fortuitous rebounds and the Panthers were able to rally from an early deficit. The victory moved Florida past the Toronto Maple Leafs and into third place in the Atlantic Division.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov and MacKenzie Weegar also scored for Florida. Sergei Bobrovsky made 35 saves as the Panthers improved to 2-0 on a key five-game West Coast trip.</p>
<p>Florida won consecutive games in California with another set at Los Angeles on Thursday. The Panthers earned a 5-3 victory at San Jose on Monday.</p>
<p>“These are big games for us,” Bobrovsky said. “I thought as a team, we gave a good effort (Wednesday). We got timely goals, guys sacrificing in the (defensive) zone. It was solid and it was fun, too. Winning is fun. You just have to continue working with each other.”</p>
<p>The Panthers look as if they are starting to emerge from a post All-Star break funk. Even with Wednesday’s victory, the Panthers are 4-6-1 since the break after heading into it on a six-game winning streak.</p>
<p>Bobrovsky improved to 22-17-5 and had his seventh game of the season in which he allowed one goal or less. It was his second one since the All-Star break.</p>
<p>“He was excellent,” head coach Joel Quenneville said of his goalie. “He made a key save on a second-period break there. … He was moving. He was on top of the crease, he was finding pucks and they had some traffic there. So he was fighting through it a bit and I thought he did a great job.”</p>
<p>Max Jones scored, and John Gibson had 28 saves for the Ducks, who dropped the opener of a six-game homestand. The Ducks have lost three of their last four games and have dropped three consecutive home games.</p>
<p>“One of our goals was to not feed their transition and I feel we kind of did a bit,” Jones said. “That was something that was critical in the game. There were times in that game we kept going back to retrieve pucks and it’s hard to get offensive zone time when we’re not clicking.”</p>
<p>Jones gave the Ducks the early lead with a goal at 16:04 of the first period. His 10th of the season came unassisted when he raced across the blue line, picked up a loose puck and fired it off the left shoulder of Bobrovsky and inside the right post.</p>
<p>The Ducks appeared as if they would take the lead into the first intermission, but Jonathan Huberdeau fired a perfect pass to Barkov as he rushed to the front of the Ducks goal and he flipped the puck past Gibson with 2.2 seconds on the clock to tie the score 1-1. It was Barkov’s 18th of the season.</p>
<p>“To give up that lead going into the intermission was deflating to say the least,” Ducks head coach Dallas Eakins said. “With that being said, you have to pick yourself up and get going again. I thought we were able to do that. … We can’t make those mistakes.”</p>
<p>The Panthers took a 2-1 lead at 10:50 of the second period when Trocheck cashed in a break. Riley Stillman’s shot past the goal, deflected off the end boards and back over the Ducks’ goal to Trocheck, who picked it out of the air with a waist-high swing for his 10th goal.</p>
<p>The Panthers received another deflection off the end boards less than four minutes later when Aaron Ekblad’s wide shot rebounded around the goal and into the left circle, where Saarela scored from a sharp angle. It was Saarela’s first career goal in his fourth NHL game.</p>
<p>“It felt good,” Saarela said. “I was lucky, got that bounce off the wall and had (what looked like) an empty netter.”</p>
<p>Weegar’s fifth of the season was scored into an empty net with just over two minutes remaining.</p>
<p>NOTES:</p>
<p>Ducks defenseman Cam Fowler, who did participate in morning skate, was a late scratch with a lower body injury. &#8230; Anaheim was kicking off a six-game homestand. &#8230; Barkov now has eight points (four goals) over his past 11 games for the Panthers. &#8230; Mike Hoffman had a goal taken away at 13:10 of the first period for the Panthers when Mark Pysyk was ruled offsides after a successful replay challenge from the Ducks. &#8230; The Panthers improved to 7-1-1 on the road against Western Conference teams.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: At Los Angeles on Thursday to face the Kings.</p>
<p>Ducks: Home against the Colorado Avalanche on Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">592123</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/04/190405-florida-panthers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190405 florida panthers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hoffman, Ekblad lead Panthers past Sharks 5-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hoffman-ekblad-lead-panthers-past-sharks-5-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 04:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=591198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE, Calif. (AP) — Evgenii Dadonov and Mike Hoffman scored, Aaron Ekblad had two assists and the slumping Florida Panthers beat the San Jose...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAN JOSE, Calif. (AP) — Evgenii Dadonov and Mike Hoffman scored, Aaron Ekblad had two assists and the slumping Florida Panthers beat the San Jose Sharks 5-3 Monday.</p>
<p>Colton Sceviour, Anton Stralman and Vincent Trocheck also scored for Florida, which had lost six of seven. Sergei Bobrovsky stopped 29 shots, and the Panthers moved within two points of idle Toronto for third place in the Atlantic Division.</p>
<p>“We really kept our composure tonight and that really helped,” Ekblad said. &#8220;Our confidence was high all night and that was a good sign that we would hold on.”</p>
<p>Dylan Gambrell, Kevin Labanc and Timo Meier each scored and Brent Burns had two assists for San Jose, which had won four of its previous five. Aaron Dell had 23 saves.</p>
<p>Hoffman scored his 22nd goal 11 minutes into the second period on a breakaway after intercepting Burns&#8217; pass near his own blue line. That put Florida up 2-1, and Sceviour made it 3-1 midway through the third.</p>
<p>“They’re a pretty opportunistic team,” Sharks interim coach Bob Boughner said. “They can finish, they’ve got some skill, so you feel I think that we played hard for one another. We got a 6-on-5 goal, we got a power-play goal, our penalty kill was good. It just seemed that when we had that momentum we gave them that once chance on the breakaway and it sort of turned the game a little bit.”</p>
<p>Dadonov scored his 24th goal off a rebound on a wrist shot from five feet out for the game’s first goal early in the first. Gambrell countered with his fourth goal at 12:30 of the first.</p>
<p>The Sharks closed within 3-2 on Labanc&#8217;s power-play goal, his 14th overall, with just over five minutes left in the third.</p>
<p>Stralman scored his fifth with just under three minutes left in the third to extend Florida’s lead to 4-2, and Meier and Trocheck traded goals late, with Trochek scoring into an empty net. Meier&#8217;s goal was his 20th.</p>
<p>“We really got that extra push when Stralman scored,” Ekblad said. “It gave us a 4-2 lead and even though they got a quick goal to make it (4-3), it really gave us an extra push. We got two big goals when we needed them. Those were big moments.&#8221;</p>
<p>NOTES: Panthers F Jonathan Huberdeau was knocked to the ice early in the third after being pushed by Barclay Goodrow into Stefan Noesen, who crashed into the back of Huberdeau’s head with his shoulder. No penalty was called on the play. The Panthers’ points leader and second leading scorer went to the bench after the play but returned midway through the third. &#8230; F Jayce Hawryluk was claimed off waivers from Florida by the Ottawa Senators. &#8230; Sharks C Noah Gregor is day-to-day with an undisclosed injury. &#8230; Sharks F Evander Kane served the second of a three-game suspension for elbowing Winnipeg Jets D Neal Pionk on Friday. &#8230; The Sharks reassigned D Jacob Middleton to the San Jose Barracuda, their AHL affiliate. &#8230; Sharks C Antti Suomela left the game for evaluation and did not return after taking a hit from D Josh Brown. Boughner said his status is day-to-day.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: At Anaheim on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Sharks: At New Jersey on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">591198</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Larsson scores 1st goal in a year, Oilers beat Panthers 4-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/larsson-scores-1st-goal-in-a-year-oilers-beat-panthers-4-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=590296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Adam Larsson scored his first goal since last February, Leon Draisaitl added an insurance goal seconds into the third period and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Adam Larsson scored his first goal since last February, Leon Draisaitl added an insurance goal seconds into the third period and the Edmonton Oilers beat the Florida Panthers 4-1 Saturday night.</p>
<p>Darnell Nurse and Kailer Yamamoto had empty-net goals in the final two minutes for the Oilers, who have won three of their last four games.</p>
<p>It was the sixth loss in the last seven games for the Panthers, who are 2-6-1 since the All-Star break. Florida had entered the break on a six-game win streak.</p>
<p>Edmonton goalie Mikko Koskinen made 33 saves, while back-up netminder Sam Montembeault stopped 25 of 27 shots for Florida.</p>
<p>Larsson&#8217;s first goal since Feb. 19, 2019 put the Oilers ahead 1-0 at the 15:14 mark of the first period on a one-timer from just inside the blue line.</p>
<p>That score was assisted by Ryan Nugent-Hopkins, who has points in 12 of his last 14 games. Nugent-Hopkins has been pesky against the Panthers with 13 points in his last 14 games against them.</p>
<p>Draisaitl&#8217;s insurance tally, into a wide open right side against an out-of-position Montembeault, came just 13 seconds into the third period. It was the 33rd goal this season for Draisaitl, who has eight points in his last four games.</p>
<p>Draisaitl entered the game leading the NHL with 90 points.</p>
<p>The Panthers cut the deficit to 2-1 at 8:45 of the third period when Jonathan Huberdeau scored his 21st goal.</p>
<p>With his assist on Huberdeau&#8217;s goal, captain Aleksander Barkov moved into second place in assists (250) in Panthers history.</p>
<p>Edmonton came close to scoring midway through the first period, but Alex Chiasson&#8217;s breakaway shot glanced off Montembeault&#8217;s stick blade.</p>
<p>Florida got a scare five minutes into the second period when Barkov left the game after receiving a blindside hit from Edmonton&#8217;s Matt Benning against the boards. Barkov returned to the bench a few minutes later.</p>
<p>Things got a little chippy after the Barkov incident. After Noel Acciari mixed it up with Benning, the Panthers&#8217; Josh Brown and Larsson dropped the gloves at center ice. Both received five-minute majors.</p>
<p>NOTES: Edmonton RW Zack Kassian began his seven-game suspension for kicking Tampa Bay defenseman Erik Cernak on Thursday. &#8230; Oilers C and former Panther Riley Sheehan played in his 500th NHL game. &#8230; The Panthers commemorated Friday&#8217;s second anniversary of the Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School shootings in Parkland with a pre-game ceremony.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Oilers: Visit Carolina on Sunday afternoon.</p>
<p>Panthers: Visit San Jose on Monday afternoon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">590296</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Van Riemsdyk has 3-point game, Flyers beat Panthers 6-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/van-riemsdyk-has-3-point-game-flyers-beat-panthers-6-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 04:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=589554</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; James van Riemsdyk had a goal and two assists and the Philadelphia Flyers beat the Florida Panthers 6-2 on Thursday night....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; James van Riemsdyk had a goal and two assists and the Philadelphia Flyers beat the Florida Panthers 6-2 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Robert Hagg, Sean Couturier, Scott Laughton, Nicolas Aube-Kubel and Tyler Pitlick scored for the Flyers. Carter Hart made 26 saves for his first road win in eight games. Hart had lost his last seven road starts, since a 3-2 shootout victory against the Boston Bruins on Nov. 10.</p>
<p>Justin Braun had three assists and Matt Niskanen had two as the Flyers improved to 9-3-1 in their past 12 games.</p>
<p>Aleksander Barkov and Jonathan Huberdeau scored for Florida. Sergei Bobrovsky allowed three goals on nine shots and was relieved by Sam Montembeault at the start of the second period. Montembeault made 16 saves. The Panthers dropped to 2-5-1 in their last eight games.</p>
<p>Trailing 4-0, Huberdeau&#8217;s shot from below the right circle got by Hart 33 seconds into the third to make the score 4-1.</p>
<p>Barkov&#8217;s wrist shot from the left circle found the net at 4:56 and closed the score to 4-2.</p>
<p>Couturier&#8217;s goal, a shot from the slot, beat Montembeault and made the score 5-2 with 5:08 left in the third. Hagg made the score 6-2 with 27 seconds left.</p>
<p>The Flyers took a 3-0 lead in the first.</p>
<p>Van Riemsdyk poked a rebound past Bobrovsky 4:24 in to make the score 1-0. Pitlick fired a shot from the right circle that went top shelf with 2:23 left in the first that made it 2-0. Aube-Kuble found a loose puck in front of the net after Florida&#8217;s MacKenzie Weegar misplayed the rebound and beat Bobrovsky with 1:28 left to stretch the lead to 3-0.</p>
<p>Laughton&#8217;s goal, a shot from close range after a feed from van Riemsdyk, built the lead to 4-0 with 1:02 left in the second.</p>
<p>NOTES: Flyers D Shayne Gostisbehere missed his fourth consecutive game with a knee injury. &#8230; Barkov&#8217;s goal was his 152nd, tying him with Pavel Bure for third in franchise history. &#8230; Panthers D Brian Boyle missed his fifth straight game with an upper-body injury. &#8230; The Panthers are 0 for 11 on the power play in their Last four games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Flyers: At the Tampa Bay Lightning on Saturday.</p>
<p>Panthers: Host the Edmonton Oilers on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">589554</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers snap 3-game skid with 5-3 win over Devils</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-snap-3-game-skid-with-5-3-win-over-devils/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=588512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEWARK, N.J. (AP) — Riding a three-game losing streak and fading in the wild-card race, the Florida Panthers needed something to get them going. They...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEWARK, N.J. (AP) — Riding a three-game losing streak and fading in the wild-card race, the Florida Panthers needed something to get them going.</p>
<p>They got it from a totally unexpected source, a fourth line quickly dubbed the helicopter line. The reason: a center playing with two defenseman. In other words, no wings.</p>
<p>Mike Matheson, Mark Pysyk and Noel Acciari each scored and accounted for eight points as the Panthers got back on track with a 5-3 victory over the New Jersey Devils on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>“The way that line played tonight, more lines have to follow that,&#8221; Panthers defenseman Anton Stralman said. “They honestly just went in working hard, doing the right things, playing on the right side of the puck and not complicated. Shooting, winning battles. They spent a lot of time in the offensive zone and that&#8217;s what we need.&#8221;</p>
<p>Florida coach Joel Quenneville, whose team had scored five goals in its last four games, smiled when asked if had found a new fourth line.</p>
<p>“I don’t know if I would call it fourth,&#8221; he said. “They were better than that.”</p>
<p>Quenneville had wanted to get Matheson back into the lineup after sitting him on Monday. Pysyk was told earlier in the morning he should be ready to play forward because someone was not feeling good.</p>
<p>Acciari was made their center.</p>
<p>“I looked at it as we’ll be a shutdown line,&#8221; he quipped. “We have four D out there and I was the honorary D. so make it five D out there. It was huge for our team. It was a bonus. I think we complemented each other out there. All three goals were in the gritty areas and that’s where they are going to come.”</p>
<p>Frank Vatrano and Brett Connolly also scored as the Panthers won for only second time (2-4-1) since returning from the All-Star break. Sam Montembeault had 25 saves in his first start since Nov. 24.</p>
<p>Jack Hughes, Kevin Rooney and Kyle Palmieri scored for the Devils, who saw their season-high six-game (3-0-3) point steak snapped. Louis Domingue made 28 saves in getting a start for MacKenzie Blackwood, who had shutouts in his last two starts.</p>
<p>“They didn’t look like defensemen out there to me,&#8221; Palmieri said of the Panthers&#8217; big line. “Obviously, that’s their position but they played well. They were hard on the pucks. The offense they generated was the way to you want to generate offense.&#8221;</p>
<p>Matheson, who like Pysyk has eight goals, gave Florida the lead for good late in the first period, scoring on a rebound in close for a 2-1 lead.</p>
<p>Pysyk, who had a hat trick against Toronto last week, stretched the margin to 3-1 early in the second with a shot in close set up by Matheson.</p>
<p>After Rooney cut the deficit to a goal on a giveaway at 4:17, Florida, which had scored five goals in its last four games, got two more in a 39-second span to push the lead to 5-2.</p>
<p>Vatrano scored on a shot from right circle at 4:59 and Acciari got his 19th of the season on a wrist shot from the slot at 5:38.</p>
<p>Palmieri closed the deficit to 5-3 with 5:30 left in the second period. The Devils had a chance to get within one less than a minute later when Hughes broke in alone, but Montembeault made a great pad pad.</p>
<p>“Ït was my first start in a while so obviously I was a little nervous in the beginning, but I just felt better as the game went on and it&#8217;s easier as a goalie when you have a lead like that,&#8221; Montembeault said.</p>
<p>NOTES: The Connolly goal ended the Devils&#8217; shutout streak of 147 minutes, 15 seconds. &#8230; Former Devil Brian Boyle missed his fourth-straight game with an upper-body injury. &#8230; Devils C Nico Hischier and D Sami Vatanen missed their fourth straight games with lower-body injuries. &#8230; On the Matheson goal, the fourth line kept the puck in the Devils&#8217; zone for more than 90 seconds and attempted seven shots, four of which were blocked. &#8230; Hughes&#8217; last goal was on Dec. 29. &#8230; The Devils held their annual Black Hockey History Month night at the game. &#8230; Devils F Joey Anderson got his first point of the season.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Panthers: Return home to host Philadelphia on Thursday.</p>
<p>Devils: Finish three-game homestand against Detroit on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">588512</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Van Riemsdyk, Hart lead Flyers past Panthers 4-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/van-riemsdyk-hart-lead-flyers-past-panthers-4-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=587839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA (AP) &#8212; Wearing a mask honoring Ray Emery, Carter Hart gave a performance &#8220;Razor&#8221; would&#8217;ve been proud to see. James van Riemsdyk had a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PHILADELPHIA (AP) &#8212; Wearing a mask honoring Ray Emery, Carter Hart gave a performance &#8220;Razor&#8221; would&#8217;ve been proud to see.</p>
<p>James van Riemsdyk had a goal and assist, Hart stopped 30 shots in his return from injury and the Philadelphia Flyers beat the Florida Panthers 3-1 Monday night.</p>
<p>Travis Sanheim, Ivan Provorov and Claude Giroux also had goals for Philadelphia, which is 6-1-1 in the last eight. The Flyers improved to 19-5-4 at home.<br />
MacKenzie Weegar scored for Florida, which has lost four straight.</p>
<p>Hart missed nine games with an abdominal strain but looked sharp in his first game since Jan. 13. His mask featured a photo of Emery&#8217;s face and an action shot of the former NHL goalie who died in 2018.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a sad story about Ray,&#8221; said Hart, who never met Emery. &#8220;I wanted to pay tribute to a guy who the staff here said they loved him.&#8221;</p>
<p>Despite missing almost one month, Hart said it took a couple shots for him to get in a groove.</p>
<p>&#8220;He looked good, he looked calm, looked poised,&#8221; van Riemsdyk said. &#8220;He made a lot of stops look easy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Panthers goalie Sergei Bobrovsky, who began his NHL career with the Flyers in 2010, had 30 saves.</p>
<p>&#8220;The results matter,&#8221; Bobrovsky said. &#8220;I thought the guys again worked hard. We got a good effort. We have to find a way to eliminate some small mistakes and find a way to score one more than the opposition team.</p>
<p>Van Riemsdyk gave the Flyers a 2-1 lead in the second on his 16th goal. Jake Voracek hopped over the boards onto the ice following a shift change, picked up a loose pick and started a 2-on-none break. Voracek slid a pass to van Riemsdyk, who slipped it past Bobrovsky.</p>
<p>Sanheim flipped in a rebound off van Riemsdyk&#8217;s shot for his eighth goal and a 3-1 lead in the final minute of the second period.</p>
<p>Giroux scored into an empty net with the Flyers short-handed late in the third.</p>
<p>Provorov blasted a shot just under the crossbar to tie it at 1 late in the first. He snapped a 17-game goal drought with his 10th this season.</p>
<p>&#8220;We gave up a lot of odd-man rushes, they had good looks, Carter made some big saves,&#8221; Flyers coach Alain Vigneault said. &#8220;We made a couple defensive plays, capitalized on our good looks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Weegar ripped a one-timer from the left circle inside the far post for his first goal since Oct. 24, giving the Panthers a 1-0 lead early in the first period. Aaron Ekblad&#8217;s slap shot from the opposite side kicked out to Weegar, who fired it home for his fourth goal. Weegar had missed 16 of the last 18 games.</p>
<p>&#8220;I know we&#8217;re frustrated with a few things and we can make excuses up but we got a great leadership group in here and we have great guys in this room,&#8221; Weegar said. &#8220;We pick everybody up and we&#8217;re not too worried about it. We&#8217;ll get scoring, we&#8217;ll finish off in the right way this year.&#8221;</p>
<p>NOTES: Bobrovsky played in his 500th NHL game. &#8230; Flyers defenseman Shayne Gostisbehere was scratched for the second straight game after returning last Thursday from a knee injury that caused him to miss 10 games. &#8230; Flyers forward Joel Farabee sat out his third in a row. &#8230; Panthers center Brian Boyle missed his fourth straight game with an upper-body injury. &#8230; Panthers forward Aleksander Barkov recorded his 400th career point with an assist on the first goal.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Visit the New Jersey Devils on Tuesday night before returning home to face the Flyers again on Thursday.</p>
<p>Flyers: Begin a three-game road trip at the New York Islanders on Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">587839</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stone, Fleury lift Golden Knights over Panthers 7-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/stone-fleury-lift-golden-knights-over-panthers-7-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 04:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=586273</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Mark Stone scored two goals and had three assists, Marc-Andre Fleury recorded the 460th win of his career and the Vegas...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Mark Stone scored two goals and had three assists, Marc-Andre Fleury recorded the 460th win of his career and the Vegas Golden Knights beat the Florida Panthers 7-2 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Max Pacioretty had two goals and an assist, Nate Schmidt scored a goal and had an assist, and Shea Theodore and Jonathan Marchessault each also scored goals. Fleury stopped 23 shots to pass the New York Rangers&#8217; Henrik Lundqvist for sole possession of fifth place on the NHL all-time list for victories.</p>
<p>Stone tied his career high with five points.</p>
<p>“He’s a good player every night, but that was another level tonight,” coach Peter DeBoer said. &#8220;Not just offensively, but defensively, too. I thought he was great.”</p>
<p>Vincent Trocheck had a goal and an assist and Mike Hoffman also scored for the Panthers. Sergei Bobrovsky allowed six goals on 29 shots before being relieved by Sam Montembeault with 11:07 left in the third. Montembeault made nine saves. Jonathan Huberdeau had two assists.</p>
<p>Leading 3-2, the Golden Knights put the game away with four goals in the third.</p>
<p>They stretched their lead to 4-2 when Schmidt’s shot from the blue line bounced off Bobrovsky and went into the net 17 seconds in.</p>
<p>Theodore scored a short-handed goal at 4:11 to make the score 5-2. Marchessault’s goal at 8:53 made the score 6-2 and chased Bobrovsky. Pacioretty’s second goal with 4:44 left made it 7-2.</p>
<p>“At the start of the third, we think we have a shot, then we give up a goal and it went downhill quickly after that. Not fun to watch,” Panthers coach Joel Quenneville said.</p>
<p>With the score tied at 1, Stone’s second goal gave the Golden Knights a 2-1 lead. Stone used some slick stickwork in the slot and put the puck high into the net at 1:49 of the second.</p>
<p>“That goal to start the third period really deflated their bench and gave us all the momentum to take over the game,&#8221; Stone said.</p>
<p>Trocheck tied it at 2 on his wraparound goal at 11:52 of the second when he came from behind the net and tucked the puck just inside the post during a power-play.</p>
<p>“It’s a 2-2 game against one of the best teams in the league,” Trocheck said. “We come out that next shift, that’s one of the most important shifts of the game, we get outworked on that one. Fourth goal, get outworked again. Fifth goal, bad play, penalty kill. Every goal we gave up, they outworked us.”</p>
<p>Vegas answered 26 seconds later on Pacioretty’s goal. Pacioretty grabbed the puck in the slot and pounded it against Bobrovsky’s pads until it trickled through to make it 3-2.</p>
<p>Stone gave Vegas a 1-0 lead 2:15 when he grabbed a rebound in the low slot and poked the puck past Bobrovsky.</p>
<p>Hoffman tied it at 1 on his power-play goal. Trocheck passed from in front of the crease out to Hoffman in the right circle and his shot beat Fleury at 16:22 of the first. Vegas challenged for goalie interference by Trocheck, but the goal stood.</p>
<p>Florida’s Brett Connolly missed a penalty shot at 6:40 of the second. Fleury became the second goaltender to make at least 20 penalty shot saves, joining Roberto Luongo (29).</p>
<p>NOTES: Panthers C Aleksander Barkov missed his third game with a lower-body injury. &#8230; D MacKenzie Weegar missed the game with an illness. &#8230; C Brian Boyle missed his third game with an upper-body injury. &#8230; The Golden Knights have purchased an American Hockey League franchise membership from Spurs Sports &amp; Entertainment (which currently operates the San Antonio Rampage in San Antonio, TX) and are applying for relocation of the franchise to Henderson/Las Vegas, Nevada.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Golden Knights: host the Carolina Hurricanes on Saturday.</p>
<p>Panthers: host the Pittsburgh Penguins on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">586273</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Werenski scores OT goal in Blue Jackets 1-0 win over Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/werenski-scores-ot-goal-in-blue-jackets-1-0-win-over-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=585243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Zach Werenski scored 1:54 into overtime and the Columbus Blue Jackets extended their points streak to nine games with a 1-0 win over the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zach Werenski scored 1:54 into overtime and the Columbus Blue Jackets extended their points streak to nine games with a 1-0 win over the Florida Panthers on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Werenski picked up the puck off the right boards, circled around to the bottom of the circle and beat former teammate Sergei Bobrovski, who had made 45 saves until then.</p>
<p>Both teams had some good looks, especially late in the game, but both goalies were outstanding.</p>
<p>Elvis Merzlikins had 32 saves in picking up his fourth shutout of the season. Columbus has won eight of nine and hasn’t lost in regulation since Jan. 9, a streak of 8-0-1.</p>
<p>The Panthers lost for just the second time in their last nine games.</p>
<p>Bobrovsky is 0-2 playing in Columbus since bolting the Blue Jackets for Florida via free agency. He also lost on New Year’s Eve, with Werenski picking up a hat trick against his old teammate in a 4-1 win.</p>
<p>Merzlikins extended his win streak to seven games. He’s 11-2 since taking over the starting job in that Dec. 31 game after Joonas Korpisalo went down with a knee injury.</p>
<p>A Columbus goal by Boone Jenner 6:06 into the game was waved off after a review. Officials determined that teammate Cam Atkinson’s stick made contact with Bobrovsky’s glove and kept the goalie from making the save.</p>
<p>NOTES: Columbus C Alexander Wennberg was placed in injured reserve with an upper-body injury suffered Sunday at Montreal. He&#8217;s expected to miss 3-4 weeks. Rookie Ryan MacInnis replaced him in the lineup. &#8230; C Aleksander Barkov, Florida&#8217;s second-leading scorer, missed his second game with a lower-body injury. &#8230; Panthers D Mark Pysyk played in his 400th NHL game.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Panthers: Host Vegas on Thursday.</p>
<p>Blue Jackets: Host struggling Detroit on Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">585243</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pysyk scores 3 times as Panthers beat Maple Leafs 5-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/pysyk-scores-3-times-as-panthers-beat-maple-leafs-5-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=584788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TORONTO (AP) — Mark Pysyk scored three times in his first career hat trick, and the Florida Panthers beat the Toronto Maple Leafs 5-3 on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TORONTO (AP) — Mark Pysyk scored three times in his first career hat trick, and the Florida Panthers beat the Toronto Maple Leafs 5-3 on Monday night.</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman had a goal and an assist for Florida, which trailed 3-1 early in the third period. Mike Matheson had three assists, and Sergei Bobrovsky made 31 saves in the Panthers&#8217; seventh win in eight games.</p>
<p>Frederik Andersen started for Toronto and stopped seven of eight shots before departing with an upper-body injury after a collision with Panthers center Frank Vatrano. Michael Hutchinson came in and allowed three goals on 13 shots.</p>
<p>Auston Matthews, William Nylander and John Tavares scored for Toronto, which had won three in a row. Mitch Marner had two assists.</p>
<p>Matthews&#8217; 37th goal of the season made it 3-1 38 seconds into the third. But Pysyk and Huberdeau scored 58 seconds apart, tying it at 3 at 3:18.</p>
<p>Hoffman put the Panthers ahead to stay when he banked his 19th off Leafs defenseman Cody Ceci and through Hutchinson&#8217;s pads at 10:30.</p>
<p>Florida, which beat Toronto 8-4 in Sunrise on Jan. 12, weathered a late surge by the Maple Leafs before Pysyk completed his hat trick with an empty-netter.</p>
<p>The Panthers were without Aleksander Barkov, who was sidelined by a lower-body injury. The star center got hurt during Saturday&#8217;s 4-0 loss at Montreal in Florida&#8217;s first game back after the All-Star break and bye week.</p>
<p>Leafs defenseman Travis Dermott returned to the lineup after missing Saturday&#8217;s 2-1 overtime win against Ottawa with an illness, while winger Kasperi Kapanen was also back following a one-game banishment to the press box for being late to Friday&#8217;s practice.</p>
<p>Andersen, who watched Hutchinson pick up the victory Saturday, was injured when Vatrano slid into the goaltender off the rush. He didn&#8217;t appear to be favoring anything as he got to his feet, but Hutchinson took over to start the second.</p>
<p>NOTES: Florida D Anton Stralman, who was selected in the seventh round of the 2005 NHL draft by Toronto and played parts of two campaigns with the Leafs, suited up for the 800th regular-season game of his career.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Visit Columbus on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Maple Leafs: Visit the New York Rangers on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">584788</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Petry, Price lead Canadiens past Panthers 4-0</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/petry-price-lead-canadiens-past-panthers-4-0/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=584079</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MONTREAL (AP) &#8212; Jeff Petry had four assists, Carey Price made 29 saves and the Montreal Canadiens beat the Florida Panthers 4-0 on Saturday. Nick...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MONTREAL (AP) &#8212; Jeff Petry had four assists, Carey Price made 29 saves and the Montreal Canadiens beat the Florida Panthers 4-0 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Nick Suzuki, Artturi Lehkonen, Tomas Tatar and Brendan Gallagher scored for the Canadiens (24-22-7), who improved to 6-2-0 in their last eight games.</p>
<p>It was Price&#8217;s third shutout of the season and No. 47 of his career. Petry recorded his first career four-point game.</p>
<p>Playing their first game since Jan. 21, the Panthers (28-17-5) were shut out for the first time this season. They had won six in a row, scoring at least four goals in each of the victories.</p>
<p>Price beat Sergei Bobrovsky in a battle of the NHL&#8217;s two highest-paid goaltenders. Bobrovsky stopped 31 shots.</p>
<p>Florida center Aleksander Barkov left in the second period after taking a hit from Shea Weber along the end boards.</p>
<p>Montreal jumped in front 5:25 into the first period. Suzuki finished off a 2-on-1 for his 10th of the season.</p>
<p>The Panthers struggled to clear bodies out of their crease for most of the game and it cost them in the second.</p>
<p>On missed coverage by Florida, Lehkonen made it 2-0 by redirecting Petry&#8217;s shot between Bobrovsky&#8217;s pads at 6:01 for his 12th of the season.</p>
<p>Tatar added to Montreal&#8217;s lead at 13:35 on a pass from Phillip Danault behind the net. Four Panthers players surrounded Tatar in the crease, but the winger still managed to get his stick on the puck, earning his team-leading 19th goal.</p>
<p>Price did his part to shut down the league&#8217;s top-ranked offense. He made his best stop on Jonathan Huberdeau on a breakaway in the first.</p>
<p>NOTES: Claude Julien coached his 400th regular-season game with the Canadiens. &#8230; Montreal sent Jesperi Kotkaniemi down to the AHL&#8217;s Laval Rocket.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: Visit the Toronto Maple Leafs on Monday night.</p>
<p>Canadiens: Host the Columbus Blue Jackets on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">584079</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Acciari scores with 5.6 seconds left, Panthers beat Wild 5-4</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/acciari-scores-with-5-6-seconds-left-panthers-beat-wild-5-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 04:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=578407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ST. PAUL, Minn (AP) — Noel Acciari scored with 5.6 seconds left in the third period and the Florida Panthers won their fifth straight game,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ST. PAUL, Minn (AP) — Noel Acciari scored with 5.6 seconds left in the third period and the Florida Panthers won their fifth straight game, beating the Minnesota Wild 5-4 on Monday night.</p>
<p>Acciari was able to tip a shot from the point by Mark Pysyk that was first tipped by Aaron Ekblad. A video review upheld the goal.</p>
<p>It was Florida’s first regulation victory in Minnesota. Since a 2001 scoreless tie during the Wild’s inaugural season, Minnesota was 10-0-1 at home against Florida, including seven wins in a row.</p>
<p>Keith Yandle had a goal and three assists, and Aleksander Barkov added a goal and an assist for Florida. Evgenii Dadonov and Vincent Trocheck also scored. Sergei Bobrovsky made 29 saves in his second consecutive start after missing two games with an upper-body injury.</p>
<p>Luke Kunin had two goals, Zach Parise scored on the power play and Jared Spurgeon added a goal and an assist for Minnesota. Alex Stalock stopped 20 shots.</p>
<p>Trochek beat Stalock between the pads with 4:08 to go, tying the game at 4.</p>
<p>Kunin’s second goal of the game — a snap shot from the slot off the glove of Bobrovsky — gave Minnesota a 4-3 lead 7:06 into the third.</p>
<p>Joel Eriksson Ek and Ryan Suter each had two assists for the Wild.</p>
<p>With the score tied 2-all, Dadonov lifted his stick waist-high to redirect a shot by Yandle early in the third, but Parise countered just more than two minutes later, putting in a rebound for his fifth goal in four games. Parise has a career-best four straight games with a power-play goal.</p>
<p>Minnesota has seven power-play goals in 13 chances during the past four games after going 4 for 27 in the previous 10.</p>
<p>A highlight-reel effort by Barkov put Florida up 2-1 midway through the second.</p>
<p>After receiving a long outlet pass from Josh Brown just inside the blue line, the Florida captain sped past Carson Soucy through the right circle and cut across the crease before flipping a shot into the top right corner as he continued moving left.</p>
<p>NOTES: Mike Hoffman has a nine-game point streak, the longest this season by a Florida player. He had a 17-game point streak last season. … Spurgeon’s goal was the 27th power-play tally of his career, moving him past Brent Burns for most by a defenseman in Wild history. … Dominic Toninato returned for Florida after being sick and sitting out Saturday. The center played four seasons at the University of Minnesota-Duluth, and was the team captain in 2016-17.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Panthers: At the Chicago Blackhawks on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Wild: Home against the Detroit Red Wings on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">578407</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panthers beat Red Wings 4-1 for season-high 4-game streak</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/panthers-beat-red-wings-4-1-for-season-high-4-game-streak/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 04:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=577657</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DETROIT (AP) — The Florida Panthers were thrilled to have banged-up goaltender Sergei Bobrovsky back on the ice. He was pretty happy about it, too....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>DETROIT (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; The Florida Panthers were thrilled to have banged-up goaltender Sergei Bobrovsky back on the ice. He was pretty happy about it, too.<p>Bobrovsky made 27 saves, helping Florida beat the Detroit Red Wings 4-1 on Saturday night to win four straight for the first time this season.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Great to get back and play again,&#x201D; he said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I missed only two games and it feels like I haven&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t played for a month.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/FlaPanthers/status/1218733777528057857?s=20</embed></div><p>Bobrovsky looked sharp and appeared to finish the game healthy after being out with an upper-body injury. Those were good signs for a team that will be without goaltender&#xC2;&#xA0;Chris Driedger&#xC2;&#xA0;for several weeks with what&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s believed to be a groin injury.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;You can see the confidence of the team when he&#x2019;s back there,&#x201D; Florida&#x2019;s do-it-all player&#xC2;&#xA0;Mark Pysyk&#xC2;&#xA0;said.</p><p>Evgenii Dadonov and Pysyk scored late in the first period and that was enough offense to beat the lowly Red Wings.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/FlaPanthers/status/1218742102508679168?s=20</embed></div><p>Detroit has dropped four games in a row, giving the once-proud franchise an NHL-worst 12-33-4 record this season.</p><p>Red Wings coach Jeff Blashill, though, liked how physical and feisty his team played in its latest loss.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We&#x2019;re not going to limp through and just kind of play these games,&#x201D; Blashill said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We&#x2019;re gonna fight like crazy to win every night and fight like crazy to get better every day.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Dylan Larkin scored the 100th goal of his career with the Red Wings.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Hopefully, there&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s a lot more,&#x201D; he said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;It doesn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t feel great right now.&#x201D;</p><p>Larkin&#x2019;s goal pulled Detroit within a goal early in the second period, but the offensively challenged team could not get closer.</p><p>Jimmy Howard stopped the first 12 shots he faced before Florida scored on two of its final four shots in the first period. He finished with 34 saves.</p><p>The veteran, whose season has been stunted by injury, has played in four straight games. The team needed Howard to be in net on consecutive nights with Jonathan Bernier out with a lower-body injury.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;The past two games, he&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s played great for us,&#x201D; Larkin said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;He&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s been our best player. We need him to keep going.&#x201D;</p><p>Dadonov scored with 2:45 left in the opening period and Pysyk scored 1:25 later, giving the Panthers a 2-0 lead.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Scoring early has been good for us,&#x201D; coach Joel Quenneville said.</p><p>Larkin had a goal 5:15 into the second period, taking advantage of open ice after coming out of the penalty box and Darren Helm&#x2019;s long pass that set him up for a breakaway.</p><p>The Red Wings had an extra skater for a fifth time early in the third and failed to take advantage, getting only one shot on Bobrovsky.</p><p>Detroit had another power play midway through the third, but negated it 21 seconds later when Larkin was called for tripping.</p><p>Shortly thereafter, Bobrovsky stopped Frans Nielsen&#x2019;s breakaway shot and rebound attempt. Seconds later, Howard made a save when Barkov was alone in front of him with a chance to restore a two-goal lead.</p><p>Florida went on the power play with seven-plus minutes left and took advantage 15 seconds later. Aleksander Barkov redirected the puck off Keith Yandle&#x2019;s pass that was intentionally wide of the net.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;A lot of power plays out there tonight and our PK was pretty good,&#x201D; Quenneville said after his team&#x2019;s penalty killers didn&#x2019;t give up a goal on seven power plays. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Bob was really good and then he was our best (penalty) killer. Early in the game, he made a couple of big saves.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>NOTES: Red Wings C Valtteri Filppula left with a lower-body injury, but is not expected to miss the next game. &#x2026; Bobrovsky missed the previous two games with an upper-body injury. &#x2026; Detroit has a losing streak of at least four games for the fifth time this season. &#x2026; Dadonov has a team-high 21 goals.</p><p>UP NEXT</p><p>Panthers: Play at Minnesota on Monday night.</p><p>Red Wings: Play at Colorado on Monday night.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">577657</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boyle scores winner, Panthers hold off Kings 4-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/boyle-scores-winner-panthers-hold-off-kings-4-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 04:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=576967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Sam Montembeault came off the bench to help the Florida Panthers hang on for a win. Brian Boyle scored the eventual...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Sam Montembeault came off the bench to help the Florida Panthers hang on for a win.</p>
<p>Brian Boyle scored the eventual winning goal and the Panthers held off a late surge to beat the Los Angeles Kings 4-3 on Thursday night to win their third straight game.</p>
<p>Montembeault made 23 saves for the Panthers after entering the game with 9:55 left in the first. Chris Driedger started in goal for the Panthers and made four saves before he injured his right leg.</p>
<p>Montembeault was recalled from Springfield of the AHL last Sunday, loaned back on Monday, and then recalled Wednesday.</p>
<p>“I had three flights in three days: Sunday, Monday and Tuesday,” Montembault said. “Obviously, I wasn’t expecting to play in this one, but it turns out we played very well and we had a good win.”</p>
<p>Mike Matheson, Frank Vatrano and Evgenii Dadonov also scored for Florida. Jonathan Huberdeau, who set the franchise points record in last Sunday’s 8-4 win over Toronto, recorded an assist on Dadonov’s goal.</p>
<p>&#8220;He did what he had to do,&#8221; coach Joel Quenneville said of Montembeault. &#8220;You lose some momentum in a game like that, but he was composed and did what he had to do.”</p>
<p>Anze Kopitar had a goal and two assists. Adrian Kempe and Alex Iafallo also scored goals for the Kings. Jack Campbell stopped 22 shots in his third start in four games. The Kings have lost six of their last seven games, including a 4-3 loss at Tampa Bay on Tuesday.</p>
<p>“They swarmed. They held on to pucks in our zone. They made us make mistakes,” Kings coach Todd McLellan said. “We’re professionals. We should be able to show up, but let’s get out of the sunshine, let’s get back to the cold weather.”</p>
<p>Behind 4-0, the Kings scored three goals in the second half of the third period.</p>
<p>Iafallo tipped in a shot by Drew Doughty with 8:18 left to make it 4-1. Kempe’s power-play goal, a shot from the right circle beat Montembeault with 4:52 left and closed the score to 4-2. Kopitar poked in a rebound with 2:40 left and the lead was trimmed to 4-3.</p>
<p>“It’s the desperation part that kicked in in the second half of the third,” Kopitar said. “We’ve got figure out how to bring that to the start of games.”</p>
<p>Leading 2-0, the Panthers stretched the score to 3-0 on Matheson’s power-play goal. Aaron Ekblad passed across to Matheson at the point and he fired the puck past Campbell at 4:55 of the third.</p>
<p>Boyle’s goal at 7:06 made it 4-0.</p>
<p>“We needed two points at home. That was the objective; we got it.” Boyle said. “It’s a good lesson to see how quickly it can get away from you.”</p>
<p>Vatrano gave the Panthers a 2-0 lead after Dominic Toninato dropped the puck to Vatrano and his one-timer from above the right circle beat Campbell on the glove side at 3:06 of the second.</p>
<p>The Panthers took a 1-0 lead on Dadonov’s power-play goal. Huberdeau made a centering pass to Dadonov, who one-timed the puck past Campbell at 6:04 of the first.</p>
<p>NOTES: Panthers G Sergei Bobrovsky missed his second game because of an upper-body injury he sustained in practice Saturday. &#8230; Kings C Blake Lizotte missed his fourth straight game and is day-to-day with a lower-body injury… Kopitar leads the Kings with 43 points, scoring 17 goals and recording 26 assists.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Kings: visit the Philadelphia Flyers on Saturday.</p>
<p>Panthers: visit Detroit Red Wings on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">576967</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huberdeau sets franchise points mark, Panthers beat Leafs 8-4</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/huberdeau-sets-franchise-points-mark-panthers-beat-leafs-8-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 04:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NHL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=574995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Jonathan Huberdeau is looking ahead after becoming the career points leader for the Florida Panthers. Huberdeau had a goal and an...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Jonathan Huberdeau is looking ahead after becoming the career points leader for the Florida Panthers.</p>
<p>Huberdeau had a goal and an assist, surpassing Olli Jokinen for the points lead with 420, and the Panthers beat the Toronto Maple Leafs 8-4 on Sunday night.</p>
<p>“It’s cool. Another great night. Couldn’t ask for better,” Huberdeau said. “Now it’s just try to take it all in tonight with my family and tomorrow focus on getting into the playoffs.”</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman scored two goals for Florida, and Aleksander Barkov and Vincent Trocheck each had a goal and two assists. Frank Vatrano, Mike Matheson and Josh Brown also scored in the Panthers’ highest scoring game of the season. Brett Connolly had two assists, and Chris Driedger made 43 saves.</p>
<p>“I see more balance in our game, more compete, we’ve got all four lines going,” coach Joel Quenneville said. “Everybody’s contributing and a lot of enthusiasm on the bench as well as the ice.”</p>
<p>The eight goals allowed were the most for Toronto since a 9-2 loss to Nashville on Nov. 18, 2014.</p>
<p>“You take (the loss) as what it is which is a good slap in the face,” Maple Leafs coach Sheldon Keefe said. “It&#8217;s a good reminder of how we can&#8217;t play if we have any intention at all of being a successful team. It was a big step backwards for us here today defensively.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mitch Marner scored twice for the Maple Leafs, and Zach Hyman had a goal and two assists. John Tavares also scored.</p>
<p>Toronto goaltender Frederik Andersen allowed four goals on 12 shots before he was pulled 49 seconds into the second period. Michael Hutchinson stopped 13 shots.</p>
<p>&#8220;Right off the bat there we were giving their best players walk-ins to the net and it&#8217;s not acceptable,” Marner said. “(We) were leaving our goalies out to dry on multiple goals tonight. It&#8217;s unfair to them and we have to be way better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marner’s 13th goal got the Maple Leafs within three early in the third. But Hoffman converted a one-timer off a pass from Huberdeau, making it 8-4 with the power-play goal 4:33 into the period.</p>
<p>Toronto had a goal disallowed with 6:49 left in the third due to a high stick by Cody Ceci.</p>
<p>Leading 3-0, the Panthers scored on their first three shots of the second. Matheson chased Andersen 49 seconds into the period. Vatrano’s short-handed goal, a shot from the low slot off a pass from Barkov, made it 5-0 at 2:25.</p>
<p>Hyman flipped in a loose puck from in front to make it 5-1 at 3:30 of the second.</p>
<p>Trocheck’s shot from the top of the right circle beat Hutchinson at 5:46 for a 6-1 lead.</p>
<p>Huberdeau’s goal, a backhanded shot from in front, stretched the Panthers’ lead to 7-1 at 12:38 of the second.</p>
<p>NOTES: Marner has nine goals and 17 assists in 17 games since returning from an ankle injury that sidelined him for 11 games. &#8230; Maple Leafs forward Andreas Johnsson returned after missing the past 15 games with a leg injury. &#8230; Panthers C Brian Boyle played his 800th NHL game. &#8230; Panthers G Sergei Bobrovsky missed the game with an upper-body injury.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Maple Leafs: Visit the New Jersey Devils on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Panthers: Host the Los Angeles Kings on Thursday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">574995</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Acciari, Bobrovsky lift Panthers over Canucks 5-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/acciari-bobrovsky-lift-panthers-over-canucks-5-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 04:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida Panthers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=574048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Noel Acciari scored two goals and Sergei Bobrovsky made 30 saves in his first start in three games to lift the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNRISE, Fla. (AP) — Noel Acciari scored two goals and Sergei Bobrovsky made 30 saves in his first start in three games to lift the Florida Panthers over the Vancouver Canucks 5-2 on Thursday night.</p>
<p>Mike Hoffman, Evgenii Dadonov and Mark Pysyk also scored for Florida. Jonathan Huberdeau had two assists to move within one point of tying Olli Jokinen for the most in Panthers franchise history (419).</p>
<p>Tyler Motte and Brock Boeser scored for the Canucks. Thatcher Demko made 44 saves.</p>
<p>The Canucks lost their second in a row after winning seven straight, and have given up 14 goals in those two losses.</p>
<p>Leading 3-1, the Panthers increased their lead on a power-play goal by Hoffman, whose shot while on one knee went high into the net with 16:20 left in the second.</p>
<p>Acciari deflected in a shot from Aaron Ekblad with 13:05 left in the third to make it 5-1. Acciari has 12 goals in his last 12 games.</p>
<p>Motte’s goal with 7:46 left made it 5-2.</p>
<p>The Panthers scored goals on their first two shots of the game.</p>
<p>Acciari made the score 1-0 when he grabbed a loose puck in the right circle and fired it past Demko 1 minute in.</p>
<p>Pysyk made it 2-0 when he took a nice pass from Colton Sceviour in the slot and pushed it by Demko at 16:59.</p>
<p>Boeser closed the score to 2-1 when he redirected a shot from the point by Tyler Myers into the net at 6:51 of the first.</p>
<p>Dadnov flipped the puck over Demko from the slot with 1:07 left in the first to make it 3-1.</p>
<p>NOTES: Panthers C Brian Boyle recorded his 100th NHL assist on the goal by Pysyk. &#8230; D MacKenzie Weegar practiced Wednesday, but missed his eighth consecutive game with an upper-body injury. &#8230; Boeser has 17 points in his last 17 games for the Canucks.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Canucks: visit the Buffalo Sabres on Saturday.</p>
<p>Panthers: host the Toronto Maple Leafs on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">574048</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/06/florida-panthers-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Florida Panthers Logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
