<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Miami Dolphins &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-dolphins/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:03:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Miami Dolphins &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>AP sources: Dolphins tell LB Van Noy he will be released</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ap-sources-dolphins-tell-lb-van-noy-he-will-be-released/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Veteran linebacker Kyle Van Noy is moving on after one season with the Miami Dolphins, and he&#8217;s not happy about it. The...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Veteran linebacker Kyle Van Noy is moving on after one season with the Miami Dolphins, and he&#8217;s not happy about it.</p>
<p>The Dolphins told Van Noy he will be released, two people familiar with the discussion confirmed to The Associated Press on condition of anonymity Tuesday because the Dolphins had not commented.</p>
<p>In a statement, Van Noy said he was disappointed and surprised.</p>
<p>“As a captain, I gave my all to the team,&#8221; he said. “I fought through a painful hip injury during the season, including spending a night in the hospital after a game. I was brought there to be a leader, and I know my teammates looked up to and respected me.”</p>
<p>Miami will clear nearly $10 million in cap space with the move. Van Noy signed a $51 million, four-year deal as a free agent a year ago.</p>
<p>Despite his injury, Van Noy had six sacks and 69 tackles in 14 games for a Dolphins defense that ranked sixth in points allowed. He has also played for the Lions and Patriots.</p>
<p>The move signals the Dolphins want to be aggressive in free agency after going 10-6 and missing the playoffs in their second season under coach Brian Flores. They also have two picks in the first round of the draft, including the No. 3 overall selection, and two picks in the second round.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874782</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins kicker Sanders signs $22 million deal through 2026</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-kicker-sanders-signs-22-million-deal-through-2026/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 19:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=865985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins kicker Jason Sanders has a new contract to go with his All-Pro status. Sanders, the Dolphins&#8217; leader in career field...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins kicker Jason Sanders has a new contract to go with his All-Pro status.</p>
<p>Sanders, the Dolphins&#8217; leader in career field goal percentage, signed a $22 million extension through 2026. The deal announced Tuesday includes $10 million guaranteed.</p>
<p>Sanders was chosen All-Pro after tying the franchise’s single-season points record with 144 in 2020. His 36 field goals made ranked second in the NFL and second in Dolphins history, and his field goal rate of 92% was a team record.</p>
<p>His career totals are 77 of 89 for 87%. Sanders was a seventh-round pick by Miami in 2018.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">865985</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/jason-sanders-e1613504646809.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/jason-sanders-e1613504646809.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/jason-sanders-e1613504646809.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Jason Sanders</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bills eliminate Dolphins with 56-26 rout; set to host Colts</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/bills-eliminate-dolphins-with-56-26-rout-set-to-host-colts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 21:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=821056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ORCHARD PARK, N.Y. (AP) — Josh Allen and the Buffalo Bills were intent on not easing into the playoffs, while ending the Miami Dolphins&#8217; chances....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ORCHARD PARK, N.Y. (AP) — Josh Allen and the Buffalo Bills were intent on not easing into the playoffs, while ending the Miami Dolphins&#8217; chances.</p>
<p>In a season-ending game in which the Dolphins had far more riding on the outcome, the Bills put an empathic stamp on their breakthrough year with a 56-26 rout on Sunday. In clinching the AFC’s second seed, Buffalo will host its first playoff game in 24 years by facing the the Frank Reich-coached Indianapolis Colts next weekend.</p>
<p>Reich is the former Bills backup who 28 years ago to the day led Buffalo to overcome a 32-point deficit in a 41-38 overtime win over the Houston Oilers in what still stands as the largest comeback in NFL history.</p>
<p>For Miami, the loss left coach Brian Flores and the Dolphins on the outside looking in by squandering an opportunity to clinch just their first postseason berth in 18 years. Rather than taking care of their own business by clinching a playoff berth with a win, the Dolphins’ postseason ended with the Colts clinching the No. 7 seed by defeating Jacksonville.</p>
<p>“We’re just worried about today, that’s where my mind is — our performance today. It’s not on anything other than that,” Flores said. “It wasn’t good enough. Right now, I’m disappointed we didn’t play well today.”</p>
<p>Not even close.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (10-6) didn’t get results they needed earlier in the day after Cleveland beat Pittsburgh and Baltimore routed Cincinnati. And the team unraveled in all three phases in being exposed by a Bills team showing no signs of relenting in racking up the second-most points in team history.</p>
<p>After falling behind 3-0 on Jason Sanders&#8217; 49-yard field goal, Buffalo responded by scoring four times in the second quarter to build a 28-6 lead at halftime. And the Bills didn’t let up in the second half.</p>
<p>Rather than rely on Cleveland beating Pittsburgh, Buffalo wrapped up the AFC’s No. 2 playoff seed with the win.</p>
<p>“It just shows that this is a different Buffalo Bills football team. We don’t have to get in on anybody’s back,” left tackle Dion Dawkins said. “This is all our doing. And it feels good to kick that front door out and sweep the East.”</p>
<p>Allen threw three touchdown passes and Isaiah McKenzie scored three times, including returning a punt return 84 yards. The defense even got on the scoreboard with Josh Norman returning the first of three Tua Tagovailoa’s interceptions 16 yards for a touchdown.</p>
<p>Allen finished 18 of 25 for 224 yards passing in playing just the first half before being replaced by Matt Barkley. Allen upped his total to 4,544 yards passing, to eclipse the team’s single-season record of 4,359 set by Drew Bledsoe in 2002.</p>
<p>Buffalo matched a franchise record with 13 wins, set in both 1990 and ’91, while also completing its first season sweep of division rivals.</p>
<p>The young, rebuilding Dolphins might have finished with double-digits wins for just the second time in 11 years, but fell well short at Buffalo.</p>
<p>“Nobody wants to get beat like that,” Dolphins cornerback Xavien Howard said.</p>
<p>“They’ve got a lot of weapons. Josh Allen, man, is a great quarterback doing some great things with the guys he’s got around him,” he added. “I feel like we’ve got something here. Everybody believes in Flores. Even though we came up short, I feel like the future is bright for us.”</p>
<p>Maybe not so bright yet at quarterback.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa finished 35 of 58 for 361 and three interceptions — one more than he had all season — over the span of four second-half possessions.</p>
<p>He closed the season with a 6-3 record, and didn’t have Ryan Fitzpatrick to bail him out as the veteran backup did in rallying Miami to a last-second 26-25 win at Las Vegas last weekend. Fitzpatrick didn’t travel with the team after testing positive for COVID-19 on Thursday.</p>
<p>“That’s not the way we wanted to go down. There are a lot of things to learn from,” Tagovailoa said. “All I can do is continue to grow, continue to get better.”</p>
<p>The Dolphins’ usually stout defense, which entered the game leading the NFL in allowing just 18.8 points per game, instead allowed the fourth-most points in franchise history, including the playoffs.</p>
<p>The Bills backups on offense combined for three touchdowns in the second half. Rookie running back Antonio Williams scored two TDs rushing in his NFL debut, a day after being called up from Buffalo’s practice squad.</p>
<p>Barkley went 6 of 13 for 164 yards, including a 56-yard TD pass to Gabriel Davis, and an interception.</p>
<p>DOUBLE-DIGIT PICKS</p>
<p>Howard matched a single-season franchise record with his 10th interception by picking off Barkley in the third quarter. Howard matched the team record set by Dick Westmoreland in 1967, and became the NFL’s first player to have 10 interceptions in one season since Antonio Cromartie had that many with the Chargers in 2007.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: Season over.</p>
<p>Bills: Face the Colts in preparing to host first playoff game since 30-27 loss to Jacksonville in wild-card round and Hall of Famer quarterback Jim Kelly’s final game on Dec. 28, 1996.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">821056</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/210103_Tua_Tagovailoa.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/210103_Tua_Tagovailoa.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/210103_Tua_Tagovailoa.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210103_Tua_Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins QB Ryan Fitzpatrick tests positive for COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-qb-ryan-fitzpatrick-tests-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 18:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=818218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Any debate about who should start for the Miami Dolphins this week at quarterback ended Thursday with backup Ryan Fitzpatrick&#8217;s positive test...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Any debate about who should start for the Miami Dolphins this week at quarterback ended Thursday with backup Ryan Fitzpatrick&#8217;s positive test for COVID-19.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick, who came off the bench to rescue his team last week, is expected to miss Sunday’s regular-season finale at Buffalo as Miami tries to clinch an AFC wild-card berth.</p>
<p>The Dolphins placed Fitzpatrick on the reserve-COVID-19 list.</p>
<p>“It hurts,” safety Eric Rowe said. “He’s a leader of our team. He brings energy, even in the Zoom meetings. But you’ve got to push forward. I’m just praying for his health.”</p>
<p>Coach Brian Flores had already said rookie Tua Tagovailoa will start his ninth game in a row Sunday, to the consternation of many Miami fans who prefer Fitzpatrick. The 38-year-old veteran replaced Tagovailoa last week in the fourth quarter and orchestrated an improbable comeback win at Las Vegas that allowed the Dolphins (10-5) to retain control of their playoff chances.</p>
<p>Miami signed Jake Rudock as Tagovailoa’s new backup. Rudock has thrown five passes in the NFL, all in 2017, and has spent multiple stints on the Dolphins’ practice squad in 2019-20.</p>
<p>The Dolphins also placed linebacker Elandon Roberts on injured reserve because of a knee injury. Everyone else on the active roster practiced Thursday, an indication no player was identified as a high-risk close contact with Fitzpatrick.</p>
<p>His availability for a possible wild-card playoff game next week is in question. The 16-year veteran has never made the postseason, and the Dolphins will clinch a postseason berth if they beat Buffalo.</p>
<p>“He’s our guy,” receiver Isaiah Ford said. “But if this year has taught us anything, it is to expect the unexpected. We all love Ryan, but we’ve got a job to do. I think everybody is focused on getting it done.&#8221;</p>
<p>COVID-19 cases are on the rise in Florida, which reported 17,192 new cases Thursday, the most yet in the state in a single day.</p>
<p>The Dolphins’ lineup has endured only modest disruptions because of the pandemic. Just one starter — running back Myles Gaskin — went on the COVID-19 list in December, and he missed two games.</p>
<p>“Everyone has had to make some sacrifices,” Flores said last week. “Overall it has been good, as long as guys follow the protocols, make the sacrifices and make smart decisions. We’re still in it, though. We’re not done by any stretch of the imagination.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">818218</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1577491182335.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1577491182335.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1577491182335.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ryan fitzpatrick</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fitz will watch as Dolphins try to get him into the playoffs</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/fitz-will-watch-as-dolphins-try-to-get-him-into-the-playoffs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 19:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=814722</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — With one more win by the Miami Dolphins, Ryan Fitzpatrick will be playoff-bound for the first time in his 16-year career. He...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — With one more win by the Miami Dolphins, Ryan Fitzpatrick will be playoff-bound for the first time in his 16-year career.</p>
<p>He might not play, though.</p>
<p>After pulling off a FitzMagic trick Saturday night to beat the Las Vegas Raiders, Fitzpatrick returns to standby mode this week. Tua Tagovailoa remains Miami’s starting quarterback heading into Sunday’s high-stakes regular-season finale at Buffalo.</p>
<p>By beating the Bills, the Dolphins (10-5) would clinch only their third playoff berth since 2001, and Fitzpatrick is trying to end a personal postseason drought. He has thrown 5,054 passes for eight teams, all in the regular season.</p>
<p>“I am well aware that I’ve never been to the playoffs, I promise you,” the 38-year-old Fitzpatrick said. &#8220;And we would love nothing more than to get there.”</p>
<p>WHAT’S WORKING</p>
<p>Coach Brian Flores’ two-quarterback system is working, even if he recoils from that label.</p>
<p>“The label is we’re going to do what we’ve got to do to win,” Flores said.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick came off the bench in the final 10 minutes Saturday to throw for 182 yards, including a desperation heave he completed in the final seconds even though his face mask was being jerked. The pass and penalty netted 49 yards to set up a field goal for a 26-25 victory.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick replaced Tagovailoa, who threw for only 94 yards on 22 attempts. The rookie improved to 6-2 as a starter but has now been benched twice in the fourth quarter, stirring plenty of debate about whether he deserves the No. 1 job in January — or next season.</p>
<p>“He has played fairly well,” Flores said. &#8220;People may disagree, but we’ll just agree to disagree in that instance.</p>
<p>&#8220;It’s not based off of one game or one quarter. There are a lot of practices that people don’t see, meetings that people don’t see, walk-throughs that no one sees. Everyone wants to make a judgment and try to make a decision for us about what we should do without all of that information.”</p>
<p>WHAT NEEDS HELP</p>
<p>Should the Dolphins lose Sunday, they can still make the playoffs with a loss by one of three teams they&#8217;re battling for an AFC wild-card spot.</p>
<p>A loss by Baltimore at Cincinnati, by Indianapolis at home against Jacksonville, or by Cleveland at home against Pittsburgh would get Miami into the postseason even with six defeats. The Ravens and Colts are favored by two touchdowns, however, and the Browns are also favored.</p>
<p>The Dolphins are 5-point underdogs. FiveThirtyEight puts their chances of making the playoffs at 73%.</p>
<p>STOCK UP</p>
<p>Second-year running back Myles Gaskin, who has been sidelined because of a knee injury and COVID-19 protocols, played for only the second time since Nov. 1 and had the best game of his career.</p>
<p>Gaskin rushed for 87 yards and had two scoring receptions, including one when he turned a short pass into a 59-yard touchdown. He totaled 169 yards from scrimmage.</p>
<p>STOCK DOWN</p>
<p>Cornerback Byron Jones had his worst game of the year. In the wild final minutes he was burned on a long pass for an 85-yard touchdown and called for a 49-yard pass interference penalty.</p>
<p>Officiating on both plays was questionable, with “calls that could go either way,&#8221; Flores said.</p>
<p>“I have a lot of confidence in Byron,&#8221; the coach said. &#8220;He has played well all year. Thankfully we were able to overcome those two situations.”</p>
<p>INJURED</p>
<p>The Dolphins hope receiver DeVante Parker (hamstring) and defensive end Shaq Lawson (shoulder) will be available this week after both missed Saturday&#8217;s game. Less promising is the outlook for receiver Jakeem Grant (ankle), guard Solomon Kindley (knee) linebacker Elandon Roberts (knee).</p>
<p>KEY NUMBER</p>
<p>0 for 10 — the Raiders on third downs Saturday. For the season Miami leads the NFL in third-down defense at 31%.</p>
<p>NEXT STEPS</p>
<p>The previous time the Dolphins played at Buffalo in January was in 1991. In December they’ve lost three in a row there by a combined score of 85-33.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">814722</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-1-e1609185587903.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-1-e1609185587903.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-1-e1609185587903.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ryan fitzpatrick (1)</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins stun Raiders 26-25 to move step closer to playoffs</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-stun-raiders-26-25-to-move-step-closer-to-playoffs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=813114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick completed a 41-yard pass to Mack Hollins while being dragged down by the facemask and the Miami Dolphins moved...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LAS VEGAS (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick completed a 41-yard pass to Mack Hollins while being dragged down by the facemask and the Miami Dolphins moved one step closer to a playoff berth when Jason Sanders’ 44-yard field goal with 1 second remaining gave them a 26-25 victory over the Las Vegas Raiders on Saturday night.</p>
<p>The Raiders (7-8) chose to run down the clock for a go-ahead field goal instead of trying for a touchdown with Josh Jacobs going down on purpose at the 1-yard line and Derek Carr taking a knee to set up Daniel Carlson’s 22-yard field goal with 19 seconds left.</p>
<p>But the Dolphins had some late-game magic with Fitzpatrick launching the deep pass to Hollins while being dragged down by Arden Key. The penalty moved the ball down to the Las Vegas 26, setting up Sanders’ winning kick.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (10-5) moved a half-game ahead of Baltimore in the AFC playoff race and can clinch a wild-card berth with a win next week at Buffalo.</p>
<p>The Raiders (7-8) were eliminated with their fifth loss in six games and will be out of the postseason for the 17th time in 18 seasons.</p>
<p>The back-and-forth final few minutes from Fitzpatrick and Carr made up for a game that lacked offensive fireworks for most of the night. After the Dolphins tied the game at 16 with 4:01 to play, the Raiders took little time to answer.</p>
<p>A holding penalty on first down put them in a hole, but Carr got them right out of it when he scrambled away from pressure despite an injured groin and launched a deep pass to Nelson Agholor, who outjumped Byron Jones for the catch.</p>
<p>Agholor then juked safety Bobby McCain and raced to the end zone for the 85-yard score that put the Raiders up 22-16 after Carlson missed the extra point.</p>
<p>That looked as if it could be costly when Fitzpatrick answered with a short pass to Myles Gaskin that turned unto a huge gain. Gaskin broke a tackle from Raekwon McMillan and then got sprung from some downfield blocks on the way to a 59-yard touchdown. Jason Sanders’ extra point gave the Dolphins the 23-22 lead.</p>
<p>That proved short-lived when Jones was called for the penalty on a deep throw to Agholor that gave the Raiders the ball at the 22. Las Vegas then ran out most of the clock but not enough.</p>
<p>NOT TUA’S TIME</p>
<p>Dolphins rookie Tua Tagovailoa struggled to move the ball with his 22 passes gaining only 94 yards. He did connect on a 10-yard TD pass to Gaskin that tied the game in the third quarter, but was pulled in the fourth for Fitzpatrick with the Raiders leading 16-13. Fitzpatrick completed two long passes to Mike Gesicki before the drive stalled and the Dolphins settled for a game-tying 22-yard field goal from Sanders.</p>
<p>WONDERFUL WALLER</p>
<p>After setting an NFL record for tight ends with 425 yards receiving the past three games, Las Vegas’ Darren Waller delivered once again for the Raiders. He had five catches for 112 yards, giving him 1,079 yards on the season for his second straight 1,000-yard campaign. The only other Raiders TE with a 1,000-yard season is Todd Christensen, who had three in the 1980s.</p>
<p>INJURY REPORT</p>
<p>Dolphins: WR Jakeem Grant left in the second half with an ankle injury. &#8230; LB Elandon Roberts was taken off on a stretcher with a knee injury in the third quarter and didn’t return.</p>
<p>Raiders: G Denzelle Good left the game with an ankle injury late in the first half.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: Visit Buffalo on Jan. 3</p>
<p>Raiders: Visit Denver on Jan. 3.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">813114</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190726 dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins eliminate Patriots from playoff race with 22-12 win</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-eliminate-patriots-from-playoff-race-with-22-12-win/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 21:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=805309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — The Miami Dolphins’ grinding ground game sent the New England Patriots into full retreat and out of the playoff picture for the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — The Miami Dolphins’ grinding ground game sent the New England Patriots <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MxplvsyTowc">into full retreat </a>and out of the playoff picture for the first time in 12 years.</p>
<p>Undrafted rookie <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sPxLFQMiFp4">Salvon Ahmed </a>and veteran Matt Breida combined for 208 yards rushing Sunday to lead the Dolphins to a 22-12 victory over the Patriots, who were eliminated from postseason contention.</p>
<p>The Dolphins entered the game last in the league in yards per carry, and Ahmed became their first 100-yard rusher since 2018, totaling 122 yards and scoring a 2-point conversion on a trick play.</p>
<p>“I just went out there to try and do my best,” Ahmed said “It’s just fun to be part of a win. This is a big win.”</p>
<p>Breida added 86 yards and the Dolphins totaled a season-high 250, the most allowed by New England in seven years.</p>
<p>The Patriots (6-8) will finish at .500 or worse for the first time since 2000, the year they drafted Tom Brady. Their NFL-record run of 11 consecutive playoff appearances will end, and they&#8217;ll fall one year short of matching the Dallas Cowboys’ NFL record of 20 consecutive winning seasons.</p>
<p>Buffalo clinched the AFC East title with a win Saturday.</p>
<p>“It’s obviously a disappointing day for us,” coach Bill Belichick said. “We didn’t do anything really well enough to win the game. We all just came up short. To win these games, we’ve got to do a better job, I’ve got to do a better job.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Dolphins (9-5) bolstered their wild-card chances and are assured of a winning record for only the second time since 2008.</p>
<p>“It’s always good to win, that’s why these guys put all the blood, sweat and tears in,” said coach Brian Flores, a Belichick protege. “I’m happy we can bring some joy to our fans, because they deserve it.”</p>
<p>With their three most productive pass catchers sitting out the game because of injuries, the Dolphins kept it on the ground. They were shut out in the first half, but mounted a 14-play, 90-yard touchdown drive midway through the second half to take the lead for good.</p>
<p>Quarterback Tua Tagovailoa ran it in from the 3 on third down after he couldn’t find an open receiver.</p>
<p>“When you have that kind of success in the run game, I think it doesn’t just help the quarterback, it helps the whole team,” Tagovailoa said.</p>
<p>The Dolphins then sprang a hook-and-ladder for the 2-point conversion, with receiver Isaiah Ford flipping a lateral to Ahmed, who ran into the end zone untouched. That put the Dolphins ahead 15-9, and they sealed the victory by mounting a grinding 75-yard touchdown drive on their next possession.</p>
<p>Ahmed became the first undrafted rookie in Dolphins history to rush for 100 yards.</p>
<p>“Ahmed ran hard. Breida ran hard. The offensive line blocked well,” Flores said. “It’s about execution, execution, execution.”</p>
<p>Cam Newton finished 17 for 27 for 209 yards, but for the second consecutive week he failed to get New England into the end zone.</p>
<p>“I just have to play better and be better,” Newton said.</p>
<p>Four times the Patriots settled for a field goal after driving inside the Miami 30. Nick Folk made kicks of 45, 36, 45 and 42 yards.</p>
<p>FAILING TO SCORE</p>
<p>The Dolphins were unable to convert several scoring chances, including when they drove 95 yards in the first quarter before J.C. Jackson made his eighth interception of the year, picking off a third-down pass by Tagovailoa at the goal line.</p>
<p>“I tried to force one in there.” Tagovailoa said.</p>
<p>An 86-yard touchdown <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_1l87SsZWyM">on a fumble return </a>by Miami’s Xavien Howard was reversed by a replay review that showed the loose ball touched another player with a foot out of bounds. The reversal represented a 10-point swing, because New England kept the ball and kicked a field goal on the next play.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Patriots: CB Stephon Gilmore (right knee) left the game in the second quarter and was helped to the locker room. LB Ja’Whaun Bentley (arm) also went to the locker room in the first half. DE John Simon (hamstring) and C David Andrews (calf) were sidelined in the second half. Leading rusher Damien Harris was inactive because of an ankle injury.</p>
<p>Dolphins: G Solomon Kindley limped off the field in the third quarter. WRs DeVante Parker (hamstring) and Jakeem Grant (hamstring) and TE Mike Gesicki (shoulder) were inactive.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: They play Saturday at the Las Vegas Raiders (7-7), who have lost four of their past five games.</p>
<p>Patriots: They play host on Monday, Dec. 28 to the Bills (11-3).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">805309</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190726 dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins wide receiver Allen Hurns, charity organization hold holiday toy drive in Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-wide-receiver-allen-hurns-charity-organization-hold-holiday-toy-drive-in-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 15:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=804386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dolphins wide receiver Allen Hurns and his foundation 88 Blessings passed out some holiday help. The player and his mother spread Christmas cheer through South...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dolphins wide receiver Allen Hurns and his foundation 88 Blessings passed out some holiday help.</p>
<p>The player and his mother spread Christmas cheer through South Florida with his Winter Wonderland Toy Drive.</p>
<p>The giveaway happened at the Miami-Dade Police Department on Northwest 81st Street and 7th Avenue.</p>
<p>Hurns said he is grateful to be in a position to help others.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s about giving. You know, 88 kids and faces getting gifts, I know it means the world to them. Also, it just gives those kids hope. I was once in their shoes. I went through the same struggles that they went through, and for them to see that I overcame a lot of these things, they kind of appreciate that,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>About 88 kids received toys and other gifts thanks to the foundation.</p>
<p>This is the organization&#8217;s fifth year of hosting a holiday event for children in the community.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">804386</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/122020-88-Blessings-toy-drive.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5a4b1c15-7e16-4619-80a5-ee977bd03d11/9a966886-bd4f-4906-a455-4f7427b3f783/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219460~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5a4b1c15-7e16-4619-80a5-ee977bd03d11/9a966886-bd4f-4906-a455-4f7427b3f783/main.mp4*~hmac=b3c780dd587fb31749a8292399ab1426e649067f5284be85273bdb606c67a68d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/122020-88-Blessings-toy-drive.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/122020-88-Blessings-toy-drive.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">122020 88 Blessings toy drive</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Patriots looking up at Dolphins in standings for a change</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/patriots-looking-up-at-dolphins-in-standings-for-a-change/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 19:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=802741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Even five time zones away in Hawaii, where Tua Tagovailoa grew up following football and dreaming of an NFL career, the New England Patriots left...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even five time zones away in Hawaii, where Tua Tagovailoa grew up following football and dreaming of an NFL career, the New England Patriots left an impression he can describe with just one word.</p>
<p>“Dominant,” Tagovailoa said.</p>
<p>No more. Mediocre is more like it in 2020, the first year of New England&#8217;s post-Tom Brady era.</p>
<p>The Patriots (6-7) head into Sunday’s game against the Dolphins and Tagovailoa with their NFL-record run of 11 consecutive playoff appearances in dire jeopardy, and their reign atop the AFC East at an end.</p>
<p>For a change, the Patriots are looking up in the December standings at the Dolphins (8-5), who need a win to bolster their chances to reach the playoffs for the first time since 2016.</p>
<p>“At this point in time, this is our most important game,” Tagovailoa said.</p>
<p>The rookie quarterback, 4-2 as a starter, will face the Patriots for the first time.</p>
<p>PLAYOFF RACE</p>
<p>Miami and New England head into their 111th meeting with both teams trailing AFC East leader Buffalo (10-3). The Patriots will finish with fewer victories than a division rival for the first time since Bill Belichick’s first season in New England in 2000, and a loss Sunday would eliminate them from playoff contention.</p>
<p>“All I know is if we go out there and we win the rest of our games, we give ourselves a chance,” Patriots running back James White said. “And then whatever else happens, it’s not really in our control.”</p>
<p>One more loss ensures that for the first time since 2000 — the year the Patriots drafted Brady — they won’t finish above .500.</p>
<p>TAKEAWAY STREAKS</p>
<p>Patriots cornerback Stephon Gilmore was the NFL Defensive Player of the Year in 2019, and Dolphins cornerback Xavien Howard is making a strong bid to succeed him.</p>
<p>Howard leads the NFL with nine interceptions, the most in a season since 2012, and is tied for first in the league with 17 passes defended. Teams continue to throw his way: Howard has an interception in each of the past five games.</p>
<p>“You would think people would learn,” teammate Christian Wilkins said.</p>
<p>Miami&#8217;s defense is much improved since Week 1, when it allowed 217 yards rushing in a loss at New England. The Dolphins rank second in the NFL in points allowed, and are tied for the league lead with 25 takeaways. Their streak of at least one takeaway in 19 consecutive games is the longest in the NFL.</p>
<p>“They’ve been very opportunistic,” Belichick said. “They’ve forced offenses into some bad plays and capitalized on them.”</p>
<p>DEFENDING McDANIELS</p>
<p>Whatever struggles the Patriots have had on offense this season, Cam Newton maintains they aren’t the fault of offensive coordinator Josh McDaniels.</p>
<p>Asked during his weekly radio appearance if play-calling in the red zone had any effect on the offense going 0 for 4 in last week’s loss to the Rams, the quarterback rose to his coach’s defense.</p>
<p>“He’s a very passionate person that I would never second-guess his theory no matter what it is,” Newton said. “There have been times where, as a player, you kind of bail your coach out because of the plays that you may make. But more times than not, Josh has bailed the whole team out because of his theory and his in-game adjustments. So, it’s give-and-take.”</p>
<p>Through 13 games, New England is ranked 27th in the NFL in the red zone, scoring a touchdown on 52% of its opportunities.</p>
<p>RETURN THREAT</p>
<p>New England&#8217;s Gunner Olszewski leads the NFL with a 20.6-yard punt return average.</p>
<p>If he continues that pace, it would be the highest return average in team history. Julian Edelman has the highest average in a season at 15.5 in 2012. Only seven NFL players have a return average of at least 20.0 yards in a single season.</p>
<p>Olszewski had a 70-yard punt return for a touchdown in Week 13 against the Chargers.</p>
<p>TUA THE TARGET</p>
<p>Should the Patriots take Tagovailoa seriously as a receiving threat? He ran into the flat as the intended receiver on a trick play last week after handing off to wideout Lynn Bowden Jr., who decided to run instead.</p>
<p>“Tua has good hands,” Dolphins receivers coach Josh Grizzard said. “He’s a card dealer back there when he gets it from center, so I’m sure he can catch the passes well.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">802741</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frustrated Dolphins still in playoff race after loss to KC</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/frustrated-dolphins-still-in-playoff-race-after-loss-to-kc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=798282</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Dolphins weren&#8217;t satisfied with putting a scare into the Kansas City Chiefs, which in itself is a sign of progress for a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Dolphins weren&#8217;t satisfied with putting a scare into the Kansas City Chiefs, which in itself is a sign of progress for a franchise striving to shake its perennial also-ran status.</p>
<p>Miami intercepted Patrick Mahomes three times and staged a frantic fourth-quarter rally by totaling 14 first downs, but still <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/mahomes-chiefs-clinch-afc-west-with-33-27-win-over-dolphins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">came up short Sunday and lost 33-27</a> to the reigning Super Bowl champions.</p>
<p>“There are no moral victories,” defensive end Christian Wilkins said. “We did some good stuff; we did some not-so good stuff. This is a good game to learn from. We didn’t get the result we wanted.”</p>
<p>The Dolphins had a 4-1 edge in turnovers and sacked Mahomes three times, including for a 30-yard loss that set up the game&#8217;s first touchdown. Rookie Tua Tagovailoa had his most productive day yet with 316 yards passing, even though his playmakers at receiver and running back were limited because of a wave of injuries.</p>
<p>With Miami’s loss, the Pittsburgh Steelers clinched a playoff spot.</p>
<p>Mahomes repeatedly hurt Miami, going 24 for 34 for 393 yards — 11.6 per attempt — and the Chiefs scored 30 consecutive points after falling behind 10-0. It was the sort of run the Dolphins&#8217; defense had hoped to avoid.</p>
<p>“The turnovers were good,” coach Brian Flores said. “We played well in spurts; we made some plays. But against a team like that, one misalignment, one miscommunication and they take advantage. That was the case today.”</p>
<p>The loss was the second in the past nine games for the Dolphins (8-5). It didn&#8217;t doom their chances of making the playoffs for only the second time since 2008, but it made winning next Sunday against New England almost imperative.</p>
<p>“It was fun to see our defense get a lot of turnovers like that,” cornerback Byron Jones said. &#8220;But it’s a little frustrating, because we gave up a lot of easy stuff.</p>
<p>“We’ve got a really good opponent coming in next week, so that’s where all our focus and attention will be.”</p>
<p>Jones forced a fumble that Miami recovered, and also <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xxz5C-c4dTc">grabbed his first interception </a>since 2017. Xavien <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2HCe9SfkgR0">Howard came up with an interception </a>for the fifth game in a row, increasing his season total to an NFL-high nine, and Eric Rowe also had a pick.</p>
<p>But the four turnovers led to just 10 points for Miami.</p>
<p>“The defense gave us many opportunities,” Tagovailoa said. “Offensively we didn’t execute the way we should have. A lot of that falls on me with leadership, not taking what the defense is giving me, pretty much making rookie mistakes. You can&#8217;t do that against a Super Bowl-caliber team like the Chiefs.”</p>
<p>Even so, the Dolphins were in contention until their onside kick failed in the final seconds. At that point, their injury list was longer than it has been all year.</p>
<p>They played without linebackers Kyle Van Noy and Elandon Roberts because of injuries, and top rusher Myles Gaskin was on the COVID-19 list. Mike Gesicki caught two touchdown passes before leaving in the fourth quarter with a shoulder problem, and wideouts DeVante Parker and Jakeem Grant went to the sideline with leg injuries.</p>
<p>Even so, Tagovailoa completed 28 passes and connected with nine receivers.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m very confident with whatever guys I&#8217;m playing with,” he said. “Those guys did a great job stepping up, because a lot of guys were down.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">798282</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/miami-dolphins.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/miami-dolphins.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/miami-dolphins.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mahomes, Chiefs clinch AFC West with 33-27 win over Dolphins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mahomes-chiefs-clinch-afc-west-with-33-27-win-over-dolphins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=798222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Patrick Mahomes took a 30-yard sack before he got the Kansas City Chiefs going in the right direction. The Chiefs overcame a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Patrick Mahomes <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PfZ5o_dunto">took a 30-yard sack </a>before he got the Kansas City Chiefs going in the right direction.</p>
<p>The Chiefs overcame a 10-point deficit and four turnovers Sunday to clinch their fifth consecutive AFC West title <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_PZu0IAjbo">by beating Miami </a>33-27.</p>
<p>Mahomes took the longest sack in the NFL in five years and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mZY4EkpfzFs">was picked off </a>three times, his first multi-interception game in more than two years. But he threw for 393 yards and two scores to help the Chiefs (12-1) earn their eighth consecutive victory.</p>
<p>It was the Chiefs’ second consecutive comeback at Hard Rock Stadium, where they won the Super Bowl in February despite Mahomes&#8217; two interceptions.</p>
<p>“We won the Super Bowl here and just clinched the AFC West — it seems every time we leave this stadium we have a hat about something we accomplished,” Mahomes said. “The (bad) part, it seems, is like I have half my interceptions at this stadium.”</p>
<p>With Miami’s loss, the Pittsburgh Steelers clinched a playoff spot.</p>
<p>Tyreek Hill ran through the Dolphins’ secondary and behind it, scoring on a 32-yard run and a 44-yard reception when Mahomes hit him in stride at the goal line.</p>
<p>Travis Kelce had eight catches for 136 yards and a touchdown, Mecole Hardman scored untouched on a 67-yard punt return, and Kansas City’s defense was stout against Tua Tagovailoa and the Dolphins’ injury-riddled offense. Chris Jones sacked the rookie for a safety for a 30-10 lead.</p>
<p>Kansas City reached 12 wins for the third consecutive season, the longest streak in club history, and has the best 13-game record in franchise history. The Chiefs set a team record with their 10th road win in a row.</p>
<p>“Glad to get the win and get out of here,&#8221; coach Andy Reid said. &#8220;That’s a good football team.”</p>
<p>The Dolphins (8-5) hurt their playoff prospects by losing for only the second time in the past nine games. Despite Miami&#8217;s bounty of takeaways, the Chiefs scored 30 consecutive points.</p>
<p>“This is an explosive team, and they went on a run there,” Dolphins coach Brian Flores said. “It was a quick spurt. That’s how they’re built; they go on runs. They went on one there. We collected ourselves, and I thought our guys did a good job of that. We played with poise and got ourselves back in the game.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa passed for 316 yards and two scores to Mike Gesicki, but also threw his first career interception, which came on his 154th attempt on a long pass that deflected off receiver Jakeem Grant.</p>
<p>That was the Dolphins’ lone turnover, while their defense kept coming up with the ball. Xavien Howard made an interception for the fifth game in a row, and Mahomes’ interception total for the season rose to five.</p>
<p>The Kansas City QB also was tripped up by Jerome Baker on a 30-yard sack.</p>
<p>But the Chiefs mounted touchdown drives of 75 and 72 yards in the second quarter to take a 14-10 halftime lead, and then used their superior speed to pull away.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa led touchdown drives of 80 and 75 yards to cut the margin to six points with 4:25 left, before the Chiefs’ Harrison Butker kicked a 46-yard field goal with a minute left. After a Miami field goal, the Chiefs recovered an onside kick to seal the win.</p>
<p>“We had many opportunities offensively,” Tagovailoa said. “I wasn’t able to execute those plays. This is the result. We ran out of time.”</p>
<p>EARLY SPUTTERING</p>
<p>Mahomes had a rough start. He threw an interception, bobbled a snap and took the big sack to set up the Dolphins’ first touchdown. Then Eric Rowe intercepted Mahomes to set up a field goal for a 10-0 Miami lead.</p>
<p>Baker corralled Mahomes on a third-and-12 play. Defensive end Emmanuel Ogbah forced Mahomes into full retreat, and when the quarterback tried to turn the corner around Baker, he was tripped up at the 3-yard line. Baker finished with 2½ sacks.</p>
<p>Howard, who leads the NFL with nine interceptions, made a spectacular one-handed grab of a pass intended for Hill in the end zone.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Chiefs: T Mike Remmers (back) left the game in the second half.</p>
<p>Dolphins: LBs Kyle Van Noy (hip) and Elandon Roberts (chest) were inactive. Gesicki (shoulder) and WRs Grant (leg) and DeVante Parker (left leg) went to the sideline.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Chiefs: They play Sunday at New Orleans.</p>
<p>Dolphins: They play host Sunday to the New England Patriots, who won when the teams met in the season opener.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">798222</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190726 dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins&#8217; Tagovailoa set to start against Bengals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-tagovailoa-set-to-start-against-bengals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=792351</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) — Miami rookie quarterback Tua Tagovailoa is active, and barring a late setback in warmups, he’s expected to start Sunday against the Cincinnati Bengals....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) — Miami rookie quarterback Tua Tagovailoa is active, and barring a late setback in warmups, he’s expected to start Sunday against the Cincinnati Bengals.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa missed last week’s game at the Jets and has been limited in practice the past two weeks with a sore thumb on his throwing hand.</p>
<p>Ryan Fitzpatrick started last week for Tagovailoa, who is 3-1 as a starter this year.</p>
<p>The Bengals placed defensive end Amani Bledsoe on the reserve-COVID-19 list, and promoted defensive tackle Kahlil McKenzie as a COVID-19 replacement.</p>
<p>In Houston, Colts punter Rigoberto Sanchez is out after he had surgery Tuesday to remove a cancerous tumor. Texans running back David Johnson is active after missing three games with a concussion.</p>
<p>The Tennessee Titans get wide receiver Adam Humphries back after he missed four straight games with a concussion. The Browns are without cornerback Denzel Ward, and Kevin Johnson will start in his place. The Titans only had to scratch four players with rookie offensive tackle Isaiah Wilson was suspended for this game after Tennessee already had declared him out because of an illness.</p>
<p>The Raiders will be without leading rusher Josh Jacobs (ankle) and safety Johnathan Abram (knee) were sidelined against the winless Jets. Both had already been ruled out Friday for the game.</p>
<p>Las Vegas got defensive end Clelin Ferrell back after he missed two games while on the reserve/COVID-19 list. He practiced all week.</p>
<p>Lions running back D’Andre Swift is inactive because of an illness. Swift, the team’s second-leading rusher with 331 yards on the ground, was downgraded to doubtful on Saturday.</p>
<p>Detroit receiver Kenny Golladay missed his fifth consecutive game with a hip injury.</p>
<p>Defensive tackle Akiem Hicks and wide receiver Allen Robinson are active for the Bears. Hicks missed last weekend’s 41-25 loss at Green Bay with a hamstring injury. Robinson was questionable with a knee injury.</p>
<p>The Jaguars are down starting cornerback Sidney Jones (Achilles) and two linebackers because of hamstring injuries, Kamalei Correa and Dakota Allen as they face the Vikings.</p>
<p>Defensive tackle DaVon Hamilton (knee) went on injured reserve. Wide receiver Chris Conley (hip), safety Jarrod Wilson (shoulder) and right tackle Jawaan Taylor (knee) are all active after being listed as questionable.</p>
<p>For the Vikings, rookie defensive end D.J. Wonnum (ankle/back) is out for the first time this season. Tight end Irv Smith Jr. (back) misses his third game out of the last four. Right guard Ezra Cleveland (ankle) returns to the starting lineup from a two-game absence. Backup running back Alexander Mattison is out with an illness.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">792351</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">tua tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over the hump? Dolphins are big favorites against Bengals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/over-the-hump-dolphins-are-big-favorites-against-bengals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 19:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=791373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Dolphins are in contention for their first AFC East title since 2008, which would ensure their first playoff berth since...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Dolphins are in contention for their first AFC East title since 2008, which would ensure their first playoff berth since 2016, which would give them a shot at their first postseason win since 2000, none of which coach Brian Flores wants to think, talk, read or hear about.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s too focused on sustaining momentum resulting from the long-struggling franchise&#8217;s recent turnaround.</p>
<p>“In this league, I don’t think you’re ever really over the hump,&#8221; Flores says. &#8220;There are just so many good teams. The league is built for parity, and there are a lot of good players.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think once you think you’re over the hump is when you go back under the hump.”</p>
<p>Flores believes no game is a gimme, not even for a Miami team that has won six of seven to improve to 7-4. The Dolphins are 11-point favorites, but they could be back under the hump unless they take seriously Sunday’s matchup against perennially woeful Cincinnati (2-8-1).</p>
<p>MISMATCH?</p>
<p>The blitz-happy Dolphins are sure to dial up the pressure on Bengals quarterback Brandon Allen, who will make his second start since Joe Burrow&#8217;s season-ending knee injury.</p>
<p>Dolphins defensive coordinator Josh Boyer is fond of multiple fronts designed to disrupt, and that&#8217;s what they&#8217;ve done. Miami ranks second in the NFL in points allowed, and third in takeaways.</p>
<p>“He definitely has an aggressive mindset,” safety Eric Rowe said. “I like being the aggressor instead of being passive and kind of just playing back. He wants to dictate what the offense does, to have the defense run the game.”</p>
<p>Without Burrow, the Bengals could be easy to confuse. They totaled 155 yards and 11 first downs in last week&#8217;s loss to the New York Giants.</p>
<p>QB UNCERTAINTY</p>
<p>Top Dolphins draft pick Tua Tagovailoa hasn&#8217;t played since he was benched in the fourth quarter of their loss at Denver on Nov. 22. He remains the No. 1 QB, but his availability is uncertain because of a sore thumb on his throwing hand that forced him to miss last week&#8217;s win over the New York Jets.</p>
<p>In Tagovailoa&#8217;s absence, Ryan Fitzpatrick threw for two touchdowns, and he remains on standby. Tagovailoa is 3-1 as the starter; Fitzpatrick is 4-3.</p>
<p>STILL THE ONE</p>
<p>Cincinnati coaches are staying with Allen despite his underwhelming performance in the loss to the Giants.</p>
<p>Allen, who last played in a game in 2019 for Denver, was promoted from the practice squad. He threw for 136 yards, had an interception and fumbled the ball away on a potentially game-winning drive with 57 seconds left, and the Bengals lost 19-17.</p>
<p>Ryan Finley was Burrow’s backup this season, and journeyman Kevin Hogan has been added to the practice squad, but the Bengals are prepared to give Allen some more time, given that he hadn’t seen live action in a year.</p>
<p>“Brandon’s got great poise, he was calm under pressure, he didn’t do anything that was out of character or anything out of expectation as far as knowing where to go and what to do and how to do it,” offensive coordinator Brian Callahan says. “There were probably a couple of timing things that as he watches the game, he’ll improve.”</p>
<p>ONE-DIMENSIONAL ATTACK</p>
<p>Making it tougher on Allen is Cincinnati’s inability to establish the run, which has been a problem since Joe Mixon went out with a foot injury in the loss to Indianapolis on Oct. 18.</p>
<p>With injuries making for an ever-changing cast on the offensive line, getting enough push for the running game has been an issue. Last week the Giants were so sure Cincinnati wasn’t going to run they were dropping up to eight defenders into pass coverage.</p>
<p>“We weren’t getting the line of scrimmage moved, and they were holding strong at the point of attack,&#8221; coach Zac Taylor said. “That’s something certainly we’ve got to improve on, because it’s a tough way when you just can’t move those front four.”</p>
<p>PERFECT</p>
<p>When kicking from 50 yards or beyond, the Dolphins&#8217; Jason Sanders has made 10 consecutive field goals, the NFL’s longest such streak. That includes eight this year.</p>
<p>“I’ve been kicking the ball really well,&#8221; Sanders says, &#8220;and I’m just excited to see where it’s going to go.”</p>
<p>It&#8217;s probably going to go through the uprights. Overall, Sanders is 24 for 25 in 2020, and his career success rate of 87% (65 for 75) is the best in team history.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">791373</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/190806-brian-flores.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/190806-brian-flores.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/190806-brian-flores.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190806 brian flores</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fitzpatrick, Dolphins keep Jets winless with 20-3 victory</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/fitzpatrick-dolphins-keep-jets-winless-with-20-3-victory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 02:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=787895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[EAST RUTHERFORD, N.J. (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick has been through it all during his many stops in the NFL — a backup and a starter,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EAST RUTHERFORD, N.J. (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick has been through it all during his many stops in the NFL — a backup and a starter, a fill-in and a franchise leader.</p>
<p>The 38-year-old quarterback is ready for it all, as he was again Sunday.</p>
<p>After being benched a few weeks ago, Fitzpatrick threw two touchdown passes while starting in place of the injured Tua Tagovailoa and the Miami Dolphins kept the New York Jets winless with a 20-3 victory.</p>
<p>“It’s kind of been the story of my career,” said Fitzpatrick, who has been with eight teams during 16 seasons. &#8220;It has been so up and down. I&#8217;m in the lineup and out of the lineup and I&#8217;m back in. I&#8217;m just trying to stay steady and provide leadership when my number is called.</p>
<p>“I love playing. I love being out there.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa was inactive with a left thumb injury, so Fitzpatrick stepped in against one of his many former teams. And he didn&#8217;t need to do too much to keep the Dolphins (7-4) in the AFC playoff hunt, not against the lowly Jets anyway.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick was 24 of 39 for 257 yards with TD throws to tight ends Mike Gesicki and Adam Shaheen, helping the Dolphins bounce back after having a five-game winning streak end last week.</p>
<p>“Ryan played well,” coach Brian Flores said. “He made enough plays to help us win the game. He spread the ball around to a number of different receivers.”</p>
<p>Actually, 10 Dolphins had at least one catch, including DeVante Parker leading the way with eight for 119 yards.</p>
<p>Flores said Tagovailoa was “very close” to being able to play in this game, but the Dolphins want to be safe with the rookie first-rounder. That means it could be back to the sideline next week for Fitzpatrick.</p>
<p>“When my number is called, I&#8217;m going to go out there and win games for this team,” Fitzpatrick said.</p>
<p>New York got its starting quarterback back as Sam Darnold played after missing the last two games with a shoulder injury. But the offense was unable to get much going. Darnold was intercepted by Nik Needham and Xavien Howard, and the Jets (0-11) twice couldn’t take advantage of takeaways by the defense.</p>
<p>“We had opportunities,&#8221; coach Adam Gase said. &#8220;We just didn&#8217;t make the plays we needed to make.”</p>
<p>Another poor offensive showing had speculation swirling again over whether New York could part ways with Gase, who was outscored 44-3 in two losses this season to his former team. The 11-game skid is the second-longest in team history, one game short of the losing streak by the 1995-96 teams under Rich Kotite.</p>
<p>After Miami went three-and-out to open the second half, New York moved the ball down the field — thanks to an impressive 27-yard grab by Breshad Perriman. But Darnold tried to make too much happen on third down at the Dolphins 32, throwing across his body on the run and into double coverage with Needham making an easy interception.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;ve got to be better,” Darnold said. “I didn&#8217;t play well enough to win a ballgame today.”</p>
<p>The Jets didn&#8217;t muster much the rest of the way — although they had some chances.</p>
<p>The Dolphins began chewing up clock late in the third quarter by focusing on the run, but it cost them when Quinnen Williams popped the ball out of Matt Breida’s hands and Harvey Langi recovered to give the Jets the ball at Miami’s 45 with 4:09 remaining in the period.</p>
<p>But New York couldn’t do anything with the takeaway, going three and out.</p>
<p>The Jets’ defense came up big again on the Dolphins’ next drive, with Jordan Jenkins knocking the ball out of Patrick Laird’s hands and Neville Hewitt scooping it up and returning it to Miami’s 26.</p>
<p>But again, New York’s offense stalled. The Jets went for it on fourth-and-1 from the 17, but Frank Gore was stuffed by Elandon Roberts for a 1-yard loss.</p>
<p>“When it comes down to fourth-and-1, it’s a mentality,” Roberts said. “I look at it as if a team wants to run the ball on fourth-and-1, it’s disrespectful.”</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick drove the Dolphins down the field and sealed the win with a 7-yard touchdown toss to Shaheen that made it 20-3 with 6:54 left.</p>
<p>QUESTIONABLE CALL</p>
<p>Gesicki gave the Dolphins a 10-3 lead with 8:56 left in the first half when Fitzpatrick threw a fade into the right corner of the end zone and the 6-foot-6 tight end used his height advantage to outreach 6-1 rookie safety Ashtyn Davis for the touchdown.</p>
<p>The drive was prolonged by a controversial call when Parker was credited with a 19-yard catch despite not appearing to ever fully control the ball before Javelin Guidry knocked it out of his hands. Gase challenged the call — and TV replays seemed to support the Jets’ argument — but it was upheld and the Dolphins scored four plays later.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Dolphins: WR Malcolm Perry injured his chest early in the game.</p>
<p>Jets: With RT George Fant (knee/ankle) out, Conor McDermott started in his place. &#8230; LG Pat Elflein made his Jets debut, replacing Alex Lewis (not injury-related). Gase said Lewis&#8217; situation is being handled “in-house” by the team, but wouldn&#8217;t elaborate. &#8230; LB Blake Cashman left with a hamstring injury.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: Host the Cincinnati Bengals next Sunday.</p>
<p>Jets: Host the Las Vegas Raiders next Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">787895</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191017-ryan-fitzpatric.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191017-ryan-fitzpatric.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/191017-ryan-fitzpatric.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">191017 ryan fitzpatrick</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins downgrade ailing Tua; Fitzpatrick likely to face Jets</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-downgrade-ailing-tua-fitzpatrick-likely-to-face-jets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=787372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins quarterback Tua Tagovailoa was downgraded to doubtful for Sunday’s game at the New York Jets, meaning it&#8217;s likely veteran Ryan Fitzpatrick will...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins quarterback Tua Tagovailoa was downgraded to doubtful for Sunday’s game at the New York Jets, meaning it&#8217;s likely veteran Ryan Fitzpatrick will make his first start since Oct. 18.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa hurt the thumb on his throwing hand in practice Wednesday and was limited in subsequent workouts this week. The rookie&#8217;s status was downgraded Saturday, and Miami elevated quarterback Reid Sinnett from the practice squad to the active roster to reinforce depth at the position.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick&#8217;s most recent start came in a 24-0 win over the Jets, one of his former teams, before he was replaced in the starting lineup by Tagovailoa. Fitzpatrick came off the bench in the fourth quarter of last week’s loss at Denver when Tagovailoa struggled.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">787372</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">tua tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins optimistic Tua will face Jets despite sore thumb</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-optimistic-tua-will-face-jets-despite-sore-thumb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 23:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=786151</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa&#8217;s sore thumb was better Thursday, and Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores expressed optimism his rookie quarterback will be able to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa&#8217;s sore thumb was better Thursday, and Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores expressed optimism his rookie quarterback will be able to play Sunday against the New York Jets.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa hurt the thumb on his throwing hand in practice and was limited in practice for the second day in a row.</p>
<p>“He got banged up a little bit,” Flores said. “I don’t think this is something we’re too worried about. &#8230; He&#8217;s getting treatment, he’s rehabbing. We&#8217;ll see how this goes. It&#8217;s sore, but he&#8217;s a tough kid. He has played through some things before.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa was sacked six times before being pulled in the fourth quarter of the Dolphins’ loss last weekend at Denver, but he remains the No. 1 quarterback ahead of veteran Ryan Fitzpatrick.</p>
<p>Offensive lineman Jesse Davis was activated off the reserve-COVID-19 list. Davis, who has started the past 52 games, went on the list Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">786151</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat, Marlins, Dolphins collaborate for Thanksgiving food drive</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-marlins-dolphins-collaborate-for-thanksgiving-food-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 01:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=784286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Three South Florida sports teams came together to feed a need in the community by organizing their respective Thanksgiving food drives. The pandemic couldn&#8217;t slow...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three South Florida sports teams came together to feed a need in the community by organizing their respective Thanksgiving food drives.</p>
<p>The pandemic couldn&#8217;t slow down South Florida&#8217;s top three sports teams from doing their part to help the community, as the Miami Dolphins made sure to score touchdowns with families in Miami Gardens by providing 850 boxed meals filled with delicious sides and a nice turkey.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s an opportunity for you to really sit down with your family and to give thanks and to be happy and to just relax for a moment,&#8221; Dolphins Senior Director of Community Affairs Leslie Nixon said. &#8220;Having the burden of trying to figure out where your next meal is gonna come from, how you&#8217;re gonna pay the bills is really tough. Again, if we can take that burden off a family member&#8217;s plate and just allow them to enjoy each other&#8217;s company, that&#8217;s really what Thanksgiving means.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Miami Marlins joined forces with Feeding South Florida to dish out 1,000 Thanksgiving dinners. Sponsored by Tito&#8217;s Handmade Vodka, the Marlins&#8217; 12th Annual Home Plate Meals Thanksgiving distribution is something Derek Jeter and the team feels is a big hit for the community during the holidays.</p>
<p>&#8220;This has always been one of our favorite times of the year to give back, and considering everything that&#8217;s gone on this year, it&#8217;s a little extra meaningful,&#8221; Jeter said. &#8220;We said early on right when we took over this organization that we wanted to be this community&#8217;s team, and part of that is being here to support the community.&#8221;</p>
<p>For two decades, Miami Heat Hall of Famer Alonzo Mourning provided hundreds of hearty meals with all the trimmings where no virus was going to stop the tradition for the Awesome 33 Thanksgiving Giveaway.</p>
<p>&#8220;Being able to provide that during a very, very difficult time, during a very devastating pandemic, to be able to provide the relief and support to all the 300 families is truly a blessing,&#8221; said Mourning.</p>
<p>The Dolphins said they&#8217;ll give out almost 22,000 meals by Thanksgiving Day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">784286</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/97c3685c-6e8f-462d-97e8-7968a5c2e76e/da314c77-7945-46f8-a02c-8687589d8cc9/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217602~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/97c3685c-6e8f-462d-97e8-7968a5c2e76e/da314c77-7945-46f8-a02c-8687589d8cc9/main.mp4*~hmac=12d74011688a465fbc67e0bc148e6a43ff382a7c1a338982a6382ad29b7daad6' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">112320 Marlins_Thanksgiving food drive</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins&#8217; Albert Wilson hosts Thanksgiving food drive in Miami Gardens</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-albert-wilson-hosts-thanksgiving-food-drive-in-miami-gardens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 15:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=783993</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins wide receiver Albert Wilson hosted a Thanksgiving food drive in Miami Gardens. On Sunday morning, Vitality Sports Management and The Albert Wilson Foundation,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami Dolphins wide receiver Albert Wilson hosted a Thanksgiving food drive in Miami Gardens.</p>
<p>On Sunday morning, Vitality Sports Management and The Albert Wilson Foundation, founded by Wilson, hosted the event in the parking lot of County Line Chiropractic Centers located at 21309 NW 2nd Ave.</p>
<p>The event was Wilson&#8217;s fifth annual food drive.</p>
<p>&#8220;This year we were able to partner with Denzel and bring it to Miami Gardens and do something bigger than I usually do,  so shoutout to him and his partners, allowing us to come and do something so close to where I play so it was very special for us,&#8221; said Wilson.</p>
<p>Families went home with turkeys, sweet potatoes and collard greens just in time for the holiday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">783993</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Albert-Wilson-e1606144952518.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/bd63bfb7-cd3d-4d89-bf52-d4d8ac5f7b2f/f29cdd64-61ac-45f4-9b5a-6f318fc9323c/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216822~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/bd63bfb7-cd3d-4d89-bf52-d4d8ac5f7b2f/f29cdd64-61ac-45f4-9b5a-6f318fc9323c/main.mp4*~hmac=345918b548747f3c24cd54bdce5648f5b0acf6a0719f2731377e7a8ab6e523b4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Albert-Wilson-e1606144952518.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Albert-Wilson-e1606144952518.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Albert Wilson</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Denver hands Tagovailoa first loss with 20-13 win over Dolphins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/denver-hands-tagovailoa-first-loss-with-20-13-win-over-dolphins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=783747</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DENVER (AP) — Justin Simmons intercepted Ryan Fitzpatrick’s pass in the end zone with 63 seconds left Sunday, sealing the Denver Broncos’ 20-13 win over...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DENVER (AP) — Justin Simmons intercepted Ryan Fitzpatrick’s pass in the end zone with 63 seconds left Sunday, sealing the Denver Broncos’ 20-13 win over the Miami Dolphins.</p>
<p>The Broncos (4-6) not only prevented Tua Tagovailoa from becoming just the second rookie in the past 40 years to win his first four starts but they sacked him a half-dozen times and knocked him from the game in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Although the Dolphins (6-4) didn’t announce an injury to Tagovailoa before game’s end, the lefty walked gingerly to the sideline after his final sack, by Bradley Chubb.</p>
<p>On the play, Tagovailoa’s left leg bent awkwardly and guard Solomon Kindley stepped on Tagovailoa’s right foot.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick entered the game with the Dolphins down 10 points and drove them to a field goal that made it a one-score deficit.</p>
<p>The Dolphins, who had won five in a row, had a chance to tie it after they turned away the Broncos at their 1.</p>
<p>Melvin Gordon was just about to score his third touchdown of the game when linebacker Andrew Van Ginkel atoned for a pair of penalties on the previous play by punching the ball loose at the 1. Safety Eric Rowe recovered.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick completed 12 of 18 passes for 117 yards — better than Tagovailoa’s line of 11-for-20 for 83 — but Simmons intercepted his underthrown pass in the end zone after he&#8217;d driven the Dolphins from their 1 to the Broncos 15-yard line.</p>
<p>The Broncos ran out the clock with Drew Lock completing a 61-yard pass to Tim Patrick on fourth-and-14 from his 16, a play that began with 4 seconds remaining.</p>
<p>Lock completed 18 of 30 passes for 270 yards with no touchdowns and an interception. He started despite missing practice time during the week because of bruised ribs.</p>
<p>Linebacker Elandon Roberts stuffed Gordon a few inches shy of the first down on fourth-and-1 from the Dolphins 14 to open the second half, but Gordon <a href="https://twitter.com/Broncos/status/1330650065971466241?s=20">scored from 20 yards </a>on Denver’s next drive, putting the Broncos ahead 20-10 late in the third quarter.</p>
<p>Brandon McManus nailed a 47-yard field goal as the first half ended, sending the Broncos into the tunnel with a 13-10 lead.</p>
<p>The Broncos got off to another bad start, failing to score a touchdown on the opening drive for the 12th consecutive time when Lock threw his 11th interception of the season.</p>
<p>Xavien Howard stepped in front of Patrick and <a href="https://twitter.com/MiamiDolphins/status/1330620872563023879?s=20">picked off his sixth pass</a> of 2020, giving Miami the ball at the Denver 22.</p>
<p>It was Lock’s league-high sixth straight game with an interception and came on his second throw. He got the start over backup Brett Rypien after missing a day of practice with bruised ribs and a strained oblique courtesy of Arden Key’s blindside hit last week in Las Vegas.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa’s first career interception, by Simmons, two plays later was negated by A.J. Bouye’s holding call, and Bouye was beaten by DeVante Parker for a <a href="https://twitter.com/thecheckdown/status/1330623729882185728?s=20">toe-tapping 3-yard touchdown catch</a> that put Miami ahead 7-0.</p>
<p>The Broncos tied it on Gordon’s <a href="https://twitter.com/Broncos/status/1330628302176829441?s=20">1-yard run</a> that capped their longest drive (six minutes) in more than a month and Denver took its first lead in three weeks on McManus’ 29-yarder.</p>
<p>FLOYD LITTLE</p>
<p>A former teammate at Syracuse says running back great Floyd Little, who has cancer, has entered hospice care. The 78-year-old Little was known as “The Franchise” in Denver because his signing was credited with keeping the team from relocating in the 1960s and with persuading voters to approve funds to build the old Mile High Stadium.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Dolphins G Solomon Kindley (foot) left briefly but returned and Broncos S Trey Marshall (lower leg) got hurt.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: visit the New York Jets on Nov. 29.</p>
<p>Broncos: host the New Orleans Saints Nov. 29.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">783747</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ogbah&#8217;s breakout season helps Dolphins join playoff race</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ogbahs-breakout-season-helps-dolphins-join-playoff-race/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 19:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=781698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Emmanuel Ogbah is leading the charge for the Miami Dolphins’ disruptive defense, motivated by a desire to stay put. “I’ve been around,”...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Emmanuel Ogbah is leading the charge for the Miami Dolphins’ disruptive defense, motivated by a desire to stay put.</p>
<p>“I’ve been around,” Ogbah said with a chuckle. “I’ve been on three teams in five years. I’m tired of moving.”</p>
<p>A breakout season has the Dolphins keen to keep him around. Ogbah is tied for fourth in the NFL with a career-high eight sacks, and has had at least one in each of the past six games while twice forcing fumbles that teammates returned for touchdowns.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s a playmaker on a unit ranked second in the NFL in takeaways per game and fourth in points allowed. While the focus in Miami has been on rookie quarterback Tua Tagovailoa, it is dramatic defensive improvement that has fueled a surprising surge by the Dolphins (6-3) into playoff contention.</p>
<p>“That’s the reason they’ve won five in a row now, the way they’re playing on defense,” said Los Angeles Chargers coach Anthony Lynn, whose potent offense netted a season-low 273 yards in last week&#8217;s loss at Miami. The Dolphins play Sunday at Denver (3-6).</p>
<p>Five veteran newcomers start for coach Brian Flores&#8217; defense, and none has made a bigger impact than Ogbah, who signed a $15 million, two-year deal in March that now looks like a bargain for the Dolphins.</p>
<p>Ogbah&#8217;s job title is end, but he&#8217;s used in a variety of ways on a defense that has thrived through its unpredictability.</p>
<p>“He has shown ability to be multiple, and we can move him around,” defensive coordinator Josh Boyer said. “He does a lot of things for us. He can set the edge, he can handle double-teams, he can rush the passer, he can rush the passer individually, he can do it with stunts. There are a lot of things he does for us that probably don&#8217;t get noticed.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ten Dolphins have at least one sack this year, in part because foes are focused on Ogbah, as cornerback Nik Needham noted after sacking the Chargers&#8217; Justin Herbert last week.</p>
<p>“When I came off the edge, the running back had his eyes locked on Ogbah,” Needham said. &#8220;That freed me up off the edge, and Herbert ran right up to me. He’s a dominant force out there for sure.”</p>
<p>At 27, he&#8217;s also a late bloomer. The Nigeria native was considered a potential NFL star after making 12 1/2 sacks as a senior at Oklahoma State, and the Cleveland Browns took him in the second round of the 2016 draft. It took him three years to total 12 1/2 sacks for the Browns, where his injuries became an issue, and they traded him to the Kansas City Chiefs. He missed the final 2 1/2 months of their Super Bowl championship season last year with a torn chest muscle.</p>
<p>“It has been a journey,” Ogbah said. “I’ve had my ups and downs.”</p>
<p>Last offseason he tried to tame the roller coaster by getting in better shape, spending some of his free agent earnings on better nutrition, acupuncture, massages and cryotherapy.</p>
<p>“I don’t think about the money; I think about it as an investment to my body,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>The payoff might lead to the playoffs, and Ogbah might have finally found a home.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">781698</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/emmanuel-ogbah-e1605728939247.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/emmanuel-ogbah-e1605728939247.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/emmanuel-ogbah-e1605728939247.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">emmanuel ogbah</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Dolphins player Carey hands out 250 Thanksgiving meals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/former-dolphins-player-carey-hands-out-250-thanksgiving-meals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 23:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=780139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With Thanksgiving just over a week away, a former Miami Dolphins player delivered some holiday handouts. The Carey Family Foundation handed out 250 holiday meals...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Thanksgiving just over a week away, a former Miami Dolphins player delivered some holiday handouts.</p>
<p>The Carey Family Foundation handed out 250 holiday meals to South Florida families at Miami Northwestern Senior High School, Monday.</p>
<p>The organization was founded by former Dolphins offensive lineman Vernon Carey Sr.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s what we need at this time. With the world so divided, and to be able to help others and encourage others, and to be able to give to one another, it means a lot to me and my family,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Each meal included a turkey, sides and dessert that can feed between six and eight people.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">780139</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201116_Vernon_Carey_Sr_Thanksgiving_food_distribution.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/cd81fbe8-3631-43d6-beaf-a3527a3b5d04/acf94ef8-560c-4738-910f-48edfd3b53f3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216830~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/cd81fbe8-3631-43d6-beaf-a3527a3b5d04/acf94ef8-560c-4738-910f-48edfd3b53f3/main.mp4*~hmac=e6826ac1f2ed01aad6dbe1a7d8a3c99a68ae0145d78c307bf079a76242c718c4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201116_Vernon_Carey_Sr_Thanksgiving_food_distribution.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201116_Vernon_Carey_Sr_Thanksgiving_food_distribution.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201116_Vernon_Carey_Sr_Thanksgiving_food_distribution</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins earn 5th straight win by beating Chargers 29-21</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-earn-5th-straight-win-by-beating-chargers-29-21/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=779575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa had help from a less-heralded rookie while Justin Herbert struggled against a blitz-happy defense. The surprising Miami Dolphins...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa had help from a less-heralded rookie while Justin Herbert struggled against a blitz-happy defense.</p>
<p>The surprising Miami Dolphins earned their fifth consecutive victory, beating the Los Angeles Chargers 29-21 Sunday.</p>
<p>Salvon Ahmed, making his first career start, ran for 85 yards on 21 carries and scored a 1-yard touchdown on Miami’s first play. The undrafted Ahmed filled in with two other running backs injured and sparked a ground game ranked fourth worst in the league.</p>
<p>Herbert threw a costly interception and was outplayed in the matchup of high draft picks by Tagovailoa, who passed for 169 yards with two scores and improved to 3-0 since taking over for Ryan Fitzpatrick. Herbert struggled against Miami’s blitzing defense and threw for a season-low 187 yards.</p>
<p>The Chargers were also outplayed on special teams, where they were hurt by two mistakes that allowed Miami to take a 14-0 lead.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (6-3) have their best nine-game record since 2001, and under second-year coach Brian Flores they’ve won more games than in all of 2019. The Chargers (2-7) dropped their third game in a row and have their worst record at this point in a season since 2015.</p>
<p>Keenan Allen had just three receptions and Mike Williams had two for Los Angeles.</p>
<p>Chargers punter Ty Long bobbled a snap and had his kicked blocked to set up the game’s first score on Ahmed’s short run. Quenton Meeks was offside on a field goal attempt by the Dolphins, giving them a first down that led to a touchdown.</p>
<p>The Dolphins were up 17-7 at halftime, increasing their NFL-best first-half point differential to plus-74.</p>
<p>Miami’s Jason Sanders made field goals of 50, 35 and 49 yards but missed from 47, ending his streak of 22 in a row. Jakeem Grant, the NFL leader in punt return yards, helped the Dolphins’ field position with three runbacks for 57 yards.</p>
<p>Miami’s Emmanuel Ogbah had a full sack for the sixth game in a row, and on the next play Xavien Howard picked off Herbert for his fifth interception of the year to set up Miami&#8217;s final touchdown.</p>
<p>An onside kick recovery helped the Dolphins seal the win.</p>
<p>Chargers linebacker Kenneth Murray Jr. also let a potential interception slip through his hands, and three plays later Miami kicked a field goal for a 20-14 lead.</p>
<p>Miami has now scored at least 21 points in seven consecutive games, the team’s longest such streak since 2001-02.</p>
<p>MIAMI&#8217;S LONE TURNOVER</p>
<p>The Dolphins were at the Chargers 9 and poised to build on a 14-0 lead when they lost a fumble on a bad snap by Ted Karras. Nick Vigil made a 44-yard return before Tagovailoa tackled him, and Herbert scored on a fourth-down sneak to make it 14-7.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Dolphins: LB Kyle Van Noy (hip) left the game in the first half. Miami was without DT Christian Wilkins and four assistant coaches because of COVID-19 protocols.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: Miami plays next Sunday at Denver for the first time since 2014.</p>
<p>Chargers: They play the second of three consecutive games against the AFC East when they host the New York Jets on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">779575</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins WR Williams goes on IR; assistants still sidelined</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-wr-williams-goes-on-ir-assistants-still-sidelined/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 19:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=777961</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins receiver Preston Williams went on injured reserve Wednesday with a foot injury, meaning he&#8217;ll be sidelined for three games and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins receiver Preston Williams went on injured reserve Wednesday with a foot injury, meaning he&#8217;ll be sidelined for three games and perhaps longer.</p>
<p>Coach Brian Flores declined to say whether Williams is expected to return this season, but said the injury is more serious than first thought, and additional tests were planned.</p>
<p>Flores also said the Dolphins remain in the NFL&#8217;s intensive protocol for COVID-19, and they were without “a few” assistant coaches during Wednesday&#8217;s practice, which was limited to a walk-through. Five assistants missed Sunday&#8217;s win at Arizona, and at least one tested positive for the coronavirus.</p>
<p>Williams, who was hurt in the game, has 18 catches for 288 yards and a team-high four TD receptions. His injury could mean more playing time for Jakeem Grant, Malcolm Perry and Lynn Bowden Jr.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">777961</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/190810_preston_williams.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/190810_preston_williams.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/190810_preston_williams.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190810_Preston_Williams</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tua approaches injury anniversary grateful to be with Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tua-approaches-injury-anniversary-grateful-to-be-with-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 19:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=777959</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa says the game ball he gave Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores last week was a token of gratitude. “For me...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa says the game ball he gave Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores last week was a token of gratitude.</p>
<p>“For me it was like, ‘Thank you for taking a shot on me,’” Tagovailoa said Wednesday. “A year ago, who would have known?”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa is fast approaching the Nov. 16 anniversary of the hip injury that ended his final Alabama season and threatened his football career. A year later, he&#8217;s 2-0 as a starter for the surprising Dolphins (5-3) heading into Sunday&#8217;s showdown against another heralded rookie quarterback, Justin Herbert, and the Los Angeles Chargers.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa is coming off a breakout performance in Sunday&#8217;s thrilling 34-31 victory at Arizona. He threw for only 93 yards in his first start, but against the Cardinals he passed for 238 yards, ran for 35, and led consecutive scoring drives to help Miami come from behind in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>As he walked off the field after taking a knee on the final play, Tagovailoa presented the ball to Flores.</p>
<p>“This is for you,” the rookie said.</p>
<p>Flores and the Dolphins decided to draft Tagovailoa with the fifth overall pick in April even though doubts lingered regarding his recovery. The Dolphins waited until Week 8 to give him the starting job, in part to ensure he was fully healthy.</p>
<p>All signs suggest he is, including the way he juked standout Cardinals safety Budda Baker on a pivotal 17-yard run.</p>
<p>“He probably wasn’t expecting that,” Tagovailoa said.</p>
<p>Flores said Tagovailoa appears to have regained all of his mobility, and might be even shiftier than he was at Alabama.</p>
<p>“He looks good,” Flores said. “I mean, I haven’t seen that dead-leg move from him in college. I thought that was a nice move. He looks healthy to me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Offensive coordinator Chan Gailey agreed. Tagovailoa was body-slammed the first time he tried to pass in his first start, but against Arizona his movement in the pocket was better, and he was elusive when scrambling while also absorbing several hits.</p>
<p>“Physically is the one thing you had the concern about,” Gailey said, “and I think he kind of relieved all our thoughts about that.”</p>
<p>Development of Tagovailoa&#8217;s NFL skills remains a work in progress slowed by the cancellation of the preseason and most summer team workouts because of the coronavirus. There are bound to be hiccups with a rookie leading an offense that has struggled to run the ball all season and is now without receiver Preston Williams, sidelined by a foot injury.</p>
<p>Flores said it helps that from the day Tagovailoa was drafted, he has been eager to learn.</p>
<p>“As a rookie, you don’t know what you don’t know,” Flores said. “He’s learning how to prepare better, and I think that has been the case even over the last couple weeks. But he’s a sponge; that I like. And he’s open to learning different things.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa said there will always be ways to improve. And while his NFL career is off to a good start, his perspective is different from before the hip injury.</p>
<p>“I don’t know if I&#8217;ll ever be my old self,” he said. “When something dramatic like that happens &#8230; it has been a journey. I&#8217;m just blessed to be here.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">777959</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tagovailoa, Dolphins rally for 34-31 win over Cardinals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tagovailoa-dolphins-rally-for-34-31-win-over-cardinals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 12:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=775753</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GLENDALE, Ariz. (AP) — The first professional matchup of Tua Tagovailoa and Kyler Murray certainly lived up to the hype. The two young quarterbacks traded...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GLENDALE, Ariz. (AP) — The first professional matchup of Tua Tagovailoa and Kyler Murray certainly lived up to the hype.</p>
<p>The two young quarterbacks traded pinpoint passes, timely scrambles and other big plays in a dazzling show of the league&#8217;s future. In the end, it was the rookie who came out with the win.</p>
<p>The 22-year-old Tagovailoa threw for 248 yards and two touchdowns in just his second NFL start as the Miami Dolphins rallied in the fourth quarter for a 34-31 victory over the Arizona Cardinals on Sunday.</p>
<p>“That was awesome. It was fun for the fans as well, not just us competing,” Tagovailoa said of the duel with Murray. “You know what you’re going to get when it comes to Kyler. You know the kind of explosive player he is. He might be the fastest player in the NFL right now. Oh my gosh, he’s faster than me.”</p>
<p>But Tagovailoa was the winner. He&#8217;s 2-0 since taking over for Ryan Fitzpatrick as the starter following the team&#8217;s bye week.</p>
<p>Miami (5-3) has won four straight games. The Cardinals (5-3) had their three-game winning streak snapped.</p>
<p>Murray, the 2019 Offensive Rookie of the Year, finished with 283 yards passing and three touchdowns, adding 106 yards rushing on 11 carries in another stellar performance. He was obviously frustrated the Cardinals couldn&#8217;t score in the fourth quarter and watched the Dolphins score 10 unanswered points for the victory</p>
<p>Arizona’s Zane Gonzalez was short on a 49-yard field goal attempt that would have tied the game with 1:53 left.</p>
<p>Murray paused for several seconds before answering a few postgame questions, struggling for a response.</p>
<p>“We came out here and laid an egg,” Murray said.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa was much more productive in his second start after throwing for just 93 yards against the Rams last week. He showed great poise during two scoring drives in the fourth quarter. The left-hander also made some plays with his feet, extending drives with scrambles. He finished with 35 yards rushing.</p>
<p>“Tua did his part,&#8221; Miami coach Brian Flores said. “It wasn’t a perfect game. He made some mistakes, like we all did. But he fought back. We fought back as a team.”</p>
<p>This matches the Dolphins’ best record at the halfway point since 2001 and the four-game winning streak is their longest since 2016.</p>
<p>Miami had a 24-17 halftime lead but Arizona tied the game early in the third quarter on Murray&#8217;s 21-yard pass to tight end Darrell Daniels, who snatched the ball away from cornerback Byron Jones as the two tumbled to the ground in the end zone.</p>
<p>The Cardinals pushed ahead 31-24 late in the third quarter on Murray&#8217;s 12-yard run. It was the seventh time in eight games the quarterback has thrown and run for at least one touchdown.</p>
<p>But the Dolphins and Tagovailoa fought back on the next series, delivering an impressive 10-play, 93-yard drive that ended with an 11-yard touchdown pass to Mack Hollins. Miami pushed ahead 34-31 with 3:30 left on a 50-yard field goal by Jason Sanders.</p>
<p>“I don’t think any moment is too big for Tua,” Miami center Ted Karras said. “He has gained the respect of everyone in that huddle, and we want to go to battle for him and keep winning games.”</p>
<p>Miami came in allowing the fewest points per game in the NFL and the defense supplied seven of its own in the first quarter. Murray was scrambling on third down when Emmanuel Ogbah smacked the ball out of his hands. Shaq Lawson scooped up the fumble and ran 36 yards for a 7-0 lead.</p>
<p>Murray played much better after that costly miscue, throwing for 151 yards and two touchdowns while also running for 52 yards in the first half.</p>
<p>BIG FOOT</p>
<p>Sanders made a 56-yard field goal as time expired in the second quarter to give the Dolphins a 24-17 halftime lead. It was the longest field goal of his three-year pro career.</p>
<p>Sanders has made 20 consecutive field goals, a franchise record.</p>
<p>COACHES OUT</p>
<p>The Dolphins had five assistant coaches unavailable on Sunday because of COVID-19 protocols.</p>
<p>They were defensive backs coach Gerald Alexander, quarterbacks coach Robby Brown, outside linebackers coach Austin Clark, defensive line coach Marion Hobby and quality control coach Kolby Smith.</p>
<p>“The protocol said those coaches had to be out,” Flores said. “Nothing is more important than the health of this team. We’re going to do everything possible to contain the virus. We all know there is a pandemic. The infections are going up. We’re trying to do everything we can.”</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Dolphins: WR Preston Williams (foot) left the game in the second quarter and didn&#8217;t return. &#8230; TE Durham Smythe was evaluated for a concussion in the second half.</p>
<p>Cardinals: CB Kevin Peterson left the game early in the second quarter for a concussion evaluation and didn&#8217;t return. Arizona was already playing without starting CB Dre Kirkpatrick, inactive with a thigh injury.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Dolphins: return home to host the Chargers next Sunday.</p>
<p>Cardinals: host the Bills next Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">775753</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Tua-Tagovailoa-e1604926579164.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tua vs Kyler as rising Dolphins visit revitalized Cardinals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tua-vs-kyler-as-rising-dolphins-visit-revitalized-cardinals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 02:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=775058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; When the Dolphins leave the oceanfront and head to the desert to play the Cardinals on Sunday, it will be about more than...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; When the Dolphins leave the oceanfront and head to the desert to play the Cardinals on Sunday, it will be about more than Tua vs. Kyler.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s about two rising teams, perhaps earlier than anyone truly thought logical. Two playoff contenders, with dynamic young coaches, one trained to test defenses with wide-open offensive schemes (Arizona&#8217;s Kliff Kingsbury). The other a former assistant in New England (Miami&#8217;s Brian Flores) who just might be a product of the Patriots&#8217; coaching tree who can succeed in charge elsewhere.</p>
<p>Arizona (5-2) comes off a bye preceded by a major step, rallying to knock off division leader Seattle in overtime. The defense is coming around, though not like Miami&#8217;s.</p>
<p>And there are the young QBs. Kyler Murray was the NFL Offensive Rookie of the Year in 2019. Tua Tagovailoa, as touted as any signal caller coming out of college in years, will make his second start for Miami.</p>
<p>“You get the feeling of who is next up going into the league,” Murray says. &#8220;Obviously, Tua had a great college career. I didn’t envision this, but I knew he’d be in the league.”</p>
<p>Twelve months ago, the Dolphins (4-3) were 0-7 under Flores. They’ve since gone from worst to first in points allowed, now giving up 18.6 per game, compared with 34 a year ago.</p>
<p>“I think people have different definitions of turnaround,” Flores says. “Right now, we’re just trying to have a good turnaround and have a good practice today. Turnaround and have a good practice tomorrow. Someone else’s interpretation of a turnaround might be different than mine is.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">775058</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins assistant coach tests positive for COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-assistant-coach-tests-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 17:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=774293</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — An unidentified Miami Dolphins assistant coach tested positive for coronavirus and was quarantined, and receiver Lynn Bowden Jr. went on the reserve/COVID-19...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MIAMI (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; An unidentified Miami Dolphins assistant coach tested positive for coronavirus and was quarantined, and receiver Lynn Bowden Jr. went on the reserve/COVID-19 list, but the team planned to play Sunday&#x2019;s game at Arizona as scheduled.<p>Because of the coach&#x2019;s positive test, practice Friday was limited to a walkthrough. Meetings were held via Zoom, and more stringent requirements regarding mask wearing were enforced.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Look, it&#x2019;s 2020,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; coach Brian Flores said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Things are ever changing. We&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ve just got to be able to adapt.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/MiamiDolphins/status/1324726531118272518</embed></div><p>The Dolphins planned to fly to Arizona later Friday, and Flores was hopeful a spread of the virus within the team could be avoided.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I feel good about how we handled the situation,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Flores said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We wouldn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t fly if we felt like there was any situation where we would create some sort of outbreak.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>The Dolphins also ruled out running back Matt Breida (hamstring) for Sunday&#x2019;s game. Leading rusher Myles Gaskin (knee) went on injured reserve earlier this week, leaving Jordan Howard, Patrick Laird and Salvon Ahmed as the available running backs.</p><p>Flores did not say whether the infected coach had symptoms. The Dolphins hadn&#x2019;t had a coronavirus case since training camp.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We all knew something eventually was going to happen at some point,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; tight end Mike Gesicki said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;It wasn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t going to be a perfect season.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Miami&#x2019;s schedule was altered earlier this season because of outbreaks involving other teams.</p><p>The Cardinals are also dealing with the virus this week. They placed linebacker Devon Kennard and cornerback Byron Murphy Jr. on the NFL&#x2019;s reserve/COVID-19 list.</p><p>The Dolphins hadn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t had a player on the list since cornerback Xavien Howard was activated from it on Aug. 27.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">774293</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/dolphins-statement.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/bf157aeb-a444-47ef-a686-4ab3d0d674e6/70476027-0839-4697-a10c-89086bdaa056/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219456~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/bf157aeb-a444-47ef-a686-4ab3d0d674e6/70476027-0839-4697-a10c-89086bdaa056/main.mp4*~hmac=4efe06aebed16efc0277f01ce53e3e1d8721a6eaf09b4eaeb33e2b0a8417d265' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/dolphins-statement.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/dolphins-statement.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins statement</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins RB Myles Gaskin placed on IR with knee injury</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-rb-myles-gaskin-placed-on-ir-with-knee-injury/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=773733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins running back Myles Gaskin went on injured reserve Thursday, meaning he will miss at least three games with a knee...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins running back Myles Gaskin went on injured reserve Thursday, meaning he will miss at least three games with a knee injury.</p>
<p>Backup Matt Breida is nursing a hamstring injury, which could mean more playing time Sunday at Arizona for Jordan Howard.</p>
<p>Gaskin has been the Dolphins’ best backfield threat with 387 yards rushing and 198 receiving.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">773733</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190726 dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins send WR Isaiah Ford to Patriots for 6th-round pick</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-send-wr-isaiah-ford-to-patriots-for-6th-round-pick/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 16:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=773052</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOXBOROUGH, Mass. (AP) — The Miami Dolphins traded receiver Isaiah Ford to the New England Patriots on Tuesday for a sixth-round draft pick in 2022....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FOXBOROUGH, Mass. (AP) — The Miami Dolphins traded receiver Isaiah Ford to the New England Patriots on Tuesday for a sixth-round draft pick in 2022.</p>
<p>The move gives the Patriots some needed experience in a receiver group that has underperformed this season and has recently been hit by a string of injuries.</p>
<p>New England also claimed defensive tackle Isaiah Mack off waivers from the Titans on Tuesday and placed tight end Devin Asiasi on injured reserve. The Asiasi move comes after coach Bill Belichick said defensive tackle Beau Allen, who signed in the offseason, is not expected to return to action after recently returning to practice from IR.</p>
<p>The Dolphins also acquired running back DeAndre Washington from Kansas City, and the teams traded conditional late-round draft picks.</p>
<p>Ford, in his third season out of Virginia Tech, was a seventh-round pick in the 2017 draft. He has 18 catches for 184 yards this season, and 41 catches for 428 yards in his career.</p>
<p>New England entered the week thin at slot receiver after Julian Edelman was placed on injured reserve at the end of last week. N’Keal Harry also continues to recover from a concussion.</p>
<p>The Patriots rank 30th in the NFL in passing, averaging 192 yards per game. They have only three passing touchdowns on the season.</p>
<p>Washington played in only one game this year for the Chiefs. He was with Oakland in 2016-19, and rushed for 1,122 yards while averaging 4.0 yards per carry.</p>
<p>He was a fifth-round draft choice by the Raiders in 2016.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">773052</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/190726-dolphins-e1564148079227.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190726 dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big plays help Dolphins beat Rams 28-17 in Tua&#8217;s 1st start</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/big-plays-help-dolphins-beat-rams-28-17-in-tuas-1st-start/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 21:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=771285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa threw his first career touchdown pass and then let his teammates take over with a succession of big...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa threw his first career touchdown pass and then let his teammates take over with a succession of big plays, and the Miami Dolphins stamped themselves as playoff contenders Sunday by earning their third consecutive win, 28-17 against the Los Angeles Rams.</p>
<p>The Dolphins struck for scores 75 seconds apart on Andrew Van Ginkel’s 78-yard fumble return and Jakeem Grant’s team-record 88-yard punt return. They came up with four takeaways in the first half and at halftime led 28-10 despite being outgained 224-54.</p>
<p>The big plays helped Tagovailoa overcome a costly early turnover in his first NFL start. The No. 5 overall pick in this year’s draft finished 12 of 22 for 93 yards.</p>
<p>Los Angeles’ Jared Goff went 35 for 61 for 355 yards and one score with two interceptions and two lost fumbles.</p>
<p>The Rams ran 92 plays to the Dolphins’ 48, and Miami won while totaling eight first downs and 145 yards.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (4-3) have outscored opponents by a combined 95-34 in the past three games, and they’re above .500 for the first time in their 23 games under second-year coach Brian Flores.</p>
<p>The Rams (5-3) did manage to give Tagovailoa a jarring NFL welcome. The first time the rookie tried to throw, the ball came loose when his arm was hit by Aaron Donald, and Tagovailoa was then driven to the turf by Michael Brockers as Leonard Floyd recovered the fumble.</p>
<p>Los Angeles scored a touchdown three plays later for a 7-0 lead.</p>
<p>Then came 28 consecutive points by the Dolphins. Tagovailoa capitalized on their first takeaway by throwing a 3-yard touchdown pass to DeVante Parker. Tagovailoa retrieved the ball as a souvenir and carried it to the sideline, where the former Alabama star entertained teammates with a celebratory dance.</p>
<p>The Rams were threatening when Emmanuel Ogbah forced a fumble by sacking Goff. Van Ginkel scooped the ball up with nothing but open field in front of him and sprinted the distance to give Miami a 14-7 lead.</p>
<p>Barely a minute later, Grant sprinted through a seam in the Rams’ punt coverage for his fifth career return TD, and his third punt return for a score, both franchise records. Tagovailoa greeted the 5-foot-6 Grant on the sideline with a leaping chest bump to the face mask.</p>
<p>Shaq Lawson’s strip-sack of Goff and Kyle Van Noy’s return gave the Dolphins the ball at the 1, and they scored on the next play for a 28-7 lead. It was a stunning sequence for the Rams, who had just eight turnovers in their first seven games and trailed for less than 54 minutes previously all season.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Two-time Rams Pro Bowl cornerback Jalen Ramsey became ill before the game and didn’t play. His replacement, David Long Jr., was beaten by Parker for Miami’s first touchdown.</p>
<p>ANTHEM</p>
<p>Fifteen Rams players knelt during “The Star-Spangled Banner.” The Dolphins stayed in the locker room during the national anthem.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Dolphins next Sunday make their first visit to Arizona since 2012.</p>
<p>The Rams have a bye before playing at Seattle on Nov. 15. The teams split last year’s series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">771285</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">tua tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tua&#8217;s 1st start for Miami against Rams will test his hip</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/tuas-1st-start-for-miami-against-rams-will-test-his-hip/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=769896</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa is about to get hit. He doesn’t know exactly when it will happen, but he knows that sometime Sunday, he’ll...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa is about to get hit.</p>
<p>He doesn’t know exactly when it will happen, but he knows that sometime Sunday, he’ll likely be tackled for the first time since last Nov. 16, when he suffered a career-threatening hip injury on his final play for Alabama.</p>
<p>Now Tagovailoa is back to test that surgically repaired hip when he makes his first NFL start Sunday for the Miami Dolphins against the Los Angeles Rams.</p>
<p>“It has been a long time coming,” Tagovailoa said. “I don’t know what the hit is going to feel like. Every hit is different that you take in football, and I don’t think you can ever prepare for hits. It’s just something you have to go out knowing it’s going to happen.”</p>
<p>That&#8217;s especially true against a stout defense like the Rams&#8217;. Aaron Donald and company are eager to give Tagovailoa an appropriate welcome to the NFL, and the Rams (5-2) also hope to build on their city&#8217;s winning vibe in the wake of October championships claimed by the Lakers and Dodgers.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (3-3) will bid for their third consecutive victory with a chance to climb above .500 for the first time under second-year coach Brian Flores.</p>
<p>RECOVERED</p>
<p>The cringe-inducing sequence has been replayed countless times in the past 50 weeks: Two Mississippi State defenders knocked off Tagovailoa’s helmet, bloodied his nose and — worst of all — dislocated his right hip.</p>
<p>He was carted off the field and taken by helicopter to the hospital, where his long comeback began.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa was medically cleared before training camp, but less than a month ago, Flores said he remained mindful of the injury and wouldn&#8217;t rush Tagovailoa&#8217;s return. Last week the coach decided to promote his rookie as a replacement for veteran Ryan Fitzpatrick, and said he has no concerns regarding how Tagovailoa will react to being hit.</p>
<p>“From a health standpoint, we feel good about where he is,” Flores said. “He’s going to get hit in the game; we know that.”</p>
<p>Against the Rams, that&#8217;s likely. Donald ranks second in the league with eight sacks, and presents a significant challenge for an offensive line with two rookies.</p>
<p>GOING THE OTHER WAY</p>
<p>Tagovailoa does most things with his right hand, from eating to golfing, but he&#8217;ll try to beat the Rams with his left hand.</p>
<p>He&#8217;ll be the first left-handed quarterback to start a game since Kellen Moore for the Dallas Cowboys on Jan. 3, 2016.</p>
<p>“I think lefties are so rare in football because all of them are in baseball,” Tagovailoa said with a laugh.</p>
<p>As Rams coach Sean McVay noted, the football spirals in the opposite direction when thrown by a lefty, which requires an adjustment by receivers — and defensive backs.</p>
<p>“Hopefully we’ll get a chance to get our hands on some of his throws and go the other way,” McVay said.</p>
<p>RAMS GET DEFENSIVE</p>
<p>While Miami’s offense has racked up plenty of points, the Rams’ defense under rookie coordinator Brandon Staley is getting increasingly tough, particularly after halftime.</p>
<p>Los Angeles is up to sixth in the NFL in yards per game allowed (313), and only Baltimore has yielded fewer points per game than the Rams (17.7). Donald and his teammates have been particularly strong after halftime, giving up only 33 total points.</p>
<p>The defense hasn’t allowed a touchdown in the second half since Week 3.</p>
<p>DOLPHINS GET DEFENSIVE TOO</p>
<p>The Dolphins are coming off their first shutout since 2014. For the first time in a decade, they’ve held two consecutive opponents to less than 150 yards passing, and their third-down conversion rate of 31% is the league&#8217;s best.</p>
<p>“It has been said time and time again: It’s amazing what you can accomplish when nobody cares who gets the credit for it,” defensive coordinator Josh Boyer said.</p>
<p>HE CAN KICK IT</p>
<p>Veteran Kai Forbath will debut as the Rams’ new kicker in Miami. The Los Angeles native joined the team last week as the probable successor to rookie Samuel Sloman, who then sealed his fate against Chicago with his third missed field-goal attempt to go with three missed extra points this season.</p>
<p>Forbath was steadily accurate inside 45 yards for his first six NFL teams, and he had been working on improving his kickoff distance at a high school just a few miles from the Rams’ training complex.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">769896</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">tua tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flores explains leadership position Tua Tagovailoa will now step into</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/flores-explains-leadership-position-tua-tagovailoa-will-now-step-into/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 19:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=768788</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s Tua time for the Miami Dolphins. Tua Tagovailoa made his Fins debut nearly two weeks ago when he replaced Ryan Fitzpatrick on the field...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s Tua time for the Miami Dolphins.</p>
<p>Tua Tagovailoa made his Fins debut nearly two weeks ago when he replaced Ryan Fitzpatrick on the field during the last two minutes of the game against the New York Jets.</p>
<p>He took five snaps and was two for two in passing.</p>
<p>Miami Dolphins head coach Brian Flores wants his rookie quarterback to know he is in charge now in the huddle as the starter.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think it&#8217;s a leadership position so once you step into that role and you step into the huddle, and everyone is listening to your voice and listening to you call the plays, so when you&#8217;re in there as the number one guy, you assume a little bit [of a] bigger role,&#8221; Flores said. &#8220;That&#8217;s just natural to the position but I think he&#8217;s just being himself which is what we try to tell all the players.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tagovailoa will make his first NFL career start this Sunday against the LA Rams at the Hard Rock Stadium.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">768788</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">tua tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rocky start to Dolphins&#8217; QB transition to Tua Tagovailoa</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/rocky-start-to-dolphins-qb-transition-to-tua-tagovailoa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 19:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=764878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Dolphins&#8217; transition to Tua Tagovailoa didn’t start the way coach Brian Flores intended, and deposed quarterback Ryan Fitzpatrick said the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Dolphins&#8217; transition to Tua Tagovailoa didn’t start the way coach Brian Flores intended, and deposed quarterback Ryan Fitzpatrick said the surprising timing left him heartbroken.</p>
<p>Flores said he regretted that most of his players found out about the change through social media rather than from him, and said benching Fitzpatrick was a difficult decision.</p>
<p>“Fitz has done a great job,” Flores said Wednesday. “But we felt like for the team now, moving forward, this is a move we need to make.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa, the fifth pick in the April draft, will make his first NFL start on Nov. 1 against the Los Angeles Rams after Miami&#8217;s bye this week.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (3-3) <a href="https://apnews.com/article/nfl-new-york-brian-flores-football-parades-b8072e7891d7f08becd942b2f62e1e0a">have won their past two games </a> by a combined score of 67-17, and Fitzpatrick said he was shocked by the timing of his demotion.</p>
<p>“It definitely caught me off guard,” the 16-year veteran said. “It was a hard thing for me to hear. Digesting the news, my heart just hurt all day.</p>
<p>&#8220;This eventually was going to happen; it was a matter of when and not if. It’s still a tough thing for me to hear, and to now have to deal with. But I&#8217;m going to do my best.”</p>
<p>Flores told Fitzpatrick and Tagovailoa of his decision Tuesday, but <a href="https://apnews.com/article/nfl-brian-flores-miami-football-ryan-fitzpatrick-5b805de50544abec00ada8b6e901bc99">the news leaked </a> before the coach could share it with other players.</p>
<p>“The one thing in this situation that’s unfortunate is that I didn’t get a chance to address the team before this was out in the media,” Flores said. &#8220;It&#8217;s not the way I or we want to do business. Unfortunately, it&#8217;s kind of the way of the world right now.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m not happy about that at all. I&#8217;ll address that to the team, and really apologize to them that they had to find out through social media. I don’t think that’s fair to them.”</p>
<p>Flores shed little light on his reason to switch quarterbacks now. Tagovailoa made his NFL debut during mop-up time last week, completing both passes in his first action since suffering a serious hip injury last November that ended his Alabama career.</p>
<p>Even Tagovailoa&#8217;s parents were surprised to hear of their son&#8217;s promotion.</p>
<p>“They didn’t believe me for a little bit,” Tagovailoa said. “My dad joked, ‘After two throws, they want to put you in?’”</p>
<p>The two Dolphins QBs have what Tagovailoa laughingly described as a father/son relationship, and they said that will continue. But both agreed that for the moment, the situation is awkward.</p>
<p>“This profession is interesting,” Fitzpatrick said, “in that I basically got fired, and my day of work today basically consists of me in Zoom meetings listening to the guy that fired me, and then locked in a room with my replacement for four hours. There aren’t a whole lot of jobs like that.”</p>
<p>While the 37-year-old Fitzpatrick is popular with his teammates, captain Jerome Baker said the locker room is excited Flores is giving Tagovailoa a chance to show what he can do.</p>
<p>“We just put all our trust in Flo,” Baker said. “If he says Tua is the man to lead us, we’re going to go with it.”</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick, in his second season with his eighth NFL team, has been characteristically inconsistent this year. He is fifth in the the league in completion percentage but third in interceptions with seven.</p>
<p>“Fitz has been great for the last year and a half,” Flores said. “I don’t know if there has been anybody more instrumental in trying to instill the culture that we&#8217;re looking for. He has made an impact on Tua and a lot of other players on this team. I have a great respect for him, and that made this decision very tough.”</p>
<p>Even so, it was a decision anticipated since the day Miami drafted Tagovailoa as a potential franchise quarterback. The cancellation of offseason drills and exhibition games because of the coronavirus slowed his NFL development, and two weeks ago, Flores said Tagovailoa wasn&#8217;t ready to start.</p>
<p>Now he is.</p>
<p>“He has gotten more comfortable,” Flores said. “Accuracy, decision making, all those things have been good in practice. Practice is very different from games, but we’re comfortable and confident he’ll be able to be competitive.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa believes he&#8217;s ready, too.</p>
<p>“Opportunities come,” Tagovailoa said, “and when they come, you’ve got to take them and run with them.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">764878</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AP source: Tagovailoa replaces Fitzpatrick as Miami starter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ap-source-tagovailoa-replaces-fitzpatrick-as-miami-starter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 16:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=763988</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa now has a role to match his jersey number. He’s the Miami Dolphins’ No. 1 quarterback. The former Alabama star...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Tua Tagovailoa now has a role to match his jersey number. He’s the Miami Dolphins’ No. 1 quarterback.</p>
<p>The former Alabama star will make his first NFL start next week for the Miami Dolphins, who are turning to him to replace Ryan Fitzpatrick, a person familiar with the team&#8217;s decision said Tuesday.</p>
<p>The person confirmed the decision to The Associated Press on condition on anonymity because the Dolphins hadn&#8217;t made an announcement.</p>
<p>The change by coach Brian Flores will come after the Dolphins’ bye this week and has been long anticipated, but the timing is surprising because the team <a href="https://apnews.com/article/nfl-new-york-brian-flores-football-parades-b8072e7891d7f08becd942b2f62e1e0a">won its past two games </a>to improve to 3-3. Tagovailoa will start at home against the Los Angeles Rams on Nov. 1.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa made his pro debut in mop-up duty at the end of <a href="https://apnews.com/article/nfl-nba-new-york-adam-gase-brian-flores-5db4636b29937540f8552fa097ed0a54">Miami&#8217;s 24-0 victory Sunday </a>over the New York Jets. He will become the 22nd quarterback to start for the Dolphins since Dan Marino retired following the 1999 season.</p>
<p>At Alabama, Tagovailoa wore Marino&#8217;s No. 13. That Dolphins jersey is retired, and so Tagovailoa now wears No. 1.</p>
<p>Touted as a potential franchise quarterback, the dynamic Tagovailoa raises the profile of a team that has been off the NFL radar for much of the past two decades. He was drafted in April with the fifth overall pick — the highest choice Miami has devoted to a QB since Bob Griese in 1967.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa is coming back from a serious hip injury that cut short his Alabama career last November. The recovery slowed his preparation to assume a starting NFL job, as did the coronavirus pandemic that forced the cancellation of offseason drills and exhibition games.</p>
<p>“He has been thrown into a very difficult situation in that he didn’t have any preseason, he didn’t have really an offseason,” Dolphins offensive coordinator Chan Gailey said Tuesday, shortly before the news of Tagovailoa’s promotion broke.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick, 37, described himself during training camp as a placeholder. He is being benched even though he ranks fifth in the NFL in completion percentage, and the Dolphins are on pace for their highest-scoring season since 1986 at 26.7 points per game.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa went 2 for 2 for 9 yards against the Jets.</p>
<p>“Under duress he made an accurate throw,” Gailey said. “Then he sat in the pocket on third down and made a throw for a first down. For a guy that hadn’t played a snap, those are real positives.”</p>
<p>After the game, Tagovailoa spent several minutes sitting alone on the field and on his phone with his parents.</p>
<p>“It was exciting to get out there,” he said. “The most important thing that came out of my conversation with my parents was just that they were happy to see me out there and playing again.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa also expressed gratitude Sunday for the support Fitzpatrick has given him.</p>
<p>“Good drive, bad drive, he comes to the sideline and just talks through his process with why he did some things,” Tagovailoa said. “I’m very fortunate to have a mentor like him who is just very encouraging on the field, and he’s just very personable off the field, as well.”</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick led cheers from the sideline when Tagovailoa took the field for the first time in 11 months.</p>
<p>“That was a cool moment for him,” Fitzpatrick said. &#8220;We were all excited to see him get out there.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa takes over an offense much-improved from a year ago, when Miami went 5-11 under rookie coach Flores. For the first time in franchise history, the Dolphins have started three draft picks in the offensive line, and they&#8217;ve allowed only 10 sacks after giving up a league-high 58 last year.</p>
<p>At Alabama, Tagovailoa threw 76 touchdown passes in 24 starts over his final two seasons. He replaced Jalen Hurts in the national championship game in January 2018 and rallied the Crimson Tide past Georgia, and the following season he was the Heisman Trophy runner-up.</p>
<p>“Most guys don’t have to go through what Tua went through in terms of the adversity that he had to overcome from an injury standpoint,” Alabama coach Nick Saban said Monday. &#8220;We hope that he does extremely well, and it surely won’t surprise me if that’s the case.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">763988</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/tua-tagovailoa.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">tua tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins turn up heat on Jets and embattled Gase, 24-0</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-turn-up-heat-on-jets-and-embattled-gase-24-0/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 23:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=762872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick threw three touchdown passes and the Miami Dolphins held the winless New York Jets without a third-down conversion...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick threw three touchdown passes and the Miami Dolphins held the winless New York Jets without a third-down conversion until the fourth quarter Sunday to get their first shutout in six years, 24-0.</p>
<p>The game was so lopsided that Miami rookie Tua Tagovailoa made his NFL debut in mop-up duty with 2:27 left. The Dolphins’ potential franchise quarterback ran onto the field to a big roar from the crowd of 10,772, and a grinning Fitzpatrick waved to encourage more cheers.</p>
<p>The Dolphins (3-3) reached .500 for the first time under second-year coach Brian Flores and moved into second place in the AFC East behind Buffalo. The Jets (0-6) became the NFL&#8217;s only winless team and continued their worst start since 1996, increasing the heat on embattled coach Adam Gase.</p>
<p>The Dolphins blanked the Jets for the first time since the January 1983 AFC championship game, which they won 14-0.</p>
<p>The two teams were a combined 0 for 19 on third downs before the Jets finally converted with 11 minutes left. The Dolphins&#8217; only third-down conversion came on a completion by Tagovailoa, who went 2 for 2 for 9 yards.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick was 18 for 27 for 191 yards for Miami. He also blocked for Myles Gaskins on a run and improvised a left-handed completion under pressure for a short gain.</p>
<p>Gaskin had 18 carries for 91 yards.</p>
<p>Joe Flacco, making his second start for the injured Sam Darnold, went 21 for 44 for 186 and an interception. He was sacked three times, once for 28 yards.</p>
<p>The Jets, who released running back Le’Veon Bell on Tuesday, had 115 yards rushing.</p>
<p>The Dolphins built a 21-0 lead in the first half. Fitzpatrick threw three short touchdown passes each from inside the 5-yard line. Adam Shaheen, Preston Williams and Durham Smythe each caught a touchdown pass.</p>
<p>The attendance of 10,772 of a capacity of 13,000 was the smallest crowd this season. Conspicuous by their absence was the usual vocal contingent of Jets fans.</p>
<p>INTERCEPTIONS</p>
<p>The Jets’ Marcus Maye made a bizarre interception on a Fitzpatrick pass intended for Preston Williams. The ball went up in the air and Maye was able to corral the loose ball by reaching behind his back and cradling the ball against his backside.</p>
<p>Xavien Howard’s second-quarter interception of Flacco&#8217;s pass was his fourth of the season, and gives him an interception in four straight games, the second-longest streak in Dolphins history. Dick Westmoreland had a five-game streak in 1967.</p>
<p>JUST FOR KICKS</p>
<p>Dolphins kicker Jason Sanders is 15 for 15 on field goal tries, a franchise record to start a season. Jets K Sam Ficken had made all nine of his field-goal attempts and his six extra-point attempts coming into the game, but missed a 55-yarder in the third quarter.</p>
<p>INJURIES</p>
<p>Jest: LB Frankie Luvu suffered a groin injury and did not return. … T Chuma Edoga left with a calf injury and did not return. … OL Alex Lewis left with a shoulder injury.</p>
<p>Dolphins: LB Andrew Van Ginkel left with a concussion in the second quarter and did not return.</p>
<p>ANTHEM</p>
<p>Running back Ty Jackson was the only player kneeling for the Jets during “The Star-Spangled Banner.”</p>
<p>The Dolphins stayed in the locker room.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Dolphins have a bye and then host the Los Angeles Rams on Nov. 1.</p>
<p>The Jets host Buffalo next Sunday. The Bills won 27-17 when the teams met in Week 1.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">762872</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AP source: Dolphins DT Godchaux expected to be out 3 months</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ap-source-dolphins-dt-godchaux-expected-to-be-out-3-months/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 18:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=759895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins defensive tackle Davon Godchaux is expected to be sidelined for three months with a biceps injury, a person familiar with...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins defensive tackle Davon Godchaux is expected to be sidelined for three months with a biceps injury, a person familiar with the situation said Tuesday, meaning he will likely miss the rest of the season.</p>
<p>The person confirmed Godchaux&#8217;s injury on condition of anonymity because the Dolphins hadn&#8217;t addressed it publicly. Godchaux received a second opinion and hopes to return before the end of the season, the person said.</p>
<p>The injury will end Godchaux&#8217;s streak of 41 consecutive starts Sunday when Miami plays the New York Jets. This year he has 16 tackles and one tackle for a loss.</p>
<p>His absence will likely mean more snaps for defensive linemen Zach Sieler and Raekwon Davis.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">759895</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/davon-godchaux-e1602615242193.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/davon-godchaux-e1602615242193.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/davon-godchaux-e1602615242193.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">davon godchaux</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Dolphins, Its4thekids team up to distribute 1,000 meals</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-dolphins-its4thekids-team-up-to-distribute-over-1000-meals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=759090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Dolphins teamed up with a local organization to donate 1,000 meals across South Florida. On Sunday, the Miami Dolphins Foundation and Its4thekids organization...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Dolphins teamed up with a local organization to donate 1,000 meals across South Florida.</p>
<p>On Sunday, the Miami Dolphins Foundation and Its4thekids organization teamed up to distribute the free food.</p>
<p>The organization&#8217;s founder, Ricky Patel, also handed out hundreds of copies of his children&#8217;s book &#8220;The Beautiful Caterpillar.&#8221;</p>
<p>He co-wrote the book with his daughter during quarantine.</p>
<p>&#8220;Its4thekids is an organization&#8211; it&#8217;s a foundation created to help out people in need, especially in this time,&#8221; said Patel. &#8220;In this pandemic, we&#8217;ve switched from not just helping out children, but helping out families in need and one of the best parts about that is we get to find restaurants that are in need of business.&#8221;</p>
<p>The meals were handed out at three different locations and were purchased from five minority-owned restaurants.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">759090</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/its4thekids.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8f99aae0-b3dc-46d9-90d2-290500f5370b/8a7f431f-631d-47b0-ba60-6cef8ad4da91/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216836~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8f99aae0-b3dc-46d9-90d2-290500f5370b/8a7f431f-631d-47b0-ba60-6cef8ad4da91/main.mp4*~hmac=d7a2891b50614356dde3fa77de354d3abc88f491e9d4ba12a79b4e6656c59836' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/its4thekids.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/its4thekids.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">its4thekids</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami&#8217;s Flores says Tua isn&#8217;t ready to assume starting role</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miamis-flores-says-tua-isnt-ready-to-assume-starting-role/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 18:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=756371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores says Tua Tagovailoa needs more time to be groomed for the job he was drafted to fill....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores says Tua Tagovailoa needs more time to be groomed for the job he was drafted to fill.</p>
<p>“As far as him being a starter, we just don’t feel like he’s ready there just yet,” Flores said Wednesday.</p>
<p>Ryan Fitzpatrick will remain the starter Sunday at San Francisco for the Dolphins, even though they&#8217;re 1-3 and lost last week at home to Seattle.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa, considered a potential franchise quarterback, was drafted with the fifth overall pick but has yet to take a snap.</p>
<p>“Right now we feel like Fitz gives us the best chance to win,” Flores said.</p>
<p>Limited game snaps for Tagovailoa as a backup to speed his development aren&#8217;t likely.</p>
<p>“I wouldn’t be in favor of something like that,” Flores said. “There are so many things pertaining to the team that you don’t want to do something for one specific person.”</p>
<p>Tagovailoa has done all the right things since joining the Dolphins in April, Flores said. Like all 2020 rookies, he was hurt by the cancellation of the exhibition season and offseason practices due to the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>“He has to keep doing what he’s doing,” Flores said. “He’s working, he’s practicing well. He’s learning every day, he’s getting better every day. If he just continues to do what he’s doing, he’s on the right trajectory.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">756371</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Not yet Tua time: Fitzpatrick to remain Dolphins&#8217; starter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/not-yet-tua-time-fitzpatrick-to-remain-dolphins-starter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 18:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=755684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick will remain the Miami Dolphins’ starting quarterback for at least another week, further delaying the NFL debut of Tua Tagovailoa....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Ryan Fitzpatrick will remain the Miami Dolphins’ starting quarterback for at least another week, further delaying the NFL debut of Tua Tagovailoa.</p>
<p>The Dolphins announced Tuesday on Twitter that Fitzpatrick will get the nod Sunday at San Francisco. The disclosure ended speculation coach Brian Flores was about to turn the offense over to Tagovailoa, drafted with the fifth overall pick as a potential franchise quarterback.</p>
<p>“I’ve been around Fitz for a long time, and I’ve seen him play very, very well,” said Miami offensive coordinator Chan Gailey, who was Fitzpatrick&#8217;s head coach in Buffalo. “He is capable of being very good for us.”</p>
<p>The 37-year-old Fitzpatrick recently described his career as a roller coaster, and that has been the case this season with Miami (1-3). In two games he has totaled four touchdown passes and no interceptions, and in the other two games — including Sunday’s loss to Seattle — he has thrown for no scores with five interceptions.</p>
<p>Against the Seahawks, Miami settled for field goals on five consecutive scoring drives, but Gailey declined to blame Fitzpatrick.</p>
<p>“If you want to point fingers, you ought to point them at me,” Gailey said, “because I could have done a better job of red-zone coaching this past week, and we wouldn’t even be having this conversation.”</p>
<p>Two of the four quarterbacks taken in the first round of this year&#8217;s draft — the Bengals’ Joe Burrow and the Chargers’ Justin Herbert — are already starting and played well Sunday. The other, Jordan Love of the Packers, has yet to play as Aaron Rodgers&#8217; backup.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa hasn&#8217;t played since a serious hip injury ended his Alabama career last November, and the cancellation of offseason practices because of the coronavirus pandemic slowed his development. But he&#8217;s ready if needed, Gailey said.</p>
<p>“He’s one play away from going in to play,” Gailey said. &#8220;I feel like he&#8217;ll go in and play well.</p>
<p>“He’s a rookie who hasn’t played a preseason game or been in a game at all. It’ll be a new experience for him, and he&#8217;ll have to go in with eyes wide open. But I think he’s going to be ready when his time is called.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">755684</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1599487131626.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1599487131626.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1599487131626.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ryan fitzpatrick</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>31-23 win over Dolphins gives Seahawks 1st 4-0 start since 2013</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/31-23-win-over-dolphins-gives-seahawks-1st-4-0-start-since-2013/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 22:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=754403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — The unbeaten Seattle Seahawks revived their blueprint from years past, winning with repeated defensive stops and one pivotal pass. Russell...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — The unbeaten Seattle Seahawks revived their blueprint from years past, winning with repeated defensive stops and one pivotal pass.</p>
<p>Russell Wilson’s record production pace slackened slightly, but his long completion in the final seconds of the first half helped the Seahawks begin to pull away, and they beat the Miami Dolphins 31-23 Sunday.</p>
<p>Wilson threw for 360 yards and two touchdowns, and Seattle improved to 4-0.</p>
<p>“For us to be 4-0 is a huge thing,” Wilson said. ”Just keep winning one game at a time, and that’s what’s really important to us.”</p>
<p>The Seahawks swept their first four games only one other time in franchise history — in 2013, when they won their only Super Bowl. They’ve scored 30 or more points in four consecutive games for the first time since 2015.</p>
<p>But it was defense that made the difference against the Dolphins (1-3), who fell behind as they settled for <a href="https://www.nfl.com/games/seahawks-at-dolphins-2020-reg-4">Jason Sanders field goals </a>on their first five scoring drives.</p>
<p>“We kept them in front of us all day long and made them earn their way,” Seattle coach Pete Carroll said.</p>
<p>Wilson connected with David Moore for 57 yards in the final seconds of the first half to set up a touchdown that gave Seattle a 17-9 halftime lead. First-round draft pick Noah Igbinoghene blew the coverage on the play.</p>
<p>“I knew what to do,” Igbinoghene said. “I just made a mistake.”</p>
<p>The Seahawks’ headsets that went out to start the drive, and Wilson called the plays himself.</p>
<p>“I’m always prepared for those moments. &#8230; I know the game plan,” Wilson said. “I know how we want to attack them.”</p>
<p>Wilson, who went 24 for 34, tied Peyton Manning’s record of 16 touchdown passes in the first four games of a season. Manning did it 2013.</p>
<p>Jet lag and the subtropical heat weren’t issues for the Seahawks. Neither were injuries that left them short-handed in the secondary.</p>
<p>Ryan Fitzpatrick was 29 for 45 and 315 yards but threw two interceptions for Miami. He also rushed for a touchdown and was the leading rusher for Miami with six carries for 47 yards.</p>
<p>“The story of the day was being able to move the ball effectively, and not being able to do anything in the red zone, whether it was a penalty or poor execution or a bad read by me.” Fitzpatrick said. “I felt like there were a lot of guys on our team that played well enough to win. I unfortunately was not one of them.”</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick scored Miami’s only touchdown with 1:50 left, but Seattle recovered the ensuing onside kick.</p>
<p>DK Metcalf had four catches for 106 yards, Moore had three for 95 yards, and Chris Carson rushed for 80 yards and a pair of touchdowns.</p>
<p>Carson was questionable coming into the game because of a sprained knee.</p>
<p>“Chris is a stud football player and isn’t backing down from anything,” Carroll said.</p>
<p>But the Seahawks were twice blanked on trips to the red zone, including when Xavien Howard intercepted Wilson. Seattle had been 10 for 10 previously this season.</p>
<p>Wilson tossed a 17-yard touchdown pass to Moore to stretch the Seahawks’ lead to 24-15 with 5:24 left in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>On their next possession, Wilson hit Metcalf with a 32-yard pass to the Dolphins 1, setting up Carson’s second touchdown to make it 31-15.</p>
<p>ATTENDANCE</p>
<p>The announced attendance was 12,369, a bit short of the 13,000 capacity. There were numerous Seahawks jerseys scattered among the crowd.</p>
<p>NOT FEELING THE HEAT</p>
<p>The heat index was over 100 degrees and the temperature was 86 degrees, but it didn’t slow down the Seahawks’ offense.</p>
<p>“It was a tough day today just because it was so hot out there, we being from the Pacific Northwest. Guys just kept battling,” Wilson said.</p>
<p>ANTHEM</p>
<p>Four Seahawks players took a knee and five others sat during The Star-Spangled Banner.</p>
<p>The Dolphins stayed in the locker room for the anthem.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Seattle plays host to Minnesota next Sunday. Wilson threw for 240 yards and two scores when the Seahawks beat the Vikings 37-30 last December.</p>
<p>Miami plays at San Francisco for the first time since 2012 next Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">754403</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flores and Dolphins will try to slow down Wilson and Seattle</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/flores-and-dolphins-will-try-to-slow-down-wilson-and-seattle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=752421</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Malcolm Butler won&#8217;t be available for Brian Flores to send into the game if the Seattle Seahawks get down to the 1-yard...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Malcolm Butler won&#8217;t be available for Brian Flores to send into the game if the Seattle Seahawks get down to the 1-yard line Sunday, and that&#8217;s not his only worry.</p>
<p>Everything has changed for Flores since the 2015 Super Bowl when he substituted Butler, who made a game-saving interception of Russell Wilson to help the New England Patriots edge Seattle.</p>
<p>“That stuff is in the past,” Flores said. “Can’t help us now.”</p>
<p>Then the Patriots&#8217; safeties coach, Flores is now in his second year as the Miami Dolphins&#8217; head coach. But Wilson and the Seahawks (3-0) are still a championship-caliber team, which means the Dolphins (1-2) will have their hands full when the teams meet for the first time in four years.</p>
<p>DEFENDING SEATTLE</p>
<p>Flores&#8217; order of “Malcolm, go!” sent Butler into the game and into Super Bowl lore. His decision is still fondly remembered in New England, as is the Seahawks&#8217; choice of plays.</p>
<p>When asked whether he anticipates that the Seahawks will run or pass in a similar situation Sunday, Flores allowed himself a small smile.</p>
<p>“They can do anything on the 1,” he said. “They’ve got a lot of options.”</p>
<p>The bigger issue for Miami is that Seattle can score from anywhere on the field. Wilson leads the NFL with 14 touchdown passes, the most after three games in league history, and the Seahawks have scored 111 points.</p>
<p>Flores&#8217; defense is coming off its best performance yet in a 31-13 win at Jacksonville. But Cam Newton and Josh Allen gave the Dolphins fits with both their running and passing, which makes the matchup against the elusive Wilson problematic.</p>
<p>“You’ve got some guys who extend plays and they’re looking to scramble,” Flores said. “There are some guys who extend plays who are looking to throw. With Russell Wilson, it can be either-or. He’s very good at both.”</p>
<p>THIN SECONDARY</p>
<p>Seattle&#8217;s secondary has been riddled by opposing quarterbacks and by injuries. The Seahawks, who have allowed a league-worst 431 yards per game, are likely to be without starting strong safety Jamal Adams. He suffered a groin strain last week against Dallas.</p>
<p>Seattle already lost nickel cornerback Marquise Blair for the season, and both cornerback Quinton Dunbar (knee) and backup safety Lano Hill (back) were inactive last week and are uncertain against the Dolphins.</p>
<p>Seattle is also likely to be without rookie linebacker Jordyn Brooks (knee), who made his first start last week.</p>
<p>“We have to quit making the errors that come from the newness and the guys not being out there together,&#8221; coach Pete Carroll said. “It has been sloppy at times, and the communication has not been as effective as it needs to be.”</p>
<p>CATCHING ON</p>
<p>In the first two weeks, Wilson was more than happy to spread the wealth with his touchdown tosses. But last week against Dallas, Wilson focused on Tyler Lockett, who set a career high with three touchdown receptions.</p>
<p>Lockett finished with nine catches for 100 yards and is on pace for a 128-catch season.</p>
<p>“We have a quarterback that can figure out a way to run around and just keep the play alive, and you never know when he’s going to be able to give it to you,” Lockett said.</p>
<p>Lockett isn’t alone in having a big start to the season. This week DK Metcalf can become the third player in league history to start the season with four consecutive games of at least 90 yards receiving and a TD catch.</p>
<p>BUSY BACK</p>
<p>Myles Gaskin, a seventh-round pick from Washington in 2019, has surprisingly beaten out veterans Matt Breida and Jordan Howard to become Miami’s No. 1 running back.</p>
<p>Gaskin leads the team with 152 yards rushing and 15 receptions, and he’s averaging 4.6 yards per touch after playing little as a rookie.</p>
<p>“Trying not to look bad,” he said. “Last year was definitely a learning, humbling experience. It makes you hungry, not playing.”</p>
<p>BETTER BLOCKING</p>
<p>The Dolphins are averaging 3.8 yards per rush and have allowed only five sacks. Their improvement over last year in both categories reflects well on a revamped line that includes two rookies, left tackle Austin Jackson and right guard Solomon Kindley.</p>
<p>“Those two have played pretty well thus far,” offensive coordinator Chan Gailey said. “They need to continue to improve, which they can. They have the ability to become very good players before it’s over.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">752421</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/brian-flores.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/brian-flores.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/brian-flores.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">brian flores</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins&#8217; Tagovailoa misses practice because of illness</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-tagovailoa-misses-practice-because-of-illness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 15:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=751471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins rookie quarterback Tua Tagovailoa missed practice Wednesday because of an illness that wasn&#8217;t related to the coronavirus, coach Brian Flores...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Dolphins rookie quarterback Tua Tagovailoa missed practice Wednesday because of an illness that wasn&#8217;t related to the coronavirus, coach Brian Flores said.</p>
<p>The Dolphins&#8217; top draft pick and former Alabama star has yet to play as the backup to Ryan Fitzpatrick. Their other quarterback, rookie Reid Sinnett, is on the practice squad.</p>
<p>Miami (1-2) plays host to Seattle (3-0) on Sunday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">751471</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/tua-tagovailoa-4.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Tua Tagovailoa</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fitzpatrick handles Jaguars again, this time with Dolphins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/fitzpatrick-handles-jaguars-again-this-time-with-dolphins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 03:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=746253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Different team, familiar result for Ryan Fitzpatrick against the Jacksonville Jaguars. Fitzpatrick accounted for three touchdowns and led Miami to a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Different team, familiar result for Ryan Fitzpatrick against the Jacksonville Jaguars.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick accounted for three touchdowns and led Miami to a 31-13 victory Thursday night, becoming the first NFL quarterback to notch six wins over the same opponent with six teams.</p>
<p>The lopsided outcome also gave the Dolphins (1-2) their first double-digit victory in 39 games, ending the longest drought in the league.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick completed his first 12 passes — a career high — as Miami scored touchdowns on its first three drives for the first time since 2011. He ended the night celebrating another victory over the Jaguars (1-2).</p>
<p>He improved to 6-2 as a starter versus Jacksonville, with wins coming with Cincinnati (2008), Buffalo (2012), Tennessee (2013), Houston (2014), the New York Jets (2015) and now Miami.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick also ran for 39 yards and a score, his 37-year-old legs looking as fresh as any in Miami’s backfield.</p>
<p>He completed 18 of 20 passes — the last one to himself — for 160 yards and two touchdowns in his latest successful outing against the Jags, who made countless mistakes while failing to consistently move the chains and get off the field on third down.</p>
<p>In short, they looked exactly like the team most outsiders expected them to be this season.</p>
<p>Jacksonville&#8217;s most egregious errors:</p>
<p>—Chris Conley dropped two passes that would have been first downs and was flagged for offensive pass interference in the third quarter. Gardner Minshew fumbled on the next play, leading to Miami’s fourth touchdown of the night.</p>
<p>—Minshew audibled to a pitch to the short side of the field on a third-and-5 play. He was sacked on the next play, ending a shot at making the game close at halftime.</p>
<p>—Left tackle Cam Robinson was disqualified for making contact with an official following Minshew’s fumble.</p>
<p>—Rookie cornerback CJ Henderson was on the wrong end of one of four pass interference calls against Jacksonville. He also failed to touch receiver Jakeem Grant down after Grant made a diving catch. Henderson clapped his hands as Grant jumped up and gained an extra 10 yards.</p>
<p>Adding injury to insult, the Jaguars may have lost linebacker Leon Jacobs for the season. Jacobs was carted off the field on the opening drive with a right knee injury.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick was already in control by then. He scored a few plays later as Jacksonville allowed a touchdown on the game&#8217;s opening drive for the third straight week.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick had TD passes to Preston Williams and Mike Gesicki — his best throw of the night — in the first half and ran for a score in the third.</p>
<p>Everything went so well for Fitzpatrick that even a pass batted down at the line of scrimmage in the fourth bounced right into his arms for a reception.</p>
<p>BRIGHT SPOT</p>
<p>Rookie running back James Robinson was one of Jacksonville&#8217;s few bright spots. He ran 11 times for 46 yards and two touchdowns and had six receptions for 83 yards.</p>
<p>WATSON’S DEBUT</p>
<p>Jaguars rookie Brandon Watson made his NFL debut against Miami, joining a small list of Black place-kickers in league history. The group includes Gene Mingo, Cookie Gilchrist, Donald Igweibuike, Obed Ariri, Cedric Oglesby and Justin Medlock.</p>
<p>Watson, an undrafted rookie from Georgia State, was called up from Jacksonville’s practice squad this week to replace Josh Lambo, who was placed on injured reserve with a hip injury.</p>
<p>Watson missed one of his two extra point attempts. He also injured a groin in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>KEY INJURIES</p>
<p>Jaguars safety Andrew Wingard was ruled out at halftime with a core muscle injury. He was filling in for starter Jarrod Wilson, who was placed on injured reserve after the opener. … Jaguars receiver DJ Chark (chest/back) was ruled out about six hours before kickoff. The team chose to be cautious with the 2019 Pro Bowl selection. He’s expected back at practice next week. &#8230; The Dolphins were without No. 1 cornerback Byron Jones (groin/Achilles tendon).</p>
<p>SOCIAL JUSTICE</p>
<p>Both teams remained in their locker room for the national anthem, continuing their push for social and racial justice.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami hosts Seattle on Oct. 4. The Dolphins have won five of the last seven meetings, including three straight in South Florida.</p>
<p>Jacksonville plays at Cincinnati on Oct. 4. The Jaguars have won two in a row against the Bengals, notching victories in 2017 and 2019.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">746253</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/ryan-fitzgerald-e1590160782325.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/ryan-fitzgerald-e1590160782325.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/ryan-fitzgerald-e1590160782325.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ryan fitzpatrick</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins fans practice social distancing at Sunday&#8217;s game</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-fans-practice-social-distancing-at-sundays-game/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=742197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Strict rules were in place at Hard Rock Stadium for the Dolphins&#8217; home opener. Fins supporters were limited in number on Sunday and were forced...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Strict rules were in place at Hard Rock Stadium for the Dolphins&#8217; home opener.</p>
<p>Fins supporters were limited in number on Sunday and were forced to sit while practicing social distancing for safety reasons.</p>
<p>Only 13,000 fans were allowed in the stands and they had to wear their masks while attending the game.</p>
<p>&#8220;I feel comfortable being here,&#8221; said Dolphins fan Aaron Seifert. &#8220;The cases are going down so I decided to show up.&#8221;</p>
<p>Staggered entryways and mobile food pick up was available for guests.</p>
<p>Those who still did not feel safe enough to sit inside the stadium were able to watch the game on the big screen outside.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">742197</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/dolphins-fans-e1600704332869.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/dolphins-fans-e1600704332869.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/dolphins-fans-e1600704332869.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins fans</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hard Rock Stadium reveals COVID-19 precautions ahead of Dolphins&#8217; home opener</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hard-rock-stadium-reveals-covid-19-precautions-ahead-of-dolphins-home-opener/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 23:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=739847</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A limited number of fans will be allowed inside Hard Rock Stadium for the Miami Dolphins&#8217; home opener, and the venue has taken multiple precautions...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A limited number of fans will be allowed inside Hard Rock Stadium for the Miami Dolphins&#8217; home opener, and the venue has taken multiple precautions to keep attending fans safe from COVID-19.</p>
<p>The Dolphins and Hard Rock Stadium explained the precautions during a tour on Friday, two days before the Dolphins host the Buffalo Bills.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our priority was to make it safe,&#8221; Senior Vice President of Stadium Operations Todd Boyan said. &#8220;The difference with, obviously, starting from the outside in.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fans will see changes beginning in the venue&#8217;s parking lot, where no tailgating will be allowed, to the entry gate, where fans can enter the venue without touching any surfaces.</p>
<p>&#8220;You can go into the stadium without having to touch anything, so you don&#8217;t need to take anything out of your pocket,&#8221; Boyan said. &#8220;Your cellphone doesn&#8217;t need to be taken out of your pocket. You can go through a screening that&#8217;s touchless.&#8221;</p>
<p>Changes were also made to the stadium&#8217;s indoor club level concession stands, the restrooms and where fans sit to watch the game.</p>
<p>&#8220;Fans will notice that the bars will not be an area where you can hang around and loiter, in front of the bars,&#8221; Boyan said. &#8220;You have 6 feet in front of you, 6 feet behind you and to the left and the right.&#8221;</p>
<p>Once inside the stadium, the changes will be visible to those in attendance. Some of the seats have been covered with &#8220;seat belts,&#8221; and a limited party of people will be allowed to sit in a row. Fans will be allowed to sit in parties of two, four and six.</p>
<p>Only 13,000 seats will be available at the 65,000 seat capacity stadium.</p>
<p>For between $20 and $60, additional fans can watch the game outside the stadium in the game day theater.</p>
<p>Hand sanitizer stations are sprinkled throughout the venue. Those attending must wear a mask at all times, unless they are eating or drinking in their seat or a dining area table on the concourse.</p>
<p>The Dolphins said there are tickets available for Sunday&#8217;s game.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">739847</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091820-hard-rock-stadium-dolphins.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/098f9acb-f0d9-445c-8ae1-d47b55402efa/752e34eb-c186-46c1-919e-cd38135423b1/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216951~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/098f9acb-f0d9-445c-8ae1-d47b55402efa/752e34eb-c186-46c1-919e-cd38135423b1/main.mp4*~hmac=95c1fce9be218e53a5dd7697f1786f63ac2a4e0d64d96a65714e94ac459a28d4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091820-hard-rock-stadium-dolphins.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091820-hard-rock-stadium-dolphins.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">091820 hard rock stadium dolphins</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fans will be allowed to attend Dolphins game on Sunday at Hard Rock Stadium</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/fans-will-be-allowed-to-attend-dolphins-game-on-sunday-at-hard-rock-stadium/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 18:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=735123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Those who missed being able to see the Miami Dolphins play at Hard Rock Stadium can once again return to the stands. When the Dolphins...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Those who missed being able to see the Miami Dolphins play at Hard Rock Stadium can once again return to the stands.</p>
<p>When the Dolphins take on the Buffalo Bills on Sunday, fans will be allowed to attend the game.</p>
<p>The team is hoping to put on a better performance for week two after losing to the Patriots 21-11 in their season opener.</p>
<p>No fans were allowed at Gillette Stadium during the Sept. 13 game.</p>
<p>The Miami Dolphins coaches and players also remained in the locker room during the National Anthem to send a message against racial injustice.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think our message was definitely heard,&#8221; said Miami Dolphins defensive tackle Christian Wilkins. &#8220;You know, we spend a lot of time as a team, trying to portray the message and I feel like it was heard for sure.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;We felt like it was best that we did what we did, so as a team we&#8217;re going to do it,&#8221; said Miami Dolphins safety Bobby McCain.</p>
<p>When the game started, the Dolphins had no answer to the Patriots&#8217; rushing attack led by Cam Newton.</p>
<p>&#8220;All of us just kind of have the same mood, just get better next week.&#8221; said Wilkins. &#8220;We&#8217;re just going to have to flush this one as soon as we can. Like I said, the 24 hour rule: move on, see what we can do better and get focused on the next one.&#8221;</p>
<p>It didn&#8217;t help the Dolphins&#8217; starting quarterback Ryan Fitzpatrick threw three interceptions.</p>
<p>&#8220;I didn&#8217;t play better in my part and we&#8217;ll move on to next week,&#8221; said Fitzpatrick.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t just Fitzpatrick who struggled.</p>
<p>&#8220;All things we can improve on,&#8221; said head coach Brian Flores. &#8220;We can improve the tackling, we can improve the run defense, we can improve the conditioning. We can work on those things over the course of the week and we&#8217;ve got a tough opponent next week and we&#8217;ll get back to it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Hard Rock Stadium will host 13,000 fans for Sunday&#8217;s game.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">735123</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/hard-rock-stadium-seating.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/hard-rock-stadium-seating.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/hard-rock-stadium-seating.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hard rock stadium seating</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Dolphins video says they&#8217;ll stay inside during anthem</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-dolphins-video-says-theyll-stay-inside-during-anthem/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 02:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=731352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Black and white Miami Dolphins players and coach Brian Flores released a video on social media Thursday saying they’ll protest racial injustice...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MIAMI (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Black and white Miami Dolphins players and coach Brian Flores released a video on social media Thursday saying they&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ll protest racial injustice by remaining in their locker room during the national anthem.<p>The two-minute, 15-second video featured nearly 20 players trading stern rhymes about the nation&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s social protest movement.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;If you speak up for change, then I shut up and play,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; safety Bobby McCain said.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/i/status/1304186433054420992</embed></div><p>The NFL plans to play the national anthem and &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Lift Every Voice and Sing&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; the Black national anthem &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; before every game this weekend, including the Dolphins&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99; opener Sunday at New England. The Dolphins have been asked several times this week by reporters whether they&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ll stand or kneel for the songs.</p><p>&#x201C;If we could just right our wrongs, we wouldn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t need two songs,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; center Ted Karras said in the video.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ll just skip the long production and stay inside,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; tight end Mike Gesicki said.</p><p>Flores, wearing a T-shirt that read VOTE, closed the video in unity with his players.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Before the media starts wondering and guessing, they just answered all your questions,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Flores said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ll just stay inside.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">731352</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/dolphins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins&#8217; Fitzpatrick starting QB for week 1, Tagovailoa will be backup</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dolphins-fitzpatrick-starting-qb-for-week-1-tagovailoa-will-be-backup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 14:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=727210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It should come as no surprise, but the Miami Dolphins have named Ryan Fitzpatrick as their starting quarterback for week one. Head coach Brian Flores...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It should come as no surprise, but the Miami Dolphins have named Ryan Fitzpatrick as their starting quarterback for week one.</p>
<p>Head coach Brian Flores made the announcement on Monday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;This isn&#8217;t groundbreaking news,&#8221; Flores said. &#8220;Fitz is going to be the starter in a year like this, you know, no OTAs, no mini-camp, modified training camp, we just felt like that was the best decision for the team. He&#8217;s done a good job through the course of the training camp and he&#8217;ll be out there.&#8221;</p>
<p>The fins decided to go with veteran Fitzpatrick for their season opener on the road against the New England Patriots on Sunday.</p>
<p>The move comes after rookie Tua Tagovailoa was the Dolphins&#8217; first-round pick during the drafts back in April.</p>
<p>Fitzpatrick currently gives the team the best chance to win.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa will serve as a backup for the week and remains the future franchise quarterback.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">727210</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1577491182335.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1577491182335.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ryan-fitzpatrick-e1577491182335.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ryan fitzpatrick</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade bust: QB Josh Rosen cut by Dolphins after 1 season</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/trade-bust-qb-josh-rosen-cut-by-dolphins-after-1-season/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=725897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — NFL cutdown day forced the Miami Dolphins to acknowledge the failure of their Josh Rosen experiment. “This just didn’t work out, and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — NFL cutdown day forced the Miami Dolphins to acknowledge the failure of their Josh Rosen experiment.</p>
<p>“This just didn’t work out, and we felt it was best to move on,” coach <a href="https://apnews.com/04c9869a0f6c4a0c202f9a684d6606e0">Brian Flores </a>said Saturday.</p>
<p>Miami released Rosen, who was acquired from Arizona in April 2019 for second- and fifth-round draft picks. He started three games last year, throwing five interceptions and one touchdown pass, and was the No. 3 quarterback behind Ryan Fitzpatrick and <a>rookie Tua Tagovailoa </a>in training camp this summer.</p>
<p>Flores declined to say whether the Dolphins regretted trading for Rosen.</p>
<p>“The most important thing is to kind of move forward and not look back,” he said. “You don’t hit on every play, on every trade, on every draft pick. Show me a team that has hit on everyone. I&#8217;ll applaud that team.”</p>
<p>The decision to cut Rosen signals the Dolphins are confident in the health of top draft pick Tagovailoa, who has returned from a career-threatening hip injury that ended his Alabama career in November.</p>
<p>But Flores spoke of Tagovailoa as an emergency option for now.</p>
<p>“If he had to go in, he would prepare himself and do the best he could,” Flores said. “He is showing improvement. If he had to go in and play, that’s how it would be. A rookie playing early on — we may have that at some other positions. If that were the case, that’s what it would be.”</p>
<p>The Dolphins&#8217; starter in the season opener Sept. 13 at New England will be the 37-year-old Fitzpatrick, their most valuable player in 2019.</p>
<p>They might add a third quarterback during this weekend&#8217;s flurry of roster moves resulting from the roster cutdowns. Jake Rudock, who was on the practice squad last year and cut in July, worked out for the team Friday.</p>
<p>Rosen was the 10th overall pick by the Cardinals in 2018, and they parted with him after drafting Kyler Murray a year ago. Rosen began last season as Miami’s backup QB, replaced Fitzpatrick as the starter in Games 3 through 5, and spent the rest of the year in the No. 2 job.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">725897</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/09/190930-josh-rosen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/09/190930-josh-rosen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/09/190930-josh-rosen.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190930 josh rosen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolphins QB Tua Tagovailoa donates equipment to charity ahead of documentary&#8217;s release</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/dolphins-qb-tua-tagovailoa-donates-equipment-to-charity-ahead-of-documentarys-release/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 22:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=725352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Dolphins&#8217; new quarterback will be showcasing his football life in a new documentary to be released over the weekend, but he is also...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Dolphins&#8217; new quarterback will be showcasing his football life in a new documentary to be released over the weekend, but he is also working to donate new equipment to children in Miami-Dade County.</p>
<p>The documentary, called &#8220;Tua,&#8221; pulls back the curtain on Tua Tagovailoa&#8217;s life before and after he was drafted by the Dolphins.</p>
<p>&#8220;You know, you got the lion and the gazelle,&#8221; Tagovailoa said. &#8220;They both wake up in the morning. They both got to run. One is running to something. One is running away from something, you know, and which one are you? For me, you take on the mindset of trying to wake up and become a lion every day. I&#8217;m chasing to be the best Tua I can be, both on and off the field.&#8221;</p>
<p>Although he has yet to take a snap in an NFL game, there is a lot of hype with the Dolphins&#8217; projected franchise quarterback, not only for what he may do on the field, but for what he is doing off the field.</p>
<p>Tagovailoa, in partnership with Fox Sports and Good Sports, Inc., are working to donate $111,111 worth of new equipment to the Boys &amp; Girls Clubs of Miami-Dade, Tuscaloosa, Alabama and Hawaii.</p>
<p>The dollar figure honors the quarterback&#8217;s No. 1 jersey, and the new equipment will keep children active.</p>
<p>&#8220;They have jerseys, and they have new football gear, and they have all these great things, whether it&#8217;s soccer, baseball, all sorts of gear they provided, so the kids can have really nice, cool stuff,&#8221; Alex Rodriguez-Roig, the President of the Boys &amp; Girls Clubs of Miami-Dade, said.</p>
<p>The donation will also help the Boys &amp; Girls Clubs of Miami-Dade with its in-person virtual learning and after-school care programs for the school year. These programs are important to keep the area&#8217;s youth engaged during the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>&#8220;You know, we have this COVID thing going on, and the ability to provide this for kids just gives hope, gives them happiness,&#8221; Rodriguez-Roig said. &#8220;It brings something else. It breaks that day-to-day thing, so it&#8217;s something that really &#8212; there&#8217;s a physical thing to it that they&#8217;re giving the larger thing is that there&#8217;s an emotional thing, so &#8216;Hey, look, somebody&#8217;s thinking about us. Somebody cares about us.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Tagovailoa continues to work towards becoming the Dolphins&#8217; starting quarterback.</p>
<p>Defensive Tackle Davon Godchaux, who played for rival Southeastern Conference school Louisiana State University, just hopes his school was included in the feature.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m excited to see that,&#8221; Godchaux said. &#8220;I hope they have the last game, you know, when LSU beat them. That&#8217;s my guy, though. He&#8217;s a great guy. He&#8217;s a great guy.&#8221;</p>
<p>WSVN is proud sponsor of the Boys &amp; Girls Clubs of Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>&#8220;Tua&#8221; premieres Sunday at 4 p.m. on Channel 7.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">725352</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/090420-tua-tagovailoa-draft-day.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/090420-tua-tagovailoa-draft-day.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/090420-tua-tagovailoa-draft-day.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">090420 tua tagovailoa draft day</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
