<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Entertainment &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/entertainment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:43:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Entertainment &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site><item>
	<title>Race, title and anguish: Meghan and Harry explain royal rift</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/race-title-and-anguish-meghan-and-harry-explain-royal-rift/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 04:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878130</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES (AP) — In a wide-ranging interview aired Sunday, Harry and Meghan described painful palace discussions about the color of their son’s skin, losing...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES (AP) — In a wide-ranging interview aired Sunday, Harry and Meghan described painful palace discussions about the color of their son’s skin, losing royal protection and the intense pressures that led the Duchess of Sussex to contemplate suicide.</p>
<p>The interview with Oprah Winfrey was the couple’s first since they stepped down from royal duties and the two-hour special included numerous revelations likely to reverberate on both sides of the Atlantic.</p>
<p>Harry told Winfrey that he felt trapped by royal life and was surprised that he was cut off financially and lost his security last year. He also said he felt his family did not support Meghan, who acknowledged her naivete about royal life before marrying Harry, as she endured tabloid attacks and false stories.</p>
<p>Meghan, who is biracial, described that when she was first pregnant with son Archie, there were “concerns and conversations about how dark his skin might be when he’s born.” The statement led Winfrey to ask “What,” incredulously and sit in silence for a moment.</p>
<p>In a rare positive moment in the interview, Harry and Meghan revealed their second would be a girl. The interview opened with Winfrey gushing over Meghan’s pregnancy and lamenting that COVID-19 protocols kept them from hugging.</p>
<p>The interview was in the United States a full day before it will air in Britain. The revelations aren&#8217;t over: Winfrey teased additional bits of the interview would be shown Monday morning on CBS.</p>
<p>In response to a question from Winfrey, Harry said he wouldn’t have left royal life if not for his wife, the actor formerly known as Meghan Markle who starred in the TV drama “Suits.” He said their relationship revealed the strictures of royal life.</p>
<p>“I wouldn’t have been able to, because I myself was trapped,” Harry said. “I didn’t see a way out.</p>
<p>“I was trapped, but I didn’t know I was trapped,” Harry said, before adding, “My father and my brother, they are trapped.”</p>
<p>Harry acknowledged that he does not have a close relationship presently with his brother William, who is heir to the throne after their father, Prince Charles.</p>
<p>Winfrey at various points in the interview ran through headlines about Meghan and at one point asked about the mental health impact. Meghan responded that she experienced suicidal thoughts and had sought help through the palace’s human resources department, but was told there was nothing they could do.</p>
<p>“I was really ashamed to say it at the time and a shame to have to admit it to Harry, especially because I know how much loss he suffered,” she said. “But I knew that if I didn’t say it that I would do it. And I just didn’t, I just didn’t want to be alive anymore.”</p>
<p>Meghan said she grew concerned about her son not having a royal title because it meant he wouldn&#8217;t be provided security.</p>
<p>Meghan said processing everything while pregnant was “very hard.” More than the “prince” title, she was most concerned about her son’s safety and protection.</p>
<p>“He needs to be safe,” a teary-eyed Meghan recalled. “We’re not saying don’t make him a prince or princess, whatever it’s going to be. But if you’re saying the title is going to affect their protection, we haven’t created this monster machine around us in terms of click bait and tabloid fodder. You’ve allowed that to happen, which means our son needs to be safe.”</p>
<p>Meghan said it was hard for her to understand why there were concerns within the royal family about her son’s skin color. She said it was hard for her to “compartmentalize” those conversations.</p>
<p>Harry, too, said there are lasting impacts about Meghan&#8217;s treatment and his relationship with his family.</p>
<p>“There is a lot to work through there,” Harry said about his relationship with his father. “I feel really let down. He’s been through something similar. He knows what pain feels like. And Archie is his grandson. I will always love him, but there is a lot of hurt that has happened.”</p>
<p>Harry said the royal family cut him off financially at the start of 2020 after announcing plans to step back from his roles. But he was able to afford security for his family because of the money his mother, Princess Diana, left behind.</p>
<p>Harry disputed rumors that he intentionally blindsided his grandmother, Queen Elizabeth II, with his decision to split. He suspects the rumors came from the institution.</p>
<p>“I’ve never blindsided my grandmother,” he said. “I have too much respect for her.”</p>
<p>Meghan, too, was complimentary toward the queen, despite saying at one point she realized some in the palace were willing to lie to “protect other members of the family.”</p>
<p>“The queen has always been wonderful to me,” Meghan said.</p>
<p>Sunday&#8217;s interview special opened with Meghan describing how naive she was about the ground rules of royal life before she married her husband, Harry, nearly three years ago. “I didn’t fully understand what the job was,” she said. She also noted that she did not know how to curtsy before meeting Queen Elizabeth II for the first time, and didn&#8217;t realize it would be necessary.</p>
<p>“I will say I went into it naively because I didn’t grow up knowing much about the royal family,” Meghan said. “It wasn’t something that was part of conversation at home. It wasn’t something that we followed.”</p>
<p>Meghan said she and Harry were aligned during their courtship because of their “cause-driven” work. But she did not fully comprehend the pressure of being linked to the prestigious royal family.</p>
<p>“There was no way to understand what the day-to-day was going to be like,” she said. “And it’s so different because I didn’t romanticize any element of it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The couple married at Windsor Castle in May 2018, and their son, Archie, was born a year later. Harry and Meghan’s departure from royal duties began in March 2020 over what they described as the intrusions and racist attitudes of the British media toward the duchess.</p>
<p>At the top of the interview, Winfrey said no topic was off limits and that Meghan and Harry were not being paid for the special.</p>
<p>In Britain, the interview is seen as poorly timed. It will air while Harry’s 99-year-old grandfather Prince Philip remains hospitalized in London after undergoing a heart procedure.</p>
<p>It is unclear what public reaction, if any, the queen and other royal family members will have to Sunday’s interview. The U.K.&#8217;s Sunday Times newspaper, citing an anonymous source, reported that the queen would not watch it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878130</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Harry_and_Meghan.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Harry_and_Meghan.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Harry_and_Meghan.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Harry_and_Meghan</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Audiences hold back, even as more movie theaters open</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/audiences-hold-back-even-as-more-movie-theaters-open/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 01:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878078</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; Theaters reopening in New York City this weekend did not set the box office on fire. North American theatrical grosses stayed relatively muted, despite...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; Theaters reopening in New York City this weekend did not set the box office on fire. North American theatrical grosses stayed relatively muted, despite some major new releases like Disney’s “Raya and the Last Dragon” and Lionsgate’s Tom Holland and Daisy Ridley action flick “Chaos Walking,” according to studio estimates Sunday.</p>
<p>Walt Disney Animation&#8217;s “ Raya and the Last Dragon ” earned an estimated $8.6 million from 2,045 locations in North America. The well-reviewed fantasy adventure, featuring the voices of Awkwafina and Kelly Marie Tran, is also available for Disney+ subscribers to rent and stream at home for $29.99. Streaming grosses were not reported.</p>
<p>Warner Bros. “Tom &amp; Jerry,” which is available to stream free for HBO Max subscribers, brought in $6.6 million from 2,563 North American theaters in its second available weekend. Last weekend the animated film scored the best domestic opening of the year with $13.7 million.</p>
<p>“Chaos Walking,” meanwhile, debuted with $3.8 million. The future set film from “Edge of Tomorrow” director Doug Liman cost around $100 million to make.</p>
<p>Approximately 80% of the domestic market is currently allowed to operate with limited capacity. Many areas in North America are not yet fully open, including Los Angeles, and most California counties, Washington D.C., and much of Canada.</p>
<p>Disney is hoping to keep “Raya” in theaters throughout the spring. There are scant major family films on the schedule until early summer and the company is hoping for increased play during spring breaks and as more territories reopen.</p>
<p>Internationally, “Raya and the Last Dragon” earned an estimated $17.6 million from 32 territories &#8212; the highest grossing of which was China with $8.4 million.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878078</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4cf7e0d0-b960-4a0f-871f-4885c46d08f2/4f1cd97a-0369-44db-b673-e1ac4e1f3e83/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217217~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4cf7e0d0-b960-4a0f-871f-4885c46d08f2/4f1cd97a-0369-44db-b673-e1ac4e1f3e83/main.mp4*~hmac=4553d56c89e509a4272339a26e4d926e126939a573554f7549dadbb4901270a5' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Apple is discontinuing the iMac Pro</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/apple-is-discontinuing-the-imac-pro/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877894</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Apple is no longer making the iMac Pro, once the most powerful computer the company offered. For those looking to get their hands...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Apple is no longer making the iMac Pro, once the most powerful computer the company offered.</p>
<p>For those looking to get their hands on the all-in-one-Mac, they can still do so for a limited time. The $4,999 standard model can still be purchased on Apple&#8217;s website, but only while supplies last. Once existing inventory runs out, the iMac Pro will no longer be available, Apple told CNN Business.</p>
<p>Apple released the iMac Pro in 2017, in which it was <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2017/06/imac-pro-most-powerful-mac-arrives-december/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">deemed</a> &#8220;the most powerful Mac ever.&#8221; The all-in-one computer aimed at creatives and professionals features advanced capabilities for graphics and 3D rendering. However, the machine hasn&#8217;t gotten any major updates in the past few years.</p>
<p>In August, Apple <a href="https://www.cnn.com/cnn-underscored/live-news/apple-november-event-2020/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">debuted</a> its 27-inch iMac, which is the go-to iMac option for most customers. The tech company added that the current model can be configured to address the needs of professionals. But for those desiring a boost in performance and expandability, they can choose the Mac Pro — a Mac tower that exceeds the capabilities of the iMac Pro.</p>
<p>Apple is gearing up a for new release of iMacs this year to replace its 21.5-inch and 27-inch models, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-01-15/apple-plans-redesigned-imac-new-mac-pro-smaller-mac-pro-cheaper-monitor" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> reported in January.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877894</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_5ce5fe5d85be3285d2f0b6cadef2aa29-h_428b0b923daf1f2cee9e97aa4a6fc585.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_5ce5fe5d85be3285d2f0b6cadef2aa29-h_428b0b923daf1f2cee9e97aa4a6fc585.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_5ce5fe5d85be3285d2f0b6cadef2aa29-h_428b0b923daf1f2cee9e97aa4a6fc585.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">iMac Pro</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Bruno Mars defends himself against cultural appropriation accusations</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/bruno-mars-defends-himself-against-cultural-appropriation-accusations/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877971</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Bruno Mars has responded to accusations that he appropriates Black culture in his musical work. In an interview with The Breakfast Club on Friday, the Grammy award-winning...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Bruno Mars has responded to accusations that he appropriates Black culture in his musical work.</p>
<p>In an interview with <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UApBNxcCfYE&amp;t=7s" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Breakfast Club</a> on Friday, the Grammy award-winning artist said, &#8220;You can&#8217;t find an interview where I haven&#8217;t talked about the entertainers who have come before me. The only reason I&#8217;m here is because of James Brown, Prince, Michael.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;This music comes from love and if you can&#8217;t hear that, I don&#8217;t know what to tell you,&#8221; he added.</p>
<p>Mars &#8212; who was born to a Filipino mother and a half Puerto-Rican, half<del> </del>Ashkenazi Jewish father &#8212; went on to explain that musicians learn from artists who have come before them and likens using those artists as inspiration to athletes using NBA legend Michael Jordan as a blueprint for their athletic careers.</p>
<p>In the past, celebrities have voiced<strong> </strong>their support for Mars and his music, but these accusations of culture appropriation have followed Mars for years.</p>
<p>In 2018, writer and activist Seren Sensei said in a video clip that Mars &#8220;plays up his racial ambiguity to cross genres.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;What Bruno Mars does, is he takes pre-existing work and he just completely, word-for-word recreates it, extrapolates it,&#8221; Sensei said. &#8220;He does not create it, he does not improve upon it, he does not make it better.&#8221;</p>
<p>Interview host Charlamagne tha God pressed Mars on whether this criticism ever gets to him.</p>
<p>&#8220;It comes with the gig,&#8221; Mars said. &#8220;There&#8217;s real merit to what people are saying about Black entertainers not getting their flowers.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mars shared that he wears his heart on his sleeve and hopes other artists will take inspiration from his work the way he&#8217;s taken inspiration from others.</p>
<p>&#8220;I hope that later on, down the road, there&#8217;s going to be a band that&#8217;s taking what we did and flipping that, and freaking that, and putting their own spin on it &#8212; because if they don&#8217;t, then what was the point of us doing this?&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877971</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Bruno_Mars.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Bruno_Mars.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Bruno_Mars.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Bruno_Mars</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Amanda Gorman, inaugural poet, &#8216;tailed&#8217; by security guard on her walk home</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/amanda-gorman-inaugural-poet-tailed-by-security-guard-on-her-walk-home/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877251</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Amanda Gorman, the nation&#8217;s first youth poet laureate, said she was &#8220;tailed&#8221; and told &#8220;you look suspicious&#8221; by a security guard as she walked home...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Amanda Gorman, the nation&#8217;s first <a href="https://www.youthlaureate.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">youth poet laureate, </a>said she was &#8220;tailed&#8221; and told &#8220;you look suspicious&#8221; by a security guard as she walked home Friday night.</p>
<p>&#8220;A security guard tailed me on my walk home tonight. He demanded if I lived there because &#8216;you look suspicious.&#8217; I showed my keys &amp; buzzed myself into my building. He left, no apology,&#8221; Gorman wrote in a post on her verified <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CMDxaXiFsmj/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Instagram</a> account.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is the reality of black girls: One day you&#8217;re called an icon, the next day, a threat,&#8221; she added.</p>
<p>In a later <a href="https://twitter.com/TheAmandaGorman/status/1368016803553710082?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a>, the 22-year-old said, &#8220;In a sense he was right. I AM A THREAT: a threat to injustice, to inequality, to ignorance. Anyone who speaks the truth and walks with hope is an obvious and fatal danger to the powers that be. A threat and proud.&#8221;</p>
<p>America&#8217;s <a href="https://www.theamandagorman.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">youngest inaugural poet</a> earned national acclaim on January 21 when she recited her poem, &#8220;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/20/politics/amanda-gorman-inaugural-poem-transcript/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Hill We Climb</a>,&#8221; as President Joe Biden took the oath of office.</p>
<p>It was mere days since a <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/17/politics/capitol-insurrection-weapons-ron-johnson/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mob of armed Trump supporters</a> wielding knives, bombs, and pepper spray stormed the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2021/02/10/security-footage-capitol-riot-plaskett-timeline-impeachment-trial-two-vpx.cnn" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Capitol</a>.</p>
<p>The encounter with the security guard Gorman describes is reminiscent of police violence and aggression against Black Americans, whose deaths have sparked national movements, including <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/26/us/black-lives-matter-explainer-trnd/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#BlackLivesMatter.</a></p>
<p>Black men are approximately 2.5 times more likely to die at the hands of police over a lifetime as compared to White men, according to research by the <a href="https://www.pnas.org/content/116/34/16793" target="_blank" rel="noopener">National Academy of Sciences.</a></p>
<p>Based on the 2019 study, Black women are about 1.4 times more likely to be killed by police compared with White women, according to the researchers.</p>
<p>In March 2020, <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/06/us/breonna-taylor-officers-fired/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Breonna Taylor</a>, a 26-year-old emergency room technician, was shot and killed by police officers inside her apartment in Louisville, Kentucky during a flawed forced entry raid.</p>
<p>Her death sparked a national rallying cry for racial justice and an overhaul of the policing system, including the campaign #SayHerName.</p>
<p>&#8220;#SayHerName is grounded in the sad reality that Black women and girls who are targeted, brutalized, and killed by police are all too often excluded from mainstream narratives around police violence,&#8221; the campaign&#8217;s webpage reads.</p>
<p>&#8220;You&#8217;re not safe anywhere. Not even safe in your own home,&#8221; <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/25/us/breonna-taylor-say-her-name-founder/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#SayHerName founder </a>and attorney <a href="https://twitter.com/sandylocks" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kimberlé Crenshaw </a>told CNN&#8217;s Erin Burnett.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877251</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/Amanda-Gorman-e1611165936491.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/Amanda-Gorman-e1611165936491.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/Amanda-Gorman-e1611165936491.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Amanda Gorman</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>California OKs reopening of ball parks, Disneyland</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/california-oks-reopening-of-ball-parks-disneyland/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877338</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a year after coronavirus restrictions shuttered major entertainment spots.</p>
<p>The state on Friday relaxed guidelines for reopening outdoor venues as a fall and winter surge seemed to be ending, with COVID-19 infection rates, hospitalizations and deaths plummeting and vaccination rates rising.</p>
<p>New public health rules would allow live concerts at stadiums and sports arenas to reopen with limited attendance April 1. Amusement parks also will be permitted to reopen in counties that have fallen from the state&#8217;s purple tier — the most restrictive — to the red tier.</p>
<p>In all cases, park capacities will be limited, and COVID-19 safety rules such as mask-wearing requirements will apply.</p>
<p>The move followed a week of milestones, with California ramping up vaccinations for the poorest neighborhoods, counties reopening more businesses and Gov. Gavin Newsom passing a measure aimed at encouraging schools that have restricted students to online learning to reopen classrooms this month.</p>
<p>“Steady opening is consistent with the data. As cases decline, we want to return to work and school,” said Dr. Jeffrey Klausner, clinical professor of preventive medicine at the University of Southern California. “Outdoor activities in particular have always been low risk. Opening these sites makes sense.”</p>
<p>The reopening can&#8217;t come too soon for Kenny King Jr., a resident of Pleasant Hill in the San Francisco Bay Area who became an annual Disneyland passholder a decade ago. He typically takes his family to the Southern California park five times a year, but the last visit was just over a year ago for his birthday.</p>
<p>King, 38, said he&#8217;s excited to return with his 8-year-old daughter, who had just started enjoying rides such as Big Thunder Mountain Railroad and Space Mountain, and to take his 2-year-old son, who was mesmerized by the lights and sounds when he visited last year.</p>
<p>“That’s something that we just made our family thing — Disney trips,” King said. “We’ll sit there at the house sometimes and we’ll be like ‘man, I just miss Disneyland.&#8217; ”</p>
<p>Also applauding were the thousands of workers who were laid off by Disneyland, Universal Studios Hollywood, Knott&#8217;s Berry Farm and other big locations. Ten thousand lost their jobs alone at Disneyland and its related attractions in Orange County, not to mention the knock-on effect to nearby restaurants and hotels.</p>
<p>Andrea Zinder, president of the local United Food and Commercial Workers Union that represents Disney workers, said employees are “excited to go back to work and provide Californians with a bit more magic in their lives.”</p>
<p>Most of the major theme parks are in Southern California, which is still in the purple category. However, Los Angeles, Orange and San Diego counties were expecting to reopen within the next few weeks as their COVID-19 numbers fall.</p>
<p>Only 16 of 58 counties currently are in the red tier, and two small counties are in the orange tier. None are yet in the yellow tier, the lowest and least restrictive.</p>
<p>Theme parks in the red tier will be limited to 15% capacity.</p>
<p>Outdoor sports will be limited to 100 people in the purple tier but will increase up to 67% in the yellow tier.</p>
<p>The San Diego Padres, Los Angeles Angels and Oakland Athletics all announced they will have fans in the stands for opening day April 1. The Los Angeles Dodgers and San Francisco Giants both start their seasons on the road and said they would announce their plans later.</p>
<p>Teams and event organizers can only sell tickets regionally in the purple tier. In the other tiers, teams and organizers can sell tickets to anyone living in California. No concessions will be allowed in the purple tier, while in others, concession sales will only be available at seats.</p>
<p>Richard Haick of San Pablo, California, already bought ticket vouchers for the Oakland A’s return and hopes to take his 10-year-old son to a game soon. His son plays Little League baseball and is very excited to attend games.</p>
<p>“It’s nice to have, even in a reduced capacity, some sense of normal,” said Haick, a 45-year-old photographer.</p>
<p>The quicker pace of reopening is tied to a new plan to vaccinate California’s most vulnerable residents. Once 2 million people across 400 ZIP codes in the most disadvantaged neighborhoods receive at least one vaccine dose, it will be easier for counties to exit the state’s most restrictive tier. Once 4 million people in those neighborhoods are vaccinated, counties will be able to open up even more.</p>
<p>It all puts California in a drastically different position than a year ago, when Gov. Gavin Newsom imposed the statewide stay-at-home order that restricted travel, shuttered businesses and forced millions of people onto unemployment. California still has among the most severe restrictions of any state and continues to discourage out-of-state visitors.</p>
<p>The state is pinning its hopes of a full reopening on inoculating enough of its 40 million residents to halt widespread COVID-19 infections.</p>
<p>More than 10 million doses had been given only three months since the first shot was given, the Department of Public Health said.</p>
<p>Just over 3 million people have been fully vaccinated, or about 10% of the population 16 and older.</p>
<p>There are hopeful signs. This week, the seven-day average rate of positive results from tests dropped this week to 2.2%, a record low.</p>
<p>Although pressure has been building to reopen the economy, health officials said the changes in guidelines were a cautious and measured rather than a wholesale approach.</p>
<p>“We will &#8230;. keep our foot on the brake, not the gas, our eyes on the road, hands on the wheel and navigate based on data and science,” said Dr. Mark Ghaly, secretary of the state Health and Human Services Agency.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877338</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219189~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4*~hmac=9db0e975a924b2cb465a0111975a103e3c17569f6dd83db5e8e6be277872acd9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">sleeping beauty castle disneyland</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Eddie Murphy wants to go back to stand-up when the pandemic is over</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/eddie-murphy-wants-to-go-back-to-stand-up-when-the-pandemic-is-over/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877359</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; After three decades and multiple blockbuster movies, Eddie Murphy is planning a return to the medium that helped launch his acting career. The &#8220;Beverly Hills...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; After three decades and multiple blockbuster movies, <a href="https://cnn.com/videos/media/2021/03/02/eddie-murphy-arsenio-hall-kimmel-interview-orig-bdk.cnn" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eddie Murphy</a> is planning a return to the medium that helped launch his acting career.</p>
<p>The &#8220;Beverly Hills Cop&#8221; star has revealed that he wants to do new stand-up comedy performances once the pandemic ends.</p>
<p>Appearing on SiriusXM&#8217;s podcast &#8220;Comedy Gold Minds with Kevin Hart&#8221; on Thursday, the actor said had it not been for Covid-19 restrictions, he would have already made a comeback.</p>
<p>&#8220;My plan was to do &#8216;Dolemite,&#8217; &#8216;Saturday Night Live,&#8217; &#8216;<a href="https://cnn.com/2021/03/04/entertainment/coming-2-america-review/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coming 2 America</a>,&#8217; and then do stand up. And then the pandemic hit, and it shut the whole sh*t down,&#8221; the &#8220;Saturday Night Live&#8221; alum explained.</p>
<p>&#8220;The whole time last year I would have been out working on my act, trying to get my sh*t right, and then the whole thing shut down.&#8221;</p>
<p>He added that &#8220;when the pandemic is over and it&#8217;s safe for everybody to go out and do it, then the plan is to do it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Murphy, who turns 60 next month, started making a name for himself on the comedy circuit in the early 1980s with his Richard Pryor-inspired stand-up and often polarizing shows.</p>
<p>His 1987 film &#8220;Raw&#8221; &#8212; which was filmed in New York City&#8217;s Madison Square Garden &#8212; received a wide release and remains the top-grossing stand-up comedy movie of all time, earning more than $50 million.</p>
<p>Murphy can next be seen in &#8220;Coming 2 America,&#8221; the hotly anticipated sequel to the 1988 comedy classic, &#8220;Coming to America.&#8221;</p>
<p>The second installment, which premieres globally on Amazon Prime Video Friday will follow newly crowned King Akeem (Eddie Murphy) as he returns to Queens, New York with his trusted confidante Semmi (Arsenio Hall) in search of his previously unknown son and heir to the throne.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877359</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/eddie-murphy.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/90ef39c4-f44a-4920-ae29-d3bc0e3d693a/3110b578-2212-454d-a777-c28846128668/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216918~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/90ef39c4-f44a-4920-ae29-d3bc0e3d693a/3110b578-2212-454d-a777-c28846128668/main.mp4*~hmac=fa2e9d626092f5e2d3a6c6645b4649ca4431b76f202567f81f60aa50c2ff561f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/eddie-murphy.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/08/eddie-murphy.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Eddie Murphy</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Luxury jewelry brand Aaron Basha&#8217;s pop-up makes weekend stop at Aventura Mall</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/luxury-jewelry-brand-aaron-bashas-pop-up-makes-weekend-stop-at-aventura-mall/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 02:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Deco Drive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877013</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[There&#8217;s treasure right here in South florida, but it&#8217;s not hidden. It&#8217;s out in the open at Aventura Mall. The luxury jewelry brand Aaron Basha...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s treasure right here in South florida, but it&#8217;s not hidden. It&#8217;s out in the open at Aventura Mall.</p>
<p>The luxury jewelry brand Aaron Basha has a pop-up this weekend. This little truck has been making its way around town, and this is your last chance to shop, in person, for some of the same jewelry celebs like to wear.</p>
<p>Regina Basha, Aaron Basha: &#8220;Aaron Basha is a brand that&#8217;s synonymous with family, special moments and making people happy. It&#8217;s magical treasures for the child at heart.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Shireen Sandoval brand is synonymous with Flamin&#8217; Hot Cheetos and gas station wine. But I digress.</p>
<p>The Basha Beach pop-up is at Aventura Mall until Monday.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFO:</strong><br />
Aaron Basha<br />
<a href="https://www.aaronbasha.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">aaronbasha.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877013</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Aaron_Basha_jewelry_Deco.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Aaron_Basha_jewelry_Deco.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Aaron_Basha_jewelry_Deco.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Aaron_Basha_jewelry_Deco</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>&#8216;Masked Singer’s&#8217; Thicke, McCarthy dish what to expect for Season 5</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/masked-singers-thicke-mccarthy-dish-what-to-expect-for-season-5/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Deco Drive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876990</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[&#8220;The Masked Singer&#8221; isn&#8217;t resting on its laurels as Season 5 promises to deliver more mystery, clues, twists, turns and, of course, celebrities. Robin Thicke...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The Masked Singer&#8221; isn&#8217;t resting on its laurels as Season 5 promises to deliver more mystery, clues, twists, turns and, of course, celebrities.</p>
<p>Robin Thicke and Jenny McCarthy gave us a sneak peek.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a new season on &#8220;The Masked Singer,&#8221; and this time, wild cards costumes could take a contestant&#8217;s spot.</p>
<p>A mystery celebrity, Cluedledoo, will be handing out hints.</p>
<p>Guest host Niecy Nash will kick things off, then Nick Cannon will return later in the season.</p>
<p>All the panelists are back, and McCarthy is ready to defend her golden ear.</p>
<p>Jenny McCarthy, reigning champion: &#8220;It&#8217;s a little tough, because Ken Jeong is not horrific at guessing this season. The only thing that I would say that I like to do in the past, I would go to escape rooms and practice figuring things out. I&#8217;d like to do that anyway, but since COVID I haven&#8217;t had the chance to do that, so I just have to rely on all the gossip magazines I&#8217;ve ever read and all the interviews I&#8217;ve done.&#8221;</p>
<p>Thicke has a fun plan to challenge her.</p>
<p>Robin Thicke, laying it on Thicke: &#8220;I plan on cracking jokes every minute on the show. This season, I&#8217;ve decided to just be the class clown and have more fun than ever.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for guesses, both panelists have impressed themselves so far.</p>
<p>Robin Thicke: &#8220;I was proud that I got Busta Rhymes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jenny McCarthy: &#8220;Season 1 where I said, &#8216;Could be Cheech or Tommy Chong.'&#8221;</p>
<p>As for spoiler alerts for Season 5, McCarthy still thinks one of the masked contestants is Jamie Foxx.</p>
<p>Robin Thicke: &#8220;Jenny hasn&#8217;t gone a season without guessing Jamie Foxx, and Season 5 is no different, so tune in and find out who Jenny thinks Jamie Foxx is this year.&#8221;</p>
<p>Just an FYI, Nash guest-hosted some of the episodes this season after Nick Cannon got COVID-19.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Masked Singer&#8221; is back on Wednesday right after Deco Drive.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876990</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/masked-singer.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/24fd356e-c107-48c1-8dbc-c05ee046ef9c/6949f0dc-fa5b-4a42-9ab2-57b5c01ab0cd/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219336~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/24fd356e-c107-48c1-8dbc-c05ee046ef9c/6949f0dc-fa5b-4a42-9ab2-57b5c01ab0cd/main.mp4*~hmac=f9d8ca63d44e6fb24ddeade94cc6b67ed9c6b7e5469bbf74ef794e38de94943b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/masked-singer.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/masked-singer.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">masked singer</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Showtime</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/showtime-227/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Deco Drive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876986</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[So many movies, so little time. This week&#8217;s Showtime includes a talking sponge and a talking dragon, and those may not even be the weirdest...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So many movies, so little time. This week&#8217;s Showtime includes a talking sponge and a talking dragon, and those may not even be the weirdest movies of the bunch. Decide for yourself.</p>
<p>Leslie Jones (as Mary Junson): &#8220;He&#8217;s supposed to be like the Prince of Wakanda.&#8221;</p>
<p>Eddie Murphy (as Akeem): &#8220;Wakanda is a fictional place.&#8221;</p>
<p>Leslie Jones (as Mary Junson): &#8220;Not to everybody.&#8221;</p>
<p>Eddie Murphy is back in &#8220;Coming 2 America.&#8221;</p>
<p>Thirty-three years after the original, Prince Akeem is now king, and when he learns he has a son back in New York, he&#8217;s off to track down the heir to the throne of Zamunda.</p>
<p>Eddie Murphy: &#8220;When I got the idea, and we got the writers, and we got it on paper, and we had a script, I was like, &#8216;OK, let&#8217;s go do it. I never felt pressure.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Tom Holland (as Todd): &#8220;You know, you might not like my dog or want to hit me over the head or something.&#8221;</p>
<p>Daisy Ridley (as Viola): &#8220;I like your dog.&#8221;</p>
<p>In &#8220;Chaos Walking,&#8221; Daisy Ridley crash-lands on a planet where all the women have disappeared.</p>
<p>On the plus side, Tom Holland lives here, but she can hear all men&#8217;s thoughts. All of them.</p>
<p>Deco asked Daisy if she can hack that in real life.</p>
<p>Daisy Ridley: &#8220;I&#8217;m quite a sensitive person, so I tend to pick up on stuff anyway, which is already stressful, because I&#8217;m like, &#8216;Oh, my God, just like live my life!'&#8221;</p>
<p>Kelly Marie Tran (as Raya): &#8220;Six years of searching. Please let this be it. Focus. Eyes forward, Tuk Tuk. Good boy.&#8221;</p>
<p>In &#8220;Raya and the Last Dragon,&#8221; evil forces have taken over.</p>
<p>Raya is a young warrior who needs to find and team up with the world&#8217;s last dragon so the two can save her homeland.</p>
<p>Taylor Takahashi (as Alfred &#8220;Boogie&#8221; Chin): &#8220;I&#8217;ve got to represent. I&#8217;ve got 5,000 years of Chinese history.&#8221;</p>
<p>Pop Smoke (as Monk): &#8220;That&#8217;s a lot of pressure.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Boogie&#8221; is about an Asian American high school basketball star who wants to score big in the NBA, but first he has to juggle his dreams with the stress of school and family.</p>
<p>Taylor Takahashi: &#8220;&#8216;Boogie&#8217; is a coming-of-age story set in New York, in the backdrop of New York, coming from an immigrant Taiwanese American family, and it&#8217;s the journey through his lens of New York City.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tom Kenny (as SpongeBob SquarePants): &#8220;I love my live. I love you so much, Gary.&#8221;</p>
<p>Tom Kenny (as Gary): : &#8220;Ow.&#8221;</p>
<p>SpongeBob is on the trail of the snail in &#8220;The SpongeBob Movie: Sponge on the Run.&#8221;</p>
<p>SpongeBob&#8217;s pet, Gary, is snail-napped, and SpongeBob goes on an epic adventure to get him back.</p>
<p>Character in &#8220;The SpongeBob Movie: Sponge on the Run&#8221;: &#8220;Seize them!&#8221;</p>
<p>Tom Kenny (as SpongeBob SquarePants): &#8220;Patrick, what are you doing?&#8221;</p>
<p>Bill Fagerbakke (as Patrick Star): &#8220;Free food!&#8221;</p>
<p>Now you can see SpongeBob for free! For a chance to win a Deco digital code to watch &#8220;The SpongeBob Movie: Sponge on the Run,&#8221; you know what to do. Send your name, address and phone number to <a href="mailto:giveaways@decodrive.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">giveaways@decodrive.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876986</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Coming_2_America_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2d138b04-7f28-4989-9f67-9bde2ce27104/11cf2f5f-73fd-4dcf-935e-96ba7dc1f667/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218687~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2d138b04-7f28-4989-9f67-9bde2ce27104/11cf2f5f-73fd-4dcf-935e-96ba7dc1f667/main.mp4*~hmac=d0ae07f7f7ae2a76c98becd1cfc28893f6c81abcd029e1bf8212d56153ea6fc3' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Coming_2_America_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Coming_2_America_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Coming_2_America_scene</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Stars of Disney&#8217;s &#8216;Raya&#8217; talk about new animated adventure, Southeast Asian representation</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/stars-of-disneys-raya-talk-about-new-animated-adventure-southeast-asian-representation/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 01:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Deco Drive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876284</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Raya and the Last Dragon&#8221; is one for the history books. It&#8217;s Disney Animation&#8217;s first movie inspired by Southeast Asia. The stars are telling Deco...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Raya and the Last Dragon&#8221; is one for the history books. It&#8217;s Disney Animation&#8217;s first movie inspired by Southeast Asia. The stars are telling Deco how cool it is to be in the new film.</p>
<p>Kelly Marie Tran (as Raya): &#8220;My name is Raya. Our lands have been at war for as long as we can remember.&#8221;</p>
<p>Disney&#8217;s got itself a new princess with the movie &#8220;Raya and the Last Dragon,&#8221; and it&#8217;s safe to say Kelly Marie Tran was excited to score the role of the title character &#8212; meaning Raya, not the dragon.</p>
<p>Kelly Marie Tran: &#8220;I freaked out. Yeah, I was absolutely afraid of it. I think that, you know, we spend so much of our lives wishing and hoping and dreaming about these things, and then we don&#8217;t really think about what we&#8217;re gonna do when we get there, so there was definitely that moment for me, of just disbelief.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kelly Marie Tran (as Raya): &#8220;We really need your help.&#8221;</p>
<p>Awkwafina (as Sisu): &#8220;I&#8217;m going to be real with you. I&#8217;m not like the best dragon.&#8221;</p>
<p>Awkwafina voices the other title character: the dragon!</p>
<p>Awkwafina: &#8220;I always love playing relatable characters. I never really thought I&#8217;d find one in a dragon, and while Sisu is very, very cool, she&#8217;s also imperfect and flawed, and she&#8217;s aware of those flaws, and she&#8217;s very trusting and loving.&#8221;</p>
<p>The film&#8217;s fictional world draws from multiple Southeast Asian countries and influences. Representation is important!</p>
<p>Awkwafina: &#8220;I hope that some people can watch the movie and identify a familiarity about the places and the people and the things they&#8217;re seeing, and people who aren&#8217;t familiar with it will gain some kind of understanding of what that world is like.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kelly Marie Tran: &#8220;It&#8217;s really been a dream come true to work on something of this scale that says something as important as I think it says.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kelly Marie Tran (as Raya): &#8220;Now, to restore peace, I must find the last dragon.&#8221;</p>
<p>Raya and the Last Dragon&#8221; hits theaters Friday and will also be available as a &#8220;Premier Access&#8221; selection on Disney Plus.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876284</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a6e57932-8962-4df1-88eb-4d1e40b77f4f/d9432fcf-811c-49e0-aeaf-64d14f04c0de/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219299~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a6e57932-8962-4df1-88eb-4d1e40b77f4f/d9432fcf-811c-49e0-aeaf-64d14f04c0de/main.mp4*~hmac=c4fe516aa43cc824eab4678afb7a1b4c6daf211d74419cbb4deb62c89b3445dd' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210304_Raya_and_the_Last_Dragon_scene</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Miami-based trio Mad3 for M3 creates &#8216;fusion&#8217; tracks from different music styles</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/miami-based-trio-mad3-for-m3-creates-fusion-tracks-from-different-music-styles/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 01:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Deco Drive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876242</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Mad3 for M3 makes music just for you. They&#8217;re a Miami-based trio with a cool mix of styles, and fans are catching on to their...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mad3 for M3 makes music just for you. They&#8217;re a Miami-based trio with a cool mix of styles, and fans are catching on to their sexy sounds. Deco caught up with the band to find out what makes Mad3 for M3 made for us.</p>
<p>The members of Mad3 for M3 &#8212; Kiddo, PJ and Alex &#8212; are all behind-the-scenes veterans of the SoFlo music scene.</p>
<p>Now, it&#8217;s their time to shine.</p>
<p>Kiddo: &#8220;We&#8217;re studio rats, so we&#8217;re in the studio all the time making music for other people, and this project is ours, so we called it Mad3 for M3, and there&#8217;s a three in there &#8217;cause there&#8217;s three of us.&#8221;</p>
<p>Their time making music for other acts came in handy when they decided to record their own material.</p>
<p>Kiddo: &#8220;The flow was great &#8217;cause we just have such a good energy together. It wasn&#8217;t that difficult &#8217;cause we&#8217;ve been working together for years, so we already had an idea of how we worked.&#8221;</p>
<p>The group has some mighty interesting musical tastes.</p>
<p>Pj McGinnis: &#8220;I&#8217;m a big fan of Jazz music, especially like &#8217;50s Jazz, so Miles Davis, John Coltrane, but I also like metal a lot, too.&#8221;</p>
<p>Forget about nailing the band to any one particular style. They&#8217;re not having any of that.</p>
<p>Alex Coombs: &#8220;Our sound is pretty much a fusion &#8212; like pop fusion. We try to take from like a bunch of different genres and whatnot.&#8221;</p>
<p>You got that right. There&#8217;s the perfect pop of &#8220;More than Friends,&#8221; the Brazilian-flavored &#8220;By Your Side&#8221; or the dreamy dance track, &#8220;Josephine.&#8221;</p>
<p>We wanted to find out if Mad3 for M3 sounded as good live, as they do in the studio.</p>
<p>We got our answer &#8212; oh yes, they do.</p>
<p>Kiddo (singing): &#8220;I wanna take you on the other side and go further than we did tonight.&#8221;</p>
<p>The music of Mad3 for M3 reflects their many influences.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s why they love representing the 305.</p>
<p>Alex Coombs: &#8220;South Florida is such a melting pot of different cultures. People tend to not realize that music is actually an influx of life, and we just transfer it out through notes.&#8221;</p>
<p>You can catch the band in action Friday night at 9 p.m. inside Taima in Doral.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFO: </strong></p>
<p>Mad3 for M3<br />
<a href="https://www.mad3form3.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.mad3form3.com</a></p>
<p>Taima Taphouse Doral<br />
5401 NW 79th Ave.<br />
Doral, FL 33166<br />
786-615-2337<br />
<a href="https://www.taimalatintap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.taimalatintap.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876242</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-mad3-for-m3.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c2a91410-c605-4882-b46c-1344551b82c4/5ade3583-87cc-467d-8af9-03bdc4d4c547/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218684~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c2a91410-c605-4882-b46c-1344551b82c4/5ade3583-87cc-467d-8af9-03bdc4d4c547/main.mp4*~hmac=5a1c1a120b98be6ddb150fd41e56aa42c86903a200a475d31401f399adfd068a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-mad3-for-m3.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-mad3-for-m3.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030421 mad3 for m3</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Osteria Morini</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/belkys-bite-blog/osteria-morini/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 22:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Belkys' Bite Blog]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875333</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[New Yorkers! They&#8217;re everywhere and now they&#8217;re bringing their restaurants with them. The New York restaurant team behind Michelin-starred Marea and Ai Fiori just opened...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New Yorkers! They&#8217;re everywhere and now they&#8217;re bringing their restaurants with them. The New York restaurant team behind Michelin-starred Marea and Ai Fiori just opened Osteria Morini inside the new Kimpton Palomar South Beach. The Italian eatery promises a Soho vibe on SoBe without the snow, only lots of outdoor dining along the Collins Canal.</p>
<p><a href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1251-e1614806410125.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875338" src="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1251-e1614806410125.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="480" height="640" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1251-e1614806410125.jpg 480w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1251-e1614806410125.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></a></p>
<p>We stopped in to give it a try and were dazzled by some of Osteria Morini&#8217;s menu items. Their charcuterie board (Batillardo $12, $35 or $45, depending on what you choose) is like none we&#8217;ve ever seen. It&#8217;s loaded with cured sliced meats and cheeses and spreads so loaded we should&#8217;ve stopped there with a glass of wine, but we didn&#8217;t (of course!).</p>
<p>Our waiter suggested the squid ink pasta (Torcia Nera $27) and wild mushroom rigatoni ($27) both were to die for. The Romana salad ($16), Morini&#8217;s version of a Caesar, is another must try and so is the Brodetto ($42) a seafood dish comprised of fish, clams, prawns and fennel in a tomato broth.</p>
<p><a href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1289-e1614806385659.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875339" src="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1289-e1614806385659.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="480" height="640" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1289-e1614806385659.jpg 480w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1289-e1614806385659.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></a></p>
<p>Morini is only open for dinner, for now. Lunch and brunch are planned for later this spring to which I say, hurry up, and make it happen.</p>
<p>Osteria Morini<br />
1750 Alton Road<br />
Miami Beach, FL 33139<br />
305-918-1037<br />
<a href="https://osteriamorini.com/miami/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">osteriamorini.com/miami</a></p>
<p>Follow me on social media @belkysnerey @bitewithbelkys on Instagram @belkysnerey on Facebook, Twitter and Snapchat</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875333</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1244-e1614806426504.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1244-e1614806426504.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1244-e1614806426504.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_1244</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1251-e1614806410125.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />

		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/IMG_1289-e1614806385659.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
</item><item>
	<title>Baia Beach Club</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/baia-beach-club/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Belkys' Bite Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=867275</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Balmy breezes, beautiful beaches, warm temps&#8230; while most of the country is under a blanket of snow, South Florida keeps on keeping on with our...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Balmy breezes, beautiful beaches, warm temps&#8230; while most of the country is under a blanket of snow, South Florida keeps on keeping on with our perfect February weather. Some of you, my foodie friends, are starting to emerge for outdoor dining, and if that&#8217;s you, add Baia Beach Club to your eating out list.</p>
<p><a href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_0578.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867282" src="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_0578.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="640" height="480" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_0578.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_0578.jpg?resize=300,225 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></a></p>
<p>Set behind the Mondrian Hotel on South Beach the restaurant overlooks beautiful Biscayne Bay. The views are fab and the food??? Yes, please! Baia Beach Club serves up Mediterranean-inspired dishes. Entrees, salads, <em>crudos</em>, breads and traditional spreads, they&#8217;ve got it, and you eat it under the stars at this waterfront oasis. Their signature rotisserie chicken is a must and so are the flatbreads.</p>
<p><a href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7549.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867283" src="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7549.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="480" height="640" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7549.jpg 480w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7549.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></a></p>
<p>If you love a good happy hour, they&#8217;ve got one of those too. The Sundown Social features drink and snack specials Monday through Friday from 4 p.m. to 7 p.m. Baia Beach Club is open for breakfast, lunch and dinner so enjoy those sunsets and fresh air and remember, we live where other people vacation.</p>
<p>Salads $19-$20<br />
Apps $12-$34<br />
Mains $27-$67</p>
<p>Baia Beach Club<br />
Mondrian Hotel South Beach<br />
1100 West Avenue<br />
Miami Beach, FL 33139<br />
<a href="https://www.baiabeachclubmiami.com/dining-and-drinks" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Baiabeachclubmiami.com/dining-and-drinks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">867275</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7545.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7545.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7545.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_7545</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_0578.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />

		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/IMG_7549.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
</item><item>
	<title>Pan.com Sandwicheria</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/pan-com-sandwicheria/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 22:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Belkys' Bite Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=576200</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Many of you know I&#8217;m from Hialeah. If you don&#8217;t know, now you do. I grew up in the City of Progress/Strip Shopping Centers, so...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many of you know I&#8217;m from Hialeah. If you don&#8217;t know, now you do. I grew up in the City of Progress/Strip Shopping Centers, so imagine my surprise when I parked at one said shopping center and walked into a sandwich shop that felt more like I was in Wynwood or South Beach than Hialeah. Pan.com Sandwicheria is that place.</p>
<p><a href="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3428.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-576213" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3428.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="480" height="640" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3428.jpg 480w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3428.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></a></p>
<p>The menu features some Cuban classics with a twist like the &#8220;Super Frita&#8221; ($9), a double frita sandwich with gouda, bacon and onion jam topped with a fried egg, crispy potatoes and served on a brioche bun. The &#8220;Reubencito&#8221; ($9) is a classic corned beef Reuben sandwich, only this one comes with fried pork chunks. The &#8220;Lechon Americano&#8221; ($8) is the pork sandwich you&#8217;ve come to know and love topped with guava BBQ sauce, avocado and arugula. Cuban Hummus ($5.50) made from chickpeas, <em>chorizo</em>, green plantains and scallions are on the appetizer list, and they make a mean &#8220;Medio Dia Croquette&#8221; ($4.50) served with a mustard sauce.</p>
<p><a href="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3431.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-576214" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3431.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="480" height="640" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3431.jpg 480w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3431.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></a></p>
<p>The menu is <em>muy rico</em>!</p>
<p>Pan.Com Sandwicheria<br />
1255 W 46th St.<br />
Hialeah, FL 33012<br />
786-409-2567</p>
<p>Follow me on Instagram, Facebook, Twitter and Snapchat @belkysnerey</p>
<p><a href="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0290.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-576211" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0290.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="480" height="640" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0290.jpg 480w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0290.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">576200</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0295.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0295.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0295.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_0295</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3428.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_3431.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/img_0290.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
</item><item>
	<title>The Deck at Island Gardens</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/the-deck-at-island-gardens/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 22:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Belkys' Bite Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=560541</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Miami. The Magic City. I don&#8217;t think there&#8217;s too many places where it looks more magical than The Deck at Island Gardens. Tucked away behind...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami. The Magic City. I don&#8217;t think there&#8217;s too many places where it looks more magical than The Deck at Island Gardens. Tucked away behind the Miami Children&#8217;s Museum on the MacArthur Causeway, the waterfront restaurant offers amazing views of the city and the mega yachts docked at it&#8217;s adjacent marina.</p>
<p>Now under new management, The Deck got a recent overhaul courtesy of Executive Chef Alfio Longo, who&#8217;s trained in a number of Michelin starred restaurants. The menu features fresh seafood starters, salads and delicious thin crust pizzas from their brick oven.</p>
<p><a href="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0819.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-560545" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0819.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="640" height="480" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0819.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0819.jpg?resize=300,225 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></a></p>
<p>There are large plates prepared table-side meant to be shared. And when I say meant to be shared I&#8217;m talking at least 4 people. We had the Oven Baked Salt Crusted Branzino served with yukon gold potatoes, baby carrots, onions, and capers tossed in a lemon olive oil.</p>
<p>A Roasted Rack of Lamb served with a mushroom, spinach and barley risotto is another table-side option. If you&#8217;re in the mood for steak, the 8-ounce Filet Mignon is the way to go. It&#8217;s served with mashed potatoes and roasted carrots in a red wine reduction.</p>
<p>A few classic pasta dishes (sweet pea risotto, spaghetti vongole, pesto pasta) round out the new and improved menu. Sundays, the party starts with a $65 per person all you can eat brunch that includes a welcome Bellini or Mimosa. Then the scene gets turned up Ibiza-Style as the sun sets, and on Thursday nights the &#8220;Forget Me Not&#8221; party allows guests to come for dinner then stay for the party under the stars when the DJ heats things up.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s an only-in-Miami kind of party with Miami itself serving as the star of the show.</p>
<p>The Deck at Island Gardens<br />
888 MacArthur Causeway<br />
Miami, FL 33132<br />
786-627-4949<br />
<a href="http://www.islandgardens.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.islandgardens.com</a></p>
<p>Follow me on Instagram, Facebook, Twitter and Snapchat @belkysnerey</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">560541</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0648.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0648.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0648.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_0648</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/12/img_0819.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
</item><item>
	<title>Mama Joon</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/mama-joon/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Belkys' Bite Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=555620</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[Don&#8217;t you love it when you go out to dinner to try a new restaurant and everything you taste just blows you away? I do!...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t you love it when you go out to dinner to try a new restaurant and everything you taste just blows you away? I do! It just happened recently when the &#8220;Hubs&#8221; and I went to Mama Joon. It wasn&#8217;t easy to find. Even our ride share driver&#8217;s GPS got it wrong (damn you construction!) but once we found it we were so happy we did.</p>
<p>This little gem is located inside the Life House Collins Park Hotel on Miami Beach. It&#8217;s just behind the hotel lobby in a beautiful atrium style room (hiiiiiigh ceilings) with seating outside as well as on their patio. The menu is pretty simple: Mediterranean home style dishes with Lebanese, Greek and some Southern Italian influences.</p>
<p><a href="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon2.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-554661" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon2.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="640" height="480" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon2.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon2.jpg?resize=300,225 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></a></p>
<p>The dishes at Mama Joon are meant to be shared. We started with &#8220;Mama&#8217;s Mezze&#8221; &#8211; a sampler of favorite dips and dishes including house-made marinated feta, babaganoush, falafal, tabouli and, my favorite, fried chickpeas. It&#8217;s served with manousheh a crispy, chewy flatbread topped and baked with za&#8217;atar, an aromatic spice blend.</p>
<p>I could&#8217;ve gone home happy after Mama&#8217;s Mezze, but the hits kept on coming. We moved on to a crispy fresh Beet Salad, a hearty Roasted Cauliflower and Halloumi cheese served on an avocado flatbread. And even though at this point I was full I couldn&#8217;t walk away from the last 2 dishes: Za&#8217;atar Spiced Chicken and Grilled Lamb Chops. The dishes on the menu range from $14 to $32.</p>
<p><a href="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon1.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-554660" src="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon1.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="640" height="853" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon1.jpg 640w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon1.jpg?resize=225,300 225w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></a></p>
<p>Some of the Mama Joon recipes are family favorite&#8217;s from the hotel&#8217;s owner. Executive Chef Harry Capacetti has added his own personal touch and the result is a magical menu served in a warm, friendly space. All I can say is Mama would be proud.</p>
<p>Mama Joon<br />
Life House Collins Park<br />
2216 Park Avenue<br />
Miami Beach, FL 33139<br />
(786) 460-1685<br />
<a href="http://www.lifehousehotels.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.lifehousehotels.com</a></p>
<p>Follow me on Instagram, Facebook, Twitter and Snapchat @belkysnerey</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">555620</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon-cover.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon-cover.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon-cover.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">mama joon cover</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />

		<media:content url="https://wpadmin.sunbeamtv.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/mama-joon1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
</item><item>
	<title>Tom Yum Soup/ Eathai, Delray Beach</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/tom-yum-soup-eathai-delray-beach/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 02:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Bite with Belkys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875396</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[You don&#8217;t have to work all day in the kitchen to make an authentic Thai meal. Dinner can be done in just five minutes. Time...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You don&#8217;t have to work all day in the kitchen to make an authentic Thai meal. Dinner can be done in just five minutes. Time to grab a Bite with Belkys.</p>
<p><strong>The Chef:</strong> Sopanut Sopochana<br />
<strong>The Restaurant:</strong> Eathai, Delray Beach<br />
<strong>The Dish:</strong> Tom Yum Soup</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>17 oz chicken, vegetable to shrimp broth (whichever you prefer)<br />
2 stalks lemongrass (peeled)<br />
1/2 inch stalk of galangal (sliced)<br />
5 kaffir lime leaves (tear in half) (or 4 tbsp of Tom Yum paste to substitute for lemongrass, galangal and lime leaves)<br />
1 tsp chili paste<br />
1/2 tsp sugar<br />
3-4 oz peeled, devined shrimp<br />
4 oz mushrooms (any kind you prefer)<br />
1/2 red onion, sliced<br />
1.5 oz fish sauce<br />
2 oz fresh lime juice<br />
Scallions and cilantro</p>
<p>Optional:<br />
1 oz sriracha<br />
1 tsp dry chili peppers</p>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Warm the broth in pot, then add lemongrass, galangal and lime leaves.</li>
<li>Bring to boil and add red onions, sugar, chili paste, shrimp, mushrooms.</li>
<li>Stir in fish sauce, lime juice and sriracha and chili peppers.</li>
<li>Finish with scallions and cilantro.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>To Plate:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Ladle into bowl. Serve hot.</li>
</ul>
<p>Eathai<br />
1832 S. Federal Highway<br />
Delray Beach, FL 33483<br />
561-270-3156<br />
<a href="https://www.eathaiflorida.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.eathaiflorida.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875396</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-tom-yum-soup.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f9d85dfd-eafb-4eef-8fc6-9c87784c9dc8/f34822d2-d407-492c-9905-9c3b3e2e17c9/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219749~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f9d85dfd-eafb-4eef-8fc6-9c87784c9dc8/f34822d2-d407-492c-9905-9c3b3e2e17c9/main.mp4*~hmac=1c15f17bca8442afae96cef933b7cea723a38eb5e4fd9df15fec017341bf2b16' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-tom-yum-soup.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-tom-yum-soup.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030321 tom yum soup</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Pastitsio/ Ornos Estiatorio, Aventura</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/pastitsio-ornos-estiatorio-aventura/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 23:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Bite with Belkys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870672</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[A slice of comfort food served Greek-style, and all you need is the pasta and a creamy sauce. Time to grab a Bite with Belkys....]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A slice of comfort food served Greek-style, and all you need is the pasta and a creamy sauce. Time to grab a Bite with Belkys.</p>
<p><strong>The Chef:</strong> Nikolaos Georgousis<br />
<strong>The Restaurant:</strong> Ornos Estiatorio, Aventura<br />
<strong>The Dish:</strong> Pastitsio</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients for main dish: </strong></p>
<p>4 tablespoons unsalted butter<br />
2 medium onions, chopped<br />
2 pounds 90% lean ground beef<br />
1/8 teaspoon ground cinnamon<br />
Salt and pepper, to taste<br />
1/2 cup water<br />
2 tablespoons tomato paste<br />
1 pound buccatini pasta<br />
3 large eggs, beaten<br />
1½ teaspoons salt<br />
12 to 16 ounces Kefalograviera cheese (use parmesan for good substitute)</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients for Bechamel Sauce: </strong></p>
<p>6 tablespoons unsalted butter<br />
3/4 cup all-purpose flour<br />
1 quart whole milk, warmed until hot<br />
1½ teaspoons salt<br />
3 large eggs</p>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation for Bechamel Sauce:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Melt the butter in a medium saucepan.</li>
<li>Whisk in the flour and then gradually whisk in the hot milk.</li>
<li>Cook, whisking constantly, until the sauce is smooth and thickened.</li>
<li>Stir in the salt, remove from heat and let cool.</li>
<li>When the sauce is lukewarm, whisk in the eggs. Set aside.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation for Meat Sauce: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Melt 4 tablespoons butter in a large skillet.</li>
<li>Add the onions and saute until softened and golden.</li>
<li>Crumble the beef into the skillet and cook with the onions until the beef is browned.</li>
<li>Stir in the cinnamon, salt and pepper.</li>
<li>Stir in the water and tomato paste, and simmer for 5 minutes. Set aside.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation for Pasta: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Cook pasta according to directions on the package.</li>
<li>Drain and rinse with cool water.</li>
<li>When pasta has cooled down, stir in the beaten eggs and 1 1/2 teaspoons salt.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Assembly: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Preheat your oven to 350 degrees. You really need a deep casserole dish for this recipe (deeper than the usual 9&#215;13-inch pyrex).</li>
<li>Scoop half of the pasta into the bottom of your prepared dish.</li>
<li>Sprinkle generously with cheese.</li>
<li>Spoon on the meat mixture to create an even layer, sprinkle with another layer of cheese.</li>
<li>Scoop the remaining pasta on top of the meat and sprinkle with more cheese!</li>
<li>Top with the cream sauce and sprinkle with the remaining cheese.</li>
<li>Bake 45 minutes, or until the sauce is bubbly and golden on top.</li>
<li>Let sit at room temperature for at least 20 minutes before serving (but it is suggested that you refrigerate to let the layers set&#8230; and then warm up later to serve).</li>
</ul>
<p>Ornos Estiatorio<br />
(located at Aventura Mall)<br />
19565 Biscayne Blvd., Suite 946<br />
Aventura, FL 33180<br />
786-697-1681<br />
<a href="https://www.michaelmina.net/restaurants/ornos-estiatorio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.michaelmina.net/restaurants/ornos-estiatorio</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870672</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022421-Pastitsio.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2b996df6-a43c-4f63-a7d9-563adbfb0a00/6473b3d2-c3d3-41ad-87bb-2d5c1be09f73/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216611~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2b996df6-a43c-4f63-a7d9-563adbfb0a00/6473b3d2-c3d3-41ad-87bb-2d5c1be09f73/main.mp4*~hmac=b7a35e34062f07b8dea1aa04489bfc5fd8cd12914d3a6cc07b99a50aa9f805bb' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022421-Pastitsio.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022421-Pastitsio.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022421 Pastitsio</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Resaca Burger/ Pisco y Nazca, Kendall</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/resaca-burger-pisco-y-nazca-kendall/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 23:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Bite with Belkys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866694</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[If you have a taste for a burger and fries, we have the recipe for you: a patty with a Peruvian twist. Time to grab...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you have a taste for a burger and fries, we have the recipe for you: a patty with a Peruvian twist. Time to grab a Bite with Belkys.</p>
<p><strong>The Chef:</strong> Javier Narvaez<br />
<strong>The Restaurant:</strong> Pisco y Nazca, Kendall<br />
<strong>The Dish:</strong> Resaca Burger</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>8 oz. 85/15 ground beef patty<br />
1 slice queso fresco &#8211; coated in flour and fried<br />
1 Kaiser roll &#8211; toasted<br />
Lettuce<br />
Kosher salt<br />
Ground black pepper<br />
1 package of shoestring potatoes<br />
Panca jam</p>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Season beef patty with salt and pepper on both sides, then 4-5 minutes on both sides.</li>
<li>Slice open Kaiser roll and toast on flattop grill.</li>
<li>Coat slice of queso fresco with flour then fry in oil until golden brown.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Ingredients to make a simple aji panca jam:</strong></p>
<p>1 8 oz. jar aji panca paste<br />
1.5 tablespoons pectin<br />
1/2 cup cane sugar<br />
1 tablespoon lemon juice</p>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation for jam: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>In a saucepan, heat panca paste to simmering.</li>
<li>Add the pectin and stir until dissolved, then add the sugar and lemon juice, stir and bring to a boil.</li>
<li>Reduce the heat to a simmer, and stir for 3 minutes.</li>
<li>Remove from heat and let cool.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>To Plate:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Starting with bottom half of bun, stack with lettuce, burger patty, panca jam, shoestring potatoes, queso fresco, then top bun half.</li>
<li>Serve with fries and rocoto aioli.</li>
</ul>
<p>Pisco y Nazca<br />
Located at The Palms and Town &amp; Country<br />
8405 Mills Drive, #206<br />
Miami, FL 33183<br />
305-630-3844<br />
<a href="https://piscoynazca.com/kendall-fl/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">piscoynazca.com/kendall-fl</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866694</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021721-pisco-y-nazca-burger.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/078d34b4-49ba-480d-ba12-c9ce7869bcab/2c22fcb6-79c0-4342-aadd-93c9efc5ddcb/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216622~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/078d34b4-49ba-480d-ba12-c9ce7869bcab/2c22fcb6-79c0-4342-aadd-93c9efc5ddcb/main.mp4*~hmac=29325bf26a4f80c92b87e725b747e42778700d10b9a15ef16470160512b89df8' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021721-pisco-y-nazca-burger.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021721-pisco-y-nazca-burger.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021721 pisco y nazca burger</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Lava Burger/ Black Market, Miami</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/lava-burger-black-market-miami/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Bite with Belkys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=858422</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[If you&#8217;re planning to go all out with snacks for this year&#8217;s big game, be sure to grab a little extra cheese and some beer...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re planning to go all out with snacks for this year&#8217;s big game, be sure to grab a little extra cheese and some beer to make a dish that&#8217;s perfect for sports fans in your family. That is what&#8217;s cooking tonight, as we grab a Bite with Belkys.</p>
<p><strong>The Chef:</strong> Brian Gonzalez<br />
<strong>The Restaurant:</strong> Black Market, Miami<br />
<strong>The Dish:</strong> Lava Burger</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients for beer cheese sauce:</strong></p>
<p>3 tbsp flour<br />
3 tbsp butter<br />
1 cup Heineken or your favorite lager<br />
1 tsp Worcestershire<br />
3 cups shredded cheddar at room temp<br />
1 tbsp sour cream<br />
1/2 tsp garlic powder<br />
1/2 tsp onion powder<br />
1/2tsp paprika<br />
2 sprigs of chopped parsley<br />
Pinch cayenne (1/4 tsp)<br />
1/2 tsp salt<br />
1/4 tsp pepper</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>1 brioche bun<br />
lettuce<br />
tomato cut 1/4 inch<br />
sliced onion<br />
1 8 oz Angus Patty<br />
2 panko crusted onion rings</p>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation for cheese:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>In pan under medium heat, melt butter, then add flour and whisk to make a roux.</li>
<li>Cook about one minute, then add milk, Worcestershire and cheese and continue whisking.</li>
<li>When cheese melts about halfway, slowly pour in beer, and whisk in paprika, cayenne pepper, onion powder, garlic powder, parsley and sour cream. Keep warm.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation for burger:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Season both sides with salt and pepper and grill for about 5 minutes on each side.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>To Plate:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Build burger with lettuce, tomato, onions, burger patty, then top with onion rings.</li>
<li>Pour warm cheese over onion rings, then cover with top half of bun.</li>
<li>Serve with fries.</li>
</ul>
<p>Black Market Miami<br />
168 SE First St.<br />
Miami, FL 33131<br />
305-400-8023<br />
<a href="https://blackmarketmia.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.blackmarketmia.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">858422</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020521-lava-burger.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1ada3d8-69ed-4407-88d4-06054e6df739/167e853f-92eb-4a96-905f-99a1167960b8/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216633~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1ada3d8-69ed-4407-88d4-06054e6df739/167e853f-92eb-4a96-905f-99a1167960b8/main.mp4*~hmac=5bc33838f376b8b409a7a27a020f965bbe28594db5ec8e5ab33202b0962eb753' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020521-lava-burger.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020521-lava-burger.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">020521 lava burger</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Sour Orange Pork Ribs/ Red Rooster, Miami</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/sour-orange-pork-ribs-red-rooster-miami/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 22:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Bite with Belkys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=847523</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[A South Florida chef&#8217;s rib recipe is so flavorful, you won&#8217;t need any barbecue sauce. That&#8217;s what&#8217;s cooking as we grab a Bite with Belkys....]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Florida chef&#8217;s rib recipe is so flavorful, you won&#8217;t need any barbecue sauce. That&#8217;s what&#8217;s cooking as we grab a Bite with Belkys.</p>
<p><strong>The Chef:</strong> Tristen Epps<br />
<strong>The Restaurant:</strong> Red Rooster, Miami<br />
<strong>The Dish:</strong> Sour Orange Pork Ribs</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients:</strong></p>
<p>1 rack St. Louis ribs<br />
4 oz sour orange juice<br />
1 clove garlic, minced<br />
1 sprig thyme<br />
1 pc bay leaf<br />
1 pc scotch bonnet<br />
1 tbsp fish sauce<br />
1 tbsp ginger, minced<br />
2 tbsp olive oil<br />
½ tsp crushed black pepper<br />
1 tsp salt<br />
1 tsp sugar</p>
<p><strong>Method of Preparation:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Remove membrane from back side of ribs and poke holes using a small knife.</li>
<li>Mix together all remaing ingredients, slather on ribs and allow to marinate 6-8 hours.</li>
<li>Bake ribs in oven at 250F for approx. 2 hours.</li>
<li>Chill. Separate ribs.</li>
<li>Deep fry ribs for approx. 4 minutes until heated through and crispy on outside.</li>
<li>Toss in the glaze.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>To Plate:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Garnish with pickled cabbage, and puffed rice.</li>
</ul>
<p>Red Rooster Overtown<br />
920 NW Second Ave.<br />
Miami, FL 33136<br />
305-640-9880<br />
<a href="https://redroosterovertown.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">redroosterovertown.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">847523</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/012721-Sour-Orange-Pork-Ribs.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f831bb6f-2e86-4377-919f-d8a7386cf426/e6f20081-6fc6-46b2-bb07-bce7103ff7d8/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216632~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f831bb6f-2e86-4377-919f-d8a7386cf426/e6f20081-6fc6-46b2-bb07-bce7103ff7d8/main.mp4*~hmac=176a74943c8d9913a7e6c838f8b09d0a6ce20d3fe3473e44e01b0bd1cf24419e' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/012721-Sour-Orange-Pork-Ribs.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/012721-Sour-Orange-Pork-Ribs.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">012721 Sour Orange Pork Ribs</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Pilates: A Story of Healing &#038; Reinvention</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/pilates-a-story-of-healing-reinvention/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 16:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shireen's Favorite Things]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=555448</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[What: When I think back on my illness, getting sick was the easy part, everything that came after was, well, devastating &#8211; there’s no other...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What:<br />
When I think back on my illness, getting sick was the easy part, everything that came after was, well, devastating &#8211; there’s no other way to put it. It was emotionally heartbreaking &amp; physically debilitating; add those two things together and life-altering is what I was left with.</p>
<p>9-years later, the tears still fall freely when processing all I’ve been through. I’m not sure I’ll ever make sense of it, but I do know there have been some great people along the way who’ve helped me fight the good fight and one of them is my beloved Pilates teacher, Gretchen Wagoner.</p>
<p>Why:<br />
When I first walked into Breathe Pilates on 79th Street in Miami’s MIMo district, it was an ordinary day, but my journey to get that moment in my life had been nothing short of extraordinary. 6 years earlier&#8230;</p>
<p>A neurologist changed my life forever when he said: “You have Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy.” Honestly, it didn’t surprise me. I knew it was coming. Not the diagnosis per se, but some kind of life altering news. For months, I’d been struggling with horrific pain in my lower back that eventually spread to my hands and feet. Like a bad rash, it crept its way up my arms and legs until I was practically immobile.</p>
<p>If you’re a regular blog reader, you probably already know the story. I contracted a virus that sparked a rare neurological condition in my body called, Guillain-Barré syndrome. Because it wasn’t diagnosed properly and in a timely manner, I now have the chronic version of it known as CIDP.</p>
<p>GBS is when your bodies immune system attacks its own nerves and the chronic version means I suffer neurological inflammation. On any given day, I can experience extreme muscle fatigue, numbness and pain in my extremities and severe soreness in my lower back. At the beginning of my illness, Immunoglobulin therapy helped tremendously, but as time wore on a less aggressive, more stabilizing approach became standard. Meaning&#8230;</p>
<p>IVIG got me out of the woods, but the years that followed, became about managing my chronic pain and trying to find some type of new normal. That’s the tricky part, no one teaches you HOW to put your life back together after getting sick or HOW to heal with limitations, but it’s been a very real part of my CIDP journey &#8211; one I haven’t shared until now.</p>
<p>I was referred to Breathe Pilates by one of my favorite doctors who had heard the owner of the studio, Gretchen Wagoner, was versed in neurological issues. When he told me I should try one of her classes, I rolled my eyes, mumbled something under my breath and changed the subject. I wasn’t being a bad patient, I was scared.</p>
<p>When I was first diagnosed with GBS, I went to physical therapy religiously, but eventually I was advised to find an exercise that would pick up where my PT left off. So — I tried a little bit of everything, but either the exercise was too aggressive or the trainer/instructor treated me like I was training for the Olympics (despite knowing my limitations.)</p>
<p>Sooner or later, I would end up flat on my back, in bed with an excruciating neurological flare-up. Sometimes it took days to recover, sometimes weeks. That’s the thing about CIDP, exercise too much you’re in pain, not enough, you’re in pain. It’s a fine line that’s almost impossible to balance and the fear of crossing it frightened me. So, I scaled back on my physical activity and as a result, started loosing the strength I had gained in PT. My doctor knew I was struggling and urged me to try Pilates. “What do you have to lose?” He said, matter-of-factly.</p>
<p>By the time I met Gretchen, I was in pretty bad shape, both physically and emotionally. I hunched to protect my spine, I was stiff from pain and inactivity and walked with a limp because of a nagging knee injury. The worst part, though, was the overwhelming sadness inside me. Serious illness does that to a person. It blatantly robs you of your physical prowess, then silently invades your psyche — until you feel helpless, alone and sometimes angry. I think Gretchen sensed that about me, though, she never said as much.</p>
<p>We started slowly with one-on-one sessions called Private’s, because I wasn’t well enough to be in an actual class. Gretchen helped me stretch and more importantly, breathe. She taught me that deep breathing was ultimately a way to connect the mind, body and spirit, which is exactly what I needed, although, I didn’t know it at the time. By the way, I liked Gretchen instantly, but I had my reservations about Pilates. I had been through so much suffering, why would THIS be any different ?</p>
<p>Week after week, session after session, Gretchen earned my trust. She was smart, funny and compassionate. She studied up on my GBS/CIDP and when my physical limitations held me back or scared me, she found different solutions; helping me rediscover myself and my body. I learned to open my chest, articulate my spine and build strength in my core area (which are the ab, pelvis and back muscles.) Eventually, I felt like a different person. I had less chronic pain and more body confidence. My limp disappeared and my posture improved.</p>
<p>If you’ve made it this far in the blog, I want you to know, it hasn’t always been unicorn and rainbows. “Pilates: A Story of Healing and Reinvention” is and continues to be a lot of hard work and dedication. Like any exercise worth doing, Gretchen says, “consistency is key” and while I’ve been committed, sometimes my CIDP has other plans for me. I still have flare-up’s, but the good news is, they happen less often, they’re less acute and&#8230;</p>
<p>When I make it to the other side of a painful few days in bed, nauseous from neuro meds and hazy from pain, Gretchen is always waiting for me — with a kind smile, words of encouragement and exercises to help me feel better. That in itself gives me strength.</p>
<p>Pilates hasn’t just helped my body, for the first time in a long time, I have hope again&#8230;that I’m going to be okay and that my new normal, my reinvention if you will, is the person I was always meant to be and while most of my stories have endings, this one doesn’t, because I’m busy living it and that’s the good part: just living — and that will always be one of my Favorite Things.</p>
<p>Where:<br />
Breathe Pilates Miami<br />
715 NE 79th Street<br />
Miami, Florida 33138</p>
<p><a href="http://www.breathepilatesmiami.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.breathepilatesmiami.com</a></p>
<p>Be Social:<br />
IG: @breathepilatesmiami<br />
FB: @breathepilatesmiami</p>
<p>“Change happens through movement and movement heals.”— Joseph Pilates</p>
<p>This blog runs in tandem with an article in the latest issue of Pilates Style Magazine, featuring my road to recovery and how Gretchen has become my secret weapon in my fight against CIDP. While you have to be a digital member of the magazine to read the article, I promise to share it once it becomes available to everyone.<br />
<a href="http://www.PilatesStyle.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.PilatesStyle.com</a></p>
<p>James Woodley Photography<br />
All photos were taken at Breathe Pilates Miami with my teacher, Gretchen Wagoner (Owner of Breathe &amp; Certified Pilates Instructor)<br />
Digital Editor: Jessie Neft-Swinger<br />
Editor: Matthew “Stay Strong, SS” Auerbach</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">555448</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/pilates.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/pilates.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/pilates.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">pilates</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Boho City Chic</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/boho-city-chic/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 17:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shireen's Favorite Things]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=505496</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[What: Playing dress-up at Boheme Boutique’s newest location inside Paradise Plaza in the Miami Design District — bringing beautiful bohemian styles to the heart of...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What:<br />
Playing dress-up at Boheme Boutique’s newest location inside Paradise Plaza in the Miami Design District — bringing beautiful bohemian styles to the heart of the Magic City. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Why:<br />
I’ve always considered myself bohemian; an independent woman wandering the world doing things on her own terms, but as I’ve grown older (and happen to be staring a pivotal birthday in the face,) I’ve realized, perhaps, I never fully understood the true nature of the word — until recently. Part of the reason I just assumed I knew what it meant was because of my New Mexico roots: a state filled with artists, actors and free spirited, hippie-dippy-minded people. I thought growing up in that kind of environment gave me an inside track to an unconventional lifestyle and a free pass to express myself without traditional guidelines. And, for the most part, I did.</p>
<p>I spent weekends wandering around Santa Fe in billowy skirts and Birkenstocks, draped in turquoise with fuzzy hair and big dreams. I went to the opera, watched flamenco dancing (Maria Benitez is my favorite,) meandered up Canyon Drive where my mother showcased her oil paintings at Pipe Dreams Gallery and roamed the Georgia O’Keefe Museum so many times, I knew it by heart. Don’t tell my mom, but I climbed the stairs to the Coyote Cafe bar so often, I knew that by heart, too. The adventures of the desert raised me and because of that I thought I was automatically bequeathed the hippie/bohemian badge of honor.</p>
<p>Grounded by the Southwest sunsets and the purity of a small town, I set out on my own life’s journey to find myself, although I was pretty sure I already knew who I was. By the way, I didn’t. Not a clue and that would be the first of many awakenings. Then — I did something that went against everything I was raised to be: I chose a high octane, aggressive, multidisciplinary television career or as I like to say, it chose me. My billowy skirts and Birkenstock’s gave way to suits and heels and my carefree attitude turned into sharp concentration with a steadfast purpose.</p>
<p>When times got tough, I would cry and wonder why I traded being a daughter of the desert for big city dreams and a career that seemed almost unattainable. Still, I pressed on and when things got really bad, I went home to New Mexico to regather my strength and recharge my spirit. Each time, though, I felt a little less bohemian and knew that part of me was changing or at least, merging with something else.</p>
<p>As the years passed, I slowly became the journalist I had always dreamed of, but constantly wondered why I had turned my back on the path of least resistance. Wasn’t being a hippie in my beloved Land of Enchantment the person I was meant to be? For old time&#8217;s sake, I’d get out a billowy skirt, my Old Gringo cowboy boots and drape myself in my favorite confetti turquoise necklace my mom gifted me and walk around whatever town I was currently calling home. I convinced myself I was a nomad gypsy, floating around in search of my true destiny. Then&#8230;</p>
<p>I moved to Miami and found myself in a place just as special as Santa Fe. The spirituality of the water, the magical surf and sand — it was different than the desert, but its pull was just as intoxicating. For the first time in a long time I felt like I was home, even though technically I was thousands of miles away from it. Is it possible to love two places equally? Time would tell.</p>
<p>Along the way, I met Edit Meurrens. A beautiful woman with a radiant smile and kind spirit. She oozes sophisticated confidence. We worked together four years ago on “A Bohemian Winter,” a blog featuring fashions from her store Boheme Boutique on Key Biscayne. I was attracted to her clothing because they reminded me of home and she did, too. Edit had that hippie vibe without even trying, but it was mixed with city sensibility.</p>
<p>When I heard she was opening another location in the Design District, I was immediately interested and wondered how her boho fashionings would resonate in Miami proper. The new store is gorgeous, snuggled into Paradise Plaza and has the same zen vibe as her flagship on Key Biscayne. The boutique is filled with goodies from Love Shack Fancy, Zimmerman, Spell &amp; The Gypsy Collective, to name a few. Whether you’re shopping for a special occasion, a beach day or vacation, you’ll find the beautifully unique at Boheme Boutique. I’m a sucker for the accessories, too: basket purses, bejeweled clutches, statement jewelry, fabulous hats&#8230; the list goes on.</p>
<p>The best part for me? Realizing the store&#8217;s “Boho City Chic” personality is the perfect mix of who I’ve actually become. A desert girl-slash-mermaid-slash-big city career woman. There’s no proper emoji for that kind of hybrid. With that being said: age has also made me realize being bohemian isn’t about where you are, geographically speaking, or what you’re wearing, it’s about a sense of freedom on the inside. Independence of thought, kindness in spirit and forgiveness and acceptance of your own humanity. It’s something I’m still working on, but at least now I have two beautiful places (New Mexico &amp; South Florida) to be “Boho City Chic” and that’s why it’s one of my #FavoriteThings. Happy Shopping !</p>
<p>Where:<br />
Boheme Boutique<br />
1st level of Paradise Plaza<br />
Miami Design District<br />
151 NE 41st Street<br />
Miami, Florida 33137</p>
<p><a href="http://www.modaboheme.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.modaboheme.com</a></p>
<p>Boheme Boutique<br />
650 Crandon Boulevard<br />
Key Biscayne, FL 33149</p>
<p>When:<br />
Monday &#8211; Saturday: 11 A.M. &#8211; 8 P.M.<br />
Sunday: 12 P.M. &#8211; 6 P.M.</p>
<p>Be Social:<br />
IG: @Bohemeboutique<br />
FB: Boheme Boutique @ShopModaBohemeKB</p>
<p>“A free spirit isn’t a rebel. A free spirit is simply free within oneself, radiating their light up and out to breathe the sweet medicine of new rhythms and roads into an often stagnant world.” — Victoria Erickson</p>
<p>James Woodley Photography<br />
all clothing &amp; accessories from Boheme Boutique<br />
styling: Edit Meurrens<br />
Hair &amp; Make-up: Odett Hernandez<br />
Digital Editor: Jessie Neft-Swinger<br />
Editor: Matthew &#8220;She Knows The Way To San Jose&#8221; Auerbach</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">505496</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/img_2882.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/img_2882.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/img_2882.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_2882</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Colors of Cuba</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/colors-of-cuba/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shireen's Favorite Things]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=500810</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[What: Celebrating the opening of “House of Yas” in Sunset Place, a couture fashion house with an authentic Cuban flair created by designer Yas Gonzalez....]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What:<br />
Celebrating the opening of “House of Yas” in Sunset Place, a couture fashion house with an authentic Cuban flair created by designer Yas Gonzalez. #StandOutMiamiStyle</p>
<p>Why:<br />
Artistic, provocative and incredibly unique — that’s how I’d describe designs by Yas Gonzalez and honestly, that’s just the tip of the iceberg, but since it’s South Florida, let’s go with the tip of a tropical oasis surrounded by the beauty of deep blue oceans, lush greenery and island architecture. In fashion terms, Yas creates sultry pieces reminiscent of 80’s Versace mixed with structured lines of modern day designer, Philip Lim.</p>
<p>I first discovered “House of Yas” last summer when someone suggested I feature the #HavanaCollection, an ode to Yas’ beloved home country of Cuba. The limited edition line consists of dresses, skirts, shirts and swimsuits decorated with iconic Havana landmarks. Yas took the photos herself and transferred them onto her body-con pieces. She even designed with her childhood memories in mind, like her grandmother’s decorative tiled floors and viola. Beautiful prints with lively personalities were born, but&#8230;</p>
<p>As fashion fate would have it, a collaboration with Yas would have to wait — to accommodate her worldly schedule. She was busy traveling to places like New York, Vancouver and Dubai to showcase her work. If that’s not impressive, how about the people she’s creatively clothed: Jennifer Lopez, Ricky Martin, Lady Gaga and more recently, #ShireenFavoriteThings. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Yas is also participating in Miami Swim Week (which is in full swing right now.) It’s where she got her start four years ago, designing an eye-popping bathing suit line right out of fashion school. Its success motivated her to open her atelier, which progressed into her first brick and mortar: “House of Yas” at Sunset Place in South Miami.</p>
<p>That’s when the fashion stars finally aligned and “Colors of Cuba” came alive when I walked into Yas’ new boutique. Not only are her designs one of a kind, you’ll be the life of the party in one of her pieces. Yas describes them as “La Vida es un carnival,” (life is a carnival) and while I agree with that spirit, I also relish in the powerful individuality of what she creates. I’m not the only one who’s noticed..</p>
<p>Yas has been featured in British Vogue, GQ and Vanity Fair. While you can shop just about any trend at “House of Yas,” I’m most attracted to her stunning special occasion dresses. I feel like a million bucks in them and that’s the point. She’s the kind of designer who creates in a way that extinguishes vulnerability and celebrates the female form, in all its gorgeous glory and that’s why I love wearing “Colors of Cuba” — one of my new #FavoriteThings.</p>
<p>Where:<br />
House of Yas<br />
Ground floor of Sunset Place<br />
5701 Sunset Drive #192<br />
Miami, Florida 33145</p>
<p>When:<br />
Tuesday &#8211; Thursday: 12 &#8211; 7 P.M.<br />
Friday &#8211; Sunday: 12 &#8211; 9 P.M.</p>
<p>shop on-line:<br />
<u><a href="http://www.houseofyas.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.houseofyas.com</a></u></p>
<p>Be Social:<br />
FB: @HouseofYas<br />
IG: @houseofyas_</p>
<p>Catch Yas’ swim designs<br />
Friday, July 12th.<br />
WeWork South of Fifth Rooftop<br />
1st Show: 5PM, 2nd Show: 7PM<br />
429 Lenox Avenue<br />
Miami Beach, Florida 33139<br />
Koko Swim Week Show</p>
<p>“Live the full life of the mind, exhilarated by new ideas, intoxicated by the romance of the unusual.” — Ernest Hemingway</p>
<p>James Woodley Photography<br />
all clothing &amp; accessories: House of Yas<br />
styling: Yas Gonzalez<br />
Hair &amp; Make-up: Odett Hernandez<br />
Digital Editor: Jessie Neft-Swinger<br />
Editor: Matthew &#8220;Artistic, provocative and incredibly unique&#8221; Auerbach</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">500810</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/img_6446.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/img_6446.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/img_6446.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_6446</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>Summer Fun</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/summer-fun/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shireen's Favorite Things]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=496448</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[What: Fashionably frolicking on Miami Beach in the hottest one-piece styles of the summer from “Bikini Island Swimwear.” Think retro suits from the 80’s &#38;...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What:<br />
Fashionably frolicking on Miami Beach in the hottest one-piece styles of the summer from “Bikini Island Swimwear.” Think retro suits from the 80’s &amp; 90’s: high cuts, low backs, a lot of texture and a little leopard print never hurt nobody. #Meow</p>
<p>Why:<br />
When it comes to celebrating a woman’s body, no one does it better than Sports Illustrated’s annual Swimsuit Edition. Not only is the magazine changing the way the world perceives beauty, it’s also changing the way women see themselves. How do I know? Because it’s changed me.</p>
<p>Gone are the days of unattainable beauty and overly airbrushed bodies. Instead, SI’s images are steadily being replaced with voluptuous curves, athletic builds and alluring individuality. In other words, REAL women are finally being celebrated and as a former beauty queen, waif-era model and current on-air television personality, it’s not only a relief, it’s empowering.</p>
<p>For years, alongside most women, I’ve held myself to unrealistic beauty standards. The constant dieting, working out and overall self-criticism has been exhausting, but now, instead of trying to be something I’m not, I’m slowly reprogramming myself to love the skin I’m in. While it’s good for the self-esteem, it’s definitely a process, especially after decades of being put under the beauty microscope by pageant officials, modeling agents and television consultants — who all wanted to transform me into THEIR definition of pretty — which honestly, was never the best version of myself. In fact, it was usually the opposite.</p>
<p>Thank God those days are over and I can focus on things like “Summer Fun” — my annual bathing suit blog featuring the latest and greatest in swimwear trends. Usually, I build a high-fashion theme around basic beachwear, but not this year. Instead, as an ode to Sports Illustrated, I wanted to peel back the layers of my body insecurities and keep things more natural while featuring looks from “Bikini Island Swimwear” in Fort Lauderdale.</p>
<p>The boutique is a rare jewel in this “buy it online” day and age. Owner &amp; Professional Fashion Stylist, Marielle Voets Ortiz, believes choosing a bathing suit should be an intimate experience. Touching the material, seeing the textures and ultimately trying it on is the key to finding what truly fits your body and personality. Marielle is also from Europe and used to boutique-style shopping and wanted to bring that type of experience to South Florida women. She combs the globe to find the most chic and sophisticated styles to fill her store with swimsuits, cover-up’s, summer fashions and accessories.</p>
<p>Everything I’ve worn from her store makes me feel confident and classically on trend, which is no easy task considering my swimsuit standards are incredibly high. It’s one thing to snap a photo on a blog, it’s another to wear a suit with reckless abandon on a girls&#8217; weekend to Key West or to Miami Beach running, jumping and swimming in the ocean — which is exactly what I did in each of these fabulous one-pieces. I felt so comfortable, I even rolled around in the sand a few times. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/1f913.png" alt="🤓" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>And while it’s eternally summer in South Florida, trends are still changing with the seasons in the rest of the world. This year, high- cut, low-back one-pieces are all the rage. Think 80’s &amp; 90’s-style swimsuits worn by some of the original SI models like Christie Brinkley, Kathy Ireland and more recently, Tyra Banks. Pretty beading, crochet overlays and fun prints keep the look modern. When choosing a suit, I think of four things: comfort, style, sophistication and sex appeal. The “Summer Fun” trend incorporates all of them, mixed with a healthy dose of pizzazz and what South Florida girl doesn’t like a little or a lot of that? During our sweltering, half-naked, wearing-as-little-clothes-as-possible months, remember&#8230;</p>
<p>Loving and accepting yourself in any capacity takes work, but it’s worth doing when the end result is #selflove &amp; #selfempowerment and with more realistic images of the female body, thanks to publications like SI, “Summer Fun” isn’t such a bad place to be and that’s why it’s one of my #FavoriteThings. Happy summer, fashionistas!</p>
<p>Where:<br />
Bikini Island Swimwear<br />
3335 NE 32nd Street<br />
Fort Lauderdale, Florida 33308<br />
<a href="http://www.bikiniislandswimwear.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.bikiniislandswimwear.com</a></p>
<p>When:<br />
Tuesday &#8211; Saturday: 10:30 A.M. &#8211; 6:00 P.M.<br />
See all the photos at <a href="http://www.ShireenSandoval.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.ShireenSandoval.com</a></p>
<p>Be Social:<br />
IG: @bikini_island_swimwear<br />
FB: @bikiniislandswimwear</p>
<p>“I would be remiss when talking about beauty secrets to not say that one of the best is to care about the world around you. That’s what really matters.” — Christie Brinkley</p>
<p>James Woodley Photography<br />
Swimsuits, handmade beach bag tote &amp; beaded sandals by Bikini Island Swimwear<br />
Jewelry: @handmademiamibeach available at @wynwoodshop<br />
Hair &amp; Make-up: Odett Hernandez<br />
Digital Editor: Jessie Neft-Swinger<br />
Editor: Matthew &#8220;Beach Boy&#8221; Auerbach</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">496448</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/img_6094.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/img_6094.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/img_6094.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_6094</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item><item>
	<title>A Cabana Clutch</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/a-cabana-clutch/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 18:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hans Morgenstern]]></dc:creator>
			<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shireen's Favorite Things]]></category>

	<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=492073</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[What: Discovering Christina’s Cabana Clutches, perfect for the South Florida fashionista who needs chic versatility for beach days, brunch plans and dinner dates. #HelloSummer ⛱...]]></description>
						<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What:<br />
Discovering Christina’s Cabana Clutches, perfect for the South Florida fashionista who needs chic versatility for beach days, brunch plans and dinner dates. #HelloSummer <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/26f1.png" alt="⛱" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Why:<br />
There are three key ingredients a South Florida girl needs to survive summer in the tropics: a strong sunscreen, a stylish SPF hat and an easy, breezy clutch that’ll take you from day to night, no questions asked. The first two I’ve always had a pretty good handle on; the last one? Not so much — until a few weeks ago.</p>
<p>That’s when I met Christina McGuire, the creator of “Christina’s Cabana,” an on-line boutique specializing in tropically-inspired clutches. The first time I saw one of her pretty purses on Instagram, I was smitten, but it was the story of WHY she created them that inspired me to write “A Cabana Clutch”&#8230;</p>
<p>Christina started her bag business out of sheer fashion frustration and believe me, most of us have been there. You’re about to wear an amazing dress, you’ve accessorized it with fabulous jewelry, you even have sassy sandals to match, but your handbag? It’s got more issues than Vogue (I read that once on a coffee cup.) Anyway, you try on every single clutch in your closet, but nothing’s quite right — they’re either too big, too small, the wrong color, the wrong texture or it’s the wrong time of day and the list goes on&#8230;</p>
<p>That’s when Christina took matters into her own hands and created “A Cabana Clutch.” It’s just what she needed, too: a bag streamlined enough to go with any outfit; adding details, like fringe, gave it posh personality. She knew she was onto something: she would go out with her friends and they kept commenting on her coordinated clutches. Each time they urged her to make more, eventually convincing her to pursue purse-making full-time and lucky for us, “Christina’s Cabana” was born. Crazy enough, that was only six months ago.</p>
<p>After her pet project turned into a bonafide business, Christina expanded, selling her clutches in select retail stores like #BrinyBoutique who provided the gorgeous dresses for the blog. She also started utilizing social media to promote her purses and that’s where I come in. Isn’t Instagram a beautiful thing? After we connected, we planned out a #FavoriteThings feature.</p>
<p>In person, Christina has a radiant glow about her, but it’s her bubbly personality that I really adore and both attributes are definitely infused into her contemporary, fringe and/or pom-pom creations. Christina also has a deep appreciation for all things tropical; naming her Cabana Clutches “The Golden Tan,” “The Oyster’s Pearl” and “The Beach Bar,” just to name a few. No two are alike either, because she hand-makes them so they’re uniquely one-of-a-kind.</p>
<p>Whether your dressing up or down, “A Cabana Clutch” will effortlessly connect the dots in your ever-changing wardrobe. Even better, you’ll be able to go from day to night without ever missing a stylish beat and that’s why it’s one of my Favorite Things.</p>
<p>Shop the Cabana Clutches here: <a href="https://www.christinascabana.com">www.christinascabana.com</a></p>
<p>Be Social:<br />
FB: @ChristinasCabana<br />
IG: @christinascabana</p>
<p>wardrobe provided by <u><a href="http://www.brinyboutique.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.brinyboutique.com</a></u><br />
IG: @brinyboutique<br />
Briny Boutique<br />
274 N Federal Highway<br />
Fort Lauderdale, FL. 33301</p>
<p>See the blog in full<br />
<a href="http://www.ShireenSandoval.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.ShireenSandoval.com</a></p>
<p>“Deep summer is when laziness finds respectability.” — Sam Keen</p>
<p>James Woodley Photography<br />
All clutches are by Christina’s Cabana and appear in the following order: The Golden Shelly Clutch, The Coral Clutch &amp; The Golden Tan Clutch<br />
Outfits provided by @brinyboutique<br />
Rings: @handmademiamibeach<br />
Hair &amp; Make-up: Odett Hernandez<br />
Digital Editor: Jessie Neft-Swinger<br />
Editor: Matthew &#8220;Captain Clutch&#8221; Auerbach</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">492073</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/img_5558.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/img_5558.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/img_5558.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">IMG_5558</media:title>
		</media:content>
</item></channel>
</rss>
