<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Florida &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 03:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Florida &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>FDOH reports nearly 4,100 cases of COVID-19 on Sunday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-nearly-4100-cases-of-covid-19-on-sunday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(WSVN) &#8211; There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,683 deaths. As of 4 p.m. Sunday,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(WSVN) &#8211; There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,683 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 4 p.m. Sunday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,944,995 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 4,098 from Saturday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 63 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 419,479 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County (5.33% positivity) and 199,643 total cases in Broward (6.99% positivity).</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 123,304, and 5,986 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,954 hospital admissions statewide. To date, 3,462,520 people in the state have been vaccinated.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877929</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vaccine site in Florida City overrun after false rumors said all could come</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/vaccine-site-in-florida-city-overrun-after-false-rumors-said-all-could-come/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FLORIDA CITY, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; A South Florida vaccination site had so few eligible takers Saturday that it started inoculating any adult who wanted a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FLORIDA CITY, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; A South Florida vaccination site had so few eligible takers Saturday that it started inoculating any adult who wanted a shot rather than let the vaccine on hand go to waste.</p>
<p>Word spread, and on Sunday, the Florida City site was overwhelmed, particularly after local state Sen. Annette Taddeo incorrectly tweeted that the federally run site would again take all comers. The Democrat, who was the party&#8217;s lieutenant governor candidate in 2014, later deleted that tweet and corrected herself.</p>
<p>Frustration and confusion set in among the hundreds of people who came to the site run by the Federal Emergency Management Agency.</p>
<p>Among those were Kathy Benezra.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m quite upset. They changed the rules in the morning,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Police had to calm the crowd when the site again enforced the state&#8217;s eligibility rules: 65 and older; frontline medical workers and police officers, teachers and firefighters over 50; and younger people with a physician&#8217;s note saying they would be endangered if they caught the virus.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article249760473.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the Miami Herald</a>, a Florida City police officer through a megaphone told 200 people waiting in line, “If you do not meet the criteria, you will not be vaccinated today.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;A lot of people went away once they heard the criteria, but [the line] was all the way around the block,&#8221; said Benezra.</p>
<p>Benezra said she got there at around 7 a.m. because she heard the site was giving vaccinations to anyone over the age of 18 who wanted one.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve been here, and now the rules have changed,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The confusion appeared to stem from what happened on Saturday.</p>
<p>Vaccines must be refrigerated at extremely cold temperatures and used that day once they are removed. Rather than letting doses go to waste, workers on Saturday reportedly began giving them out to any adult regardless of profession or medical history.</p>
<p>That is not unusual &#8211; many drugstores, for example, will inject anyone in the store at closing time if they have leftover vaccines that would spoil otherwise.</p>
<p>Word of what reportedly happened at the Florida City site quickly spread online, and people came from miles to the small town on the Florida peninsula&#8217;s southern tip to get their shots.</p>
<p>The FEMA-run site administers 500 doses per day.</p>
<p>Mike Jachles with the Florida Association of Public Information Officers issued a statement that reads in part, &#8220;The FEMA-supported sites are adhering to the governor&#8217;s most recent executive order.&#8221;</p>
<p>Many who met the eligibility requirements received their vaccine doses at the larger FEMA-run site at Miami-Dade College&#8217;s North Campus.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was very easy, and I&#8217;m very happy to live in this country,&#8221; said patient Magda Caceres..</p>
<p>&#8220;Super quick, super easy,&#8221; said patient Viviane Carneiro.</p>
<p>Schoolteachers and school employees of all ages are also eligible at FEMA-supported sites.</p>
<p>&#8220;Once the governor opened it up to teachers, I&#8217;m like, &#8216;I&#8217;m out here as soon as I can,'&#8221; said Angel Beswick.</p>
<p>For her, the MDC site was the happiest place on Earth.</p>
<p>&#8220;It feels like I&#8217;m at Disney World, honestly. I&#8217;m so excited,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>As the race to vaccinate continues, Miami-Dade County Mayor Daniella Levine Cava urged the governor to <a href="https://twitter.com/MayorDaniella/status/1368636288170139648?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expand eligibility requirements</a>.</p>
<p>Sunday night, state officials reported 3,878 vaccinations at the three FEMA-run sites in South Florida. Of these inoculations, 3,160 took place at the MDC North Campus site, 321 at the Florida City site and 397 at the site located in Sweetwater.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign, <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health’s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877886</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e6a6b095-305e-4268-b30e-f3dce3a92d40/31a5600a-64fd-42f4-8840-39600067b2d1/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219472~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e6a6b095-305e-4268-b30e-f3dce3a92d40/31a5600a-64fd-42f4-8840-39600067b2d1/main.mp4*~hmac=cc47177d472206de319fcbc2d73936f4d27701f0d4ff731e89a2c52f37b30133' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kindness brings huge tips to Florida restaurant server</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/kindness-brings-huge-tips-to-florida-restaurant-server/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877768</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JUNO BEACH, Fla. (AP) — On a random Thursday night, restaurant server Kimberly Filion got the surprise of her life, not once but twice: two...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JUNO BEACH, Fla. (AP) — On a random Thursday night, restaurant server Kimberly Filion got the surprise of her life, not once but twice: two staggeringly high tips on otherwise modest checks. The tips, inspired by a national tip-off challenge that started among rival college basketball fans in Cincinnati, totaled to $2,800.</p>
<p>Filion, a single mother of four who has worked at Kirby’s Sports Grille in Juno Beach for the past six years, had never heard of the Crosstown Tip-Off Challenge that has revved up fans of University of Cincinnati and Xavier University since an Xavier Musketeers fan left a $1,000 tip at a local burger joint in January. Last week, a UC Bearcats fan in Wyoming, Ohio, left a $7,000 tip on a $65 check at a local Italian café.</p>
<p>The Juno Beach server learned about the challenge from a customer on that Thursday night, Feb. 18. Filion was fascinated, not only because she was a struggling server but because she had a personal connection to Ohio &#8212; she is a graduate of Ohio State University. She mentioned that in passing to the customer.</p>
<p>“And then he leaves a $1,300 tip on a $30 tab,” says Filion, 45, who also serves as Kirby’s bar manager.</p>
<p>The exact check amount was $29.71, but the server’s eyes went to the handwritten total &#8212; $1,329.71 &#8212; and the note scribbled beneath it, saying “Go XU!!”</p>
<p>The customer left another note as well: “Five Kelley Boys love Kirby’s in Juno Beach, FL! They cook your catch! Let’s go XU nation! Let’s get this to the national level!”</p>
<p>Filion says she ran after the customer when she saw the tip, but he was gone.</p>
<p>Floored, she recounted the incident later that evening to one of her regular customers. The guy had no particular loyalty to Xavier or to U.C., but he’s a big fan of Kirby’s bar. When Filion reviewed his check, she got her second shock of the night: a $1,500 tip on a $78 tab.</p>
<p>“He wrote something like, ‘I want to be the king,’” she says.</p>
<p>HELPING OTHERS</p>
<p>Filion shared her news with coworkers. Then she shared her tips with them.</p>
<p>“I tried to spread the wealth as much as I could,” she says. “We have employees here who are single moms. We have one employee who just had a baby.”</p>
<p>She knows their daily challenges have been made more severe during the pandemic. She knows this because this has been her struggle as well.</p>
<p>By the time her first big-tipping customer had taken his seat at Kirby’s bar that Thursday, Filion had run the daily marathon that is her life. She had made breakfast for her school-age kids, packed their lunches, spirited them to different schools, all on less than five hours of sleep.</p>
<p>As she does most days, the single mother of four raced through it all before heading in for her shift, which can run as late at 1:30 a.m.</p>
<p>Her boss, Sean Kirby, describes her as an “awesome” employee and “a hard worker.” And Filion says she loves her job.</p>
<p>“We have the most amazing, loyal customers ever. They make coming in so worthwhile,” says Filion.</p>
<p>The pay, however, doesn’t always love her back. She earns less than $5.40 an hour and relies on tips to boost her take-home pay to at least minimum-wage levels.</p>
<p>On the night of Feb. 18, the friendly customer at the bar asked her how business was going. Filion told him times were tough for the industry. She’s not one to chatter on about her woes to a customer. In fact, she sometimes refers to herself as “the therapist,” a sympathetic ear ready to listen to her customers vent. But that night, she vented a bit herself when the customer asked how things were.</p>
<p>“Everyone’s hurting. Honestly, I’m exhausted. I’m putting orange juice in my kids’ cereal,” she recalls telling the customer.</p>
<p>Kirby’s is a go-to neighborhood pub that’s locally famous for its meaty, Maryland-style crab cakes. The welcoming spot has been around for 17 years, but like many restaurants across the country, Kirby’s has lost a considerable amount of its dine-in crowd. The pub’s owner says the influx of newcomers moving to the area from the north is not translating into more customers.</p>
<p>“They’ll come to Florida. We see the traffic. But they’re not getting out,” says Kirby. “This is supposed to be our busiest time of the year.”</p>
<p>The pub has stepped up its takeout service and is expected to undergo renovations to create an open-sided dining area, he says.</p>
<p>But even as they pack more meals to go for takeout customers, servers like Filion too often see nothing for it in their take-home pay.</p>
<p>“You’d be surprised how many people don’t even leave a dollar &#8212; not one dollar &#8212; when they pick up their order. People are clueless sometimes. It is what it is. I’m working double time to make it up. I have to &#8212; I have four kids,” says Filion, who coaches her 7-year-old daughter’s soccer team on her days off.</p>
<p>She offers the example of a recent takeout order that totaled to $178.</p>
<p>“The customer says, ‘Can you help me put it in the trunk?’ Sure, no problem. And they just drive away, leaving nothing,” says Filion, a Long Island native who moved to Palm Beach County 13 years ago.</p>
<p>She started working as a server after her marriage broke up. In addition to her daily shuffle of mom duties, she was still nursing her youngest child when she got the job. “But you do what you have to do,” she says.</p>
<p>Then again, you might expect the daughter of the late Hall of Fame harness driver Hervé Filion to understand a thing or two about dealing with unpredictable shifts in pacing, in horses in life.</p>
<p>The way she deals with them is to take ownership, she says. For her, working at the pub is not just about completing her shifts, says Filion.</p>
<p>“This is your local, family-owned bar and it’s my home away from home. The people here are like my family. Some of my customers ask me if I live here. I tell them I sleep on top of the pool table,” she says. “People say, ‘Hey, are you the owner?’ I think that’s because I treat it as if it’s my place.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877768</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Parade held in Palm Beach County for 7 vets unable to board Honor Flight due to pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/parade-held-in-palm-beach-county-for-7-vets-unable-to-board-honor-flight-due-to-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 04:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877646</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DELRAY BEACH, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A parade in Palm Beach County served as a special salute for seven veterans who were unable to go on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DELRAY BEACH, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A parade in Palm Beach County served as a special salute for seven veterans who were unable to go on an annual flight to the nation capital due to the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>Palm Beach County Sheriff&#8217;s deputies and fire rescue vehicles took part in a caravan that drove past the veterans&#8217; homes, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>Honor Flight South Florida aimed to ensure some of the nation&#8217;s oldest veterans had an unforgettable reminder of how grateful people are for their service.</p>
<p>The vets were supposed to be passengers on an Honor Flight to Washington, D.C. last year. They would have had the chance to visit memorials that were built in honor of them and their fallen comrades.</p>
<p>But their trip was postponed due to the pandemic.</p>
<p>U.S. Army Lt. Col. Bill Schwartz, a World War II vet, was the parade&#8217;s grand marshal.</p>
<p>&#8220;To see this kind of a welcome, I mean, it&#8217;s overbearing, and it&#8217;s wonderful,&#8221; he said, &#8220;It&#8217;s a little icing on the cake for those who served.&#8221;</p>
<p>Schwartz was part of the first wave on Normandy Beach and one of the few to survive that D-Day battle.</p>
<p>The caravan started in Delray Beach and stopped at the homes of the veterans in the Boca Raton area, where their families and neighbors gathered to join in the celebration.</p>
<p>Honor Flight South Florida plans on a few more honor parades to pay tribute to more veterans who had to have their Honor Flights postponed.</p>
<p>The organization plans to bring back Honor Flights later in 2021, with the first ones scheduled to go out in September.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877646</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1259a82-101d-4dc6-bcd5-6fe5102908c8/2d9593c7-10bc-4401-b14a-202d1a014c61/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217003~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1259a82-101d-4dc6-bcd5-6fe5102908c8/2d9593c7-10bc-4401-b14a-202d1a014c61/main.mp4*~hmac=544ea4a71c593e719fee112b93dd87ff01ad8c063876a8a707b7df50a32d704f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 4,600 cases of COVID-19 on Saturday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/fdoh-reports-over-4600-cases-of-covid-19-on-saturday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,620 deaths. As of 2:30 p.m. Saturday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,620 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2:30 p.m. Saturday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,940,897 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 4,684 from Friday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 98 deaths.</p>
<div id="see-through" class="seethrough-in-article-ad" data-google-query-id="CLrpt42znO8CFRgXAQodDBMDGQ">
<div id="google_ads_iframe_/1055211/wsvn/see-through_0__container__"></div>
</div>
<p>There are now 418,411 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 198,995 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 123,033, and 5,975 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,863 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877369</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus_generic_</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>School of blacktip sharks spotted swimming off coast of Florida beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/school-of-blacktip-sharks-spotted-swimming-of-coast-of-florida-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 22:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876869</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SINGER ISLAND, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A beautiful view of a school of sharks was caught on camera earlier this week. Photographer Paul Dabill captured stunning...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SINGER ISLAND, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A beautiful view of a school of sharks was caught on camera earlier this week.</p>
<p>Photographer Paul Dabill captured stunning drone video of a school of hundreds of blacktip sharks swimming off the coast of Singer Island, Wednesday.</p>
<p>Dabill posted the video to Facebook.</p>
<div class="fb-post" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/PaulDabillPhotography/posts/3884058041671535" data-width="552"></div>
<p>Some of the sharks could be seen jumping out of the water and doing twirls in the air.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://myfwc.com/wildlifehabitats/profiles/saltwater/sharks/blacktip-shark/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Florida Fish and Wildlife</a>, large schools will often form during annual migration times. The sharks will go southward and into deeper coastal waters during the winter months.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876869</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/blacktip-sharks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/blacktip-sharks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/blacktip-sharks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">blacktip sharks</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Levine Cava mulls lifting Miami-Dade curfew in April as vaccinations ramp up across South Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/levine-cava-mulls-lifting-miami-dade-curfew-in-april-as-vaccinations-ramp-up-across-south-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 21:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Miami-Dade Mayor Daniella Levine Cava said she is considering lifting the countywide curfew in early April if the positivity rate stays below a certain percentage,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Miami-Dade Mayor Daniella Levine Cava said she is considering lifting the countywide curfew in early April if the positivity rate stays below a certain percentage, as new federal vaccination sites continue to increase access to the COVID-19 vaccine.<p>According to a spokesperson for the mayor, Levine Cava sent a memo to the county commissioners on Friday outlining her decision to lift the curfew by April 5 if current trends continue and the 14-day average is at or below 5.5% at that time.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/MayorDaniella/status/1368016304284778503</embed></div><p>In a statement, Levine Cava wrote, &#x201C;We can&#x2019;t afford to let our guard down when we are so close to the finish line. I am confident that by continuing to work together with our residents and businesses, we can drive down our positivity rate below the 5.5% mark needed to minimize community spread of COVID-19.&#x201D;</p><p>The curfew extends from midnight until 6 a.m.</p><p>Hours earlier, 7News cameras captured patients at the <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-opens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FEMA vaccination site</a> at Miami-Dade College&#x2019;s North Campus.</p><p>Patients said they waited no longer than an hour to receive their vaccine. They were given the opportunity to choose between the Pfizer vaccine and the single-shot Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine.</p><p>&#x201C;I decided to go Johnson &amp; Johnson,&#x201D; said Vian Azzou.</p><p>Levine Cava touted the increase in inoculations countywide.</p><p>&#x201C;The total number of vaccines is maybe approaching 50,000 per week,&#x201D; she said.</p><p>The MDC site currently has the capacity to vaccinate 3,000 people a day.</p><p>Patient Dion Maclin said he also opted for the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine.</p><p>&#x201C;There may be some travel plans. Me and my family have been talking about traveling a little bit,&#x201D; he said, &#x201C;but we&#x2019;re still going to be cautious until we&#x2019;re all through this.&#x201D;</p><p>In addition to the FEMA sites now up and running, locations like Publix and Winn-Dixie supermarkets are expanding access as well.</p><p>Who can get vaccinated depends on the site itself.</p><p>State sites allow Floridians 65 and older to receive their vaccine, as well as those 18 or older with severe health conditions as long as they bring <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this form</a> filled out and signed by their doctor.</p><p>They also welcome school employees and first responders 50 years of age or older.</p><p>At the federally supported sites, any school employee 18 or older can receive their shot.</p><p>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis said access may soon be expanding.</p><p>&#x201C;If the demand is softening, we can then go and get some of the folks who are 60 to 65, and get them in, and then we&#x2019;ll move to 55 and do it,&#x201D; he said.</p><p>On Friday, the Florida Department of Health reported <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5900-cases-of-covid-19-on-friday/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">5,975 new cases</a> of the virus and a positivity rate of 5%. The state&#x2019;s death toll has risen to 31,522.</p><p>Dr. Anthony Fauci said he is worried people are becoming too comfortable and predicts another surge of cases on the horizon.</p><p>&#x201C;Many countries in Europe have seen just that. They had a decrease in cases over a six-week period, they plateaued, and now, over the past week, they saw an increase in cases by 9%,&#x201D; he said.</p><p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p><p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign,&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p><p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#x2019;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876830</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b035774e-e968-4470-9979-98bf49749be1/ac99f926-bfd1-42d9-b5f5-e67610fb84d3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219370~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b035774e-e968-4470-9979-98bf49749be1/ac99f926-bfd1-42d9-b5f5-e67610fb84d3/main.mp4*~hmac=84e641ecd827a5ab35285ba68ee2a99cfc8dd716cafbc7ba9ccbf86bea7849fa' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Daniella_Levine_Cava</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Officials: Tennessee teen kidnapped by father in 2019 may be held captive in Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/officials-tennessee-teen-kidnapped-by-father-in-2019-may-be-held-captive-in-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 19:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Officials say a teen who was kidnapped by her father in 2019 is potentially being held in Florida. According to the Hamilton County District Attorney&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Officials say a teen who was kidnapped by her father in 2019 is potentially being held in Florida.</p>
<p>According to the Hamilton County District Attorney&#8217;s Office in Tennessee, 17-year-old Daphne Westbrook was kidnapped by her father, John Oliver Westbrook in Oct. 2019.</p>
<p>Officials said she never came back after a weekend visit with her father in Chattanooga. Her dogs, Fern and Strawberry, were also missing.</p>
<figure id="attachment_876789" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-876789" style="width: 932px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-876789" src="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="932" height="524" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg 932w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg?resize=300,169 300w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg?resize=768,432 768w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg?resize=775,435 775w" sizes="(max-width: 932px) 100vw, 932px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-876789" class="wp-caption-text">Courtesy: Hamilton County District Attorney&#8217;s Office</figcaption></figure>
<p>&#8220;We believe Daphne is being held against her will, unable to communicate with the outside world,&#8221; the district attorney&#8217;s office said. &#8220;Our investigation shows she is endangered both physically and mentally, and is routinely being drugged and/or kept drunk to incapacitate her.&#8221;</p>
<p>Officials said John Westbrook is an &#8220;IT expert specializing in security, block chain technology, and bitcoin.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;He is communicating in a way that’s almost impossible to trace, which makes it extremely difficult for investigators to generate significant leads in this case,&#8221; officials said in a statement. &#8220;We know he is earning money contracting with small businesses to do computer security work.&#8221;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/tennessee-teen-kidnapped-by-father-in-2019-may-be-in-tampa-officials-say" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fox 13 reports</a> that officials believe John Westbrook may have sought shelter with a relative near Tampa, possibly his sister Starla Westbrook who lives in Sebring.</p>
<p>Officials said Starla is refusing to cooperate with investigators and recently worked at a Ross store. They also added that she uses the name Sharlena Peters on Facebook and YouTube.</p>
<p>Hamilton County authorities said John may have altered his appearance, along with Daphne&#8217;s, and might be using hair dye and fake teeth.</p>
<p>&#8220;Daphne has not been allowed to attend school or visit a doctor and is being deprived of medication,&#8221; authorities added. &#8220;She is in increasingly at serious risk of physical and emotional danger and we need your help to find her.&#8221;</p>
<p>Anyone who may have spotted Daphne, John or her dogs is asked to call the Hamilton County District Attorney&#8217;s Office at 1-423-209-7425. Tips can also be submitted to FindingDaphne@hcdatn.org.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876773</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Daphne-and-John-Westbrook.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Daphne-and-John-Westbrook.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Daphne-and-John-Westbrook.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Daphne and John Westbrook</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/westbrook-dogs.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 5,900 cases of COVID-19 on Friday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5900-cases-of-covid-19-on-friday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 19:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,522 deaths. As of 2:30 p.m. Friday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,522 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2:30 p.m. Friday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,936,207 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,975 from Thursday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 135 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 417,447 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 198,387 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 122,709, and 5,958 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,632 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876769</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida couple charged after child found dead, 2 others found malnourished</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida-couple-charged-after-child-found-dead-2-others-found-malnourished/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 17:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876653</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CLEARWATER, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; Authorities say a Florida couple is facing charges ranging from manslaughter to child neglect involving three children, one of whom died...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CLEARWATER, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; Authorities say a Florida couple is facing charges ranging from manslaughter to child neglect involving three children, one of whom died last year.</p>
<p>The Pinellas County Sheriff&#8217;s Office says 33-year-old Ashley Ferguson and 34-year-old Matthew Ferguson were arrested Thursday. She is charged with aggravated manslaughter of a child and two counts of child neglect. He faces three counts of child neglect.</p>
<div class="fb-post" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/pinellassheriff/posts/4696940690332628" data-width="552"></div>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t immediately clear if they have lawyers to represent them.</p>
<p>The case began in July 2020, when deputies were sent to a Clearwater home to investigate a report of an unresponsive child. That child was pronounced dead at the home.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/clearwater-couple-charged-with-manslaughter-neglect-after-childs-death" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fox 13 reports</a> that the other children could not speak and their legs were so weak they could barely walk. The children were deprived of nutrition, medical treatment and parental care.</p>
<p>Investigators also said the children had bedsores, diaper rash and severely matted hair. Deputies said Ashley Ferguson admitted that the children’s primary source of food was milk.</p>
<p>The sheriff&#8217;s office also said that the couple never got medical treatment for the children. They added that Ashley Ferguson also admitted to Matthew Ferguson that she had lied about medical appointments.</p>
<p>Detectives said the two surviving children received immediate medical care, including oral surgery and feeding therapy. In addition, they will also get physical and speech therapy.</p>
<p>The couple was booked into the Pinellas County jail. Ashley Ferguson was being held without bail. Matthew Ferguson was being held in lieu of $40,000 bail.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876653</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Ashley-and-Matthew-Ferguson.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Ashley-and-Matthew-Ferguson.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Ashley-and-Matthew-Ferguson.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Ashley and Matthew Ferguson</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pollo Tropical offering $3.05 tropichops on Friday in honor of 305 Day</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/pollo-tropical-offering-3-05-tropichops-on-friday-in-honor-of-305-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 15:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pollo Tropical is offering a big discount on one of their staple dishes in honor of 305 Day. To celebrate 305 Day, the restaurant is...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pollo Tropical is offering a big discount on one of their staple dishes in honor of 305 Day.</p>
<p>To celebrate 305 Day, the restaurant is offering regular-sized chicken or shrimp tropichops for $3.05.</p>
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/CMCiO_Kj0CF/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="13" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:500px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);">
<div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CMCiO_Kj0CF/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> </p>
<div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;">
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div>
<div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div>
<div style="padding-top: 8px;">
<div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div>
</div>
<div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;">
<div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div>
</div>
<div style="margin-left: 8px;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div>
<div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div>
</div>
<div style="margin-left: auto;">
<div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div>
<div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div>
</div>
<p></a></p>
<p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CMCiO_Kj0CF/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank">A post shared by Pollo Tropical® (@pollotropical)</a></p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<p><script async src="//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"></script></p>
<p>The deal is only valid on Friday, March 5th (3-05) and customers have to use the promotional code <span class="Normal__Char">CTCMIA305</span>.</p>
<p>The offer is valid in-store, online or through the MyPollo app.</p>
<p>Pollo Tropical is not the only restaurant celebrating 305 Day.</p>
<p><a href="https://wsvn.com/entertainment/night-owl-cookies-unveils-specialty-cookies-for-305-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Night Owl Cookies</a> also announced several Miami-inspired cookies available on Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876592</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/04/pollo-tropical.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/04/pollo-tropical.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/04/pollo-tropical.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">pollo tropical</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snorkeler finds almost 70 pounds of cocaine worth over $1.5 million floating off Florida Keys</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/snorkeler-finds-almost-70-pounds-of-cocaine-worth-over-1-5-million-floating-off-florida-keys/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 20:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CRAIG KEY, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; Authorities have found almost 70 pounds of cocaine floating off the coast of the Florida Keys. The Monroe County Sheriff&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CRAIG KEY, Fla. (WSVN) &#x2014; Authorities have found almost 70 pounds of cocaine floating off the coast of the Florida Keys.<p>The Monroe County Sheriff&#x2019;s Office said they were notified around 1:50 p.m. after a snorkeler found a floating bale near Craig Key, Wednesday.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/mcsonews/status/1367561245801525254</embed></div><p>The sheriff&#x2019;s office then notified U.S. Border Patrol who responded and found the bale, which contained 25 bricks of cocaine, weighing about 68 pounds.</p><p>Authorities said the drugs are valued at over $1.5 million.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876032</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/EvqFdZQXIAMqc4o.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/137ec917-0ef3-4ef1-8d55-9661c05866e5/a1e319db-5574-4017-bc9f-20749d643c36/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219459~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/137ec917-0ef3-4ef1-8d55-9661c05866e5/a1e319db-5574-4017-bc9f-20749d643c36/main.mp4*~hmac=042da90897e226441817007f175645d60cb424aa4fbec5012ee5d7b17b2b7fa8' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/EvqFdZQXIAMqc4o.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/EvqFdZQXIAMqc4o.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">EvqFdZQXIAMqc4o</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 6,000 new cases of COVID-19 on Thursday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-6000-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-thursday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875999</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,387 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.93 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,387 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,930,232 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 6,118 from Wednesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 120 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 416,021 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 197,542 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 122,226, and 5,937 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,338 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875999</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeSantis faces growing charges of vaccine favoritism</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/desantis-faces-growing-charges-of-vaccine-favoritism/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 18:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and state health officials came under deeper scrutiny amid revelations that seniors in a wealthy enclave in Key...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and state health officials came under deeper scrutiny amid revelations that seniors in a wealthy enclave in Key Largo received hundreds of life-saving vaccinations as early as mid -January, giving ammunition to critics who say the Republican governor is favoring wealthy constituents over ordinary Floridians.</p>
<p>The revelations were the latest example of wealthy Floridians getting earlier access to coronavirus vaccines, even as the state has lagged in efforts to get poorer residents vaccinated.</p>
<p>DeSantis pushed back Thursday, saying a local hospital — not the state — was behind the vaccinations of more than 1,200 residents of the exclusive Ocean Reef Club in Key Largo, Florida, and that the state “wasn&#8217;t involved in it in any shape or form.”</p>
<p>Despite the governor&#8217;s denials of quid pro quos, the charges of favoritism were amplified by money pouring into the governor&#8217;s campaign coffers from wealthy benefactors with ties to communities awarded vaccination sites — like the one in Key Largo. One resident of Ocean Reef, Republican former Illinois Gov. Bruce Rauner, last week gave the Florida governor&#8217;s campaign committee $250,000.</p>
<p>Revelations about Ocean Reef residents getting vaccinated were <a href="https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/florida-keys/article249666463.html">first reported by the Miami Herald</a>.</p>
<p>The inequitable distribution of the COVID-19 vaccines is becoming a public relations challenge for the governor. As of Wednesday, nearly 3.3 million Floridians had received at least one shot of the two-step vaccination process, about three-quarters of them 65 or older. But less than 6% have been Black — about a third of their share of the state&#8217;s population.</p>
<p>Florida Agriculture Commissioner Nikki Fried joined Democratic U.S. Rep. Charlie Crist in calling for federal officials to probe the DeSantis administration’s vaccine distribution programs.</p>
<p>“If this isn’t public corruption, I don’t know what is,” Fried said Thursday at a press conference in the Florida Capitol, calling on the FBI&#8217;s public corruption to launch an investigation.</p>
<p>“Give campaign contributions big dollars, get special access to vaccines &#8212; ahead of seniors, ahead of our teachers, ahead of our farmworkers and so many of our residents here in our state of Florida who are scared and who are wanting these vaccines.”</p>
<p>Citing reporting from the Herald, Fried noted that DeSantis in February had his biggest fundraising haul since 2018, when he was running for governor.</p>
<p>In asking the U.S. Department of Justice to look into matter, Crist, a former Florida governor, asserted last week that DeSantis were benefiting &#8220;political allies and donors, over the needs of higher-risk communities and existing county waitlists.”</p>
<p>Both Crist and Fried are considering campaigns to oppose DeSantis in next year&#8217;s gubernatorial election.</p>
<p>Other Florida Democrats, including the top Democrat in the state Senate, Gary Farmer, joined in the call for a federal investigation.</p>
<p>&#8220;The exchange of hard-to-get vaccines for political contributions is nothing short of criminal,&#8221; Farmer said in a letter dashed off to acting U.S. Attorney General Monty Wilkinson.</p>
<p>During a Thursday news conference, DeSantis expressed no misgivings about the early vaccinations at the exclusive Key Largo community.</p>
<p>“If you are 65 and up, I am not worried about your income bracket,&#8221; he said. “I am worried about your age bracket because it’s the age, not the income, that shows the risk.”</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the governor called the controversy “a manufactured narrative with political motivations.”</p>
<p>“Leadership matters and because of Governor Ron DeSantis’ commitment to ensuring vaccine access to all seniors – regardless of background, income or zip code – millions of seniors have received the vaccine, resulting in over 50 percent of our state’s senior population being vaccinated, the highest in the nation,” said the spokesperson, Meredith Beatrice.</p>
<p>The Republican Party of Florida came to the governor’s defense, calling the controversy “another bogus conspiracy theory.”</p>
<p>“It doesn’t matter what party you belong to, whether you are rich or poor, if you qualify for the vaccine, you can get a vaccine,” said Helen Aguirre Ferre, the state party’s executive director.</p>
<p>The Ocean Reef Club, a senior community in Key Largo, had more than 1,200 homeowners vaccinated through their second dose by late January, according to a message to community members by the management obtained by the Miami Herald.</p>
<p>Those vaccinations came at a time when “the majority of the state has not received an allocation of first doses,” the management noted.</p>
<p>Officials from Monroe County, home to Key Largo, said the affluent club’s medical center received the vaccines through the Baptist Health hospital as part of the governor’s program to vaccinate communities with a populations of people 65 and older. County spokeswoman Kristen Livengood said the allocations were coordinated through Baptist and the state of Florida.</p>
<p>In recent weeks, other reports have surfaced of wealthy retirement communities getting exclusive access to vaccine doses through pop-up vaccine sites. Democrats have criticized him for choosing those places, but the governor’s office has noted that more than half of them have been in Democratic stronghold counties of Broward and Palm Beach. Supporters of DeSantis say he has also coordinated clinics with faith-based groups in underserved areas.</p>
<p>Jared Moskowitz, a Democrat and the state&#8217;s director of the Division of Emergency Management, said the administration is working “diligently” to increase vaccine access in underserved communities.</p>
<p>After Publix was made the sole distributor of vaccines in Palm Beach County in late January, the mayors of predominately Black farming communities in the area urged the governor to reconsider, and the state set up a vaccine station shortly after.</p>
<p>While critics point to disparities in vaccine distributions as a call for more outreach into underserved areas of the state, including in communities of color and impoverished neighborhoods, DeSantis noted that &#8220;demand was relatively tepid in FEMA sites in Miami, Tampa, Orlando and Jacksonville. The governor said the four sites had the capacity to administer 12,000 doses but only vaccinated 6,500 people.</p>
<p>—-</p>
<p>A previous version of the story erroneously reported the donation amount given by former Illinois Gov. Bruce Rauner to the Florida governor&#8217;s campaign committee.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875989</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Ron_DeSantis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9869b8c4-f2be-4b0b-954e-a8840c8a45ba/f4320913-c238-4fde-b63e-3c996e3f9730/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217159~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9869b8c4-f2be-4b0b-954e-a8840c8a45ba/f4320913-c238-4fde-b63e-3c996e3f9730/main.mp4*~hmac=a5f6f5a53ecdddd677dba160e875c5b26dbadd57e09fa6d723520039961c103a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Ron_DeSantis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_Ron_DeSantis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210304_Ron_DeSantis</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Card Sound Road reopens after overnight brush fire in South Miami-Dade</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/card-sound-road-reopens-after-overnight-brush-fire-in-south-miami-dade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 13:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One of the two roads leading into the Florida Keys was shut down overnight after a brushfire tore through South Miami-Dade. The Monroe County Sheriff&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the two roads leading into the Florida Keys was shut down overnight after a brushfire tore through South Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>The Monroe County Sheriff&#8217;s Department said the three-way stop Card Sound Road and County Road 905 had to be closed due to the blaze, just before 1 a.m., Thursday.</p>
<p>Deputies reopened Card Sound Road to motorists just before 4:15 a.m., saying the brush fire was under control.</p>
<p>No injuries were reported.</p>
<p>It remains unclear what ignited the fire.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875752</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_South_Miami_Dade_brush_fire.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1fe5565c-a596-4ac6-a645-a6b5b59413c0/8e5c3a35-d345-448f-a717-2eeb5cf9ca95/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219846~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1fe5565c-a596-4ac6-a645-a6b5b59413c0/8e5c3a35-d345-448f-a717-2eeb5cf9ca95/main.mp4*~hmac=246475970a2820650e97eb9ea511004e26e44dc8433f1115d2b8a191f05a645b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_South_Miami_Dade_brush_fire.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210304_South_Miami_Dade_brush_fire.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210304_South_Miami_Dade_brush_fire</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 6K new cases of COVID-19 on Wednesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-6k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-wednesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.92 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,267 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Wednesday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.92 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,267 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Wednesday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,924,114 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 6,014 from Tuesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 132 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 414,776 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 196,771 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 121,652, and 5,911 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,024 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875252</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Attorneys say Joe Exotic of &#8216;Tiger King&#8217; wants new trial</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/attorneys-say-joe-exotic-of-tiger-king-wants-new-trial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 14:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875019</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Joe Exotic of “Tiger King&#8221; fame has found new attorneys who say they plan to file a motion for a new...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Joe Exotic of “Tiger King&#8221; fame has found new attorneys who say they plan to file a motion for a new trial in a matter of months.</p>
<p>Joe Exotic, whose real name Joseph Maldonado-Passage, was <a href="https://apnews.com/article/f3d40f4a4134f4e903da8c5ed2a0878f">sentenced in January 2020</a> to 22 years in federal prison for violating federal wildlife laws and for his role in a failed murder-for-hire plot targeting his chief rival, Carole Baskin, who runs a <a href="https://apnews.com/article/volunteer-bitten-carole-baskin-sanctuary-66a3a67eae93955dcb1fd6409bce1743">rescue sanctuary</a> for big cats in Florida. Baskin was not harmed.</p>
<p>Maldonado-Passage’s new attorneys, John Phillips and Amy Hanna, plan to file a motion for a new trial in federal court in Oklahoma once the appeals process wraps up in a month or two, Phillips said in a phone interview Tuesday.</p>
<p>Phillips, who is based in Jacksonville, has previously represented former White House aide Omarosa Manigault Newman in a public brawl with President Donald Trump.</p>
<p>“This isn&#8217;t our first rodeo, so to speak,” Phillips said.</p>
<p>Maldonado-Passage had previously been represented by federal public defenders in the Oklahoma case.</p>
<p>Phillips wouldn&#8217;t say what arguments he plans to make in a motion for a new trial, but it will rely on footage, both aired and unaired, from the Netflix television series, “Tiger King: Murder, Mayhem and Madness.” Statements from the TV series that could have helped Maldonado-Passage weren&#8217;t presented to jurors during his trial, Phillips said.</p>
<p>“For sure, I know there is material in there that will help him out,&#8221; Phillips said.</p>
<p>Phillips said he became involved with the case after providing advice to the family of Don Lewis, Baskin&#8217;s former husband who disappeared in 1997. Lewis’ case remains open and a Florida sheriff last year assigned a detective supervisor to handle new leads.</p>
<p>The TV series extensively covered Maldonado-Passage’s repeated accusations that Baskin killed her husband and possibly fed him to her tigers. Baskin has never been charged with any crime and released a statement at the time refuting the accusations made in the series.</p>
<p>Maldonado-Passage got in touch with the law firm, and Phillips flew out to the Texas prison where Maldonado-Passage is serving his sentence recently, the attorney said.</p>
<p>“I became familiar with all things ‘Tiger King,'&#8221; Phillips said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875019</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/joe-exotic-1.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/joe-exotic-1.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/joe-exotic-1.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">joe exotic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>911 calls released after Louisiana woman allegedly abandons 3 children in West Palm Beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/911-calls-released-after-louisiana-woman-allegedly-abandons-3-children-in-west-palm-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Authorities have released 911 calls one day after a Louisiana woman allegedly abandoned three children at different locations across West Palm Beach. One call came...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Authorities have released 911 calls one day after a Louisiana woman allegedly <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/pbso-louisiana-woman-abandoned-3-children-after-driving-to-west-palm-beach/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">abandoned three children</a> at different locations across West Palm Beach.</p>
<p>One call came in at around 5 a.m. from a Shell gas station near Okeechobee Boulevard and Drexel Road when an 8-year-old was seen wandering around the property.</p>
<p>Miesha Perkins, 36, stands accused of abandoning the three children on Monday. Besides the 8-year-old at the Shell gas station, a 3-year-old was left at a downtown West Palm Beach Publix, and a 1-year-old, authorities said, was left locked in a car while Perkins walked away.</p>
<p>All three children are OK thanks to people like Christopher Melton, who works at the Shell gas station and called 911.</p>
<p>&#8220;I just witnessed a mother get into an altercation with her daughter,&#8221; Melton said to a 911 dispatcher, &#8220;and now, the daughter is walking along the side of Okeechobee Boulevard heading towards downtown, and the mother, before that, she drove off in her car.&#8221;</p>
<p>Melton said over the phone he could not believe what he was seeing.</p>
<p>&#8220;She was sitting down,&#8221; he said. &#8220;She couldn&#8217;t even handle the fact that her mother just left her. Yeah, she was just sitting there in between gas pumps.&#8221;</p>
<p>Authorities said Perkins is not the mother to any of the children. They added she was helping the children&#8217;s father, who is a friend, and his three children move to West Palm Beach from Louisiana.</p>
<p>Investigators believe Perkins left the father somewhere along the Florida Turnpike before she allegedly abandoned the children. Perkins&#8217; mother said her daughter suffers from bipolar disorder.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is something that she would&#8217;ve never done if she was on her medication,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Perkins faces three child neglect charges relating to the incident.</p>
<p>&#8220;No child deserves it. No person deserves it,&#8221; Melton said. &#8220;Everyone deserves to have someone that has their back, especially at that young age. For her to be just left there is absolutely absurd.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874638</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-911-calls-west-palm-beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/eb13f73c-1d44-41e8-af16-c85356d6607e/b8887889-c0b1-4aa3-8be9-0905aa54a09a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216613~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/eb13f73c-1d44-41e8-af16-c85356d6607e/b8887889-c0b1-4aa3-8be9-0905aa54a09a/main.mp4*~hmac=98ebdf03f3a7f231724f0fb4e62b9ab7ff25080ecc9296b79550f602ed623fec' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-911-calls-west-palm-beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-911-calls-west-palm-beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030221 911 calls west palm beach</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coast Guard calls off search for missing pilot last seen off Boca Raton</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/coast-guard-calls-off-search-for-missing-pilot-last-seen-off-boca-raton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 23:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874595</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Coast Guard has called off its search for a missing pilot last seen off Boca Raton. Brenden Spratt, 87, was flying a small...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Coast Guard has called off its search for a missing pilot <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/us-coast-guard-identifies-pilot-flying-missing-plane-last-seen-near-boca-raton/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last seen off Boca Raton</a>.</p>
<p>Brenden Spratt, 87, was flying a small plane last Friday morning when it disappeared around 17 miles southeast of Boca Raton.</p>
<p>Over the weekend, crews worked to find the missing pilot and <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/coast-guard-continues-search-for-missing-plane-last-seen-off-boca-raton/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">his plane</a>.</p>
<p>The search was called off Monday night after days of searching nearly 16,000 square miles.</p>
<p>Rescue crews did not locate any debris.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874595</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-missing-pilot.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/413ca697-2bc8-4a7b-bdbd-d349a64712a0/a31b9a98-b282-498b-99e8-8bd6bebc7766/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216510~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/413ca697-2bc8-4a7b-bdbd-d349a64712a0/a31b9a98-b282-498b-99e8-8bd6bebc7766/main.mp4*~hmac=83105bbb7a62d4a2b1274b8d02956c7de798f18968445969de6df823904d34c9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-missing-pilot.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-missing-pilot.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030221 missing pilot</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 7K new cases of COVID-19 on Tuesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-7k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-tuesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 19:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,135 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Tuesday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,135 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Tuesday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,918,100 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 7,179 from Monday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 136 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 412,908 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 196,114 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 121,226, and 5,892 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,731 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874386</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida officials seek to replace jobless benefits system</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida-officials-seek-to-replace-jobless-benefits-system/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873841</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida officials are recommending that the state&#8217;s antiquated unemployment processing system be replaced after a review confirmed what had long been...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida officials are recommending that the state&#8217;s antiquated unemployment processing system be replaced after a review confirmed what had long been known: a broken system full of glitches that was incapable of handling the unprecedented deluge of jobless claims spawned by the coronavirus outbreak.</p>
<p>The state&#8217;s Department of Economic Opportunity is recommending that the current system, known as CONNECT, be discarded and replaced with a more robust and modern system that employs cloud-based technology that could allow the system to more nimbly respond to increased demands.</p>
<p>The department, which oversees the state&#8217;s unemployment system, is asking lawmakers for $73 million over the next two years to modernize the system that left hundreds of thousands of jobless Floridians without unemployment checks for weeks and sometimes months.</p>
<p>The director of the agency, Dane Eagle, told lawmakers Monday that Florida was not alone in its struggles.</p>
<p>“We are far behind in where we need to be,” he said. “Florida is not the only state to experience these challenges.&#8221;</p>
<p>But as the unemployment rate surged when businesses closed, Florida was <a href="https://apnews.com/article/ec6da9c1e29d0fa10a74812201ac97e2">among the slowest states</a> — if not the slowest — in getting unemployment checks to those with no other income to pay mortgages, rents and other necessities.</p>
<p>Glenn Barca, a 53-year-old self-employed driver who had to max out his credit cards to pay bills and groceries while waiting months for his unemployment checks, said it took 70 to 80 attempts just to complete a simple application process because the website repeatedly crashed.</p>
<p>“The process was a nightmare,” said Barca, who typically makes the bulk of his income during Florida’s busy tourist season until the pandemic halted travel.</p>
<p>“Although late, it’s still never too late to try and get answers so we can hopefully begin to see drastic changes,” he said Monday.</p>
<p>Gov. Ron DeSantis, who likened the benefits claim system to an “old jalopy” breaking down at the Daytona 500, ordered the inspector general to investigate. The Economic Opportunity Department launched a review of its own, and the results were presented Monday to the legislative select committee on pandemic preparedness and response.</p>
<p>The report makes clear that the system was neither prepared nor responsive at a time of crisis, when some 1.3 million Floridians, at the peak of unemployment in April, tried to access benefits through online portals that <a href="https://apnews.com/article/5ad29f05102e6cdfda803650ae745c24">continually crashed</a> or phone systems that only <a href="https://apnews.com/article/7e2c1653f31a42717b030fd3262e2f86">added to frustrations</a>.</p>
<p>The long awaited inspector general’s report could be released in a matter of weeks. The inspector general’s findings are current being reviewed by economic opportunity officials.</p>
<p>The CONNECT system prompted concern from the start. Soon after the online portal launched in October 2013, it was beset by system crashes that prevented people from claiming benefits. Despite previous audits that identified numerous glitches, many of the problems were never addressed. Those same system failures prevented people from accessing the system.</p>
<p>Critics warned that the system was doomed to fail.</p>
<p>“Unfortunately, as it turns out, we were absolutely correct,&#8221; said Democratic state Rep. Evan Jenne, the House minority co-leader.</p>
<p>Since the start of the pandemic, more than 3.1 million people have filed unemployment claims in Florida. The state has paid out more than $23.1 billion in benefits — less than a fourth of that from the state&#8217;s reemployment assistance program.</p>
<p>The rest of the funds came from federal pandemic relief packages, some of it earmarked to supplement meager unemployment checks and to provide benefits to gig workers and others who were not eligible for traditional state benefits.</p>
<p>The state&#8217;s electronic portal was initially unable to process claims filed by freelancers and other independent contractors, adding to confusion, frustration and anger. The state eventually put in place a parallel electronic system to handle claims from nontraditional workers.</p>
<p>In fact the state&#8217;s electronic portal was so overwhelmed that state officials reverted to filing claims on paper forms.</p>
<p>As part of its just-completed review, the Department of Economic Opportunity is also asking lawmakers for authority to establish an Office of Accountability and Transparency, but it was unclear in a presentation submitted to the pandemic committee exactly what its role would be. In addition, it wants to create a Reemployment Assistance Modernization Strategic Planning Office to oversee the modernization effort.</p>
<p>The new money requested by the Economic Opportunity Department adds to the $39 million COVID-19-related outlays in its current year budget. The $73 billion being requested for the next two years would nearly double the department’s budget during the same time period. A more modest $8 million is also being requested to supplement the department&#8217;s typical annual budget of $41.3 million in the three years after.</p>
<p>Before the pandemic, the Reemployment Assistance System budget was about $12 million annually.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the state’s Unemployment Benefit Trust Fund has been dramatically depleted. Its balance is now just $777 million &#8212; less than a fifth of the $4 billion it had before the pandemic.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873841</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/060520-unemployment-system.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/060520-unemployment-system.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/060520-unemployment-system.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">060520 unemployment system</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PBSO: Louisiana woman abandoned 3 children after driving to West Palm Beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/pbso-louisiana-woman-abandoned-3-children-after-driving-to-west-palm-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 23:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873782</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Louisiana woman has been arrested after, authorities said, she abandoned three children at three different locations in and near West Palm Beach. Her family...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Louisiana woman has been arrested after, authorities said, she abandoned three children at three different locations in and near West Palm Beach. Her family said mental illness is to blame for her actions.</p>
<p>According to the Palm Beach Sheriff&#8217;s Office, they received a 911 call stating that a woman had abandoned an 8-year-old child at a Shell gas station near Okeechobee Boulevard and Drexel Road in unincorporated West Palm Beach, at around 5 a.m., Monday.</p>
<p>About four hours later at 9 a.m., investigators said, West Palm Beach Police received a call stating that a woman had abandoned a 3-year-old child at a Publix along Palm Beach Lakes Boulevard.</p>
<p>Then, at around 9:15 a.m., West Palm Beach Police learned that the woman&#8217;s vehicle, a 2018 white Chevy Equinox, was located off Sunrise Avenue and North Ocean Boulevard.</p>
<p>Responding officers arrived to find the woman, later identified as 36-year-old Miesha Perkins, walking away from her SUV. Inside the closed and locked vehicle, investigators said, was a 1-year-old child.</p>
<p>From her balcony, area resident Jill Slack watched officers pull the toddler from the car.</p>
<p>&#8220;First, I didn&#8217;t know what they were looking for in the car,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I didn&#8217;t know whether someone had passed out in the back seat. Was it an animal? Then, when I saw it was a baby, oh, my gosh, I just lost it. So sad. As soon as I heard it crying, I was like, &#8216;Thank God.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Perkins was detained and questioned by police. She was later arrested and charged with three counts of child neglect.</p>
<p>&#8220;How could she do that? How can anyone treat children that way?&#8221; said Slack.</p>
<p>Speaking on the phone with 7News, Perkins&#8217; mother said her daughter suffers from bipolar disorder.</p>
<p>&#8220;This is something that she would have never done if she was on her medication. No, this is not normal,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Detectives learned Perkins and the children&#8217;s father were driving down to West Palm Beach from Louisiana. At some point, authorities said, Perkins argued with the children&#8217;s father and left him at an unknown location.</p>
<p>Investigators said she began abandoning the children one by one after she arrived in Palm Beach County.</p>
<p>According to the suspect&#8217;s mother, Perkins was a friend of the children&#8217;s father and was helping him move the family down to West Palm Beach after the children&#8217;s mother died a few months ago.</p>
<p>Pamela said she hopes her daughter is given the medical care she needs.</p>
<p>&#8220;If she did something like that, she&#8217;s in a manic state, and she needs to be in the hospital, and that&#8217;s what I want them to do: send her to the hospital,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Perkins is being held at the Palm Beach County Jail.</p>
<p>She refused to appear in court on Tuesday morning and is being held on a $30,000 bond. The 36-year-old has been ordered not to have any contact with the victims or any children upon release.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873782</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210301_Miesha_Perkins_mugshot.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/22049ee6-ba44-440a-adce-7fd53ac68674/1f2c7cf3-704f-4758-bd9b-ffd4dbde5d81/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216624~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/22049ee6-ba44-440a-adce-7fd53ac68674/1f2c7cf3-704f-4758-bd9b-ffd4dbde5d81/main.mp4*~hmac=d1d7464342d9cc4dce3e2aec52eee3d353865608d4ab0e96534be380e6558326' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210301_Miesha_Perkins_mugshot.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210301_Miesha_Perkins_mugshot.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210301_Miesha_Perkins_mugshot</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida nurse left paralyzed from neck down after COVID-19-related illness</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida-nurse-left-paralyzed-from-neck-down-after-covid-19-related-illness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873660</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LARGO, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A Florida nurse has been left paralyzed from the neck down after he contracted a deadly illness shortly after beating COVID-19....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LARGO, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A Florida nurse has been left paralyzed from the neck down after he contracted a deadly illness shortly after beating COVID-19.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/covid-19-related-illness-leaves-largo-nurse-paralyzed-from-neck-down" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fox 13</a>, 23-year-old Desmon Silva has been recovering in a Massachusetts hospital with his mother by his side.</p>
<p>In July, Silva was out to dinner with his girlfriend when he started suffering neck pains. Minutes later, he lost feeling in his hands and was rushed to the hospital.</p>
<p>By the time he made it to the hospital, he was unresponsive, placed on a ventilator and was admitted to the intensive care unit.</p>
<p>Doctors ultimately determined Silva was paralyzed from the neck down.</p>
<p>Silva&#8217;s mother, Barbara Bonnett, told Fox 13 her son tested positive for COVID-19 about two months before he was rushed to the hospital, but said his case was mild and he recovered.</p>
<p>However, the virus weakened his immune system, and he developed an infection called Acute Disseminated Encephalomyelitis or ADEM, an illness that attacks the central nervous system.</p>
<p>Now, doctors are working to study Silva&#8217;s case and are trying to find out why he became paralyzed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873660</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/desmon-silva.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/desmon-silva.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/desmon-silva.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">desmon silva</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeSantis: Police, firefighters, teachers ages 50+ will be eligible for COVID-19 vaccines</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/desantis-police-firefighters-teachers-ages-50-will-be-eligible-for-covid-19-vaccines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announced he will be expanding COVID-19 vaccine access to more members of the community. Last week, DeSantis mentioned expanding vaccine access...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announced he will be expanding COVID-19 vaccine access to more members of the community.</p>
<p>Last week, DeSantis mentioned expanding vaccine access to more first responders and teachers, but on Monday morning, the governor said he will be making it official.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ll be signing an executive order later today to expand vaccine eligibility to all sworn law enforcement officers aged 50 and above, all firefighters aged 50 and above and all K-12 school personnel aged 50 and above,&#8221; he said during a media conference. &#8220;If you look at those numbers, the law enforcement and fire, some of them already got it because we focused on first responders, you&#8217;re talking about 20,000, 25,000 people maybe. Then with the schools, we probably could do all of that 50 up &#8212; K-12 personnel and police/fire with just our J&amp;J shipment.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Public Schools Superintendent Alberto Carvalho discussed how the expansion will benefit local employees.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re talking about school site employees working at K-12 institutions: teachers, custodians, cafeteria workers, bus drivers, bus aides,&#8221; he said, &#8220;those individuals who have direct contact with our school population, about 8,500 employees.&#8221;</p>
<p>DeSantis&#8217; announcement comes as Publix supermarkets begin administering the vaccine at 136 of their pharmacies across South Florida.</p>
<p>Pedro Lopez, a healthcare worker, received his first dose of the Moderna vaccine at a Publix pharmacy in Miami Shores, Monday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m definitely happy. I just didn&#8217;t want to get the virus,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Lopez said it took a little persistence to secure an appointment, but the registration process was simple and being able to come to a nearby Publix was convenient.</p>
<p>&#8220;It looks like it&#8217;s good news for a lot of people,&#8221; he said. &#8220;Luckily, I got in. I was able to register, register for myself, register for my wife &#8212; we&#8217;re healthcare workers &#8212; and I registered for my parents as well, so they should be coming in later on tonight.&#8221;</p>
<p>South Florida healthcare workers and seniors now have more options to get the vaccine, including at a Walmart in Lauderdale Lakes.</p>
<p>Lauderdale Lakes Mayor Hazelle Rogers visited the site to get her vaccine.</p>
<p>&#8220;We need to get the population out, put vaccines in arms, and that&#8217;s why I wanted to do this publicly, so my community will see that I took my vaccine,&#8221; said Rogers.</p>
<p>Monday night, Holy Cross Health in Fort Lauderdale announced they will be extending vaccine criteria to include people under 65 with certain medical conditions.</p>
<p>The vaccine rollout unfolds one day after the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/johnson-johnsons-covid-19-vaccine-gets-the-nod-from-cdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">got the go-ahead from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention</a> for emergency use for all adults.</p>
<p>It is ready to be shipped out to pharmacies and vaccination sites across the country.</p>
<p>Vaccine doses left a Kentucky UPS facility early Monday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;Supply will be limited for the next couple of weeks following this initial distribution of nearly four million doses,&#8221; said White House Coronavirus Response Coordinator Jeff Zients. &#8220;The company then expects to deliver approximately 16 million doses.&#8221;</p>
<p>Experts are making it clear that they recommend all three COVID-19 vaccines.</p>
<p>&#8220;All of these vaccines are very safe, and they&#8217;re very effective,&#8221; said Johnson &amp; Johnson CEO Alex Gorsky on CNN.</p>
<p>Unlike the Pfizer and Moderna alternatives, the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine only requires one shot and is easier to store.</p>
<p>&#8220;This means we now have three safe and highly effective vaccines that prevent serious illness, hospitalization and death from COVID-19,&#8221; said CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky.</p>
<p>As cellphone video of maskless revelers in close proximity continues to surface, Walensky cautioned that it is still too early to return to pre-pandemic routines.</p>
<p>&#8220;I am really worried about reports that more states are rolling back the exact public health measures we have recommended to protect people from COVID-19,&#8221; she said. &#8220;It&#8217;s not the time to relax the critical safeguards that we know can stop the spread of COVID-19 in our communities.&#8221;</p>
<p>As of Monday, the U.S. has reported 28,614,504 cases of the virus and 513,393 deaths.</p>
<p>Experts worry that cases and deaths are inching higher.</p>
<p>&#8220;The most recent seven-day average of cases, approximately 67,200, represents an increase of a little over 2% compared to the prior seven days,&#8221; said Walensky. &#8220;Similarly, the most recent seven-day average of deaths has also increased, more than 2% from the previous seven days to nearly 2,000 deaths per day.&#8221;</p>
<p>Starting Wednesday, Miami Dade College&#8217;s North Campus will become a <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/mdc-north-campus-among-4-federal-mass-vaccination-centers-announced-for-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">federal mass vaccination site</a> capable of administering thousands of doses a day.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873603</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ron-desantis.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e7c8f07e-42fe-4fa7-a022-c35fb990b6d8/58c8397c-ea87-466f-b289-59ca6ecebd60/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219961~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e7c8f07e-42fe-4fa7-a022-c35fb990b6d8/58c8397c-ea87-466f-b289-59ca6ecebd60/main.mp4*~hmac=dcd95b3f30c53d326ed232721818b3d6760069b0b1865f6571e67ac646f067ad' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ron-desantis.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ron-desantis.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ron desantis</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over less than 2K new cases of COVID-19 on Monday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-less-than-2k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-monday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,999 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Monday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.91 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,999 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Monday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,910,921confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 1,700 from Sunday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 147 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 410,952 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 195,217 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 120,868, and 5,861 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,426 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873633</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070657_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070657_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070657_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NASA&#8217;s DC headquarters renamed for &#8216;Hidden Figures&#8217; scientist Mary Jackson</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/nasas-dc-headquarters-renamed-for-hidden-figures-scientist-mary-jackson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 16:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; The name of Mary Jackson, NASA&#8217;s first African American female engineer and one of the barrier-breaking inspirations for the book &#8220;Hidden Figures,&#8221; officially adorns...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>(CNN) &#x2014; The name of&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.nasa.gov/content/mary-w-jackson-biography" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mary Jackson</a>, NASA&#x2019;s first African American female engineer and one of the barrier-breaking inspirations for the book &#x201C;Hidden Figures,&#x201D; officially adorns the space agency&#x2019;s Washington, DC, headquarters.<p>NASA&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/25/us/mary-w-jackson-hidden-figures-nasa-building-trnd/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced its decision</a> last year to name the building in Jackson&#x2019;s honor. Members of her family, including granddaughter Wanda Jackson, were at Friday&#x2019;s renaming ceremony along with Acting NASA Administrator Steve Jurczyk, the agency announced. Jackson died in 2005 at the age of 83.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/NASA/status/1365455355715592195</embed></div><p>Jackson worked at NASA for 34 years, starting as a research mathematician, and eventually became the agency&#x2019;s first Black female engineer. She later moved into administration and worked at NASA&#x2019;s equal opportunity office, leading programs that influenced the hiring and promotion of female mathematicians, engineers and scientists.</p><p>In 2019, Jackson was&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/09/us/hidden-figures-congressional-medals-trnd" target="_blank" rel="noopener">posthumously awarded the Congressional Gold Medal</a>, the nation&#x2019;s highest civilian honor, under the Hidden Figures Congressional Gold Medal Act. Her African American colleagues at NASA&#x2019;s Langley Research Center in Virginia &#x2014; Christine Darden, Katherine Johnson and Dorothy Vaughan &#x2014; were also honored with the medal.</p><p>Jackson was one of the subjects of the book &#x201C;Hidden Figures,&#x201D; which was turned into the 2016 film of the same name, starring Janelle Mon&#xC3;&#xA1;e as Jackson and detailing the contributions of the Black women to an early spaceflight.</p><p>The women were&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/13/us/nasa-street-hidden-figures-trnd/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">so-called human computers</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;who did the complex calculations that made space travel possible. They played pivotal roles in World War II aircraft testing, supersonic flight research, and sending the Voyager probes to explore the solar system. They also helped land the first man on the moon in 1969.</p><p>&#x201C;NASA facilities across the country are named after people who dedicated their lives to push the frontiers of the aerospace industry. The nation is beginning to awaken to the greater need to honor the full diversity of people who helped pioneer our great nation,&#x201D; former NASA Administrator Jim Bridenstine said in a&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.nasa.gov/press-release/nasa-names-headquarters-after-hidden-figure-mary-w-jackson" target="_blank" rel="noopener">news release last year</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;announcing the renaming plans.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873524</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/062520-mary-w-jackson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/062520-mary-w-jackson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/062520-mary-w-jackson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">062520 mary w jackson</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Officials: 1 dead in Jupiter single-engine plane crash</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/officials-1-dead-in-jupiter-single-engine-plane-crash/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 01:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JUPITER, Fla. (AP) — One person died when a single-engine plane crashed into the brush near a South Florida airport on Sunday, according to authorities....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JUPITER, Fla. (AP) — One person died when a single-engine plane crashed into the brush near a South Florida airport on Sunday, according to authorities.</p>
<p>The Luscombe 8A went down toward the end of a runway at Tailwinds Airport near Jupiter, according to the Martin County Sheriff’s Office and Palm Beach County Fire Rescue.</p>
<p>The Federal Aviation Administration said there were possibly two people on board when the plane crashed at about 12:30 p.m. under “unknown circumstances,” news outlets reported.</p>
<p>One person was taken to the hospital, a fire rescue spokesperson said. Nobody involved was identified and the condition of the hospitalized person was not immediately released.</p>
<p>The National Transportation Safety Board was set to handle the investigation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873160</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/small_plane_crash_generic.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/small_plane_crash_generic.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/small_plane_crash_generic.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">small_plane_crash_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 men arrested after Florida-Georgia manhunt that left deputy critically injured</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/2-men-arrested-after-florida-georgia-manhunt-that-left-deputy-critically-injured/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Two men have been arrested following a manhunt on Saturday that crossed from Florida into Georgia and left a deputy in critical condition,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Two men have been arrested following a manhunt on Saturday that crossed from Florida into Georgia and left a deputy in critical condition, according to the Georgia Bureau of Investigation.</p>
<p>The GBI <a href="https://gbi.georgia.gov/press-releases/2021-02-28/gbi-investigates-officer-involved-shooting-decatur-county" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> preliminary information indicated the deputy was shot during a pursuit that began in Seminole County, Florida, when a deputy tried to conduct a traffic stop for reckless driving on two men driving in a white pickup truck.</p>
<p>The men refused to stop and fired a weapon at officers pursuing them, who returned fire, the GBI said in a news release. The chase continued into Georgia, where Decatur County deputies joined the pursuit.</p>
<p>The suspects drove into the driveway of a home and &#8220;attempted to gain entry shooting through the door&#8221; but left after the homeowner returned fire, according to the release.</p>
<p>One of the suspects then shot a Decatur County deputy arriving at the scene, the GBI said. The deputy was taken to a local hospital for surgery and is in critical condition.</p>
<p>The suspects fled in their truck, which they wrecked &#8220;a short time later in a wooded area,&#8221; the release said. A Georgia State Patrol helicopter and crew joined the manhunt following the wreck.</p>
<p>One of the suspects, identified as Brad Phillips, 41, was taken into custody without further incident, the GBI said in the release. He&#8217;s been charged with aggravated assault on a peace officer.</p>
<p>The GBI identified the second suspect as Troy Arthur Phillips. He has been arrested and is in police custody.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873134</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/10/police-tape-lights.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/10/police-tape-lights.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/10/police-tape-lights.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">police tape lights</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump calls for GOP unity, repeats lies about election loss</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/trump-calls-for-gop-unity-repeats-lies-about-election-loss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 23:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Taking the stage for the first time since leaving office, former President Donald Trump called for GOP unity, even as he...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Taking the stage for the first time since leaving office, former President Donald Trump called for GOP unity, even as he exacerbated intraparty divisions by attacking fellow Republicans and promoting lies about the election in a speech that made clear he intends to remain a dominant political force.<p>Speaking Sunday at the Conservative Political Action Conference, where he has been hailed as a returning hero, Trump blasted his successor, President Joe Biden, and tried to lay out a vision for the future of the GOP that revolves firmly around him, despite his loss in November.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Do you miss me yet?&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Trump said after taking the stage to his old rally soundtrack and cheers from the supportive crowd.</p><p>Trump, in his speech, tried to downplay the civil war gripping the party over the extent to which Republicans should embrace him, even as he unfurled an enemies list, calling out by name the 10 House Republicans and seven GOP senators who voted to impeach or convict him for inciting the U.S. Capitol riot. He ended by singling out Rep. Liz Cheney, the No. 3 House Republican, who has faced tremendous backlash in Wyoming for saying Trump should no longer play a role in the party or headline the event.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/cspan/status/1366166341544267776?s=20</embed></div><p>While he insisted the division was merely a spat &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;between a handful of Washington, D.C., establishment political hacks and everybody else, all over the country,&#x201D; Trump had a message for the incumbents who had dared to cross him: &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Get rid of &#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;em all.&#x201D;</p><p>The conference, held this year in Orlando instead of the Washington suburbs to evade COVID-19 restrictions, served as a tribute to Trump and Trumpism, complete with a golden statue in his likeness on display. Speakers, including many potential 2024 hopefuls, argued that the party must embrace the former president and his followers, even after the deadly insurrection at the Capitol on Jan. 6.</p><p>They also repeated in panel after panel his unfounded claims that he lost reelection only because of mass voter fraud, even though such claims have been rejected by judges, Republican state officials and Trump&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s own administration.</p><p>Trump, too, continued to repeat what Democrats have dubbed the &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;big lie,&#x201D; calling the election &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;rigged&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; and insisting that he won in November, even though he lost by more than 7 million votes.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;As you know, they just lost the White House,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; he said of Biden, rewriting history.</p><p>It is highly unusual for past American presidents to publicly criticize their successors in the months after leaving office. Ex-presidents typically step out of the spotlight for at least a while; Barack Obama was famously seen kitesurfing on vacation after he departed, while George W. Bush said he believed Obama &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;deserves my silence&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; and took up painting.</p><p>Not Trump.</p><p>He delivered a sharp rebuke of what he framed as the new administration&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s first month of failures, especially Biden&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s approach to immigration and the border.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Joe Biden has had the most disastrous first month of any president in modern history,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Trump said.</p><p>White House press secretary Jen Psaki had brushed off the expected criticism last week. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ll see what he says, but our focus is certainly not on what President Trump is saying at CPAC,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; she told reporters.</p><p>Aside from criticizing Biden, Trump used the speech to crown himself the future of the Republican Party, even as many leaders argue they must move in a new, less divisive direction after Republicans lost not just the White House, but both chambers of Congress.</p><p>Though Trump has flirted with the the idea of creating a third party, he pledged Sunday to remain part of &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;our beloved&#x201D; GOP.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;m going to continue to fight right by your side. We&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;re not starting new parties,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; he said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We have the Republican Party. It&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s going to be strong and united like never before.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Yet Trump spent much of the speech lashing out at those he has deemed insufficiently loyal and dubbed &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;RINOs&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Republican in name only &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; for failing to stand with him.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We cannot have leaders who show more passion for condemning their fellow Americans than they have ever shown for standing up to Democrats, the media and the radicals who want to turn America into a socialist country,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Trump said.</p><p>Trump did not use his speech to announce plans to run again, but he repeatedly teased the prospect as he predicted a Republican would win back the White House in 2024.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;And I wonder who that will be,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; he offered. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Who, who, who will that be? I wonder.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>It remains unclear, however, how much appetite there would be for another Trump term, even in the room of staunch supporters.</p><p>The conference&#x2019;s annual unscientific straw poll of just over 1,000 attendees found that 97% approved of the job Trump did as president. But they were much more ambiguous when asked whether he should run again, with only 68% saying he should.</p><p>If the 2024 primary were held today and Trump were in the race, just 55% said they would vote for him, followed by Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis at 21%. Without Trump in the field, DeSantis garnered 43% support, followed by 8% for South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem and 7% each for former Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Texas Sen. Ted Cruz.</p><p>While he no longer has his social media megaphone after being barred from Twitter and Facebook, Trump had been inching back into public life even before the speech. He called into conservative news outlets after talk radio star Rush Limbaugh&#x2019;s death and has issued statements, including one blasting Mitch McConnell after the Senate Republican leader excoriated Trump for inciting the Capitol riot. McConnell has since said he would &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;absolutely&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; support Trump if he were the GOP nominee in 2024.</p><p>At his Mar-a-Lago club in Palm Beach, Florida, Trump has also been quietly meeting with aides and senior party leaders as he builds his post-presidential political operation. While he has already backed several pro-Trump candidates, including one challenging an impeachment supporter, aides have been working this past week to develop benchmarks for those seeking his endorsement to make sure the candidates are serious and have set up full-fledged political and fundraising organizations before he gets involved.</p><p>They are also planning a new super PAC that could raise unlimited amounts of money, though one aide cautioned they were still deciding whether to create a new entity or repurpose an existing America First super PAC.</p><p>Trump hinted at the effort Sunday, voicing his commitment to helping elect Republicans and calling on attendees to join him.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I stand before you today to declare that the incredible journey we begun together &#x2026; is far from being over,&#x201D; he said.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873114</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210228_Trump_CPAC_speech.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8909287c-9202-4ffd-866b-673c61796bc7/ea9c6eaf-4f9f-4af9-804d-5aba3f239fac/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219873~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8909287c-9202-4ffd-866b-673c61796bc7/ea9c6eaf-4f9f-4af9-804d-5aba3f239fac/main.mp4*~hmac=cdbe2c46a22ada9eda1bac583591cb3ffa827ba491de77a66391e7e1bb9f5378' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210228_Trump_CPAC_speech.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210228_Trump_CPAC_speech.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210228_Trump_CPAC_speech</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 5K new cases of COVID-19 on Sunday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-sunday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 19:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.9 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,852 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Sunday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.9 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,852 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Sunday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,909,221 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,539 from Saturday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 118 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 410,717 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 194,992 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 120,735, and 5,857 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,344 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872845</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida lawmakers face challenges as 60-day session begins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/florida-lawmakers-face-challenges-as-60-day-session-begins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Coronavirus, budget questions, anti-riot legislation and an attempt to reign in large technology companies will be among issues lawmakers will take...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Coronavirus, budget questions, anti-riot legislation and an attempt to reign in large technology companies will be among issues lawmakers will take up in their 60-day session that begins Tuesday.</p>
<p>But so will bicycle seats, alcohol-to-go and baby boxes.</p>
<p>More than 2,500 bills have been filed ahead of the 2021 session. While most won’t pass, the Legislature will be grappling with a wide variety of issues under new Republican leaders, House Speaker Chris Sprowls and Senate President Wilton Simpson, all while figuring out how to do business in a pandemic.</p>
<p>The budget is the only bill lawmakers are required to pass, and lawmakers won’t get the latest revenue estimates until after session starts. One factor they won&#8217;t consider is potential federal COVID-19 relief money.</p>
<p>“We were being told at the end of last year the federal government is going to bring in money for the state governments, and they didn’t. I don’t think you can depend on Washington to do anything right. A lot of clowns in Washington and they don’t get a lot done,” said Simpson.</p>
<p>Gov. Ron DeSantis proposed a $96.6 billion for the fiscal year that begins July 1, or $4.3 billion more than the current budget. That might be overly optimistic considering the financial hit Florida has taken during the pandemic.</p>
<p>“It’s just not feasible, it’s not realistic and, most importantly, it’s not going to happen,” said Democratic Rep. Evan Jenne, a member of the House Appropriations Committee.</p>
<p>Senate Appropriations Committee Chairwoman Kelli Stargel also said it will be a tough budget year.</p>
<p>“While we have all been relieved to see revenue collections come in over estimate in recent months, it is important to remember our starting point for planning for this budget was a $2.7 billion shortfall,” said Stargel, a Republican. “Modest gains do not negate the challenge before us. Reductions will be necessary.”</p>
<p>A priority for DeSantis, Sprowls and Simpson is passing protections for businesses and health care facilities that would shield them from COVID-19 lawsuits.</p>
<p>“What our bill says is, ’Look, if you’re trying to do the right thing, if you’re following guidelines by the state or the CDC, we want to make sure that you have a sense of financial security,” Sprowls said.</p>
<p>The speaker says he wants the protections to be the first legislation to pass, along with a bill that would make it a felony to profit off a pandemic by making false or misleading marketing claims about personal protective equipment or the availability or access to a vaccine.</p>
<p>Another priority for DeSantis and Republican leaders is a so-called anti-riot bill that would enhance penalties for crimes committed during a violent protest, not allow people arrested during such a demonstration to be released from jail before a first court appearance and create new felonies for organizing or participating in a violent demonstration.</p>
<p>DeSantis proposed the idea after a summer of protests held around the country to call attention to police violence against African Americans. But he has since pointed to the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol as a reason to support it.</p>
<p>Still, Democrats say he’s trying to squash the voice of groups like Black Lives Matter.</p>
<p>“This law would disproportionately hurt communities of color trying to exercise their constitutional rights,” said Democratic Rep. Dianne Hart. “This will give bad actors in law enforcement and the criminal justice system additional weapons to harm, incarcerate and kill Black and brown Floridians.”</p>
<p>Republican leaders will also target large technology companies like Twitter, Facebook and Amazon. DeSantis calls them “Big Tech cartels” that manipulate consumers and censor conservative politicians and ideologies. He and other Republicans point to then-President Donald Trump being banned from social media, and Amazon shutting down the conservative social media site Parler.</p>
<p>“Big Tech has come to look more like Big Brother with each passing day,” DeSantis said at a recent news conference. “But this is 2021, not 1984, and this is real life, not George Orwell’s fiction.”</p>
<p>Beyond leaders&#8217; priorities, there are hundreds of other bill covering a wide variety of topics. One would permanently allow restaurants to sell alcohol with delivered or take-out meals. DeSantis allowed the practice to help restaurants during the pandemic.</p>
<p>A number of bills involve children, like one that would increase the time parents can surrender an infant from one week to one month. It also would allow “baby boxes” at some fire stations and hospitals so parents can drop off infants without doing so face-to-face.</p>
<p>Two child safety bills would require child care facilities to install alarms in vans so drivers can check to make sure no children are left inside and raise the age children must be in booster seats from 5 to 6.</p>
<p>Among more obscure bills is an effort to amend a law that makes it illegal to ride a bike without a seat. Violators face a $15 fine. It would make an exception for elliptical bikes and others that are manufactured to be used without a seat.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872389</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180306_florida_house_floor.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180306_florida_house_floor.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180306_florida_house_floor.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180306_Florida_House_floor</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coast Guard continues search for missing plane last seen off Boca Raton</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/coast-guard-continues-search-for-missing-plane-last-seen-off-boca-raton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872357</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Coast Guard are continuing their search for a missing plane that was last seen off the coast of Boca Raton. Coast Guard officials...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Coast Guard are continuing their search for a missing plane that was last seen off the coast of Boca Raton.</p>
<p><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">Coast Guard officials said Saturday morning crews and partner agencies are searching for a 1991 Lancair 320 with one person on board.</span></p>
<p><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">The aircraft was last seen around 17 miles southeast of Boca Raton.  </span></p>
<p><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">If you have any information on this case, contact Coast Guard D7 Command Center at 305-415-6800.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872357</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022721-missing-plane-boca-raton.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022721-missing-plane-boca-raton.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022721-missing-plane-boca-raton.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022721 missing plane boca raton</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Police searching for woman in theft of $15K ring at Key West jewelry store</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/police-searching-for-woman-in-theft-of-15k-ring-at-key-west-jewelry-store/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872179</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Police are seeking the public&#8217;s help in their search for a woman in connection with the theft of a ring in Key West. According to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Police are seeking the public&#8217;s help in their search for a woman in connection with the theft of a ring in Key West.</p>
<p>According to Key West Police, the subject stole the pricey ring from a jewelry store on Duval Street.</p>
<p>Investigators said the 14-karat white gold women&#8217;s diamond ring is valued at $15,000.</p>
<p>Officials said the woman may live in Homestead but could also be residing in the Lower Keys.</p>
<p>If you have any information on this theft or the woman&#8217;s whereabouts, call Monroe County Crime Stoppers at 800-346-TIPS or Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a reward of up to $5,000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872179</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_ring_thief_Key_West_Crime_Stopers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/de54a9a8-aac8-432f-8dcd-4ce56aa71c1a/096ffe28-7533-45b9-9564-157b7f7cbe0e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216978~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/de54a9a8-aac8-432f-8dcd-4ce56aa71c1a/096ffe28-7533-45b9-9564-157b7f7cbe0e/main.mp4*~hmac=f320314c3f1d4d8f1650a54750a27d6b16c99204628c15cd453b619c193e0456' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_ring_thief_Key_West_Crime_Stopers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_ring_thief_Key_West_Crime_Stopers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210226_ring_thief_Key_West_Crime_Stopers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 men arrested, charged with felony lobster violations in Monroe County</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/2-men-arrested-charged-with-felony-lobster-violations-in-monroe-county/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two men have been arrested in Monroe County for allegedly having over 100 undersized crustaceans in their possession. Osvaldo Hernandez, 65, and Vladimir Medina Martin,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two men have been arrested in Monroe County for allegedly having over 100 undersized crustaceans in their possession.</p>
<p>Osvaldo Hernandez, 65, and Vladimir Medina Martin, 45, were pulled over during a traffic stop when officers noticed a fishy odor emitting from the car.</p>
<p>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission officers confiscated 100 undersized wrung lobster tails, four short, live lobsters and 17 short stone crab claws.</p>
<p>The two men were then arrested and charged with enhanced felony lobster violations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871949</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022621-lobster-violations.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5c1185c9-854a-405d-88e4-8bde2509a9c8/12fdd523-b424-4365-8e42-ee790926250f/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216521~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5c1185c9-854a-405d-88e4-8bde2509a9c8/12fdd523-b424-4365-8e42-ee790926250f/main.mp4*~hmac=a4255d576170fbb5c039309de168a52a9eb6f95a1f5756acf659ee7c17ff6b8d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022621-lobster-violations.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022621-lobster-violations.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022621 lobster violations</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man helps locate wedding ring in Key West for newly engaged couple</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/man-helps-locate-wedding-ring-in-key-west-for-newly-engaged-couple/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 23:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Key West man saved the bliss of a recently engaged couple after he found their missing engagement ring. During the special moment earlier this...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Key West man saved the bliss of a recently engaged couple after he found their missing engagement ring.</p>
<p>During the special moment earlier this week, Evan Dunaway opened the ring box to propose to Molly Murphy, his longtime girlfriend, and the ring fell into the water before she could see it.</p>
<p>&#8220;As soon as he opened that box, it was gone,&#8221; Murphy said. &#8220;I didn&#8217;t even get a glimpse of it. We cried. I didn&#8217;t know if I should be so happy or so sad.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dunaway said he had planned a romantic boating trip to pop the question while out on the water, but when the time came to present the ring, it was gone.</p>
<p>&#8220;As the ring went into the water, obviously, I felt a little bit like a bad dream that you can&#8217;t wake up from,&#8221; Dunaway said.</p>
<p>Alex Corpion recently started working for Ring Finders, a company that searches for lost rings in the water, and he already closed his first case. He later learned of what happened to Dunaway as he proposed to his fiancé in Key West.</p>
<p>&#8220;I saw I had a missed call from a lady named Molly, and they asked if I could come and help them search for a ring,&#8221; Corpion said.</p>
<p>Corpion packed up all his gear and met up with the group the next day. They hopped onto a boat and traveled for an hour back to the sandbar where the ring had fallen out. Around 15 minutes later, Corpion found the missing engagement ring.</p>
<p>He returned it to the couple, and Dunaway was able to propose a second time. This time with the ring going where it belonged: on his fiancé&#8217;s finger!</p>
<p>&#8220;I was just crying. I didn&#8217;t even know what to think,&#8221; Murphy said. &#8220;He took two scoops, and there it was just sitting in the basket! Now, I feel like I&#8217;m wearing treasure every single day. It&#8217;s amazing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Corpion was glad he was able to save the couple&#8217;s special moment.</p>
<p>“You can see the relief and excitement and the overwhelming appreciation of what all this means,&#8221; said Corpion. &#8220;It’s an amazing feeling. I truly cannot get enough of it. I can’t wait to do it again!”</p>
<p>Corpion said he did not charge the couple to find the ring and said he loves seeing the smiles on the faces of the people he helps.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871839</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/man-finds-ring.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fc6a0e2a-bad2-40dc-ac58-9652e6aa2a9f/d561007e-8923-44c1-829a-7f20ff1e57fd/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216663~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fc6a0e2a-bad2-40dc-ac58-9652e6aa2a9f/d561007e-8923-44c1-829a-7f20ff1e57fd/main.mp4*~hmac=f5de3db7d35dc8ae1e39b23b814ad07df2b35760ea7488a029a7c4f2e06a9d0a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/man-finds-ring.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/man-finds-ring.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">man finds ring</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports nearly 6K new cases of COVID-19 on Friday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-nearly-6k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-friday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 19:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,624 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Friday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,624 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Friday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,898,223 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,922 from Thursday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 146 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 408,096 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 193,560 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 119,911, and 5,799 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 79,021 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871890</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/coronavirus-testing-2-e1594391327260.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/coronavirus-testing-2-e1594391327260.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/coronavirus-testing-2-e1594391327260.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus testing</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Port Richey grandfather arrested after allegedly raping his 13-year-old granddaughter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/port-richey-grandfather-arrested-after-allegedly-raping-his-13-year-old-granddaughter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871770</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PINELLAS PARK, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A Port Richey man has been taken into police custody after he allegedly raped his 13-year-old granddaughter. According to Pinellas...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PINELLAS PARK, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A Port Richey man has been taken into police custody after he allegedly raped his 13-year-old granddaughter.</p>
<p>According to Pinellas Park Police, 51-year-old Terence Edwin Phillips was staying with the victim and her family after his Port Richey home lost power.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/port-richey-grandfather-accused-of-raping-his-13-year-old-granddaughter" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fox 13 reports</a> the teenager told detectives her grandfather came into her room and sexually battered her in her bed in the early morning hours on Saturday.</p>
<p>Police arrested Phillips on Thursday and charged him with two counts of felony sexual battery.</p>
<p>He is currently being held on a $200,000 bond.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871770</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Terence-Edwin-Phillips.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Terence-Edwin-Phillips.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Terence-Edwin-Phillips.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Terence Edwin Phillips</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDLE: Infant, toddler reported missing in Highlands County found safe</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/fdle-infant-toddler-reported-missing-in-highlands-county-found-safe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 03:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AVON PARK, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A 1-month-old girl and a 1-year-old boy who were reported missing in Highlands County have been found safe, authorities said....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>AVON PARK, Fla. (WSVN) &#x2014; A 1-month-old girl and a 1-year-old boy who were reported missing in Highlands County have been found safe, authorities said.<p>The Florida Department of Law Enforcement on Thursday night issued a Florida Missing Child Alert for Kinyin Barfield and John Barfield.</p><p>Officias said the children had been last seen in the area of the 1000 block of Canberra Circle in Avon Park and may have been in the company of 30-year-old Jessica Wooten.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/fdlepio/status/1365176922133696513?s=20</embed></div><p>Just after 12:45 a.m. on Friday, FDLE tweeted out, &#x201C;The children are safe.&#x201D;</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871522</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210225_Avon_Park_missing_children.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210225_Avon_Park_missing_children.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210225_Avon_Park_missing_children.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210225_Avon_Park_missing_children</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peppa Pig theme park to open at LEGOLAND Florida in 2022</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/peppa-pig-theme-park-to-open-at-legoland-florida-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 20:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871177</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WINTER HAVEN, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; Peppa Pig fans will soon be able to visit the theme park of their dreams. LEGOLAND Florida has announced plans...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINTER HAVEN, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; Peppa Pig fans will soon be able to visit the theme park of their dreams.</p>
<p>LEGOLAND Florida has announced plans for the world&#8217;s first Peppa Pig Theme Park, set to open in 2022.</p>
<p>&#8220;Designed to be the ultimate day for little ones, this all-new standalone theme park will feature multiple rides, interactive attractions, themed playscapes and water play areas &#8212; complete with “muddy puddles” of course &#8212; and fun live shows daily, all based on instantly recognizable locations from the globally popular brand,&#8221; the park said in a release.</p>
<p>Guests will also be able to meet Peppa and her friends at the park.</p>
<p>Specifics on the rides and attractions will be released in summer. However, LEGOLAND said the park will be a separately ticked park that will operate year-round.</p>
<p>The park will also have annual passes, along with inclusive passes that allow for admission to the LEGOLAND Theme park, the LEGOLAND water park and other locations.</p>
<p>For more information, <a href="https://www.peppapigthemepark.com/florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871177</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/RENDERING_Front-Gate_Peppa-Pig-Theme-Park-at-LEGOLAND-Florida-Resort.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/RENDERING_Front-Gate_Peppa-Pig-Theme-Park-at-LEGOLAND-Florida-Resort.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/RENDERING_Front-Gate_Peppa-Pig-Theme-Park-at-LEGOLAND-Florida-Resort.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">RENDERING_Front Gate_Peppa Pig Theme Park at LEGOLAND Florida Resort</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 6K new cases of COVID-19 on Thursday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-6k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-thursday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 19:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,478 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.89 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,478 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Thursday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,892,301 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 6,640 from Wednesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 138 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 406,987 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 192,738 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 119,373, and 5,771 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 78,744 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871173</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5057462_1920-e1588100104186.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to get the COVID-19 vaccine in South Florida</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/where-to-get-the-covid-19-vaccine-in-south-florida/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 14:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=817116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has opened the distribution of vaccines to members of the general population who are 65 years or older, police officers and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has opened the distribution of vaccines to members of the general population who are 65 years or older, police officers and firefighters 50 years of age and all teachers.</p>
<p>Several hospitals and sites require appointments in order for eligible South Floridians to receive the vaccine.</p>
<p><strong>NOTE: Health officials warn that &#8220;appointments are limited at this time. More appointments will be made available as vaccine supply increases and additional sites open.&#8221;</strong></p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Federally Run Site</strong></span></p>
<p><strong>Miami-Dade College North: </strong>A federal vaccination site has opened at the Miami-Dade College North Campus. The walk-up site will open from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m. daily and will administer 2,000 vaccines daily without appointments. For more information, <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-opens-on-wednesday/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong><u>Statewide Programs</u></strong></p>
<p><b>MyVaccine Florida</b> &#8211; The state has developed a pre-registration system to schedule vaccinations for priority populations. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> to pre-register.</p>
<p><b>Walmart | Sam&#8217;s Club</b> will be allowing eligible Floridians to receive the COVID-19 vaccine at select Walmart and Sam’s Club stores through the new Federal Retail Pharmacy Program. <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/select-walmart-locations-to-begin-administering-covid-19-vaccines-this-week/">Click here</a> for participating Walmart and Sam&#8217;s Club locations.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Broward County</strong></span></p>
<p><strong>Broward Health</strong> will begin COVID-19 vaccinations at its new community stand-up site at Inter Miami CF Stadium at Lockhart Park. The site will be open Monday through Friday and expects to vaccinate up to 500 pre-registered patients a day. To register, <a href="https://www.browardhealth.org/pages/being-healthy-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>FDOH Broward: </strong>The Florida Department of Health in Broward is providing vaccination appointments to people who meet the requirements at various sites across the county. For more information or to view the vaccination sites, <a href="https://www.broward.org/CoronaVirus/Pages/Vaccination-Sites.aspx">click here</a>. To make an appointment, <a href="https://browardcovidvaccine.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Memorial Healthcare System: </strong>Memorial Healthcare System is offering vaccines to those who meet the requirements, by appointment only. Appointments can be scheduled through MyChart if you are an existing patient. If you are a new patient, please call 954-276-4340 to schedule your COVID-19 vaccine. For more information, <a href="https://mychart.mhs.net/mychart/Authentication/Login?" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida"><strong>Publix Supermarket</strong></a>: Starting Friday, February 26 after 7:00 a.m. EST, eligible customers can access COVID-19 vaccine appointment availability beginning Monday, March 1.  For more information, <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Broward College North Campus in Coconut Creek</a>: </strong>Hosts a state-run vaccination site. This location will accept walk-ups and those who have proactively scheduled appointments.  <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Coral Square Mall</a>: </strong>Individuals 65+, long-term facility residents and staff, healthcare personnel with direct patient contact and individuals deemed to be extremely vulnerable to COVID-19 by hospital providers. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Tradewinds Park</a>: </strong>Individuals 65+, long-term facility residents and staff, healthcare personnel with direct patient contact and individuals deemed to be extremely vulnerable to COVID-19 by hospital providers. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Markham Park</a>:</strong> Individuals 65+, long-term facility residents and staff, healthcare personnel with direct patient contact and individuals deemed to be extremely vulnerable to COVID-19 by hospital providers. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Tree Tops Park</a>: </strong>Individuals 65+, long-term facility residents and staff, healthcare personnel with direct patient contact and individuals deemed to be extremely vulnerable to COVID-19 by hospital providers. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Snyder Park</a>: </strong>Individuals 65+, long-term facility residents and staff, healthcare personnel with direct patient contact and individuals deemed to be extremely vulnerable to COVID-19 by hospital providers. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Central Broward Regional Park</a>: </strong>Individuals 65+, long-term facility residents and staff, healthcare personnel with direct patient contact and individuals deemed to be extremely vulnerable to COVID-19 by hospital providers. <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/">Click here</a> for more.</p>
<p><strong>Holy Cross Health</strong>: Those under age 65 <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">who meet the requirements</a> can request an appointment at the hospital. Priority will be given to Holy Cross Medical Group patients.</p>
<p><strong>Collins Community Center</strong>: The City of Oakland Park is offering free vaccines to seniors 65+ by appointment only at the Collins Community Center at 3900 NE Third Avenue. To make an appointment, call 954-630-4335, Monday to Friday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. Appointments are available Monday to Saturday, 10 a.m. to 3 p.m. You do not have to be a resident of Oakland Park.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Miami-Dade County</strong></span></p>
<p><strong>County Vaccination Program: </strong>Miami-Dade County is coordinating closely with hospital and healthcare partners, the Florida Department of Health, municipalities, and private partners to vaccinate members of the community. For more information, <a href="https://www.miamidade.gov/global/initiatives/coronavirus/vaccine/home.page" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>. To book an appointment, <a href="https://vaccines.nomihealth.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Jackson Health System</strong> is offering vaccines to those 65 years old and older. Certain adults 55 and older <span style="text-decoration: underline;">with specific medical conditions</span> are now able to schedule a COVID-19 vaccination. To make an appointment, <a href="https://jhsmiami.org/comvac/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/CLfR8B_LMzF/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="13" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:500px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);">
<div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CLfR8B_LMzF/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> </p>
<div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;">
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div>
<div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div>
<div style="padding-top: 8px;">
<div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div>
</div>
<div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;">
<div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div>
</div>
<div style="margin-left: 8px;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div>
<div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div>
</div>
<div style="margin-left: auto;">
<div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div>
<div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div>
</div>
<p></a></p>
<p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CLfR8B_LMzF/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank">A post shared by Jackson Health System (@jacksonhealth)</a></p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<p><script async src="//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"></script></p>
<p><strong>Mt. Sinai:</strong> First Responders and seniors over 65 can schedule an appointment by calling 305-674-2312, Monday-Friday from 8 a.m. &#8211; 5 p.m. and Saturday &#8211; Sunday from 8 a.m. &#8211; 1 p.m. No walk-ins will be accepted.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/hard-rock-stadium-unveiled-as-covid-19-vaccination-site/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hard Rock Stadium</a>: </strong>Seniors 65 and older are able to call 1-888-499-0840 to make an appointment to get vaccinated at the Hard Rock Stadium. The stadium currently offers 1,000 appointments available per day and additional appointments are dependent on additional vaccine doses allocated by the federal government.</p>
<p><a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/baptist-health-to-begin-offering-covid-19-vaccines-to-seniors-high-risk-patients/"><strong>Baptist Health</strong></a>: Baptist Health South Florida will begin offering COVID-19 vaccines to senior residents and people who are at high risk of serious illness from the virus, beginning Monday, Jan. 11. The hospital is only offering a limited number of appointments and will offer more as they receive more vaccines. For more information, <a href="https://baptisthealth.net/coronavirus/vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here.</a></p>
<p><strong>Jessie Trice Community Health System</strong>: Seniors 65 and older are able to call 305-637-6400 and make an appointment to get vaccinated. Testing will be conducted Wednesday through Friday from 8:30 a.m. to 4 p.m.</p>
<p><strong>Miami VA: </strong> Miami VA Healthcare System is offering COVID-19 Vaccines to all eligible Veterans, regardless of age, in Miami-Dade, Broward and Monroe counties who are active patients of the Miami VA Healthcare System. To schedule an appointment, Veterans can call 305-575-7000 or contact their care team.</p>
<p><strong>Navarro Discount Pharmacies:</strong> Seniors 65+ can schedule COVID-19 vaccines at all their Miami-Dade County locations.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.cvs.com/immunizations/covid-19-vaccine">CVS y Mas</a>: </strong>Seniors 65+ can schedule COVID-19 vaccines at all their Miami-Dade County locations. For more information, <a href="https://www.cvs.com/immunizations/covid-19-vaccine">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Fresco y Mas: </strong>The grocery change Fresco y Mas is offering COVID-19 vaccines to eligible recipients at their store located at 18300 SW 137Th Avenue in SW Miami-Dade. For more information <a href="https://www.frescoymas.com/pharmacy/covid-vaccine">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.winndixie.com/pharmacy/covid-vaccine/">Winn-Dixie</a>: </strong>Winn-Dixie&#8217;s pharmacy will begin offering COVID-19 vaccines to eligible recipients two Miami-Dade locations: 1155 NW 11th Street and 1150 NW 54th Street in Miami. For appointments and more information <a href="https://www.winndixie.com/pharmacy/covid-vaccine/">click here</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida"><strong>Publix Supermarket</strong></a>: Starting Friday, February 26 after 7:00 a.m. EST, eligible customers can access COVID-19 vaccine appointment availability beginning Monday, March 1.  For more information, <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida">click here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Overtown Youth Center</strong>: No appointment is necessary for those who want to get vaccinated at the Overtown Youth Center, located at 450 NW 14th St. The site is open seven days a week from 8:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. Organizers said they are able to administer 200 vaccine doses each day.</p>
<p><strong>Ronselli Park in Sweetwater</strong>: Long-term facility residents and staff, persons 65 years of age and older, health care personnel with direct patient contact, police officers, firefighters and school employees 50 years of age and older can get vaccinated at the site. It is open daily from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. Walk-ups are allowed and appointments are not necessary. A total of 500 doses will be administered daily.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Monroe County</strong></span></p>
<p><strong>FDOH Monroe: </strong>The Florida Department of Health in Monroe County is providing vaccination appointments to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Long-term care facility residents and staff</li>
<li>Persons 65 years of age and older</li>
<li>Persons under 65 deemed medically vulnerable</li>
<li>Health care personnel with direct patient contact</li>
<li>K-12 school employees</li>
<li>Sworn law enforcement officers 50 years of age and older</li>
<li>Firefighters 50 years of age and older</li>
</ul>
<p>Call 305-293-7500 to schedule an appointment to be vaccinated at their site in Tavernier.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.winndixie.com/pharmacy/covid-vaccine/">Winn-Dixie</a>: </strong>Winn-Dixie&#8217;s pharmacy will begin offering COVID-19 vaccines to eligible recipients at two of their Monroe County locations (Key West and Tavernier). For appointments and more information <a href="https://www.winndixie.com/pharmacy/covid-vaccine/">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">817116</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/vaccinated.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/vaccinated.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/vaccinated.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">vaccinated vaccine vaccination</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sheriff: Florida man starved 2 dogs to death inside abandoned home</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/sheriff-florida-man-starved-2-dogs-to-death-inside-abandoned-home/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 23:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; A Florida man is facing animal abuse charges after investigators said two dogs died in his care, sheriff&#8217;s officials said. David...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MELBOURNE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; A Florida man is facing animal abuse charges after investigators said two dogs died in his care, sheriff&#8217;s officials said.</p>
<p>David Fritsch, 33, left two dogs locked in a master bedroom with no food for several weeks, Brevard County Sheriff Wayne Ivey said in a Facebook Live post.</p>
<p>Ivey called it &#8220;one of the worst absolute cases of animal cruelty I&#8217;ve ever seen in my 40 years as a cop.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to the sheriff, the dogs ate chips of wood from furniture, plastic bottles, plastic bags and band-aids in an attempt to stay alive.</p>
<p>&#8220;These poor animals were literally eating furniture and their own feces trying desperately to stay alive,&#8221; Ivey said.</p>
<p>Investigators were alerted to the situation in January when someone called about two dogs being abandoned in a home. Animal services workers found the dogs dead in the home.</p>
<p>During the live video, the sheriff walked Fritsch into the jail.</p>
<p>&#8220;I guess you didn&#8217;t get the memo about don&#8217;t hurt animals.&#8221; the sheriff said.</p>
<p>Fritsch remained in the Brevard County Jail on Wednesday. Jail records do not list a lawyer for him.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870687</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/David-Fritsch.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/David-Fritsch.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/David-Fritsch.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">David Fritsch</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports 7,128 new cases of COVID-19 on Wednesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-7128-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-wednesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.88 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,340 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Wednesday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.88 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,340 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Wednesday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,885,661 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 7,128 from Tuesday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 127 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 405,563 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 191,968 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 118,853, and 5,747 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 78,472 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870511</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070658_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida library to be renamed after former President Obama</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida-library-to-be-renamed-after-former-president-obama/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A Florida library is being renamed after a former president. St. Petersburg&#8217;s main library will officially be renamed the President...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A Florida library is being renamed after a former president.</p>
<p>St. Petersburg&#8217;s main library will officially be renamed the President Barack Obama Main Library on Friday, <a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/st-petes-main-library-to-be-renamed-after-former-president-obama" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fox 13 reports</a>.</p>
<p>The dedication will come as a part of the city&#8217;s Black History Month celebrations and to honor the nation&#8217;s first Black president.</p>
<p>&#8220;Highlighting Barack Obama&#8217;s extraordinary story and history-making presidency in this way will inspire generations of young people,&#8221; Mayor Rick Kriseman said in a statement. &#8220;I believe the President Barack Obama Main Library will not only complement city buildings bearing the name of local trailblazers, but will serve as an example to other cities.&#8221;</p>
<p>City officials originally announced in 2018 that the library would be named after the former president.</p>
<p>According to Fox 13, a dedication ceremony will take place Friday at 11 a.m., with the installation of a sign with the library&#8217;s new name. It is one of the first changes in the planned $6 million in renovations for the 55-year-old building.</p>
<p>Other planned changes include the reconfiguration of interior spaces, a renovated outdoor patio, additional parking spaces, ADA-compliant restrooms and more.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our main library has always been an exciting hub for learning in our city,&#8221; Kriseman said. &#8220;It is made all the better by honoring President Obama.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870522</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/ap_19347146527165-e1588704407877.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/ap_19347146527165-e1588704407877.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/ap_19347146527165-e1588704407877.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Barack Obama</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palm Beach County refuses to lower flags for Rush Limbaugh</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/palm-beach-county-refuses-to-lower-flags-for-rush-limbaugh/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870467</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Palm Beach County defied Gov. Ron DeSantis on Wednesday, refusing to lower its courthouse flags to half-staff in honor of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Palm Beach County defied Gov. Ron DeSantis on Wednesday, refusing to lower its courthouse flags to half-staff in honor of the late conservative broadcaster Rush Limbaugh — a move that the governor&#8217;s office called “petty.”</p>
<p>The county&#8217;s courthouse flags remained at full staff, ignoring Gov. Ron DeSantis&#8217; Tuesday afternoon order directing its U.S. and Florida flags to be flown at half-staff. He also ordered the Town of Palm Beach and the State Capitol in Tallahassee to fly their flags at half-staff from sunrise to sunset on Wednesday. Those flags were lowered.</p>
<p>Palm Beach County would only say it followed “normal protocols&#8221; on Wednesday, but Commissioner Melissa McKinlay posted a statement on Twitter saying, “The lowering of flags should be a unifying gesture during solemn occasions, such as in remembrance of the young lives lost during the Parkland High School massacre or first responder line of duty deaths.&#8221; She was referring to the 2018 shooting at Marjory Stoneman Douglas in nearby Parkland that left 17 dead.</p>
<p>McKinlay continued: “Although Rush Limbaugh was a significant public figure, he was also an incredibly divisive one who hurt many people with his words and actions.&#8221;</p>
<p>The governor&#8217;s press office issued a statement late Wednesday saying, “It is unfortunate that Palm Beach County would rather engage in petty politics than honor the death of one of their county’s and state’s most prominent residents and a Presidential Medal of Freedom recipient.”</p>
<p>A year ago, then-President Donald Trump awarded Limbaugh the Presidential Medal of Freedom, the nation’s highest civilian honor, during his final State of the Union address. The day before, Limbaugh had announced that he was battling advanced lung cancer. Limbaugh had for decades championed conservatism — often stridently at the expense of liberals and Democrats.</p>
<p>Officials in the Town of Palm Beach, the wealthy island enclave where Limbaugh lived for two decades, issued a statement saying its policy is to comply with governor&#8217;s orders to lower the flags. Trump also lives in Palm Beach at his Mar-a-Lago club and he and Limbaugh were close friends.</p>
<p>Flags are typically lowered to honor prominent government officials, as well as law enforcement officers and members of the military killed in the line of duty. DeSantis has said Limbaugh’s stature justified the honor.</p>
<p>Limbaugh, 70, died of lung cancer on Feb. 17. DeSantis called Limbaugh a legend during a news conference two days later and indicated he would direct flags to be flown at half-staff to honor him.</p>
<p>But many Democrats objected. Nikki Fried, Florida’s agriculture commissioner and the only statewide Democratic officeholder, said Monday that she would not abide by the Republican governor’s orders. She said she would notify all state officers she oversees to disregard the governor’s order.</p>
<p>St. Petersburg Mayor Rick Kriseman posted on Twitter that his city would not honor hatred, racism, bigotry, homophobia or anything else Limbaugh has spewed over the years.</p>
<p>The governor’s order does not apply to any of the offices controlled by Fried or the city of St. Petersburg.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870467</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Rush-Limbaugh-2-e1614198147823.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c4b0eae8-7497-416f-a07c-e6de508ad953/03912625-6874-4cb2-ab91-d7db88345a90/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217166~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c4b0eae8-7497-416f-a07c-e6de508ad953/03912625-6874-4cb2-ab91-d7db88345a90/main.mp4*~hmac=154e74bc14560a6d6c0cec0080cebda74897439e4c545ebcd96bc1ffa4fe2291' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Rush-Limbaugh-2-e1614198147823.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Rush-Limbaugh-2-e1614198147823.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Rush Limbaugh 2</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Rush Limbaugh&#8217;s home state, a flap over lowering flags</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/in-rush-limbaughs-home-state-a-flap-over-lowering-flags/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 22:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — In life, the conservative radio host Rush Limbaugh was a divisive figure, who proudly waved the flag of conservatism and wallowed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — In life, the conservative radio host Rush Limbaugh was a divisive figure, who proudly waved the flag of conservatism and wallowed in the controversies he helped ignite. In death, those controversies follow him as partisans in his home state of Florida debate over whether to lower flags in his honor.</p>
<p>Gov. Ron DeSantis called Limbaugh a “legend” and ordered flags to be flown at half-staff as a show of respect after the longtime broadcaster, 70, died Wednesday of cancer.</p>
<p>But Democrats, who have long been on the receiving end of Limbaugh&#8217;s harangues, objected.</p>
<p>Nikki Fried, Florida&#8217;s agriculture commissioner and the only statewide Democratic officeholder, said Monday that she would not abide by the Republican governor&#8217;s orders. Fried is considering a bid for governor.</p>
<p>“Lowering to half-staff the flag of the United States of America is a sacred honor that pays respect to fallen heroes and patriots,” she said in a statement. She said she would notify all state officers she oversees to disregard the governor&#8217;s order.</p>
<p>Fried oversees about two dozen agricultural law enforcement inspection stations, more than three dozen state forests and nine regional licensing offices — all of which fly the flags of the United States and Florida.</p>
<p>“My concern is that the governor is bending over backwards to honor a radio host who has consistently made racist, polarizing and conspiracy comments,” Fried said in an interview Monday afternoon.</p>
<p>“It is really inappropriate,” she said of the flag lowering, “and the governor is playing politics with this American treasure, which is our flag.”</p>
<p>A year ago, President Donald Trump awarded Limbaugh the Presidential Medal of Freedom, the nation’s highest civilian honor, during his final State of the Union address.</p>
<p>The day before, Limbaugh had announced that he was battling advanced lung cancer.</p>
<p>Limbaugh had for decades championed conservativism — often stridently at the expense of liberals and Democrats.</p>
<p>Fried was not the only elected official to bemoan the governor&#8217;s decision.</p>
<p>“Not lowering flags for Rush,” the mayor of St. Petersburg, Rick Kriseman, tweeted on Monday. “In St. Pete we don’t honor hatred, racism, bigotry, homophobia, or anything else he has spewed over the years. We are, however, honoring the life of Deputy Michael Magli of the Pinellas County Sheriff’s Office.”</p>
<p>Earlier in the day, DeSantis had ordered flags to fly at half-staff to pay tribute to Magli, who died last week after being struck by a vehicle while on duty in Pinellas County, home to St. Petersburg in the state&#8217;s Tampa Bay region.</p>
<p>The governor’s office declined to elaborate on the state’s protocols for lowering flags.</p>
<p>Flags are typically lowered to honor prominent government officials, as well as law enforcement officers and members of the military killed in the line of duty. However, the governor also has the authority to lower the flags to commemorate tragedies, most recently the third anniversary of the Parkland high school shootings that took the lives of 17 students and staff members.</p>
<p>DeSantis said Limbaugh&#8217;s stature justified the honor.</p>
<p>“When there’s things of this magnitude, once the date of interment for Rush is announced, we’re going to be lowering the flags to half-staff,” DeSantis said at a Friday news conference in Palm Beach County.</p>
<p>“Not much needs to be said,” the governor said. “He was an absolute legend. He was a friend of mine, and just a great person.”</p>
<p>Fried said she would not move to punish any of her managers who might follow her “strong guidance” and instead decide to comply with the governor&#8217;s order.</p>
<p>“If somebody chooses to lower the flag, there are no penalties,” she said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870003</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022321-Rush-Limbaugh.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3f666706-1064-4b97-88e2-0a32c65ce3ad/43766c63-9544-4075-ab55-a46f7fe8cbde/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217134~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3f666706-1064-4b97-88e2-0a32c65ce3ad/43766c63-9544-4075-ab55-a46f7fe8cbde/main.mp4*~hmac=d78aa4592ea4a4f6e711a8e8e50d7dbf34cd35f98d6f9533f2db4dfe5eecf5e7' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022321-Rush-Limbaugh.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022321-Rush-Limbaugh.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022321 Rush Limbaugh</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida deputies find missing 13-year-old girl in hotel room with 22-year-old man she met online</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida-deputies-find-missing-13-year-old-girl-in-hotel-room-with-22-year-old-man-she-met-online/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[EDGEWATER, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; Florida deputies say a 13-year-old girl who went missing was found inside a hotel room with a 22-year-old man she met...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>EDGEWATER, Fla. (WSVN) &#x2014; Florida deputies say a 13-year-old girl who went missing was found inside a hotel room with a 22-year-old man she met online.<p>The Volusia County Sheriff&#x2019;s Office shared deputy body camera video showing the moments leading up to the detention of the man who was found in the room with the girl.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ULochab_Dc0&amp;feature=youtu.be&amp;ab_channel=VolusiaSheriff%27sOffice</embed></div><p>Investigators said they responded to a report of a missing child on Thursday after the girl&#x2019;s grandmother said she never came home and she didn&#x2019;t show up to a basketball game after school.</p><p>The sheriff&#x2019;s office said Deputy Royce James spoke to a friend of the girl who said the victim was planning on going to a motel with someone she met online. The friend said she believed the man&#x2019;s name began with a T and was possibly named Tyler, and that he was from Orlando. She also said the victim may have been picked up at a nearby dollar store.</p><p>Officials said James went to the dollar store to look for security video and found surveillance images of the victim at the store. An employee reported the girl said she was waiting for someone to pick her up.</p><p>Investigators said Deputy James then began searching nearby hotels and upon reaching the third one, learned that a man named Tyler Johnson, with an address listed out of Orlando, had rented a room.</p><p>Deputies went to the man&#x2019;s room where they found the girl inside with the man, officials said.</p><p>Investigators said when Deputy James came into the room, the girl ran and gave him a hug.</p><p>The girl was ultimately taken to a Department of Children and Families facility for evaluation before being taken home.</p><p>Deputies arrested 22-year-old Tyler Thompson. He has been charged with interference of custody and using a computer to lure a child. Additional charges remain pending.</p><p>Thompson was released on $15,000 bond.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869821</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/man-arrested-hotel.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/749c60a3-b796-48ea-af9e-2b76f13871ac/e9617164-74eb-4973-b288-fb9a1982cac2/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216664~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/749c60a3-b796-48ea-af9e-2b76f13871ac/e9617164-74eb-4973-b288-fb9a1982cac2/main.mp4*~hmac=6fced969c3cc5964ca963f2233295261a24b1c83622b1bd5f3021e7427b9165f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/man-arrested-hotel.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/man-arrested-hotel.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">man arrested hotel</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 5K new cases of COVID-19 on Tuesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-over-5k-new-cases-of-covid-19-on-tuesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 19:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869843</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.87 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,213 deaths. As of 2 p.m. Tuesday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.87 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 30,213 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2 p.m. Tuesday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,878,533 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 5,610 from Monday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 148 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 404,499 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 191,065 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 118,151, and 5,721 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 78,212 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869843</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/covid-19-5070656_1920.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid-19 test coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Samaritan returns lost wallet to Florida woman&#8217;s home</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/good-samaritan-returns-lost-wallet-to-florida-womans-home/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 16:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[YULEE, Fla. (AP) — A Florida woman said she was reunited with her lost wallet after a good Samaritan found it at Walmart and returned...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>YULEE, Fla. (AP) — A Florida woman said she was reunited with her lost wallet after a good Samaritan found it at Walmart and returned it to her home.</p>
<p>Debra Glover-Crosby was shopping at the northern Jacksonville store on Saturday when she noticed she had lost her wallet and had to pay with cash, <a href="https://www.firstcoastnews.com/article/news/local/good-samaritan-drives-to-womans-home-to-return-her-wallet-she-lost-at-florida-walmart/77-9ab71b1e-8bfb-4498-9275-cbc580b07e4e" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Coast News</a> reported. As she was returning home, her doorbell security system notified her someone was at her door.</p>
<p>She opened the application on her phone to find a <a href="https://www.facebook.com/debra.glovercrosby/videos/10218059328785933" target="_blank" rel="noopener">video </a>of a man saying he had found her wallet and would place it by the Amazon packages outside her Yulee home, about 10 miles (16 kilometers) from the store.</p>
<p>“Hey Ms. Crosby, I found your wallet at Walmart in River City&#8230;I’m going to put it by the Amazon boxes,&#8221; the man said in the security video.</p>
<p>The wallet was returned with all of its contents, Glover-Crosby said. The good Samaritan didn&#8217;t identify himself.</p>
<p>“I probably would have taken it to customer service,&#8221; Glover-Crosby told First Coast News. &#8220;But he brought it all the way personally to my house. Concealed it&#8230; Gave me a message of where he found it. And I thought that was a lot of above and beyond.&#8221;</p>
<div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text">
<p>&#8220;If he is watching this, I want him to know that he makes me so proud,&#8221; Crosby said. &#8220;I have three sons of my own and I would hope that they do the exact same thing.&#8221;</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869776</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/returned-wallet.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7e3da38e-9d5b-400a-86be-584b0f4da0b5/ecb8f887-cbd5-44c4-a17e-2c60c6e7ddbb/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219876~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7e3da38e-9d5b-400a-86be-584b0f4da0b5/ecb8f887-cbd5-44c4-a17e-2c60c6e7ddbb/main.mp4*~hmac=7dca8556f9008b7f65454aa362097ae053e8c70966a1d75cc0a0660493ed2501' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/returned-wallet.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/returned-wallet.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">returned wallet</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Professional python hunter uses hunting dogs to track down reptiles invading Florida&#8217;s swamps</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/professional-python-hunter-uses-hunting-dogs-to-track-down-reptiles-invading-floridas-swamps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A professional python hunter is using some four-legged helpers to sniff out snakes hiding in Florida&#8217;s swamps. He uses a team of trained dogs to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A professional python hunter is using some four-legged helpers to sniff out snakes hiding in Florida&#8217;s swamps.</p>
<p>He uses a team of trained dogs to hunt invasive species of pythons.</p>
<p>Mike Kimmel is a trapper, snake hunter and conservationist who specializes in capturing invasive species that are running amok in South Florida&#8217;s swamps, including pythons, iguanas and monitors.</p>
<p>Kimmel said that what makes him different from other python hunters is that he uses a pack of trained dogs, particularly his dog Moose.</p>
<p>&#8220;So, me and Moose, we make a great team together. He stays close with me when we&#8217;re hunting pythons, hopefully a little bit in front of me, slowly putting his nose to the ground, working a scent trail, taking me to where he thinks the python is, and when he finds that python he stops, locks in on it, and naturally points at it, kind of like a bird dog. That&#8217;s when I know it&#8217;s time for me to go in, go hands-on with the python and get it out of the ecosystem,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Kimmel said that Moose has shown great success in hunting pythons in the short amount of time he started using him. He said that he&#8217;s been working with Moose to hunt down invasive reptiles since he was a puppy, and he has come to understand the mission to keep them out of Florida&#8217;s wetlands.</p>
<p>However, Kimmel feels that although he and Moose are being successful in removing pythons from swamps, they&#8217;re barely managing the problem because while some of the native wildlife has returned in the areas they&#8217;re focusing on, the python infestation is getting worse everywhere else.</p>
<p>&#8220;To me, I feel using dogs, using new technologies is gonna be a game-changer. These pythons are adapting, and we need to keep adapting with them,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>At the moment, Florida does not allow state-contracted trappers to use dogs in any of its python programs. Kimmel said the state should reconsider because of how effective hunting dogs are.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869424</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022221-python-hunting-dog.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7e05df17-52a1-4028-8f37-51a246706886/6508a163-b518-4760-b054-2a7520e84b2b/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615220039~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7e05df17-52a1-4028-8f37-51a246706886/6508a163-b518-4760-b054-2a7520e84b2b/main.mp4*~hmac=441fc16e404d16b4c6f2d0ddd88301705b85c920dbe39deac67cc79b0f03fdba' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022221-python-hunting-dog.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022221-python-hunting-dog.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022221 python hunting dog</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
