<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:38:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>News &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Good Samaritans help 2 hurt in SW Miami-Dade shooting that left 1 dead; suspect charged</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/good-samaritans-help-2-hurt-in-sw-miami-dade-shooting-that-left-1-dead-suspect-charged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 03:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878085</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Good Samaritans raced to help a woman and an elderly man minutes after, police said, they were shot inside of a Southwest Miami-Dade home during...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Good Samaritans raced to help a woman and an elderly man minutes after, police said, they were <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/search-underway-for-19-year-old-after-shooting-in-sw-miami-dade-leaves-1-dead-2-injured/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">shot inside of a Southwest Miami-Dade home</a> during a domestic dispute that left a man dead and led to the arrest of a 19-year-old suspect.</p>
<p>Ring doorbell video captured area resident Lisa Pelaez and her husband rendering aid to a 74-year-old man moments after he fled the home, in the area of Southwest 142nd Avenue and 294th Street, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;He&#8217;s shooting up the house,&#8221; the man is heard saying in the video.</p>
<p>&#8220;He&#8217;s still there?&#8221; asked Pelaez.</p>
<p>&#8220;Yeah!&#8221; said the man.</p>
<p>According to Miami-Dade Police, Ruben Warren Williams ran away after shooting three of his family members. His cousin, identified as 27-year-old Carlton Tillman, was pronounced dead at the scene.</p>
<p>Detectives said four children were in the home when the shots rang out.</p>
<p>“According to investigators, there was a verbal dispute inside of the residence that escalated and led to shots fired,” said MDPD detective Khristopher Welch.</p>
<p>&#8220;We were so scared,&#8221; said Pelaez.</p>
<p>Investigators said Williams&#8217; grandfather had asked him not to smoke marijuana in the house, and that led to an argument.</p>
<p>Police said Williams became angry and opened fire, striking Tillman, his grandfather and his aunt.</p>
<p>Detectives said the suspect&#8217;s aunt and grandfather jumped from a second-floor window. The grandfather broke both his ankles, and even still, both he and the suspect&#8217;s aunt ran for help.</p>
<p>Pelaez, who lives two doors down, said the older victim headed to her home.</p>
<p>&#8220;The aunt, who jumped out of the second-story building, went this way, and the grandfather went this way to my house,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I opened the door immediately. He said, &#8216;I&#8217;ve been shot. My grandson shot me; he&#8217;s shooting everybody.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Pelaez said she immediately called 911 and tried to treat his wounds.</p>
<p>&#8220;My husband ran and grabbed a towel from our closet, he put the towel on his back, on the gunshot wound,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I ran in the house, and I grabbed a chair, and we sat him down on the chair. The grandfather said, &#8216;My legs broke, my legs broke,&#8217; and I&#8217;m asking the grandfather, &#8216;Where&#8217;s the lady, where&#8217;s the lady?'&#8221;</p>
<p>Surveillance video captured Williams&#8217; aunt as she limped to a nearby home.</p>
<p>&#8220;I picked her up, and I put her to the side of the house to try and hide her body,&#8221; said a resident at this home. &#8220;I didn&#8217;t know where the guy was at the time. In that short instant, the paramedics came, so they were able to take over.&#8221;</p>
<p>Police said <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/19-year-old-arrested-charged-with-murder-in-shooting-that-left-man-dead-2-others-injured/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Williams was arrested Saturday</a> after he hopped into a woman&#8217;s car and forced her to drive for hours at gunpoint.</p>
<p>Investigators said the suspect also shot and killed a neighbor&#8217;s dog during the rampage.</p>
<p>Neighbors said they&#8217;re thankful for Williams&#8217; quick capture.</p>
<p>&#8220;My friends and my family and I are so relieved, you do not understand,&#8221; said Pelaez.</p>
<p>&#8220;At the end of the day, that&#8217;s good. Hopefully the lady survives,&#8221; said the resident who helped Williams&#8217; aunt.</p>
<p>Williams is facing multiple charges, including second-degree murder, aggravated battery with a deadly weapon, child abuse and animal cruelty with intent to injure or kill.</p>
<p>As of Sunday night, police have not identified the surviving victims, who remain at Jackson South Medical Center. Their conditions are currently unknown.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878085</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_SWMD_shooting_male_victim_Ring_surveillance_video.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/76c9e722-dc7c-4c90-ab4d-6e1ddbea0202/5f9d12e6-a63c-4850-97bf-0300463894e4/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219391~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/76c9e722-dc7c-4c90-ab4d-6e1ddbea0202/5f9d12e6-a63c-4850-97bf-0300463894e4/main.mp4*~hmac=16edc3f7dd3e5c445430ebb4ee30d6e19aa4bdd7ebc97c78a0a5226d3cdacc66' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_SWMD_shooting_male_victim_Ring_surveillance_video.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_SWMD_shooting_male_victim_Ring_surveillance_video.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_SWMD_shooting_male_victim_Ring_surveillance_video</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maskless spring breakers spotted in Fort Lauderdale, Miami Beach, raising COVID concerns</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/maskless-spring-breakers-spotted-in-fort-lauderdale-miami-beach-raising-covid-concerns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878088</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Spring breakers spotted without face masks at two popular South Florida destinations have raised concerns that the gatherings could lead to an increase in coronavirus...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Spring breakers spotted without face masks at two popular South Florida destinations have raised concerns that the gatherings could lead to an increase in coronavirus cases.</p>
<p>This weekend brought <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/local-leaders-urge-spring-breakers-to-social-distance-wear-masks-as-crowds-grow/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more large crowds</a> to Fort Lauderdale Beach. 7News cameras captured many revelers not wearing masks or following COVID protocols.</p>
<p>More maskless beachgoers were spotted Sunday in Miami Beach.</p>
<p>That city&#8217;s leaders are hoping to keep things calm by <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-beach-fort-lauderdale-implement-rules-and-safety-guidelines-as-spring-break-begins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">closing beaches</a> at 7 p.m. and ordering businesses along the beach to shut down by midnight.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878088</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_maskless_spring_breakers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d0310398-38e0-4f48-b1a3-528cfb5e6b9b/2be62b9e-2a35-4fd2-ad44-fb83e6c8a172/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217761~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d0310398-38e0-4f48-b1a3-528cfb5e6b9b/2be62b9e-2a35-4fd2-ad44-fb83e6c8a172/main.mp4*~hmac=4c828b9aee35dd86511ad5ed8afc5ecc3f0949f0599ad4094f0956ebcc70ec54' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_maskless_spring_breakers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_maskless_spring_breakers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_maskless_spring_breakers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 166,000 hens die in Arizona farm fire</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/over-166000-hens-die-in-arizona-farm-fire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 01:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Over 166,000 laying hens died on Saturday after a fire broke out at a bird warehouse in Arizona. Flames engulfed three massive warehouses...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Over 166,000 laying hens died on Saturday after a fire broke out at a bird warehouse in Arizona.</p>
<p>Flames engulfed three massive warehouses containing chickens and hens at Hickman&#8217;s Family Farms in Arlington, about 50 miles west of Phoenix, according to the Maricopa County Sheriff&#8217;s Office (MCSO).</p>
<p>The fire broke out when a piece of equipment malfunctioned and caught fire, Hickman&#8217;s Family Farms spokesperson Sharman Hickman told CNN.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re just trying to get back to business,&#8221; Hickman said. &#8220;We&#8217;re still mourning the loss of all those chickens and hens.&#8221;</p>
<p>There is no indication of foul play, said Sgt. Joaquin Enriquez of the MCSO.</p>
<p>Farm employees reported a fire at one of their bird warehouses around 1 p.m. But by the time first responders arrived at the scene two more warehouses had caught fire.</p>
<p>One adult was transported to a local hospital for smoke inhalation and is in stable condition, Buckeye Valley Fire District spokesperson Sarah Mendoza told CNN.</p>
<p>Hickman&#8217;s Family Farms has been in business for over 70 years, and the farm has been run by the same family for four generations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878034</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/192e3189-b603-40bb-97e4-1fdbc2a60a8f/708a617f-e81c-4cf1-942a-b057c1cd1040/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216599~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/192e3189-b603-40bb-97e4-1fdbc2a60a8f/708a617f-e81c-4cf1-942a-b057c1cd1040/main.mp4*~hmac=c6bc1c915d725f3191972c845c55839078c08b3b6735fefda9d8497b14aa5dc0' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian disinformation campaign working to undermine confidence in COVID-19 vaccines used in US</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/russian-disinformation-campaign-working-to-undermine-confidence-in-covid-19-vaccines-used-in-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 01:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878015</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Online platforms directed by Russian intelligence are spreading disinformation about two of the coronavirus vaccines being used in the US, a State Department spokesperson confirmed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Online platforms directed by Russian intelligence are spreading disinformation about two of the coronavirus vaccines being used in the US, a State Department spokesperson confirmed to CNN on Sunday.</p>
<p>The agency&#8217;s Global Engagement Center identified three Russian outlets &#8212; News Front, New Eastern Outlook and Oriental Review &#8212; that are spreading not only misinformation about the virus, but also regarding &#8220;international organizations, military conflicts, protests; and any divisive issue that they can exploit,&#8221; according to the spokesperson.</p>
<p>&#8220;These sites all vary in their reach, tone, and audience &#8212; but they all are spreading Russian propaganda and disinformation. The State Department&#8217;s finding of a link between these sites and Russian Intelligence is a result of a joint interagency conclusion,&#8221; the spokesperson said.</p>
<p>The GEC leads efforts &#8220;to recognize, understand, expose, and counter foreign state and non-state propaganda and disinformation efforts aimed at undermining or influencing the policies, security, or stability of the United States, its allies, and partner nations,&#8221; according to its website.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/russian-disinformation-campaign-aims-to-undermine-confidence-in-pfizer-other-covid-19-vaccines-u-s-officials-say-11615129200" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Wall Street Journal </a>first reported on the disinformation.</p>
<p>The campaign comes as the US and other countries race to vaccinate people using three vaccines developed in record time by the drug makers Pfizer/BioNTech, Moderna and Johnson &amp; Johnson. US officials have been working to increase confidence in the drugs in recent months as studies showed a concerning level of vaccine hesitancy among some people, though that has decreased as the rollout has progressed.</p>
<p>A spokesman for the Kremlin denied to the Journal that the country&#8217;s intelligence services were spearheading the disinformation campaign.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s nonsense. Russian special services have nothing to do with any criticism against vaccines,&#8221; the spokesman, Dmitry Peskov, told the newspaper.</p>
<p>The Journal reported that, &#8220;Russian state media and Russian government Twitter accounts have made overt efforts to raise concerns about the cost and safety of the Pfizer vaccine in what experts outside the US government say is an effort to promote the sale of Russia&#8217;s rival Sputnik V vaccine.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;The emphasis on denigrating Pfizer is likely due to its status as the first vaccine besides Sputnik V to see mass use, resulting in a greater potential threat to Sputnik&#8217;s market dominance,&#8221; a forthcoming report by the Alliance for Securing Democracy says, according to the Journal.</p>
<p>One outlet in the disinformation campaign, News Front, used international reports to play &#8220;up the risk that a person who receives the Pfizer or Moderna Inc. vaccines could contract Bell&#8217;s palsy, in which facial muscles are paralyzed,&#8221; according to the Journal, which noted that while a small number of side effects have been reported by vaccine recipients, the shots are overwhelmingly safe and effective.</p>
<p>Pamela Eisele, a spokeswoman for Pfizer, told the newspaper that so far, &#8220;millions of people have been vaccinated with our vaccine following the endorsement of regulators in multiple countries.&#8221;</p>
<p>A spokeswoman for Moderna didn&#8217;t immediately respond to the Journal&#8217;s request for comment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878015</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Floyd&#8217;s cause of death, ex-cop&#8217;s force will be keys at trial</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/floyds-cause-of-death-ex-cops-force-will-be-keys-at-trial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877997</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis police officer was swiftly fired and charged with murder after bystander video showed him pressing his knee into George Floyd&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis police officer was swiftly fired and charged with murder after bystander video showed him pressing his knee into George Floyd&#8217;s neck, ignoring the Black man&#8217;s cries that he couldn&#8217;t breathe. But even with that powerful footage, legal experts say the case isn&#8217;t a slam dunk.</p>
<p>Jury selection begins Monday in Derek Chauvin&#8217;s trial, which is expected to come down to two key questions: Did Chauvin&#8217;s actions cause Floyd&#8217;s death, and were his actions reasonable?</p>
<p>“It’s hard not to watch the video and conclude that the prosecutors will not have any trouble with this case,” said Susan Gaertner, the former head prosecutor in neighboring Ramsey County. “But it’s not that simple.”</p>
<p>Floyd was declared dead May 25 after Chauvin, who is white, pressed his knee against Floyd’s neck <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/prosecutors-officer-was-on-floyds-neck-for-about-9-minutes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">for about nine minutes</a>, holding his position even after Floyd went limp as he was handcuffed and lying on his stomach. Floyd’s death sparked sometimes violent protests in Minneapolis and beyond, and led to a nationwide reckoning on race.</p>
<p>Chauvin is charged with second-degree unintentional murder and second-degree manslaughter, and a panel of appeals court judges ruled Friday that the judge must consider reinstating a third-degree murder charge that he dismissed last fall. Three other officers, all of whom also were fired, face trial in August on charges of aiding and abetting the second-degree murder and manslaughter counts.</p>
<p>The second-degree murder charge requires prosecutors to prove Chauvin caused Floyd&#8217;s death while committing or trying to commit a felony — in this case, third-degree assault. The manslaughter charge has a lower bar, requiring proof that Chauvin caused Floyd&#8217;s death through negligence that created an unreasonable risk, and consciously took the chance of causing severe injury or death.</p>
<p>Exactly how Floyd died is shaping up as a major flashpoint of the trial.</p>
<p>Chauvin&#8217;s attorney, Eric Nelson, argues in court documents that Floyd likely died from fentanyl he consumed, or a combination of fentanyl, methamphetamine and underlying health conditions — not as a result of Chauvin&#8217;s knee on his neck.</p>
<p>But Hennepin County Judge Peter Cahill wrote last fall that for the second-degree murder charge, prosecutors don&#8217;t have to prove that Chauvin was the sole cause of Floyd&#8217;s death — only that his conduct was a “substantial causal factor.”</p>
<p>Still, defense attorneys who aren&#8217;t connected to the case say all Nelson has to do is raise reasonable doubt in a single juror&#8217;s mind.</p>
<p>“Although he had him pinned under his knee and he’s yelling ‘I can’t breathe! I can’t breathe!’ there’s an argument that (Chauvin) wasn’t exerting pressure and his inability to breathe was due to the drugs in his system or something to that effect, or his anxiety,” said F. Clayton Tyler, a prominent local defense attorney.</p>
<p>Defense attorneys say it also may not be easy to establish that Chauvin was committing the felony of assault — as required for the second-degree murder charge in this case. That&#8217;s because Chauvin is authorized to use force as a police officer, and his attorneys will argue that his use of force against Floyd was reasonable.</p>
<p>Gaertner said the defense will face a challenge of trying to move the jury’s focus off of the video and the strong emotion it generates. They&#8217;ll instead try to focus on the medical evidence and Floyd’s underlying conditions while trying to portray the circumstances of the arrest as “justifiable consistent with police norms,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Brandt and Tyler said Chauvin will likely have to take the stand to explain why he felt he had to hold Floyd down for so long. Brandt said he’ll likely say he followed his training, and that it was necessary because his experience with other suspects under the influence of drugs shows that things can suddenly become erratic and dangerous.</p>
<p>Prosecutors, however, have submitted a list of previous instances in which Chauvin used chokeholds or similar restraints on the job. Cahill ruled they can admit only one as evidence: a 2017 arrest in which Chauvin restrained a female by placing his knee on her neck while she was prone on the ground.</p>
<p>Cahill also ruled that prosecutors can tell jurors about a 2015 incident in which Chauvin saw other officers place a suicidal, intoxicated male in a side-recovery position after using a stun gun on him. Cahill said prosecutors can introduce that if they can show Chauvin was present when a medical professional said that the male could have died if officers had prolonged the detention.</p>
<p>Brandt said telling the jury about those events will allow prosecutors to show that Chauvin knew the proper way to restrain someone and provide relief, and that he had done it wrong before.</p>
<p>Brandt said the third-degree murder charge could be easier for prosecutors to prove if it&#8217;s reinstated because they wouldn&#8217;t have to show Chauvin intended to commit assault. Instead, they must prove his actions caused Floyd&#8217;s death, and that they were reckless and without regard for human life.</p>
<p>The second-degree manslaughter count alleges Chauvin took a risk that a reasonable person would have known could cause death. To defend against that, Brandt said, Chauvin could argue that he had used the same hold in the past and didn&#8217;t think it would cause a problem.</p>
<p>However, Brandt said “the whole case” against Chauvin is the video capturing the amount of time he restrained Floyd.</p>
<p>“You hear on the video the passersby, the onlookers saying, ‘Dude, he can’t breathe. Let him up. What are you doing? You are killing him,’” Brandt said. “I mean, it’s almost like they are giving a play-by-play.”</p>
<p>Tyler said if he were a prosecutor, he’d use a still shot of Chauvin’s expressionless face from that video and keep it in view for the jury to see.</p>
<p>“I mean, the look on his face,” Tyler said. “If I was prosecuting this case, I have to say, I’d have that picture up there. You want to show indifference? Just look at him.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877997</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Chauvin_Floyd.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/812320ba-7b39-4d87-9d03-61bf4e9e286e/a2aa5109-fcd6-4826-a8f2-436b2fe8f6b3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218149~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/812320ba-7b39-4d87-9d03-61bf4e9e286e/a2aa5109-fcd6-4826-a8f2-436b2fe8f6b3/main.mp4*~hmac=51392e00d99577f9bcc5a3941bbf1c06d3a51f7ce330b9bdd539d63d79dc13fd' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Chauvin_Floyd.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Chauvin_Floyd.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Chauvin_Floyd</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Authorities to seek charges after violent Boulder party that left 3 officers injured</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/authorities-to-seek-charges-after-violent-boulder-party-that-left-3-officers-injured/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; Authorities promised Sunday to pursue criminal charges after a massive party near the University of Colorado in Boulder devolved into a violent confrontation...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; Authorities promised Sunday to pursue criminal charges after a massive party near the University of Colorado in Boulder devolved into a violent confrontation with police that left three officers injured.</p>
<p>Hundreds of people flooded the streets in an area known as the Hill on Saturday night and when told to leave threw bottles, rocks and other objects at police and firefighters, police said.</p>
<p>At least one car was damaged when the mob flipped it over, and police brought in a SWAT team and used tear gas to break up the crowd that numbered 500 to 800 people at its peak, said Boulder Police Chief Maris Herold.</p>
<p>Images shared by local media showed no social distancing and most without masks despite the coronavirus pandemic. Fireworks were set off in the middle of the street and a law enforcement armored vehicle and a fire truck were damaged, according to police and local media.</p>
<p>At one point Herold said a “tactical decision” was made to withdraw some officers when a group of about 100 people started to rush them. It took more than three hours to disperse the crowd, according to a timeline she provided.</p>
<p>Boulder County District Attorney Michael Dougherty described the rowdy behavior amid the coronavirus pandemic as “shameful.”</p>
<p>“I hear people refer to it as a party. I don&#8217;t regard flipping over a car as a party and I don&#8217;t regard people who throw bottles and rocks at firefighters and police as a party,” he said. “Those are criminal acts and will be treated as such.”</p>
<p>No arrests were made at the scene, police said.</p>
<p>Officers were reviewing officer body camera footage and shared social media videos and photos to identify the individuals involved. They also set up a <a href="https://bouldercopd.evidence.com/axon/citizen/public/hill-disturbance">portal </a>on the city&#8217;s website to allow the public to submit additional video footage or other evidence from the disturbance.</p>
<p>Herold said it was a calculated call not to make any arrests immediately, out of worry that sending in officers would agitate the large crowd. She added that the department had “excellent” video to help it pursue those responsible for the violence.</p>
<p>The three injured officers were recovering, including one who was struck in the hand and another who was hit in the face but was wearing a gas mask, Herold said. City vehicles suffered thousands of dollars in damages and private property also was harmed, she said.</p>
<p>The Hill neighborhood has been known for decades for sometimes raucous parties and there have been previous confrontations that resulted in violence, including 12 officers injured in a 1997 riot near the school.</p>
<p>But city officials said during a Sunday press conference that the stakes from Saturday&#8217;s events are particularly high amid the pandemic, with potentially dire consequences. Health officials advised anyone who participated to quarantine for at least 10 days and to get tested for COVID-19.</p>
<p>CU Boulder students returned to campus for hybrid and in-person learning in mid-February.</p>
<p>University officials apologized to Boulder residents who live near the school and said students who were involved in violence, property damage or failing to disperse would be held accountable.</p>
<p>“If they can&#8217;t meet our expectation, they are not welcome at the university,” said CU Boulder Chief Operating Officer Patrick O&#8217;Rourke. He added that the university knows its students were involved and “We are not going to try to shift the blame.”</p>
<p>After the party broke up, other students came to the scene with garbage bags to pick up the large amounts of trash left behind.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877987</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f0ac3c7d-d4b9-475c-87ab-57cf56beeb48/b938ccf4-2b96-4ebb-bd50-79e12e68fa1e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216973~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f0ac3c7d-d4b9-475c-87ab-57cf56beeb48/b938ccf4-2b96-4ebb-bd50-79e12e68fa1e/main.mp4*~hmac=d7fb1ac3dfc0b05f751a8b927c5081729880641d35fd78cce67b47200e8e3b97' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime Stoppers: Reward raised to $12K for information in fatal shooting of 6-year-old in Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/crime-stoppers-reward-raised-to-12k-for-information-in-fatal-shooting-of-6-year-old-in-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 23:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877966</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The reward for information leading to an arrest in the fatal drive-by shooting of a 6-year-old girl in a Miami neighborhood has been raised to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The reward for information leading to an arrest in the <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/family-6-year-old-girl-dies-after-shooting-in-miami-victim-mourned-at-memorials/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fatal drive-by shooting</a> of a 6-year-old girl in a Miami neighborhood has been raised to $12,000.<p>Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers confirmed the increase in a tweet posted late Sunday afternoon.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/CrimeStopper305/status/1368696075847139336?s=20</embed></div><p>According to City of Miami Police, Chassidy Saunders was attending another child&#x2019;s birthday party on Northwest Sixth Place, near 54th Street, when the gunman or gunmen opened fire into the crowd of women and children, Jan. 16.</p><p>Paramedics rushed Saunders to Ryder Trauma Center, where she succumbed to her injuries.</p><p>Two other people, both adults, were also shot, but they survived.</p><p>The girl&#x2019;s death prompted <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade-county-leaders-community-members-call-for-change-amid-rise-in-gun-violence/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">calls for change</a> to what local leaders called a &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;gun violence epidemic&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; in Miami-Dade County.</p><p>If you have any information on this fatal shooting, contact City of Miami Police or Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a reward of up to $12,000.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877966</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/Chassidy-Saunders.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/54db214f-f397-41e4-b7b9-44196130d07c/132e53f0-64e8-4b9c-962d-86a60d081036/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217695~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/54db214f-f397-41e4-b7b9-44196130d07c/132e53f0-64e8-4b9c-962d-86a60d081036/main.mp4*~hmac=62b877ec2528e169539b00eaa1129f5dc8ced8ed3a583341981210bb328d75e1' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/Chassidy-Saunders.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/Chassidy-Saunders.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Chassidy Saunders</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cuomo defiant as top New York lawmakers call on him to quit</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/cuomo-defiant-as-top-new-york-lawmakers-call-on-him-to-quit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 22:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877956</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — The two top Democrats in New York’s legislature withdrew their support for Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Sunday amid mounting allegations of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — The two top Democrats in New York’s legislature withdrew their support for Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Sunday amid mounting allegations of sexual harassment and undercounting COVID-19 deaths in nursing homes.</p>
<p>Senate Majority Leader Andrea Stewart-Cousins became the first senior Democrat in the state to say the three-term governor should resign. Assembly Speaker Carl Heastie stopped short of demanding that Cuomo quit, but said in a statement that “it is time for the Governor to seriously consider whether he can effectively meet the needs of the people of New York.”</p>
<p>On Saturday, two more women who worked for Cuomo publicly accused him of inappropriate behavior, on the heels of other allegations in recent weeks.</p>
<p>“Every day there is another account that is drawing away from the business of government,” Stewart-Cousins said in a statement. “New York is still in the midst of this pandemic and is still facing the societal, health and economic impacts of it. We need to govern without daily distraction. For the good of the state Governor Cuomo must resign.”</p>
<p>Her public push for his resignation came shortly after a Sunday press conference where Cuomo said it would be “anti-democratic” for him to step down.</p>
<p>“There is no way I resign,” Cuomo told reporters.</p>
<p>“They don’t override the people&#8217;s will, they don’t get to override elections,&#8221; he said. &#8220;I was elected by the people of New York state. I wasn’t elected by politicians.”</p>
<p>In a brief phone conversation Sunday prior to the press conference, Cuomo told Stewart-Cousins he wouldn’t quit and they would have to impeach him if they wanted him out of office, according to a person who was briefed by someone on the call. The person spoke to The Associated Press on condition of anonymity because the call was intended to be private.</p>
<p>Cuomo said the next six months will determine how successfully New York emerges from the coronavirus pandemic. “I’m not going to be distracted because there is too much to do for the people,” he said, noting that the state must pass a budget within three weeks and administer 15 million more COVID-19 vaccines.</p>
<p>Support for Cuomo has eroded with surprising speed as he&#8217;s faced twin scandals, one over his treatment of women in the workplace, and a second over his administration&#8217;s months-long refusal to release complete statistics on COVID-19 deaths in nursing homes.</p>
<p>Some lawmakers have been infuriated by revelations that Cuomo&#8217;s administration delayed releasing some data about deaths of nursing home patients in hospitals, at least partly because of concerns it could be used against them by President Donald Trump&#8217;s administration.</p>
<p>Several women have publicly told of feeling sexually harassed, or at least made to feel demeaned and uncomfortable. The state’s attorney general is investigating. Cuomo has urged people to wait for that investigation to conclude before they judge him.</p>
<p>Others who have called for Cuomo&#8217;s resignation include U.S. Rep. Kathleen Rice, a Long Island Democrat.</p>
<p>Former adviser Lindsey Boylan, 36, said Cuomo made inappropriate comments on her appearance, joked about playing strip poker and once kissed her on the lips at the end of a meeting. Former aide, 25-year-old Charlotte Bennett, said Cuomo asked if she ever had sex with older men and made other comments she interpreted as gauging her interest in an affair.</p>
<p>Another former aide, Ana Liss, told The Wall Street Journal in a story published Saturday that when she worked as a policy aide to the governor between 2013 and 2015, Cuomo called her “sweetheart,” kissed her hand and asked personal questions including whether she had a boyfriend.</p>
<p>Asked about Liss&#8217; story at his news conference Sunday, Cuomo said such talk was “my way of doing friendly banter.”</p>
<p>Echoing comments he made in a news conference last week, Cuomo acknowledged he’d made jokes and asked personal questions in an attempt to be collegial and frequently greeted people with hugs and kisses.</p>
<p>“I never meant to make anyone feel any uncomfortable,&#8221; he said. Cuomo has denied touching anyone inappropriately.</p>
<p>While Cuomo has been apologetic in recent days over his behavior, at least tacitly acknowledging that some of the things women have said are true, he&#8217;s also singled out a few accusations as flatly false.</p>
<p>On Sunday he disputed a story told by about him by Karen Hinton, a former press aide to Cuomo when he served as the federal housing secretary under President Bill Clinton.</p>
<p>In a story published Saturday in The Washington Post, Hinton detailed an uncomfortable hotel room interaction she had with Cuomo when the two met in California years ago as they were trying to patch things up after an estrangement.</p>
<p>Hinton said that as she got up to leave, Cuomo gave her a hug that was “very long, too long, too tight, too intimate.”</p>
<p>She described the encounter not as sexual harassment but as a “power play” for “manipulation and control.” She was no longer an aide to Cuomo at the time.</p>
<p>Asked Sunday about Hinton’s account Cuomo said it was “not true” and noted that the two had been longtime political adversaries.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877956</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/andrew-cuomo--e1588004907181.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/427b8fa8-7008-4398-95bd-5163d4147f4f/ae3442a0-d2a9-40fa-9d02-df8993c220b4/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218045~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/427b8fa8-7008-4398-95bd-5163d4147f4f/ae3442a0-d2a9-40fa-9d02-df8993c220b4/main.mp4*~hmac=4e0e303a6350123a8ea9ddcb8ca5b76d68b644dfd488b19d80800549367dd2d9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/andrew-cuomo--e1588004907181.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/andrew-cuomo--e1588004907181.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Andrew Cuomo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk lost $27 billion last week</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/elon-musk-lost-27-billion-last-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 22:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Elon Musk&#8217;s net worth plunged last week as tech stocks got hammered and Tesla shares&#8217; stunning rise quickly unraveled. Wall Street is growing increasingly nervous...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Elon Musk&#8217;s <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/investing/elon-musk-pay-wealth-tesla-stock-options/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">net worth</a> plunged last week as tech stocks got hammered and Tesla shares&#8217; stunning rise quickly unraveled.</p>
<p>Wall Street is growing increasingly nervous about rising bond yields, which could make borrowing more expensive. That could eat into corporate profits, which is why investors have begun to reverse some of the positions they took over the past year in high-growth but risky tech stocks like Tesla.</p>
<p>Tesla&#8217;s stock fell 11.5% last week. Musk, who owns nearly 18% of Tesla&#8217;s shares, bore most of the brunt of that massive sell-off.</p>
<p>Musk&#8217;s wealth fell by $27 billion last week, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/billionaires/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg&#8217;s Billionaires Index</a>. The decline in his net value is roughly equal to the entire fortune held by Dyson founder James Dyson &#8212; the 52nd richest person in the world, according to Bloomberg.</p>
<p>Musk and Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos have been swapping places atop Bloomberg&#8217;s list of richest people in the world since January. But Musk now sits in a distant second place: $157 billion, compared to Bezos&#8217; net worth of $177 billion. Musk remains $21 billion ahead of Microsoft founder Bill Gates, who remains the third-richest person on the planet.</p>
<p>Tesla&#8217;s stock gained 743% in 2020, propelling it to No. 5 on the list of most valuable companies on the stock market. After losing 15% this year, Tesla&#8217;s stock has since fallen to No. 7, behind Facebook and Berkshire Hathaway but ahead of JPMorgan Chase.</p>
<p>Even if Tesla&#8217;s stock continues to sink, Musk still stands to become much richer in 2021 and beyond.</p>
<p>He received four grants to buy 8.4 million Tesla shares in 2020. Each of those was worth $5 billion at Friday&#8217;s closing price, although some of that will be shaved off because Musk will have to pay the exercise price. Musk will probably receive three additional options grants this year, each as large and as lucrative as those he received in 2020.</p>
<p>Musk has not exercised any of his options. Executives typically exercise them when they are due to expire, or to free up cash. Musk has never sold Tesla shares.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877948</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Elon_Musk.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Elon_Musk.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Elon_Musk.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Elon_Musk</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>19-year-old arrested, charged with murder in shooting that left man dead, 2 others injured</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/19-year-old-arrested-charged-with-murder-in-shooting-that-left-man-dead-2-others-injured/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 22:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Police have arrested a 19-year-old man in connection to a shooting at a Southwest Miami-Dade home that left a man dead and sent a woman...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Police have arrested a 19-year-old man in connection to a <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/search-underway-for-19-year-old-after-shooting-in-sw-miami-dade-leaves-1-dead-2-injured/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">shooting at a Southwest Miami-Dade home</a> that left a man dead and sent a woman and an elderly man to the hospital.</p>
<p>According to Miami-Dade Police, Ruben Warren Williams opened fire during an argument at a home in the area of Southwest 142nd Avenue and 294th Street, just after 11:15 a.m., Saturday.</p>
<p>Police and fire rescue crews responded to the neighborhood to find three victims suffering from gunshot wounds. One of them, later identified as 27-year-old Carlton Tillman, was pronounced dead.</p>
<p>Police said the two other victims, a 74-year-old man and a woman, jumped from a second-story window and ran to area homes where good Samaritans rendered aid before crews arrived and took over.</p>
<p>Paramedics airlifted the surviving victims to Jackson South Medical Center in critical condition.</p>
<p>Officials said two firearms were recovered at the scene.</p>
<p>Police took Williams into custody late Saturday night. He is facing multiple charges, including second-degree murder, aggravated battery with a deadly weapon, child abuse and animal cruelty with intent to injure or kill.</p>
<p>As of Sunday afternoon, police have not identified the surviving victims.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877941</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Ruben_Williams_mugshot.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Ruben_Williams_mugshot.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Ruben_Williams_mugshot.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Ruben_Williams_mugshot</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports nearly 4,100 cases of COVID-19 on Sunday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/fdoh-reports-nearly-4100-cases-of-covid-19-on-sunday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877929</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(WSVN) &#8211; There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,683 deaths. As of 4 p.m. Sunday,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(WSVN) &#8211; There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,683 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 4 p.m. Sunday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,944,995 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 4,098 from Saturday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 63 deaths.</p>
<p>There are now 419,479 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County (5.33% positivity) and 199,643 total cases in Broward (6.99% positivity).</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 123,304, and 5,986 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,954 hospital admissions statewide. To date, 3,462,520 people in the state have been vaccinated.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877929</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus-1.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vaccine site in Florida City overrun after false rumors said all could come</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/vaccine-site-in-florida-city-overrun-after-false-rumors-said-all-could-come/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FLORIDA CITY, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; A South Florida vaccination site had so few eligible takers Saturday that it started inoculating any adult who wanted a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FLORIDA CITY, Fla. (AP/WSVN) &#8212; A South Florida vaccination site had so few eligible takers Saturday that it started inoculating any adult who wanted a shot rather than let the vaccine on hand go to waste.</p>
<p>Word spread, and on Sunday, the Florida City site was overwhelmed, particularly after local state Sen. Annette Taddeo incorrectly tweeted that the federally run site would again take all comers. The Democrat, who was the party&#8217;s lieutenant governor candidate in 2014, later deleted that tweet and corrected herself.</p>
<p>Frustration and confusion set in among the hundreds of people who came to the site run by the Federal Emergency Management Agency.</p>
<p>Among those were Kathy Benezra.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m quite upset. They changed the rules in the morning,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Police had to calm the crowd when the site again enforced the state&#8217;s eligibility rules: 65 and older; frontline medical workers and police officers, teachers and firefighters over 50; and younger people with a physician&#8217;s note saying they would be endangered if they caught the virus.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article249760473.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the Miami Herald</a>, a Florida City police officer through a megaphone told 200 people waiting in line, “If you do not meet the criteria, you will not be vaccinated today.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;A lot of people went away once they heard the criteria, but [the line] was all the way around the block,&#8221; said Benezra.</p>
<p>Benezra said she got there at around 7 a.m. because she heard the site was giving vaccinations to anyone over the age of 18 who wanted one.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve been here, and now the rules have changed,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The confusion appeared to stem from what happened on Saturday.</p>
<p>Vaccines must be refrigerated at extremely cold temperatures and used that day once they are removed. Rather than letting doses go to waste, workers on Saturday reportedly began giving them out to any adult regardless of profession or medical history.</p>
<p>That is not unusual &#8211; many drugstores, for example, will inject anyone in the store at closing time if they have leftover vaccines that would spoil otherwise.</p>
<p>Word of what reportedly happened at the Florida City site quickly spread online, and people came from miles to the small town on the Florida peninsula&#8217;s southern tip to get their shots.</p>
<p>The FEMA-run site administers 500 doses per day.</p>
<p>Mike Jachles with the Florida Association of Public Information Officers issued a statement that reads in part, &#8220;The FEMA-supported sites are adhering to the governor&#8217;s most recent executive order.&#8221;</p>
<p>Many who met the eligibility requirements received their vaccine doses at the larger FEMA-run site at Miami-Dade College&#8217;s North Campus.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was very easy, and I&#8217;m very happy to live in this country,&#8221; said patient Magda Caceres..</p>
<p>&#8220;Super quick, super easy,&#8221; said patient Viviane Carneiro.</p>
<p>Schoolteachers and school employees of all ages are also eligible at FEMA-supported sites.</p>
<p>&#8220;Once the governor opened it up to teachers, I&#8217;m like, &#8216;I&#8217;m out here as soon as I can,'&#8221; said Angel Beswick.</p>
<p>For her, the MDC site was the happiest place on Earth.</p>
<p>&#8220;It feels like I&#8217;m at Disney World, honestly. I&#8217;m so excited,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>As the race to vaccinate continues, Miami-Dade County Mayor Daniella Levine Cava urged the governor to <a href="https://twitter.com/MayorDaniella/status/1368636288170139648?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expand eligibility requirements</a>.</p>
<p>Sunday night, state officials reported 3,878 vaccinations at the three FEMA-run sites in South Florida. Of these inoculations, 3,160 took place at the MDC North Campus site, 321 at the Florida City site and 397 at the site located in Sweetwater.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign, <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health’s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877886</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e6a6b095-305e-4268-b30e-f3dce3a92d40/31a5600a-64fd-42f4-8840-39600067b2d1/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219472~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e6a6b095-305e-4268-b30e-f3dce3a92d40/31a5600a-64fd-42f4-8840-39600067b2d1/main.mp4*~hmac=cc47177d472206de319fcbc2d73936f4d27701f0d4ff731e89a2c52f37b30133' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Florida_City_COVID_vaccination_site_line</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>GOP pushes bills to allow social media &#8216;censorship&#8217; lawsuits</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/gop-pushes-bills-to-allow-social-media-censorship-lawsuits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877852</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) — Republican state lawmakers are pushing for social media giants to face costly lawsuits for policing content on their websites, taking aim at a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) — Republican state lawmakers are pushing for social media giants to face costly lawsuits for policing content on their websites, taking aim at a federal law that prevents internet companies from being sued for removing posts.</p>
<p>GOP politicians in roughly two dozen states have introduced bills that would allow for civil lawsuits against platforms for what they call the “censorship” of posts. Many protest the deletion of political and religious statements, according to the National Conference of State Legislatures. Democrats, who also have called for greater scrutiny of big tech, are sponsoring the same measures in at least two states.</p>
<p>The federal liability shield has long been a target of former President Donald Trump and other Republicans, whose complaints about Silicon Valley stifling conservative viewpoints were amplified when the companies cracked down on misleading posts about the 2020 election.</p>
<p>Twitter and Facebook, which are often criticized for opaque policing policies, took the additional step of silencing Trump on their platforms after the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol. Twitter has banned him, while a semi-independent panel is reviewing Facebook&#8217;s indefinite suspension of his account and considering whether to reinstate access.</p>
<p>Experts argue the legislative proposals are doomed to fail while the federal law, <a href="https://apnews.com/article/d3e09c4037e2fc17558492b9bdce1ecc">Section 230</a> of the Communications Decency Act, is in place. They said state lawmakers are wading into unconstitutional territory by trying to interfere with the editorial policies of private companies.</p>
<p>Len Niehoff, a professor at the University of Michigan Law School, described the idea as a “constitutional non-starter.”</p>
<p>“If an online platform wants to have a policy that it will delete certain kinds of tweets, delete certain kinds of users, forbid certain kinds of content, that is in the exercise of their right as an information distributer,&#8221; he said. “And the idea that you would create a cause of action that would allow people to sue when that happens is deeply problematic under the First Amendment.”</p>
<p>The bills vary slightly but many allow for civil lawsuits if a social media user is censored over posts having to do with politics or religion, with some proposals allowing for damages of $75,000 for each blocked post. They would apply to companies with millions of users and carve out exemptions for posts that call for violence, entice criminal acts or other similar conduct.</p>
<p>The sponsor of Oklahoma&#8217;s version, Republican state Sen. Rob Standridge, said social media posts are being unjustly censored and that people should have a way to challenge the platforms&#8217; actions given their powerful place in American discourse. His bill passed committee in late February on a 5-3 vote, with Democrats opposed.</p>
<p>“This just gives citizens recourse,” he said, adding that the companies “can&#8217;t abuse that immunity” given to them through federal law.</p>
<p>Part of a broad, 1996 federal law on telecoms, <a href="https://uscode.house.gov/view.xhtml?req=(title:47%20section:230%20edition:prelim)">Section 230</a> generally exempts internet companies from being sued over what users post on their sites. The statute, which was meant to promote the growth of the internet, exempts websites from being sued for removing content deemed to be “obscene, lewd, lascivious, filthy, excessively violent, harassing, or otherwise objectionable&#8221; as long as the companies are acting in “good faith.”</p>
<p>As the power of social media has grown, so has the prospect of government regulation. Several congressional hearings have been held on content moderation, sometimes with Silicon Valley CEOs called to testify. Republicans, and some Democrats, have argued that the companies should lose their liability shield or that Section 230 should be updated to make the companies meet certain criteria before receiving legal protection.</p>
<p>Twitter and Facebook also have been hounded over what critics have described as sluggish, after-the-fact account suspensions or post takedowns, with liberals complaining they have given too much latitude to conservatives and hate groups.</p>
<p>Trump railed against Section 230 throughout his term in office, well before Twitter and Facebook blocked his access to their platforms after the assault on the Capitol. Last May, he signed a largely symbolic <a href="https://apnews.com/article/fc30f9ebdff9d3d33a870e7374f8ffa6">executive order</a> that directed the executive branch to ask independent rule-making agencies whether new regulations could be placed on the companies.</p>
<p>“All of these tech monopolies are going to abuse their power and interfere in our elections, and it has to be stopped,” <a href="https://apnews.com/article/election-2020-joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-media-e79eb5164613d6718e9f4502eb471f27">he told supporters</a> at the Capitol hours before the riot.</p>
<p>Antigone Davis, global head of safety for Facebook, said these kinds of proposals would make it harder for the site to remove posts involving hate speech, sexualized photos of minors and other harmful content.</p>
<p>“We will continue advocating for updated rules for the internet, including reforms to federal law that protect free expression while allowing platforms like ours to remove content that threatens the safety and security of people across the United States,” she said.</p>
<p>In a statement, Twitter said: “We enforce the Twitter rules judiciously and impartially for everyone on our service – regardless of ideology or political affiliation – and our policies help us to protect the diversity and health of the public conversation.”</p>
<p>Researchers have not found widespread evidence that social media companies are biased against conservative news, posts or materials.</p>
<p>In a February <a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/5b6df958f8370af3217d4178/t/60187b5f45762e708708c8e9/1612217185240/NYU+False+Accusation_2.pdf">report, </a>New York University&#8217;s Stern Center for Business and Human Rights called the accusations political disinformation spread by Republicans. The report recommended that social media sites give clear reasoning when they take action against material on their platforms.</p>
<p>“Greater transparency — such as that which Twitter and Facebook offered when they took action against President Trump in January — would help to defuse claims of political bias, while clarifying the boundaries of acceptable user conduct,” the report read.</p>
<p>While the federal law is in place, the state proposals mostly amount to political posturing, said Darrell West, vice president of governance studies at the Brookings Institution, a public policy group.</p>
<p>“This is red meat for the base. It&#8217;s a way to show conservatives they don&#8217;t like being pushed around,” he said. “They&#8217;ve seen Trump get kicked off Facebook and Twitter, and so this is a way to tell Republican voters this is unfair and Republicans are fighting for them.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877852</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/twitter-1795652_1920-e1590186363883.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/twitter-1795652_1920-e1590186363883.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/07/twitter-1795652_1920-e1590186363883.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">twitter-1795652_1920</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amid the rubble of Mosul, Pope Francis declares hope &#8216;more powerful than hatred&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/amid-the-rubble-of-mosul-pope-francis-declares-hope-more-powerful-than-hatred/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 16:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877829</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Standing amid the rubble left behind by the now-defeated ISIS terrorists in the Iraqi city of Mosul, Pope Francis on Saturday declared hope to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Standing amid the rubble left behind by the now-defeated ISIS terrorists in the Iraqi city of Mosul, <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/05/middleeast/iraq-pope-francis-visit-arrival-baghdad-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pope Francis</a> on Saturday declared hope to be &#8220;more powerful than hatred and peace more powerful than war.&#8221;</p>
<p>Francis called for &#8220;harmonious coexistence&#8221; of people from different backgrounds and cultures while leading a prayer at a square overlooking the ruins of the Syro-Catholic Church in Mosul&#8217;s Old City. Once an ISIS stronghold, the whole city has been completely destroyed in 2017, during the nine-months-long battle over its control.</p>
<p>&#8220;Here in Mosul, the tragic consequences of war and hostility are all too evident,&#8221; Francis said. &#8220;How cruel it is that this country, the cradle of civilization, should have been afflicted by so barbarous a blow, with ancient places of worship destroyed and many thousands of people &#8212; Muslims, Christians, Yazidis and others &#8212; forcibly displaced or killed!&#8221;</p>
<p>Thousands of people were killed during the battle to recapture Mosul from ISIS, which controlled the city between 2014 and 2017.</p>
<p>The visit to Mosul came on the third day of the <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/04/middleeast/iraq-pope-christians-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pope&#8217;s tour of the war-ravaged nation</a>, the first-ever papal visit to Iraq and Francis&#8217; first trip outside Italy since the coronavirus pandemic began. He has repeatedly denounced religious extremism and called for friendship between religions during the trip.</p>
<p>After leaving Mosul, Francis traveled to the Qaraqosh, the largest Christian city in Iraq. Like Mosul, Qaraqosh was also controlled by the ISIS terrorist group for more than two years.</p>
<p>The Pope visited the city&#8217;s Church of the Immaculate Conception, where he gave a speech and led a prayer. He was greeted by thousands of people there &#8212; a marked difference from his visits to other locations across Iraq. The government has imposed a total curfew for the entirety of the four-day papal visit to minimize health and security risks.</p>
<p>Late on Sunday, the Pope was scheduled to hold celebrate Mass at the Franso Hariri Stadium in Erbil, according to Iraq state-run Iraqiya TV. Some 8,000 people have gathered at the stadium to welcome the Pope there, security officials told CNN. The plan had been to have the 35,000 seats stadium at some 50% capacity with an empty seat between each of the attendees to allow for social distancing, according to officials. However, images from the stadium showed swathes of the stadium stands filled with people seated closely together without social distancing.</p>
<p>Earlier Sunday, Francis met with Nechirvan Barzani, the president of the Kurdish Regional Government, the semi-autonomous region in northern Iraq.</p>
<p>The Pope is believed to have long wished to go to Iraq, which figures heavily in the Old Testament, and whose dwindling Christian minority has suffered greatly from the country&#8217;s long cycles of violence.</p>
<p>Thought to be one of the oldest Christian communities in the world, prior to the 2003 US invasion, there were 1.5 million Christians in Iraq. Around 80% of them have since fled, according to leading Christian clerics there.</p>
<p>He touched down in Baghdad on Friday, where he was met by Iraqi Prime Minister Mustafa al-Kadhimi. Francis later met with clerics and other officials at a Baghdad church that was the site of a bloody 2010 massacre.</p>
<p>On Saturday, the Pope held a historic meeting with revered Shia Muslim cleric <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/06/middleeast/pope-francis-nayaf-grand-ayatollah-intl-hnk/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani</a> in the holy city of Najaf before visiting Ur, the ancient Iraqi city where Jews, Christians and Muslims believe their common patriarch Abraham was born.</p>
<p>Francis then returned to Baghdad on Saturday afternoon and celebrated Mass at the Chaldean Cathedral of Saint Joseph. He is scheduled to leave Iraq on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877829</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180825_pope_francis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180825_pope_francis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180825_pope_francis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180825_Pope_Francis</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden marking &#8216;Bloody Sunday&#8217; by signing voting rights order</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/biden-marking-bloody-sunday-by-signing-voting-rights-order/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877784</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — A new executive order from President Joe Biden directs federal agencies to take a series of steps to promote voting access, a move that...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>WASHINGTON (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; A new&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2021/03/07/fact-sheet-president-biden-to-sign-executive-order-to-promote-voting-access/">executive order</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;from President Joe Biden directs federal agencies to take a series of steps to promote voting access, a move that comes as congressional Democrats press for a&#xC2;&#xA0;sweeping voting and elections bill&#xC2;&#xA0;to counter efforts to&#xC2;&#xA0;restrict voting access.<p>His plan was announced during a&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/speeches-remarks/2021/03/07/pre-taped-remarks-by-president-biden-as-prepared-for-delivery-at-the-martin-coretta-scott-king-unity-breakfast/">recorded address</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;on the 56th commemoration of &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Bloody Sunday,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; the 1965 incident in which some 600 civil rights activists were viciously beaten by state troopers as they tried to march for voting rights in Selma, Alabama.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Every eligible voter should be able to vote and have it counted,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Biden said in his remarks to Sunday&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s Martin and Coretta King Unity Breakfast before signing the order. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;If you have the best ideas, you have nothing to hide. Let the people vote.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/WhiteHouse/status/1368611436516245506?s=20</embed></div><p>Biden&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s order includes several modest provisions. It directs federal agencies to expand access to voter registration and election information, calls on the heads of agencies to come up with plans to give federal employees time off to vote or volunteer as nonpartisan poll workers, and pushes an overhaul of the government&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s Vote.gov website.</p><p>Democrats are attempting to solidify support for House Resolution 1, which touches on virtually every aspect of the electoral process. It was approved Wednesday on a near party-line vote, 220-210.</p><p>The voting rights bill includes provisions to restrict partisan gerrymandering of congressional districts, strike down hurdles to voting and bring transparency to a murky campaign finance system that allows wealthy donors to anonymously bankroll political causes.</p><p>Democrats say the bill will help stifle voter suppression attempts, while Republicans have cast the bill as unwanted federal interference in states&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99; authority to conduct their own elections.</p><p>The bill&#x2019;s fate is far from certain in the closely divided Senate. Conservative groups have undertaken a $5 million campaign to try persuade moderate Senate Democrats to oppose rule changes needed to pass the measure.</p><p>With his executive order, Biden is looking to turn the spotlight on the issue and is using the somber commemoration of Bloody Sunday to make the case that much is at stake.</p><p>Bloody Sunday proved to be a turning point in the civil rights movement that led to passage of the Voting Rights Act of 1965. Similarly, Biden is hoping the Jan. 6 sacking of the U.S. Capitol by a pro-Donald Trump mob will prove to be a clarion call for Congress to take action to improve voter protections.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;In 2020 &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; with our very democracy on the line &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; even in the midst of a pandemic &#xE2;&#x80;&#x93; more Americans voted than ever before,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Biden said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Yet instead of celebrating this powerful demonstration of voting &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; we saw an unprecedented insurrection on our Capitol and a brutal attack on our democracy on January 6th. A never-before-seen effort to ignore, undermine and undo the will of the people.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Biden&#x2019;s also paid tribute to the late civil rights giants Rev. C.T. Vivian, Rev. Joseph Lowery and Rep. John Lewis. All played critical roles in the 1965 organizing efforts in Selma and all died in within the past year.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877784</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/biden-march-2.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c4b8bec5-ce54-490a-9170-76dfeee30313/053495f6-27c2-4642-8ead-ef6eded14d92/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218057~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c4b8bec5-ce54-490a-9170-76dfeee30313/053495f6-27c2-4642-8ead-ef6eded14d92/main.mp4*~hmac=e8683a114226c79cfbc5b7c5fa9feef7dc40642fd6ff9f61d2e9303de269b70f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/biden-march-2.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/biden-march-2.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">biden</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Workers worry about safety, stress as states ease mask rules</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/workers-worry-about-safety-stress-as-states-ease-mask-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 14:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSON, Mississippi (AP) — Leo Carney worries that bigger crowds and mask-less diners could endanger workers at the Biloxi, Mississippi, seafood restaurant where he manages...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSON, Mississippi (AP) — Leo Carney worries that bigger crowds and mask-less diners could endanger workers at the Biloxi, Mississippi, seafood restaurant where he manages the kitchen. Maribel Cornejo, who earns $9.85 an hour as a McDonald&#8217;s cook in Houston, can&#8217;t afford to get sick and frets co-workers will become more lax about wearing masks, even though the fast food company requires them.</p>
<p>As more jurisdictions join Texas, Mississippi and other states in <a href="https://apnews.com/article/texas-other-states-ease-covid-19-restrictions-af9fc214690270fe617864abc772ecce">lifting mask mandates</a> and easing restrictions on businesses, many essential workers — including bartenders, restaurant servers and retail workers — are relieved by changes that might help the economy but also concerned they could <a href="https://apnews.com/article/rochelle-walensky-coronavirus-pandemic-fe2e65c19506b99ebdb8f1e0badc846b">make them less safe</a> amid a pandemic that health experts warn is far from over.</p>
<p>Many business owners on the Mississippi Gulf Coast were glad Gov. Tate Reeves decided to eliminate mask requirements, limits on seating in restaurants and most other binding restrictions. “But the workers themselves&#8230; especially ones that have pre-existing conditions, they’re scared right now,” Carney said.</p>
<p>“This just puts us back in a situation where we’re on the frontlines, under the gun again,” said Carney, who sees Black Mississippians facing the greatest risks from the decision that took effect Wednesday. COVID-19 has disproportionately affected Black and Latino people in the United States, and many Gulf Coast restaurants have a significant number of Black employees.</p>
<p>Public health experts tracking the trajectory of more contagious virus variants have warned that lifting restrictions too soon could lead to another lethal wave of infections. Although vaccination drives are accelerating as drug manufacturers ramp up production, many essential workers are not yet eligible for COVID-19 vaccines in Mississippi and other states.</p>
<p>Alabama’s state health officer on Friday advised residents to keep following standard infection-prevention recommendations even though the governor is letting the state’s <a href="https://apnews.com/article/kay-ivey-extends-alabama-mask-order-coronavirus-bd11f67b77915a7cd9320b714f222869">mask mandate expire </a>next month.</p>
<p>“There is nothing magical about the date of April 9. We don’t want the public to think that’s the day we all stop taking precautions,” State Health Officer Scott Harris said.</p>
<p>The governors of Iowa, Montana, North Dakota also have ended mask requirements or plan to suspend them soon. The governor of South Carolina on Friday lifted an executive order requiring face coverings in government office buildings and restaurants, leaving it up to state administrators and restaurant operators to develop their own guidelines.</p>
<p>Governors in several other states, including Michigan and Louisiana, eased the operating limits for bars, restaurants and other businesses in recent days.</p>
<p>The National Retail Federation, the largest retail trade association in the U.S., issued a statement Wednesday encouraging shoppers to wear masks. Some retail chains, including Target and supermarket operator Albertson&#8217;s, plan to continue requiring them for both customers and workers in states that no longer make them mandatory.</p>
<p>Texas Retailers Association President and CEO George Kelemen said he thinks many members will continue to require workers — but not necessarily customers — to wear masks and other protective gear.</p>
<p>“Retailers know their customers best,” he said.</p>
<p>McDonald’s cook Cornejo, 43, said the end of Texas’ mask mandate next week alarms her because several of her co-workers already were lax about keeping their faces covered. She said co-workers she has asked to pull their masks back over their noses politely acquiesced, but not always for long.</p>
<p>“There are just different attitudes,” said Cornejo, whose 19-year-old son began working as a cashier at the same restaurant to help pay the family’s bills. “Some say it’s just too difficult to keep it on for eight hours, especially when it gets hot.”</p>
<p>The director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Dr. Rochelle Walensky, encouraged Americans to “do the right thing” by continuing to abide by recommendations for routine mask use and social distancing &#8211; even if their states lift restrictions.</p>
<p>Dr. William Schaffner, a professor of preventive medicine at Vanderbilt University in Tennessee, said individuals who wear masks still risk infection from unmasked shoppers and diners. He called Texas Gov. Greg Abbott’s decision to lift COVID-19 restrictions starting March 10 “entirely too soon and entirely too carefree.”</p>
<p>While deaths and new confirmed cases have plummeted from their January peaks nationwide, they’re still running at high levels, while outbreak indicators in some states have risen in recent weeks. In Mississippi, for example, the 7-day rolling average of the virus positivity rate rose from 11.47% on Feb. 19 to 12.14% on March 5, and the state&#8217;s 7-day rolling average of daily deaths increase during the same period from 15 per day to 20.71 per day.</p>
<p>Workers in cities that still have mask mandates or jobs at businesses that maintain their own virus-prevention rules anticipate defiance from customers emboldened by their governors’ actions and weary of taking precautions.</p>
<p>Molly Brooks, 25, a barista at a Farmers Branch, Texas, coffee shop, said she has regularly dealt with customers who walked out or bullied her and her colleagues when they were asked to wear a mask. Brooks worries how they&#8217;re going to enforce the rule, which the coffee shop plans to keep in place, now that Texas&#8217; governor lifted the statewide mask mandate.</p>
<p>“We are gearing up for the emotional toll that this is going to take,” said the 25-year-old barista, who started working for the coffee shop in November while looking for a job in education. “The people who don&#8217;t want to wear them are still going to fight&#8230;and now they are going to have even more ammunition.”</p>
<p>Square Books in Oxford, Mississippi, home of the University of Mississippi, will require masks and allow only eight customers at a time. Although General Manager Lyn Roberts believes the rules will make many customers feel safe, bookstore employee Paul Fyke said he observed a change in Oxford almost as soon as the Board of Aldermen chose to follow the governor&#8217;s lead and did away with the college town&#8217;s mask mandate.</p>
<p>“I mean, really, even on the drive home, you can kind of already see there were places where, for a lot of people, it was triumph,” he said on Thursday, the day after Oxford&#8217;s mask requirement ended. “They were happy to be removing them.”</p>
<p>Still, some workers are cautiously hopeful that fewer restrictions will bring more customers, tips and job security after a year short on all three.</p>
<p>In San Francisco, where the mayor last week announced the return of indoor dining and the reopening of movie theaters and gyms, Dino Keres had no qualms about serving drinks to customers bellying up to the bar inside Sam&#8217;s Grill.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s partly because he was about to get his second vaccine dose, but also because nobody on staff was infected when indoor dining was briefly permitted last fall. What’s more, masks are required unless people are eating, and indoor seating is limited to 25% of capacity.</p>
<p>“We have already went through this once, and now the timing feels about right to try it again,” Keres said Thursday.</p>
<p>Ro Hart, an assistant general manager and hostess at Tony’s Pizza Napoletana in San Francisco, said the return of indoor dining in the city provoked a mixture of joy and anxiety.</p>
<p>“We are happy to be bringing in more revenue, but we are little nervous, too, because we have to be more stringent about making sure everyone keeps their masks on when they’re not eating,” Hart said, adding that she would be far more worried if San Francisco didn&#8217;t require masks.</p>
<p>“We feel for our brothers and sisters at all those restaurants in Texas,” she said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877775</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200710_Disney_employees_face_masks</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bloody Sunday memorial honors late civil rights giants</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/bloody-sunday-memorial-honors-late-civil-rights-giants/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 13:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877771</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SELMA, Ala. (AP) — Activists who gathered virtually and in person to commemorate a pivotal day in the civil rights struggle that became known as...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SELMA, Ala. (AP) — Activists who gathered virtually and in person to commemorate a pivotal day in the civil rights struggle that became known as Bloody Sunday called on people to continue the fight for voting rights as they also honored giants of the civil rights movement, including the late U.S. Rep. John Lewis, who died last year.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.selmajubilee.com/">Selma Bridge Crossing Jubilee</a> marks the 56th anniversary of Bloody Sunday — the day on March 7, 1965, that civil rights marchers were brutally beaten by law enforcement officers on Selma’s Edmund Pettus Bridge. Lewis, the Rev. Joseph Lowery, the Rev. C.T. Vivian, and attorney Bruce Boynton were the late civil rights leaders honored on Sunday.</p>
<p>The day became a turning point in the fight for voting rights. Footage of the beatings helped galvanize support for passage of the Voting Rights Act of 1965.</p>
<p>This year’s commemoration comes as some states seek to roll back expanded early and mail-in voting access and efforts have been unsuccessful to restore a key section of the Voting Rights Act that required states with a history of discrimination to get federal approval for any changes to voting procedures.</p>
<p>Many speakers throughout the day&#8217;s events emphasized the need for continued activism to protect voting access.</p>
<p>“Voter suppression is still alive and well,&#8221; said U.S. Rep. Teri Sewell, a Democrat who represents the 7th Congressional District which includes Selma. “It reminds us that progress is elusive and every generation must fight and fight again.”</p>
<p>Sewell spoke during a video that featured comments from activists, mayors, members of Congress and others about the historic anniversary. Later, organizers played video footage of activists, many who had been part of the original Bloody Sunday events in 1965, crossing the bridge once again. They wore masks and in keeping with social distancing requirements designed to stop the coronavirus, spread out across the bridge as they walked.</p>
<p>The event typically brings thousands of people to Selma. However, most of the events were held virtually this year because of the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
<p>The annual <a href="http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?oeidk=a07ehmlomcwef65374d&amp;llr=jlhbevkab">Martin &amp; Coretta King Unity Breakfast</a> was held as a drive-in event. The outdoor event included some in-person speakers such as Rev. Bernard LaFayette, and the founders of the group Black Voters Matter. Cliff Albright, one of the group&#8217;s founders, spoke about the continued need to fight for voter access.</p>
<p>“The movement is not over,&#8221; he said as people in their cars honked in support. “What we are asking folks today is for us to commit to that moment, for us to commit to this movement.”</p>
<p>Others spoke via video link or in prerecorded messages. President Joe Biden appeared via a prerecorded message, in which he announced an executive order aimed at promoting voting access.</p>
<p>“Every eligible voter should be able to vote and have that vote counted,” Biden said. “If you have the best ideas, you have nothing to hide. Let the people vote.”</p>
<p>Lowery, a charismatic and fiery preacher, is often considered the dean of the civil rights veterans and led the Southern Christian Leadership Conference.</p>
<p>Vivian began organizing sit-ins against segregation in the 1940s and later joined forces with the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. In 1965, Vivian led dozens of marchers to a courthouse in Selma, confronting the local sheriff on the courthouse steps and telling him the marchers should be allowed to register to vote. The sheriff responded by punching Vivian in the head.</p>
<p>Boynton was arrested for entering the white part of a racially segregated bus station in Virginia, launching a chain reaction that ultimately helped to bring about the abolition of Jim Crow laws in the South. Boynton contested his conviction, and his appeal resulted in a U.S. Supreme Court decision that prohibited bus station segregation.</p>
<p>His case inspired the Freedom Riders of 1961 — a group of young activists who went on bus rides throughout the South to test whether court-ruled desegregation was actually being enforced. They faced violence from white mobs and arrest by local authorities.</p>
<p>Organizers acknowledged the fallen civil rights leaders and planned to lay wreaths at the bridge in their honor.</p>
<p>The march across the Selma bridge was sparked by events in nearby Marion, where a Black man had been killed by a white Alabama state trooper during peaceful protests for voting rights. Jimmie Lee Jackson, a 26-year-old church deacon, was shot while trying to protect his mother from being hurt and died eight days later. In response, activists in Marion and Selma gathered for a march on March 7, their goal the state capital in Montgomery.</p>
<p>Although the Jackson case occurred in 1965, it has particular resonance in 2021 as the state of Minnesota prepares to try former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin in the death of George Floyd, an African American. Floyd died after Chauvin, who is white, pressed his knee onto Floyd’s neck while Floyd was held face-down on the ground in handcuffs, saying he couldn’t breathe. Body camera footage indicates Chauvin’s knee was on Floyd’s neck for about nine minutes. Floyd was later pronounced dead at a hospital.</p>
<p>Jury selection begins Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877771</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/200301_rep_john_lewis_selma.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/200301_rep_john_lewis_selma.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/200301_rep_john_lewis_selma.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200301_Rep_John_Lewis_Selma</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kindness brings huge tips to Florida restaurant server</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/kindness-brings-huge-tips-to-florida-restaurant-server/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877768</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JUNO BEACH, Fla. (AP) — On a random Thursday night, restaurant server Kimberly Filion got the surprise of her life, not once but twice: two...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JUNO BEACH, Fla. (AP) — On a random Thursday night, restaurant server Kimberly Filion got the surprise of her life, not once but twice: two staggeringly high tips on otherwise modest checks. The tips, inspired by a national tip-off challenge that started among rival college basketball fans in Cincinnati, totaled to $2,800.</p>
<p>Filion, a single mother of four who has worked at Kirby’s Sports Grille in Juno Beach for the past six years, had never heard of the Crosstown Tip-Off Challenge that has revved up fans of University of Cincinnati and Xavier University since an Xavier Musketeers fan left a $1,000 tip at a local burger joint in January. Last week, a UC Bearcats fan in Wyoming, Ohio, left a $7,000 tip on a $65 check at a local Italian café.</p>
<p>The Juno Beach server learned about the challenge from a customer on that Thursday night, Feb. 18. Filion was fascinated, not only because she was a struggling server but because she had a personal connection to Ohio &#8212; she is a graduate of Ohio State University. She mentioned that in passing to the customer.</p>
<p>“And then he leaves a $1,300 tip on a $30 tab,” says Filion, 45, who also serves as Kirby’s bar manager.</p>
<p>The exact check amount was $29.71, but the server’s eyes went to the handwritten total &#8212; $1,329.71 &#8212; and the note scribbled beneath it, saying “Go XU!!”</p>
<p>The customer left another note as well: “Five Kelley Boys love Kirby’s in Juno Beach, FL! They cook your catch! Let’s go XU nation! Let’s get this to the national level!”</p>
<p>Filion says she ran after the customer when she saw the tip, but he was gone.</p>
<p>Floored, she recounted the incident later that evening to one of her regular customers. The guy had no particular loyalty to Xavier or to U.C., but he’s a big fan of Kirby’s bar. When Filion reviewed his check, she got her second shock of the night: a $1,500 tip on a $78 tab.</p>
<p>“He wrote something like, ‘I want to be the king,’” she says.</p>
<p>HELPING OTHERS</p>
<p>Filion shared her news with coworkers. Then she shared her tips with them.</p>
<p>“I tried to spread the wealth as much as I could,” she says. “We have employees here who are single moms. We have one employee who just had a baby.”</p>
<p>She knows their daily challenges have been made more severe during the pandemic. She knows this because this has been her struggle as well.</p>
<p>By the time her first big-tipping customer had taken his seat at Kirby’s bar that Thursday, Filion had run the daily marathon that is her life. She had made breakfast for her school-age kids, packed their lunches, spirited them to different schools, all on less than five hours of sleep.</p>
<p>As she does most days, the single mother of four raced through it all before heading in for her shift, which can run as late at 1:30 a.m.</p>
<p>Her boss, Sean Kirby, describes her as an “awesome” employee and “a hard worker.” And Filion says she loves her job.</p>
<p>“We have the most amazing, loyal customers ever. They make coming in so worthwhile,” says Filion.</p>
<p>The pay, however, doesn’t always love her back. She earns less than $5.40 an hour and relies on tips to boost her take-home pay to at least minimum-wage levels.</p>
<p>On the night of Feb. 18, the friendly customer at the bar asked her how business was going. Filion told him times were tough for the industry. She’s not one to chatter on about her woes to a customer. In fact, she sometimes refers to herself as “the therapist,” a sympathetic ear ready to listen to her customers vent. But that night, she vented a bit herself when the customer asked how things were.</p>
<p>“Everyone’s hurting. Honestly, I’m exhausted. I’m putting orange juice in my kids’ cereal,” she recalls telling the customer.</p>
<p>Kirby’s is a go-to neighborhood pub that’s locally famous for its meaty, Maryland-style crab cakes. The welcoming spot has been around for 17 years, but like many restaurants across the country, Kirby’s has lost a considerable amount of its dine-in crowd. The pub’s owner says the influx of newcomers moving to the area from the north is not translating into more customers.</p>
<p>“They’ll come to Florida. We see the traffic. But they’re not getting out,” says Kirby. “This is supposed to be our busiest time of the year.”</p>
<p>The pub has stepped up its takeout service and is expected to undergo renovations to create an open-sided dining area, he says.</p>
<p>But even as they pack more meals to go for takeout customers, servers like Filion too often see nothing for it in their take-home pay.</p>
<p>“You’d be surprised how many people don’t even leave a dollar &#8212; not one dollar &#8212; when they pick up their order. People are clueless sometimes. It is what it is. I’m working double time to make it up. I have to &#8212; I have four kids,” says Filion, who coaches her 7-year-old daughter’s soccer team on her days off.</p>
<p>She offers the example of a recent takeout order that totaled to $178.</p>
<p>“The customer says, ‘Can you help me put it in the trunk?’ Sure, no problem. And they just drive away, leaving nothing,” says Filion, a Long Island native who moved to Palm Beach County 13 years ago.</p>
<p>She started working as a server after her marriage broke up. In addition to her daily shuffle of mom duties, she was still nursing her youngest child when she got the job. “But you do what you have to do,” she says.</p>
<p>Then again, you might expect the daughter of the late Hall of Fame harness driver Hervé Filion to understand a thing or two about dealing with unpredictable shifts in pacing, in horses in life.</p>
<p>The way she deals with them is to take ownership, she says. For her, working at the pub is not just about completing her shifts, says Filion.</p>
<p>“This is your local, family-owned bar and it’s my home away from home. The people here are like my family. Some of my customers ask me if I live here. I tell them I sleep on top of the pool table,” she says. “People say, ‘Hey, are you the owner?’ I think that’s because I treat it as if it’s my place.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877768</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200830_Miami-Dade_restaurant_dining_area_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Parade held in Palm Beach County for 7 vets unable to board Honor Flight due to pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/florida/parade-held-in-palm-beach-county-for-7-vets-unable-to-board-honor-flight-due-to-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 04:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877646</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DELRAY BEACH, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A parade in Palm Beach County served as a special salute for seven veterans who were unable to go on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DELRAY BEACH, Fla. (WSVN) &#8212; A parade in Palm Beach County served as a special salute for seven veterans who were unable to go on an annual flight to the nation capital due to the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>Palm Beach County Sheriff&#8217;s deputies and fire rescue vehicles took part in a caravan that drove past the veterans&#8217; homes, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>Honor Flight South Florida aimed to ensure some of the nation&#8217;s oldest veterans had an unforgettable reminder of how grateful people are for their service.</p>
<p>The vets were supposed to be passengers on an Honor Flight to Washington, D.C. last year. They would have had the chance to visit memorials that were built in honor of them and their fallen comrades.</p>
<p>But their trip was postponed due to the pandemic.</p>
<p>U.S. Army Lt. Col. Bill Schwartz, a World War II vet, was the parade&#8217;s grand marshal.</p>
<p>&#8220;To see this kind of a welcome, I mean, it&#8217;s overbearing, and it&#8217;s wonderful,&#8221; he said, &#8220;It&#8217;s a little icing on the cake for those who served.&#8221;</p>
<p>Schwartz was part of the first wave on Normandy Beach and one of the few to survive that D-Day battle.</p>
<p>The caravan started in Delray Beach and stopped at the homes of the veterans in the Boca Raton area, where their families and neighbors gathered to join in the celebration.</p>
<p>Honor Flight South Florida plans on a few more honor parades to pay tribute to more veterans who had to have their Honor Flights postponed.</p>
<p>The organization plans to bring back Honor Flights later in 2021, with the first ones scheduled to go out in September.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877646</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1259a82-101d-4dc6-bcd5-6fe5102908c8/2d9593c7-10bc-4401-b14a-202d1a014c61/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217003~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b1259a82-101d-4dc6-bcd5-6fe5102908c8/2d9593c7-10bc-4401-b14a-202d1a014c61/main.mp4*~hmac=544ea4a71c593e719fee112b93dd87ff01ad8c063876a8a707b7df50a32d704f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Honor_Flight_parade_Delray_Beach</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Socially distant Broward Heart Walk kicks off at NSU in memory of Rick Case</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/socially-distant-broward-heart-walk-kicks-off-at-nsu-in-memory-of-rick-case/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 04:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877634</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The 2021 Broward Heart Walk Digital Experience kicked off this weekend at Nova Southeastern University in Fort Lauderdale. The events local sponsors &#8212; City Furniture,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 2021 Broward Heart Walk Digital Experience kicked off this weekend at Nova Southeastern University in Fort Lauderdale.</p>
<p>The events local sponsors &#8212; City Furniture, Cleveland Clinic Florida and Rick Case Automotive Group &#8212; raised money for a good cause.</p>
<p>The walk benefits the American Heart Association, a nonprofit that funds research and helps bring awareness to cardiovascular issues.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re hoping that the Broward Heart Walk will raise over $1.5 million this year for The American Heart Association,&#8221; said Andrew Koenig, president of City Furniture. &#8220;They&#8217;re going to put that money to great use: for life-saving research, very critical important awareness, to really save lives, and create happier and healthier lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>This year&#8217;s event was held in memory of Rick Case. The late community leader helped the Heart Walk reach fundraising goals for many years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877634</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Broward_Heart_Walk_caravan.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8cd60d2a-675f-435b-a5db-bf5da0345439/a67b4aa5-2eb1-4c14-96c2-615bbd64d280/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216997~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8cd60d2a-675f-435b-a5db-bf5da0345439/a67b4aa5-2eb1-4c14-96c2-615bbd64d280/main.mp4*~hmac=a51b65bd2e6073eafd45ed9ecbdae7442c0158ff167e35f6ceaa76ca86f2dc59' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Broward_Heart_Walk_caravan.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Broward_Heart_Walk_caravan.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Broward_Heart_Walk_caravan</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Local firefighters climb for lung disease research at Hard Rock Stadium</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/local-firefighters-climb-for-lung-disease-research-at-hard-rock-stadium/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877620</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Some South Florida firefighters joined other volunteers in climbing for a cause at Hard Rock Stadium. The 17th annual Fight for Air Climb took place...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some South Florida firefighters joined other volunteers in climbing for a cause at Hard Rock Stadium.</p>
<p>The 17th annual Fight for Air Climb took place at Hard Rock Stadium, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>More than 400 people attended the event, hosted by the American Lung Association, and helped raise more than $130,000 both online and in-person.</p>
<p>The money will help fund efforts to end lung disease and address the COVID crisis by finding ways to prevent the spread of future respiratory viruses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877620</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Air_Climb_Hard_Rock_Stadium.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6feee092-0024-448c-864a-15f934267bc5/79caedec-7f6c-4d73-922b-79cae6234954/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219085~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6feee092-0024-448c-864a-15f934267bc5/79caedec-7f6c-4d73-922b-79cae6234954/main.mp4*~hmac=b39f90c824ac6f091aac009f344d012a92462875d8d3604f26b0ae6144ce2a65' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Air_Climb_Hard_Rock_Stadium.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Air_Climb_Hard_Rock_Stadium.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Air_Climb_Hard_Rock_Stadium</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>9 displaced after fire sparks at Lauderhill home</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/9-displaced-after-fire-sparks-at-lauderhill-home/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 03:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nine people were left without a place to call home after a fire broke out inside their house in Lauderhill. Crews from multiple fire rescue...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nine people were left without a place to call home after a fire broke out inside their house in Lauderhill.</p>
<p>Crews from multiple fire rescue departments responded to the scene of the blaze on Northwest 44th Court, near 77th Terrace, Friday night.</p>
<p>Five adults and four children were displaced as result of the fire. They are being assisted by the American Red Cross.</p>
<p>The cause of the fire remains under investigation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877609</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Lauderhill_house_fire.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5d743e44-870b-4955-bb27-bdb8f824a2a7/938de742-5025-4daf-979d-2388a2771f39/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219064~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5d743e44-870b-4955-bb27-bdb8f824a2a7/938de742-5025-4daf-979d-2388a2771f39/main.mp4*~hmac=219bfbc8b2237e2eb82948f59a1b90ef1b82c4c0f464e69feaf7248d26049e0c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Lauderhill_house_fire.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Lauderhill_house_fire.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Lauderhill_house_fire</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>23-foot boat stolen overnight from family-owned business in Doral</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/23-foot-boat-stolen-overnight-from-family-owned-business-in-doral/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 02:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The owner of a freight forwarding business in Doral is reeling hours after thieves were caught on surveillance video driving away with a 23-foot boat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The owner of a freight forwarding business in Doral is reeling hours after thieves were caught on surveillance video driving away with a 23-foot boat in the middle of the night.</p>
<p>Nelson Gonzalez of MVP International Freight Systems spoke with 7News on Saturday about the overnight theft of a 23-foot Robalo.</p>
<p>&#8220;This was actually shipping to our customer in Aruba,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It&#8217;s a big deal to a big customer, and not only that; in these trying times, freight forwarding has suffered a lot. This affects us a lot.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gonzalez said he left the family-owned business at around midnight on Friday, and not long after, someone started scoping it out.</p>
<p>About an hour and a half later, Gonzalez said, the crooks made their move.</p>
<p>&#8220;We thank God we had cameras, and we have cameras from different angles in every single part of this warehouse, so we were able to take pictures and post them out,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>The surveillance video captured a pickup truck backing up. Someone is seen getting out and hitching the boat onto the truck.</p>
<p>Three minutes later, the thieves drove off with the boat in tow.</p>
<p>&#8220;We saw that it&#8217;s a Ford F-150 extended cab &#8212; it&#8217;s a workman&#8217;s truck &#8212; and it had a spotter,&#8221; said Gonzalez, &#8220;so a spotter was actually spotting with them, and he was driving a Ford Focus.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now Gonzalez is hoping someone is able to get the vessel back where it belongs.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re all trying to feed our families. We&#8217;re all trying to keep our employees afloat, so any business, anything that we get, we have to make the best out of it,&#8221; he said, &#8220;and this is not just a hard blow to us. This also [affects] our customers who live on the islands.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gonzalez said his customer in Aruba is now out about $12,000.</p>
<p>If you have any information on this theft, call Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a $1,000 reward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877572</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Doral_boat_theft.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f7c780d1-f818-466d-88e8-2b309b2098ec/58ad6421-b614-493c-b699-3cb3676717f8/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216958~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f7c780d1-f818-466d-88e8-2b309b2098ec/58ad6421-b614-493c-b699-3cb3676717f8/main.mp4*~hmac=b2a28e632538b9d0a4cc580511f06cc9d91db59ef6cf959c97f14a4a08e7dd3f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Doral_boat_theft.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Doral_boat_theft.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Doral_boat_theft</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Food truck swiped outside owners&#8217; NE Miami-Dade apartment found in Allapattah</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/food-truck-swiped-outside-owners-ne-miami-dade-apartment-found-in-allapattah/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 02:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877562</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A food truck that was stolen in front of its owners outside the couple&#8217;s Northeast Miami-Dade apartment building has been found. The victims, Chef Bryan...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A food truck that was <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/ne-miami-dade-couples-food-truck-stolen-from-outside-apartment-complex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stolen in front of its owners</a> outside the couple&#8217;s Northeast Miami-Dade apartment building has been found.</p>
<p>The victims, Chef Bryan Rivas and Andrea Larrotta, said the trailer was recovered in Allapattah, Friday night, hours after it was stolen.</p>
<p>The couple said they use the truck to make a living, and it&#8217;s gotten them through the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>The truck will need some work. The name of the couple&#8217;s business had been painted over in black when it was recovered.</p>
<p>Larrotta said that&#8217;s not all they&#8217;re worried about now.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s mixed emotions because it feels great, and at the same, it doesn&#8217;t feel so good because of how they kind ofvandalized it a little bit,&#8221; she said. &#8220;They painted over our wrap, so we couldn&#8217;t see our logo. Inside, it&#8217;s a disaster.&#8221;</p>
<p>Surveillance cameras captured the thief getting away with the heavy haul from the couple&#8217;s apartment building.</p>
<p>It was found with the help of a GPS tracker.</p>
<p>Police have not made any arrests.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877562</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_NEMD_stolen_food_truck_found.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1d6d1438-41bd-4f4d-b842-1929cf39c2a4/89f0602d-c7b4-4be4-ab74-f59aa38490b0/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219108~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1d6d1438-41bd-4f4d-b842-1929cf39c2a4/89f0602d-c7b4-4be4-ab74-f59aa38490b0/main.mp4*~hmac=e5824e29848a1644b453999c3f2c1061575cc147210ae9dfec1289b41a1b2fd3' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_NEMD_stolen_food_truck_found.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_NEMD_stolen_food_truck_found.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_NEMD_stolen_food_truck_found</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Motorcycle officer hospitalized after crash at NE Miami-Dade intersection</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/motorcycle-officer-hospitalized-after-crash-at-ne-miami-dade-intersection/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 01:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877546</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A collision in Northeast Miami-Dade sent a motorycle police officer to the hospital. According to the Florida Highway Patrol, the crash happened after the driver...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A collision in Northeast Miami-Dade sent a motorycle police officer to the hospital.</p>
<p>According to the Florida Highway Patrol, the crash happened after the driver of an SUV made an improper left turn and into the path of the Miami Beach Police motorcycle officer at Northeast 186th Street and 26th Avenue, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>The officer was transported to Aventura Hospital with injuries that are serious but not life-threatening.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877546</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_NWMD_police_involved_crash.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_NWMD_police_involved_crash.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_NWMD_police_involved_crash.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_NEMD_police_involved_crash</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Search underway for 19-year-old after shooting in SW Miami-Dade leaves 1 dead, 2 injured</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/search-underway-for-19-year-old-after-shooting-in-sw-miami-dade-leaves-1-dead-2-injured/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Police are searching for a 19-year-old man in connection to a shooting in a Southwest Miami-Dade home that left a man dead and sent a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Police are searching for a 19-year-old man in connection to a shooting in a Southwest Miami-Dade home that left a man dead and sent a woman and an elderly man to the hospital.</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Police and Fire Rescue units responded to the scene of the incident in the area of Southwest 142nd Avenue and 294th Street, just after 11:15 a.m., Saturday.</p>
<p>&#8220;According to investigators, there was a verbal dispute inside of the residence that escalated and led to shots fired,&#8221; said MDPD detective Khristopher Welch.</p>
<p>Michael Baker told 7News he is the suspect&#8217;s uncle.</p>
<p>&#8220;I hate what my nephew did, and I want to punish him, but you have to let the Lord work in His way,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Area resident Sarah Smith said she heard gunfire.</p>
<p>&#8220;I heard gunshots. I heard like five to six,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Baker described the incident as an escalation of a family dispute.</p>
<p>&#8220;There is shock, because we have a good family, and this is the first time this here has happened in our family, period,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Detectives said the suspect, who they have identified as Ruben Warren Williams, then took off. First responders later found the three victims.</p>
<p>&#8220;An adult male was pronounced deceased on scene by Miami-Dade Fire Rescue. The other adult male and adult female were transported by Miami-Dade Fire Rescue to an area hospital in critical condition,&#8221; said Welch.</p>
<p>Detectives have identified the adult male as 27-year-old Carlton Tillman.</p>
<p>Investigators spent the afternoon and evening working the case, while neighbors said they are now on edge.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s really scary to think that, like, it&#8217;s so close to home, and it&#8217;s just like, can I even be safe in my own home? It&#8217;s really hard,&#8221; said Smith.</p>
<p>If you have any information on this shooting or Williams&#8217; whereabouts, call Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a $3,000 reward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877483</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_SWMD_shooting_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/63207cdb-27f0-4936-8d86-d642b3cf6158/f0b18fa8-d6b0-4e8c-94e1-2462c0631228/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219181~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/63207cdb-27f0-4936-8d86-d642b3cf6158/f0b18fa8-d6b0-4e8c-94e1-2462c0631228/main.mp4*~hmac=9f14b213ba2d217c34423c270f647ca869acc52aae42854dfe9b992197de6037' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_SWMD_shooting_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_SWMD_shooting_scene.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_SWMD_shooting_scene</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smooth vaccination process at MDC North site despite large turnout, rainy weather</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/smooth-vaccination-process-at-mdc-north-site-despite-large-turnout-rainy-weather/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[More than 3,000 people came to the federal COVID-19 vaccination site at Miami Dade College&#8217;s North Campus, but despite the large crowds, patients described a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than 3,000 people came to the federal COVID-19 vaccination site at Miami Dade College&#8217;s North Campus, but despite the large crowds, patients described a smooth relatively short process.</p>
<p>It was busy and bustling Saturday morning at the <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/new-mass-vaccination-site-at-mdc-north-opens/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">massive FEMA-run site</a>, located in Northwest Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>Among those who lined up for their dose was 83-year-old Henry Sturrup.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m certainly glad I came here this morning,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It was the best thing that could have happened to me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Others said they waited hours just for a parking spot, but once they had one, the crew made the process of actually receiving a shot quick and easy.</p>
<p>&#8220;Great job, amazing people. They&#8217;re heroes; I love it,&#8221; said patient Roberto Carneiro.</p>
<p>Rainy weather rolled in Saturday afternoon, but it didn&#8217;t stop some from coming out.</p>
<p>&#8220;I am grateful for the opportunity to be protected,&#8221; said Mercedes Medina, a professor at Miami Dade College.</p>
<p>Medina said she is at a higher risk of getting seriously ill from COVID-19 because she has diabetes.​</p>
<p>She said she been teaching virtually, and after being fully vaccinated, she hopes to see her students in person soon.</p>
<p>&#8220;There&#8217;s something about that live engagement that I miss,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I love the remote teaching that gives flexibility, but it shouldn&#8217;t be in place of live teaching.&#8221;</p>
<p>At one point, the downpour caused a pause in operations at the site, but crews were able to reopen once the rain abated.</p>
<p>With the rain likely playing a part, some patients said their wait was much shorter than those who showed up earlier.</p>
<p>Medina said she waited in the car line for just 10 minutes, and the vaccination process took about 30.</p>
<p>&#8220;They were very organized,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The FEMA-run site is open seven days a week from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m.</p>
<p>All Florida residents 65 and older can get a vaccine, as well as police officers and firefighters 50 and older.</p>
<p>Anyone over the age of 18 who is a teacher, school employee or has underlying health conditions is also allowed to receive the vaccine.</p>
<p>Patients who have one those of medical conditions need to bring a doctor&#8217;s note or <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this form</a> signed by a doctor.</p>
<p>When adding the totals from sites in Sweetwater and Florida City to those at the MDC location, state officials said, 4,093 people were vaccinated on Saturday. Of these inoculations, 3,093 took place at the MDC site, 2,344 with the Pfizer vaccine and 749 with the single-shot Johnson&amp; Johnson vaccine.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccination sites in Florida, click <a href="https://floridahealthcovid19.gov/covid-19-vaccines-in-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you would like to pre-register for a vaccine at the new site, click <a href="https://myvaccine.fl.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>To check for vaccination appointment availability at Publix locations, click <a href="https://www.publix.com/covid-vaccine/florida" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>For more information about vaccinations at Holy Cross Health and a list of the medical conditions that will qualify patients for an appointment, click <a href="https://www.holy-cross.com/covidvaccine?hcmacid=a0Z5G000009JPk3UAG" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you have a severe underlying health condition that makes you eligible for the vaccine and need a form for your healthcare to sign, <a href="http://ww11.doh.state.fl.us/comm/_partners/covid19_report_archive/covid-physician-form/EO-21-47-Form.pdf">click here</a>.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health’s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877491</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b39b3bf8-a6ff-44a9-b31e-7d51b5aaf4b0/a2dd09ec-1524-4684-adf3-b2ecfef91ec6/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217390~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b39b3bf8-a6ff-44a9-b31e-7d51b5aaf4b0/a2dd09ec-1524-4684-adf3-b2ecfef91ec6/main.mp4*~hmac=1efae1ee946514ab7951ece3a9518bc695080efb7e9ca37bd43d6468ec45d8e7' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_MDC_North_Campus_vaccination_site_line_entrance</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man arrested in ex-partner&#8217;s fatal shooting in Hialeah</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/man-arrested-in-ex-partners-fatal-shooting-in-hialeah/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 23:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Police have arrested a man in connection to the fatal shooting in Hialeah of a woman who, her family said, was his wife. Hialeah Police...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Police have arrested a man in connection to the <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/woman-dies-after-shooting-in-hialeah-family-says-victims-husband-is-suspect/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fatal shooting in Hialeah</a> of a woman who, her family said, was his wife.</p>
<p>Hialeah Police confirmed they took Joel Luis Polanco into custody on Saturday.</p>
<p>They had been searching for him since Friday morning, when officers responded to the home of the victim&#8217;s parentsm on the corner of East 40th Street and Seventh Avenue, and found the woman with multiple gunshot wounds. She was pronounced dead at the scene.</p>
<p>Neighbors said the 40-year-old victim was a mother of two.</p>
<p>Police have not released her identity, but her brother identified her as Jozory Carida Espinosa.</p>
<p>Espinosa&#8217;s family said she had been married to Polanco for 15 years, and the shooting stemmed over their divorce.</p>
<p>Polanco is facing a first-degree murder charge and is being held without bond at the Turner Guilford Knight Correctional Center.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877462</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Joel_Luis_Polanco.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7cbd33a9-d9d5-4d6a-bd30-6d511d42f975/33fb7c3d-01d5-487b-963d-fa3210f5d600/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216860~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7cbd33a9-d9d5-4d6a-bd30-6d511d42f975/33fb7c3d-01d5-487b-963d-fa3210f5d600/main.mp4*~hmac=c052e6b2e4e20b6c7bb710514a426333aff8b5769349d9101812db049d04d9d2' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Joel_Luis_Polanco.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Joel_Luis_Polanco.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Joel_Luis_Polanco</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>12-year-old arrested for 4 carjacking incidents in Washington, DC</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/12-year-old-arrested-for-4-carjacking-incidents-in-washington-dc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 22:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; A 12-year-old boy was arrested Thursday evening after a series of attempted armed carjackings and one successful one in Washington, DC. All four...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; A 12-year-old boy was arrested Thursday evening after a series of attempted armed carjackings and one successful one in Washington, DC.</p>
<p>All four incidents happened in the span of one hour, according to a Metropolitan Police Department (MPD) <a href="https://mpdc.dc.gov/release/arrest-made-and-additional-suspect-sought-armed-carjacking-gun-offenses-fifth-district" target="_blank" rel="noopener">news release.</a></p>
<p>The boy was arrested by the MPD on the same day and charged with four counts of armed carjacking, the news release said. Police are still searching for a second suspect who was seen on a surveillance camera.</p>
<p>The incidents began around 6:30 p.m., when a rideshare driver was picking up a customer and was approached by the two suspects. One of the suspects pointed a gun at him from the driver&#8217;s side door and ordered him to get out of the vehicle, according to an incident report. The other suspect grabbed the victim&#8217;s phone.</p>
<p>The driver refused to exit the car and was able to drive away.</p>
<p>About 45 minutes later, the suspects approached another rideshare driver, according to an incident report. One suspect opened the front passenger door and waved a handgun at the driver, demanding his car keys. The driver managed to drive away, and the suspects once again fled the scene, according to the incident report.</p>
<p>At around 7:20 p.m., the two suspects approached a man who was walking toward his car. One suspect pointed a handgun at the man and demanded the car keys. The other suspect pulled out a bag from the car and took a laptop before the pair fled the scene, according to an incident report.</p>
<p>Less than 10 minutes after the third carjacking, the suspects approached a woman who was sitting in her car. One suspect opened the driver&#8217;s side of the car, pointed a handgun at the woman and ordered her to get out of her car, according to police.</p>
<p>The woman said she was unable to understand due to a language barrier, an incident report said. A suspect then motioned to the woman to exit her car. The suspects drove away in the car, which was eventually recovered, police said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877466</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/180110-new-police-lights.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/180110-new-police-lights.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/180110-new-police-lights.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180110-new-police-lights</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elderly man who went missing in Miami found at hospital</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/elderly-man-who-went-missing-in-miami-found-at-hospital/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 22:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An 85-year-old man has been located at a local hospital, two days after he went missing in Miami, police said. According to City of Miami...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An 85-year-old man has been located at a local hospital, two days after he went missing in Miami, police said.<p>According to City of Miami Police, Joseph Legagneur had been last seen along the 100 block of Northeast 75th Street, at around 10 a.m., Thursday.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/MiamiPD/status/1368324993004748804?s=20</embed></div><p>He stands 4 feet, 11 inches tall, weighs around 110 pounds, and has salt-and-pepper hair and brown eyes. It is unknown what he was wearing at the time of his disappearance.</p><p>Investigators said Legagneur suffers from memory loss.</p><p>Late Sunday afternoon, police confirmed he was found at a hospital but did not provide further details about his condition.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877441</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Joseph_LeGagneur.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Joseph_LeGagneur.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Joseph_LeGagneur.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Joseph_Legagneur</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDOH reports over 4,600 cases of COVID-19 on Saturday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/fdoh-reports-over-4600-cases-of-covid-19-on-saturday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,620 deaths. As of 2:30 p.m. Saturday, the Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There have now been more than 1.94 million reported cases of the coronavirus in Florida, with 31,620 deaths.</p>
<p>As of 2:30 p.m. Saturday, the Florida Department of Health reported 1,940,897 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the state, an increase of 4,684 from Friday’s update.</p>
<p>The state also reported a single-day increase of 98 deaths.</p>
<div id="see-through" class="seethrough-in-article-ad" data-google-query-id="CLrpt42znO8CFRgXAQodDBMDGQ">
<div id="google_ads_iframe_/1055211/wsvn/see-through_0__container__"></div>
</div>
<p>There are now 418,411 total confirmed cases in Miami-Dade County and 198,995 total cases in Broward.</p>
<p>The total number of cases in Palm Beach County has now reached 123,033, and 5,975 total cases have been reported in Monroe County.</p>
<p>Health officials reported 80,863 hospital admissions statewide.</p>
<p>For a full breakdown of the cases in Florida, <a href="https://experience.arcgis.com/experience/96dd742462124fa0b38ddedb9b25e429" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877369</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/coronavirus_generic_2.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus_generic_</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden, Dems prevail as Senate OKs $1.9T virus relief bill</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/biden-dems-prevail-as-senate-oks-1-9t-virus-relief-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — An exhausted Senate narrowly approved a $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill Saturday as President Joe Biden and his Democratic allies notched a victory they...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — An exhausted Senate narrowly approved a $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill Saturday as President Joe Biden and his Democratic allies notched a victory they called crucial for hoisting the country out of the pandemic and economic doldrums.</p>
<p>After laboring all night on a mountain of amendments — nearly all from Republicans and rejected — bleary-eyed senators approved the sprawling package on a 50-49 party-line vote. That sets up final congressional approval by the House next week so lawmakers can whisk it to Biden for his signature.</p>
<p>The huge measure — its cost is nearly one-tenth the size of the entire U.S. economy — is Biden’s biggest early priority. It stands as his formula for addressing the deadly virus and a limping economy, twin crises that have afflicted the country for a year.</p>
<p>“This nation has suffered too much for much too long,” Biden told reporters at the White House after the vote. “And everything in this package is designed to relieve the suffering and to meet the most urgent needs of the nation, and put us in a better position to prevail.”</p>
<p>Saturday&#8217;s vote was also a crucial political moment for Biden and Democrats, who need nothing short of party unanimity in a 50-50 Senate they run with Vice President Kamala Harris&#8217; tiebreaking vote. They hold a slim 10-vote House edge.</p>
<p>Not one Republican backed the bill in the Senate or when it initially passed the House, underscoring the barbed partisan environment that&#8217;s characterized the early days of Biden&#8217;s presidency.</p>
<p>A small but pivotal band of moderate Democrats leveraged changes in the legislation that incensed progressives, hardly helping Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., guide the measure through the House. But rejection of their first, signature bill was not an option for Democrats, who face two years of running Congress with virtually no room for error.</p>
<p>In a significant sign, the chair of the Congressional Progressive Caucus, representing around 100 House liberals, called the Senate&#8217;s weakening of some provisions “bad policy and bad politics” but “relatively minor concessions.” Rep. Pramila Jayapal, D-Wash., said the bill retained its “core bold, progressive elements.”</p>
<p>“They feel like we do, we have to get this done,” Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y., said of the House. He added, “It&#8217;s not going to be everything everyone wants. No bill is.”</p>
<p>In a written statement, Pelosi invited Republicans &#8220;to join us in recognition of the devastating reality of this vicious virus and economic crisis and of the need for decisive action.”</p>
<p>The bill provides direct payments of up to $1,400 for most Americans and extended emergency unemployment benefits. There are vast piles of spending for COVID-19 vaccines and testing, states and cities, schools and ailing industries, along with tax breaks to help lower-earning people, families with children and consumers buying health insurance.</p>
<p>Republicans call the measure a wasteful spending spree for Democrats’ liberal allies that ignores recent indications that the pandemic and economy was turning the corner.</p>
<p>“The Senate has never spent $2 trillion in a more haphazard way,&#8221; said Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky. He said Democrats&#8217; “top priority wasn&#8217;t pandemic relief. It was their Washington wish list.”</p>
<p>The Senate commenced a dreaded “vote-a-rama” — a continuous series of votes on amendments — shortly before midnight Friday, and by its end around noon dispensed with about three dozen. The Senate had been in session since 9 a.m. EST Friday.</p>
<p>Overnight, the chamber looked like an experiment in sleep deprivation. Several lawmakers appeared to rest their eyes or doze at their desks, often burying their faces in their hands. At one point, Sen. Brian Schatz, D-Hawaii, at 48 one of the younger senators, trotted into the chamber and did a prolonged stretch.</p>
<p>Sen. Dan Sullivan, R-Alaska, missed the votes to attend his father-in-law’s funeral.</p>
<p>The measure follows five earlier ones totaling about $4 trillion enacted since last spring and comes amid signs of a potential turnaround.</p>
<p>Vaccine supplies are growing, deaths and caseloads have eased but remain frighteningly high, and hiring was surprisingly strong last month, though the economy remains 10 million jobs smaller than pre-pandemic levels.</p>
<p>The Senate package was delayed repeatedly as Democrats made eleventh-hour changes aimed at balancing demands by their competing moderate and progressive factions.</p>
<p>Work on the bill ground to a halt Friday after an agreement among Democrats on extending emergency jobless benefits seemed to collapse. Nearly 12 hours later, top Democrats and West Virginia Sen. Joe Manchin, perhaps the chamber&#8217;s most conservative Democrat, said they had a deal, and the Senate approved it on a party-line 50-49 vote.</p>
<p>Under their compromise, $300 weekly emergency unemployment checks — on top of regular state benefits — would be renewed, with a final payment Sept. 6. There would also be tax breaks on some of that aid, helping people the pandemic abruptly tossed out of jobs and risked tax penalties on the benefits.</p>
<p>The House relief bill, largely similar to the Senate&#8217;s, provided $400 weekly benefits through August. The current $300 per week payments expire March 14, and Democrats want the bill on Biden&#8217;s desk by then to avert a lapse.</p>
<p>Manchin and Republicans have asserted that higher jobless benefits discourage people from returning to work, a rationale most Democrats and many economists reject.</p>
<p>The agreement on jobless benefits wasn&#8217;t the only move that showed moderates&#8217; sway.</p>
<p>The Senate voted Friday to eject a House-approved boost in the federal minimum wage to $15 an hour by 2025, a major defeat for progressives. Eight Democrats opposed the increase, suggesting that Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and other liberals pledging to continue the effort will face a difficult fight.</p>
<p>Party leaders also agreed to restrict eligibility for the $1,400 stimulus checks for most Americans. That amount would be gradually reduced until, under the Senate bill, it reaches zero for people earning $80,000 and couples making $160,000. Those ceilings were higher in the House version.</p>
<p>Many of the rejected GOP amendments were either attempts to force Democrats to cast politically awkward votes or for Republicans to demonstrate their zeal for issues that appeal to their voters.</p>
<p>These included defeated efforts to bar funds from going to schools that don&#8217;t reopen their doors or let transgender students born male participate in female sports. One amendment would have blocked aid to so-called sanctuary cities, where local authorities don&#8217;t help federal officials round up immigrants in the U.S. illegally.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877361</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1b604760-368c-431a-bf7a-51afb4eb3851/ceda37c6-0318-4ce8-be8e-2f462705280e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219266~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1b604760-368c-431a-bf7a-51afb4eb3851/ceda37c6-0318-4ce8-be8e-2f462705280e/main.mp4*~hmac=a612601c17e3b4d22170015de4d10cf47dc18354afbfab811e83adc47f4dda64' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Senate_passes_COVID19_bill</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pope, top Iraq Shiite cleric deliver message of coexistence</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/pope-top-iraq-shiite-cleric-deliver-message-of-coexistence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 18:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PLAINS OF UR, Iraq (AP) — Pope Francis walked through a narrow alley in Iraq’s holy city of Najaf for a historic meeting with the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PLAINS OF UR, Iraq (AP) — Pope Francis walked through a narrow alley in Iraq’s holy city of Najaf for a historic meeting with the country’s top Shiite cleric, and together they delivered a powerful message of peaceful coexistence in a country still reeling from back-to-back conflicts over the past decade.</p>
<p>In a gesture both simple and profound, Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani welcomed Francis into his spartan home. Afterward, he said religious authorities have a role in protecting Iraq’s Christians, and that Christians should live in peace and enjoy the same rights as other Iraqis. The Vatican said Francis thanked al-Sistani for having “raised his voice in defense of the weakest and most persecuted” during some of the most violent times in Iraq’s recent history</p>
<p>Al-Sistani, 90, is one of the most senior clerics in Shiite Islam, and <a href="https://apnews.com/article/iraq-ali-al-sistani-pope-francis-saddam-hussein-59818e71b874766877b951f332bfeb8b">his rare but powerful political interventions have helped shape present-day Iraq</a>. He is a deeply revered figure in Shiite-majority Iraq and his opinions on religious and other matters are sought by Shiites worldwide.</p>
<p>Later in the day, the pope met with Iraqi religious leaders in the shadow of a symbol of the country’s ancient past — the 6,000-year-old ziggurat in the Plains of Ur, also the traditional birthplace of Abraham, the biblical patriarch revered by Jews, Christians and Muslims.</p>
<p>Such interfaith forums are a staple of Francis’ international trips. But in strife-torn Iraq the televised gathering of figures from across the country’s religious spectrum was nearly unheard of: From Shiite and Sunni Muslims to Christians, Yazidis and Zoroastrians and tiny, lesser known, ancient and esoteric faiths like the Kakai, a sect among ethnic Kurds, Mandaeans and Sabaean Mandaeans. Missing from the picture was a representative of Iraq’s once thriving, now nearly decimated Jewish community, though they were invited, the Vatican said.</p>
<p>Together, the day’s two main events gave symbolic and practical punch to the central message of Francis’ visit, calling for Iraq to embrace its diversity. It is a message he hopes can preserve the place of the thinning Christian population in the tapestry.</p>
<p>Still, it faces a tough sell in a country where every community has been traumatized by sectarian bloodshed and discrimination and where politicians have tied their power to sectarian interests.</p>
<p>In al-Sistani, Francis sought the help of an ascetic, respected figure who is immersed in those sectarian identities but is also a powerful voice standing above them.</p>
<p>Their meeting in al-Sistani’s humble home, the first ever between a pope and a grand ayatollah, was months in the making, with <a href="https://apnews.com/article/pope-ayatollah-meeting-preparation-iraq-6ebc225f98c0f711f4e86227df34d517">every detail painstakingly negotiated beforehand</a>.</p>
<p>Early Saturday, the 84-year-old pontiff, travelling in a bullet-proof Mercedes-Benz, pulled up along Najaf’s narrow and column-lined Rasool Street, which culminates at the golden-domed Imam Ali Shrine, one of the most revered sites in Shiite Islam.</p>
<p>He then walked the few meters (yards) down an alley to al-Sistani’s home. As a masked Francis entered the doorway, a few white doves were released in a sign of peace. He emerged just under an hour later, still limping from an apparent flare-up of sciatica nerve pain that makes walking difficult.</p>
<p>A religious official in Najaf called the 40-minute meeting “very positive.” He spoke on condition of anonymity because he was not authorized to brief media.</p>
<p>The official said al-Sistani, who normally remains seated for visitors, stood to greet Francis at the door of his room — a rare honor. The pope removed his shoes before entering al-Sistani’s room and was served tea and a plastic bottle of water.</p>
<p>Al-Sistani and Francis sat close to one another, without masks. Al-Sistani spoke for most of the meeting, the official said. Al-Sistani, who rarely appears in public or even on television, wore black robes and a black turban, in simple contrast to Francis’ all-white cassock.</p>
<p>The official said there was some concern about the fact that the pope had met with so many people the day before. Francis has received the coronavirus vaccine but al-Sistani has not. The aging ayatollah, who underwent surgery for a fractured thigh last year, looked tired.</p>
<p>After the meeting ended, Francis paused before leaving the room to have a last look, the official said.</p>
<p>In a statement issued by his office afterward, al-Sistani affirmed that Christians should “live like all Iraqis, in security and peace and with full constitutional rights.” He pointed out the “role that the religious authority plays in protecting them, and others who have also suffered injustice and harm in the events of past years.”</p>
<p>Al-Sistani wished Francis and the followers of the Catholic Church happiness and thanked him for taking the trouble to visit him in Najaf, the statement said.</p>
<p>Iraqis cheered the meeting, and the prime minister responded to it by declaring March 6 a National Day of Tolerance and Coexistence in Iraq.</p>
<p>”We welcome the pope’s visit to Iraq and especially to the holy city of Najaf and his meeting with Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani,” said Najaf resident Haidar Al-Ilyawi. “It is a historic visit and hope it will be good for Iraq and the Iraqi people.”</p>
<p>Iraq’s Christians, battered by violence and discrimination, hope a show of solidarity from al-Sistani will help secure their place in Iraq and ease intimidation from Shiite militiamen against their community.</p>
<p>Al-Sistani’s voice is a powerful one, often for moderation.</p>
<p>After the 2003 U.S.-led invasion, his opinions forced American administrators to alter their transition plans, and his approval opened the way for Iraq’s Shiites to participate in force in post-Saddam Hussein elections. In 2019, as anti-government demonstrations gripped the country, his sermon led to the resignation of then-prime minister Adil Abdul-Mahdi.</p>
<p>But his word is not law. After 2003, he repeatedly preached calm and restraint as the Shiite majority came under attack by Sunni extremists. Yet brutal Shiite reprisals against Sunni civilians fed a years-long cycle of sectarian violence.</p>
<p>His 2014 fatwa, or religious edict, calling on able-bodied men to join the security forces in fighting the Islamic State group helped ensure the extremists’ defeat. But it also swelled the ranks of Shiite militias, many closely tied to Iran and now blamed for discrimination against Sunnis and Christians.</p>
<p>Later, Pope Francis evoked the common reverence for Abraham to speak against religious violence at the inter-faith gathering at the Plains of Ur, near the southern city of Nasiriyah.</p>
<p>“From this place, where faith was born, from the land of our father Abraham, let us affirm that God is merciful and that the greatest blasphemy is to profane his name by hating our brothers and sisters,” Francis said. “Hostility, extremism and violence are not born of a religious heart: they are betrayals of religion.”</p>
<p>The Vatican said Iraqi Jews were invited to the event but did not attend, without providing further details. Iraq’s ancient Jewish community was decimated in the 20th century by violence and mass emigration fueled by the Arab-Israeli conflict, and only a handful remain.</p>
<p>Ali Thijeel, a Nasiriyah resident who attended the event, said he hoped the pope’s visit would encourage investment in the area to attract pilgrims and tourists. “This is what we were waiting for,” he said. “This is a message to the government and politicians. They should take care of this city and pay attention to our history.”</p>
<p>Francis’ visit — his first international trip since the start of the coronavirus pandemic — comes amid a surge in COVID-19 cases in Iraq. Despite concern about infections, Francis celebrated Mass in a packed, stuffy Chaldean Catholic Cathedral later Saturday in Baghdad that featured chanted Scripture readings and a maskless choir singing hymns.</p>
<p>“Love is our strength, the source of strength for those of our brothers and sisters who here too have suffered prejudice, indignities, mistreatment and persecutions for the name of Jesus,” Francis told the faithful, who did wear masks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877352</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/AP21065258719098.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/AP21065258719098.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/AP21065258719098.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">APTOPIX Iraq Pope</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>California OKs reopening of ball parks, Disneyland</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/california-oks-reopening-of-ball-parks-disneyland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a year after coronavirus restrictions shuttered major entertainment spots.</p>
<p>The state on Friday relaxed guidelines for reopening outdoor venues as a fall and winter surge seemed to be ending, with COVID-19 infection rates, hospitalizations and deaths plummeting and vaccination rates rising.</p>
<p>New public health rules would allow live concerts at stadiums and sports arenas to reopen with limited attendance April 1. Amusement parks also will be permitted to reopen in counties that have fallen from the state&#8217;s purple tier — the most restrictive — to the red tier.</p>
<p>In all cases, park capacities will be limited, and COVID-19 safety rules such as mask-wearing requirements will apply.</p>
<p>The move followed a week of milestones, with California ramping up vaccinations for the poorest neighborhoods, counties reopening more businesses and Gov. Gavin Newsom passing a measure aimed at encouraging schools that have restricted students to online learning to reopen classrooms this month.</p>
<p>“Steady opening is consistent with the data. As cases decline, we want to return to work and school,” said Dr. Jeffrey Klausner, clinical professor of preventive medicine at the University of Southern California. “Outdoor activities in particular have always been low risk. Opening these sites makes sense.”</p>
<p>The reopening can&#8217;t come too soon for Kenny King Jr., a resident of Pleasant Hill in the San Francisco Bay Area who became an annual Disneyland passholder a decade ago. He typically takes his family to the Southern California park five times a year, but the last visit was just over a year ago for his birthday.</p>
<p>King, 38, said he&#8217;s excited to return with his 8-year-old daughter, who had just started enjoying rides such as Big Thunder Mountain Railroad and Space Mountain, and to take his 2-year-old son, who was mesmerized by the lights and sounds when he visited last year.</p>
<p>“That’s something that we just made our family thing — Disney trips,” King said. “We’ll sit there at the house sometimes and we’ll be like ‘man, I just miss Disneyland.&#8217; ”</p>
<p>Also applauding were the thousands of workers who were laid off by Disneyland, Universal Studios Hollywood, Knott&#8217;s Berry Farm and other big locations. Ten thousand lost their jobs alone at Disneyland and its related attractions in Orange County, not to mention the knock-on effect to nearby restaurants and hotels.</p>
<p>Andrea Zinder, president of the local United Food and Commercial Workers Union that represents Disney workers, said employees are “excited to go back to work and provide Californians with a bit more magic in their lives.”</p>
<p>Most of the major theme parks are in Southern California, which is still in the purple category. However, Los Angeles, Orange and San Diego counties were expecting to reopen within the next few weeks as their COVID-19 numbers fall.</p>
<p>Only 16 of 58 counties currently are in the red tier, and two small counties are in the orange tier. None are yet in the yellow tier, the lowest and least restrictive.</p>
<p>Theme parks in the red tier will be limited to 15% capacity.</p>
<p>Outdoor sports will be limited to 100 people in the purple tier but will increase up to 67% in the yellow tier.</p>
<p>The San Diego Padres, Los Angeles Angels and Oakland Athletics all announced they will have fans in the stands for opening day April 1. The Los Angeles Dodgers and San Francisco Giants both start their seasons on the road and said they would announce their plans later.</p>
<p>Teams and event organizers can only sell tickets regionally in the purple tier. In the other tiers, teams and organizers can sell tickets to anyone living in California. No concessions will be allowed in the purple tier, while in others, concession sales will only be available at seats.</p>
<p>Richard Haick of San Pablo, California, already bought ticket vouchers for the Oakland A’s return and hopes to take his 10-year-old son to a game soon. His son plays Little League baseball and is very excited to attend games.</p>
<p>“It’s nice to have, even in a reduced capacity, some sense of normal,” said Haick, a 45-year-old photographer.</p>
<p>The quicker pace of reopening is tied to a new plan to vaccinate California’s most vulnerable residents. Once 2 million people across 400 ZIP codes in the most disadvantaged neighborhoods receive at least one vaccine dose, it will be easier for counties to exit the state’s most restrictive tier. Once 4 million people in those neighborhoods are vaccinated, counties will be able to open up even more.</p>
<p>It all puts California in a drastically different position than a year ago, when Gov. Gavin Newsom imposed the statewide stay-at-home order that restricted travel, shuttered businesses and forced millions of people onto unemployment. California still has among the most severe restrictions of any state and continues to discourage out-of-state visitors.</p>
<p>The state is pinning its hopes of a full reopening on inoculating enough of its 40 million residents to halt widespread COVID-19 infections.</p>
<p>More than 10 million doses had been given only three months since the first shot was given, the Department of Public Health said.</p>
<p>Just over 3 million people have been fully vaccinated, or about 10% of the population 16 and older.</p>
<p>There are hopeful signs. This week, the seven-day average rate of positive results from tests dropped this week to 2.2%, a record low.</p>
<p>Although pressure has been building to reopen the economy, health officials said the changes in guidelines were a cautious and measured rather than a wholesale approach.</p>
<p>“We will &#8230;. keep our foot on the brake, not the gas, our eyes on the road, hands on the wheel and navigate based on data and science,” said Dr. Mark Ghaly, secretary of the state Health and Human Services Agency.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877338</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219189~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4*~hmac=9db0e975a924b2cb465a0111975a103e3c17569f6dd83db5e8e6be277872acd9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">sleeping beauty castle disneyland</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Father arrested in India for beheading his 17-year-old daughter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/father-arrested-in-india-for-beheading-his-17-year-old-daughter-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 17:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Police in India&#8217;s northern Uttar Pradesh state have arrested a man who confessed to beheading his teenage daughter. Sarvesh Kumar was arrested as he was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Police in India&#8217;s northern <a href="https://cnn.com/2020/09/29/asia/india-dalit-woman-gang-rape-murder-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uttar Pradesh</a> state have arrested a man who confessed to beheading his teenage daughter.</p>
<p>Sarvesh Kumar was arrested as he was walking toward a police station in Hardoi district on Wednesday night, carrying the severed head of his 17-year-old daughter.</p>
<p>&#8220;He was making his way on foot to the police station to confess what he had done,&#8221; a spokesperson for Hardoi Police told CNN on Friday.</p>
<p>&#8220;He told police he had seen his daughter with a young man that he believes she was seeing, which made him angry as he was against it,&#8221; the spokesperson added.</p>
<p>As Kumar, a vegetable seller from Pandetara village, made the one-mile walk from his home to the police station, local passersby alerted the police, who stopped him and began to film him.</p>
<p>During this time, according to the police spokesperson, Kumar told authorities about his daughter&#8217;s relationship, saying he had found her alone at home, locked her in a room and severed her head using a knife.</p>
<p>&#8220;Considering the situation, he was calm. He wasn&#8217;t crying or hysterical. When the policemen were speaking to him, they asked him to place his daughter&#8217;s head on the ground and to sit down, which he listened to without arguing back,&#8221; the police spokesperson told CNN.</p>
<p>Kumar is currently in custody where he continues to be questioned, the spokesperson added. A list of charges will be compiled once the investigation has been completed. He will have access to a public lawyer once he has been formally charged, and he will remain in custody until the trial, police said.</p>
<p>India reported 24 so-called &#8220;<a href="https://cnn.com/2020/05/18/asia/pakistan-honor-killing-hnk-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">honor killings</a>&#8221; in 2019, according to statistics from the country&#8217;s National Crime Records Bureau.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877334</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_016d0742c0ff0ffc22baa7b9427273b3-h_18cca017ffe6a0a2b1c6a9bad8954c75.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_016d0742c0ff0ffc22baa7b9427273b3-h_18cca017ffe6a0a2b1c6a9bad8954c75.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_016d0742c0ff0ffc22baa7b9427273b3-h_18cca017ffe6a0a2b1c6a9bad8954c75.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Hardoi, India</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;We&#8217;re walking into the mouth of the monster&#8217; by loosening Covid-19 restrictions, expert says</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/were-walking-into-the-mouth-of-the-monster-by-loosening-covid-19-restrictions-expert-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877317</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; More states are relaxing measures to protect against Covid-19 as variants circulate in the United States &#8212; a combination that means &#8220;we&#8217;re walking into the mouth of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; More states are<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/05/health/us-coronavirus-friday/index.html"> relaxing measures</a> to protect <a href="https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2020/health/coronavirus-us-maps-and-cases/">against Covid-19</a> as variants circulate in the United States &#8212; a combination that means &#8220;we&#8217;re walking into the mouth of the monster,&#8221; an infectious disease expert said.</p>
<p>A variant first identified in the UK has now been reported in 2,672 cases in 46 states as of Thursday, according to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. And it is spreading quickly.</p>
<p>&#8220;We literally are sitting on top of that, at a time when instead of actually getting better prepared for it, we&#8217;re opening up and inviting the virus in,&#8221; said Michael Osterholm, director of the Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy at the University of Minnesota.</p>
<p>&#8220;Right now, that (UK variant) is about to take off the United States,&#8221; Osterholm told <a href="https://www.cnn.com/shows/the-lead">CNN&#8217;s Jake Tapper.</a> &#8220;A number of states have seen it go from 1 or 2% of the viruses identified, to now over 20 to 30%.&#8221;</p>
<p>This week, <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/03/politics/greg-abbott-texas-criticism-coronavirus-handling/index.html">Texas </a>and Mississippi joined the list of states to remove mandates for citizens to wear masks and expanded capacity for businesses.</p>
<p>With vaccine eligibility opening up to most US adults by the summer, support for measures to protect against the virus is waning, according to a new survey.</p>
<p>Although less than a third of people said there should be fewer measures, support for additional restrictions has been on the decline since November, according to new research from the Pew Research Center.</p>
<p>But health experts say the road to herd immunity still has a long way ahead, and masks and other restrictions are still crucial to managing the pandemic.</p>
<p>A new CDC study demonstrates &#8220;that masks work,&#8221; CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said during a White House Covid-19 briefing on Friday.</p>
<p>&#8220;You have decreases in cases and deaths when you wear masks and you have increases in cases and deaths when you have in-person restaurant dining, and so we would advocate for policies &#8212; certainly while we&#8217;re at this plateau of a high number of cases &#8212; that would listen to that public health science,&#8221; Walensky said.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>States range on loosening restrictions</h3>
<p>As the US moves closer to widespread vaccinations, many states are changing their policies around Covid-19 restrictions.</p>
<p>In Maine, Gov. Janet Mills said Friday the state will continue to require masks, but she announced a new framework to slowly reopen the state. By March 26, capacity for indoor gatherings in the state will increase to 50% and outdoor will increase to 75%.</p>
<p>And in West Virginia, beginning Saturday, some businesses including restaurants, bars, gyms and museums can open with 100% seating capacity, but social distancing will still be required, Gov. Jim Justice said Friday.</p>
<p>In Texas, any business will be allowed to open 100% beginning March 10, and the order for residents to wear masks has been lifted.</p>
<p>Not all state leaders feel comfortable with the changes.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m deeply concerned about states that lift the mask mandate because what you&#8217;re doing is sending a signal that it&#8217;s not important anymore, and that is not true. In fact, it is just as important as ever,&#8221; North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper said.</p>
<p>&#8220;I would encourage my fellow governors and local officials who are making decisions in some states to keep the mask mandate, to show good examples and to continue doing responsible things.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Detroit mayor declines Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine allocation</h3>
<p>Many experts have celebrated the authorization of the third coronavirus vaccine: Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s, which is a single shot and is stored at temperatures more convenient for transportation and storage.</p>
<p>But there has been some pushback.</p>
<p>Detroit Mayor <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/04/health/detroit-mayor-johnson-and-johnson-vaccine/index.html">Mike Duggan on Thursday said the city declined</a> an initial allocation of the newly authorized vaccine.</p>
<p>Duggan turned down the shipment because the city is able to meet current demand with its supply of the Pfizer/BioNTech and Moderna vaccines &#8212; even as his administration expanded vaccine eligibility Thursday to residents ages 50 and older with chronic medical conditions.</p>
<p>All three vaccines are highly effective at preventing serious illness from Covid-19, and health officials have urged people to take any Covid-19 vaccine they are offered.</p>
<p>&#8220;The day may come in March or April when every single Moderna and Pfizer is committed, and we still have people who need a vaccine. And at that point we will set up a Johnson &amp; Johnson center. I don&#8217;t see that in the next couple of weeks,&#8221; Duggan said.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>CDC guidance for the vaccinated</h3>
<p>CDC guidance for people who have been vaccinated is coming soon, Walensky said. The guidance had been expected to release this week.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our goal and what is most important is that people who have been vaccinated and those not yet vaccinated are able to understand the steps they can take to protect themselves and their loved ones,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>More than 82 million vaccine doses have been given out in the US, and after a year of life turned upside down, many want to know what the future holds.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think people need practical advice about how to go about their everyday lives,&#8221; said Julia Marcus, an infectious disease epidemiologist at Harvard. &#8220;I think without guidance, people may make decisions that are not informed.&#8221;</p>
<p>While the guidelines will not give the vaccinated permission to start living like it&#8217;s 2019 again, according to a Biden administration official, the guidelines do offer some hope that the end of total social isolation is near.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877317</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Woman dies after hit-and-run in Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/woman-dies-after-hit-and-run-in-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 14:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A woman was killed following a hit-and-run in Miami, police said. City of Miami Police and Fire Rescue units responded to a possible assault near...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A woman was killed following a hit-and-run in Miami, police said.</p>
<p>City of Miami Police and Fire Rescue units responded to a possible assault near Northwest 79th Street and Second Court, where they found a woman in her 30&#8217;s unresponsive, Saturday morning.</p>
<p>Paramedics rushed the victim in critical condition to Jackson Memorial Hospital&#8217;s Ryder Trauma Center, where she later succumbed to her injuries.</p>
<p>If you have any information on the hit-and-run, you&#8217;re urged to call police or Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a $3,000 reward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877238</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Miami_hit_and_run_woman_killed.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/31fb6146-31d3-403e-87bd-f729753ef811/faff59d9-e0cc-4f68-860e-bf5d5f41b53a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219073~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/31fb6146-31d3-403e-87bd-f729753ef811/faff59d9-e0cc-4f68-860e-bf5d5f41b53a/main.mp4*~hmac=84c0628c9e0450e4ffa428f05be1d19feadfe17933586f056d1a56fd013eba55' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Miami_hit_and_run_woman_killed.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210306_Miami_hit_and_run_woman_killed.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210306_Miami_hit_and_run_woman_killed</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York cinemas reopen, brightening outlook for theaters</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/new-york-cinemas-reopen-brightening-outlook-for-theaters/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — After growing cobwebs for nearly a year, movie theaters in New York City reopen Friday, returning film titles to Manhattan marquees...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — After growing cobwebs for nearly a year, movie theaters in New York City reopen Friday, returning film titles to Manhattan marquees that had for the last 12 months instead read messages like “Wear a mask” and “We’ll be back soon.”</p>
<p>Shortly after noon at the Angelika Film Center on Houston Street, Holly Stillman was already feeling emotional coming out of the first New York showing of Lee Isaac Chung’s tender family drama “Minari.” “My mask is drenched,” she said.</p>
<p>But she was equally overwhelmed by being back in a cinema. Though Stillman feared the experience would be too restrictive because of COVID-19 protocols, she instead found it euphoric.</p>
<p>“It was just you and the movie screen,” said Stillman. “It was wonderful to smell the popcorn as soon as I got into the theater — even though I don’t eat popcorn.”</p>
<p>Less than half of movie theaters are open nationwide, but reopenings are quickening. Theaters in many other areas reopened last summer around the release of Christopher Nolan’s “Tenet,” but that attempted comeback fizzled. Throughout, theaters remained shut in the five boroughs. For a year almost to the date, one of the world’s foremost movie capitals stayed dark.</p>
<p>For a theatrical business that has been punished by the pandemic, the resumption of moviegoing in New York — is a crucial first step in revival.</p>
<p>“It’s a symbolic moment,” said Michael Barker, co-president of the New York-based Sony Pictures Classics, which on Friday released the Oscar contenders “The Father” and “The Truffle Hunters” in Manhattan theaters. “It says that there is hope for the theatrical world to reactivate itself.”</p>
<p>For some moviegoers who consider the big screen the only way to see a movie, the long-in-coming day had almost religious significance.</p>
<p>“Moviegoing for me is like going to church,” said JM Vargas, who had tickets Friday to “Minari,” “The Last Dragon” and “Chaos Walking.” “I’ve been waiting a year to go back to church.”</p>
<p>Cinemas in the city are currently operating at only 25% capacity, with a maximum of 50 per each auditorium. As in other places, mask wearing is mandatory, seats are blocked out and air filters have been upgraded.</p>
<p>Many theaters were caught off guard when Gov. Andrew Cuomo said cinemas could, under those conditions, reopen. Some of the city’s prominent theaters, including the Film Forum, the Alamo Drafthouse, the Metrograph and Regal Cinemas were targeting openings in the coming weeks. Some needed more time to prepare. After sitting dormant all winter, the Cinema Village in Manhattan two weeks earlier burst a pipe, flooding the lobby — one last bit of bad luck in a grueling year.</p>
<p>“This was the worst horror movie. I don’t think any Hollywood director could have dreamed it up,” said Nicolas Nicolaou, owner of the Cinema Village and theaters in Queens and New York. “We didn’t realize we’d be 100% shutdown for this long.”</p>
<p>New York, along with Los Angeles (where theaters are still closed), is one of the top movie markets. For smaller films, it’s a vital epicenter of word-of-mouth. For blockbusters, it’s a lucrative necessity. Without New York or Los Angeles open, Hollywood studios have pushed most of their larger productions until more theaters are open, or they’ve steered films to streaming services.</p>
<p>“The New York opening is very significant to the theater business in New York, in the nation and in the globe,” says John Fithian, president of the National Association of Theater Owners. “We in the movie theater business live off of movies that play all around the country and all around the world. We keep seeing those movies leave the theatrical release schedule to move to later dates because there just haven’t been enough markets. New York is the most important of those markets.”</p>
<p>Lately, with President Biden’s prediction that every adult can be vaccinated by the end of May, the outlook for theaters has been brightening for the first time in a long time. Last weekend, “Tom &amp; Jerry” overperformed at the box office with $14.1 million in ticket sales, even while it streamed on HBO Max. Though Universal Pictures pushed the “Fast &amp; Furious” sequel “F9” from late May to late June, other movies have moved up on the calendar, reversing the postponement tide.</p>
<p>Sony Pictures said it will release “Peter Rabbit 2: The Runaway” in May. Paramount Pictures’ “A Quiet Place II” moved into the May 28 date vacated by “F9.” The Walt Disney Co.’s “Black Widow” currently remains slated for May 7. Adding to the optimism: Southern California theaters are expected to reopen over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>“It’s not that we’re going back to record-breaking business this summer,” said Fithian. “We’re going to crawl, then we’re going to walk and then we’re going to run. It’s going to take into 2022 before sustained profitability comes back into the business.”</p>
<p>But at least on Friday, New York’s cinema lobbies were, if not crowded, again bustling. Sold-out signs for the evening adorned box-office windows. Even a little star power returned. Liam Neeson was to stop by the AMC at Lincoln Square to introduce “The Marksman.”</p>
<p>At the IFC Center in Greenwich Village, masked moviegoers flocked to films to play catch up — even if the movies were streaming. IFC is hosting a four-week “What’d We Miss?” series of movies the theater couldn’t play over the last 12 months, including “First Cow” and “MLK/FBI.”</p>
<p>“We’re used to being present for the birth of these movies for New York audiences when they move into the public realm,” said John Vanco, senior vice president of the IFC Center. The circumstances, he granted, weren’t ideal. But they were better than nothing. “I don’t look at 25% as being not good enough,” said Vanco. “I look at it as better than 0%.”</p>
<p>At the IFC, Tykon Herman settled in for “Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom,” and had tickets for a 5 p.m. of “The Trial of the Chicago 7.”</p>
<p>“I’m one of the very few that don’t have Netflix,” said Herman, laughing. “I’m just old-fashioned. I’ve loved the theater experience from the time I saw ‘E.T.’ It’s not going to be the same but sitting down in front of this screen makes me feel like things may be getting back to normal soon.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877232</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Europe staggers as infectious variants power virus surge</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/europe-staggers-as-infectious-variants-power-virus-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In a matter of just days, 45 children and 14 staff members had tested positive.</p>
<p>Genetic analysis confirmed what officials already suspected: The highly contagious coronavirus variant first identified in England was racing through the community, a densely packed city of nearly 40,000 with a chemical plant and a Pirelli bicycle tire factory a 15-minute drive from the heart of Milan.</p>
<p>“This demonstrates that the virus has a sort of intelligence. &#8230; We can put up all the barriers in the world and imagine that they work, but in the end, it adapts and penetrates them,’’ lamented Bollate Mayor Francesco Vassallo.</p>
<p>Bollate was the first city in Lombardy, the northern region that has been the epicenter in each of Italy’s three surges, to be sealed off from neighbors because of virus variants that the World Health Organization says are powering another uptick in infections across Europe. The variants also include versions first identified in South Africa and Brazil.</p>
<p>Europe recorded 1 million new COVID-19 cases last week, an increase of 9% from the previous week and a reversal that ended a six-week decline in new infections, WHO said Thursday.</p>
<p>“The spread of the variants is driving the increase, but not only,’’ said Dr. Hans Kluge, WHO regional director for Europe, citing “also the opening of society, when it is not done in a safe and a controlled manner.”</p>
<p>The variant first found in the U.K. is spreading significantly in 27 European countries monitored by WHO and is dominant in at least 10 countries: Britain, Denmark, Italy, Ireland, Germany, France, the Netherlands, Israel, Spain and Portugal.</p>
<p>It is up to 50% more transmissible than the virus that surged last spring and again in the fall, making it more adept at thwarting measures that were previously effective, WHO experts warned. Scientists have concluded that it is also more deadly.</p>
<p>“That is why health systems are struggling more now,” Kluge said. “It really is at a tipping point. We have to hold the fort and be very vigilant.”</p>
<p>In Lombardy, which bore the brunt of Italy’s spring surge, intensive care wards are again filling up, with more than two-thirds of new positive tests being the UK variant, health officials said.</p>
<p>After putting two provinces and some 50 towns on a modified lockdown, Lombardy&#8217;s regional governor announced tightened restrictions Friday and closed classrooms for all ages. Cases in Milan schools alone surged 33% in a week, the provincial health system&#8217;s chief said.</p>
<p>The situation is dire in the Czech Republic, which this week registered a record-breaking total of nearly 8,500 patients hospitalized with COVID-19. Poland is opening temporary hospitals and imposing a partial lockdown as the U.K. variant has grown from 10% of all infections in February to 25% now.</p>
<p>Two patients from hard-hit Slovakia were expected to arrive Saturday for treatment in Germany, where authorities said they had offered to take in 10 patients.</p>
<p>Kluge cited Britain’s experience as cause for optimism, noting that widespread restrictions and the introduction of the vaccine have helped tamp down the variants there and in Israel. The vaccine rollout in the European Union, by comparison, is lagging badly, mostly because of supply problems.</p>
<p>In Britain, the emergence of the more transmissible strain sent cases soaring in December and triggered a national lockdown in January. Cases have since plummeted, from about 60,000 a day in early January to about 7,000 a day now.</p>
<p>Still, a study shows the rate of decline slowing, and the British government says it will tread cautiously with plans to ease the lockdown. That process begins Monday with the reopening of schools. Infection rates are highest in people ages 13 to 17, and officials will watch closely to see whether the return to class brings a spike in infections.</p>
<p>While the U.K. variant is dominant in France, forcing lockdowns in the French Riviera city of Nice and the northern port of Dunkirk, the variant first detected in South Africa has emerged as the most prevalent in France&#8217;s Moselle region, which borders Germany and Luxembourg. It represents 55% of the virus circulating there.</p>
<p>Austria&#8217;s health minister said Saturday the U.K. variant is now dominant in his country. But the South Africa variant is also a concern in a district of Austria that extends from Italy to Germany, with Austrian officials announcing plans to vaccinate most of the 84,000 residents there to curb its spread. Austria is also requiring motorists along the Brenner highway, a major north-south route, to show negative test results.</p>
<p>The South Africa variant, now present in 26 European countries, is a source of particular concern because of doubts over whether the current vaccines are effective enough against it. The Brazilian variant, which appears capable of reinfecting people, has been detected in 15 European countries.</p>
<p>WHO and its partners are working to strengthen the genetic surveillance needed to track variants across the continent.</p>
<p>The mayor of Bollate has appealed to the regional governor to vaccinate all 40,000 residents immediately, though he expects to be told the vaccine supply is too tight.</p>
<p>Bollate has recorded 3,000 positive cases and 134 deaths — mostly among the elderly — since Italy was stricken a year ago. It took the brunt in the resurgence in November and December, and was caught completely off guard when the U.K. variant arrived, racing through school-age children before hitting families at home.</p>
<p>“People are starting to get tired that after a year there is no light at the end of the tunnel,” Vassallo said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877227</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">010221 coronavirus_UK variant_B117</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fighting Biden virus aid, GOP rekindles Obama-era strategy</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/fighting-biden-virus-aid-gop-rekindles-obama-era-strategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Republicans have one goal for President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief package: erode public support for the rescue plan by portraying it...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Republicans have one goal for President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion <a href="https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-legislation-coronavirus-pandemic-bills-2ffd868f5d3abed426e34e9427174813">COVID-19 relief package</a>: erode public support for the rescue plan by portraying it as too big, too bloated and too much wasteful public spending for a pandemic that’s almost over.</p>
<p>Senate Republicans prepared Saturday to vote lockstep against the relief bill, taking the calculated political risk that Americans will sour on the big-dollar spending for vaccination distribution, unemployment benefits, money for the states and other outlays as unnecessary, once they learn all the details.</p>
<p>Reviving a page from their 2009 takedown of President Barack Obama’s costly recovery from the financial crisis, they expect their opposition will pay political rewards, much like the earlier effort contributed to the House Republicans&#8217; rise to power.</p>
<p>It’s a tested strategy but comes at an uncertain, volatile time for the nation. Americans are experiencing flickers of optimism at the one-year anniversary of the deadly outbreak as more people are vaccinated. But new strains of the virus and a still shaky economy could unleash another devastating cycle of infections, lockdowns and deaths. More than 500,000 Americans have died.</p>
<p>So far, public support for Biden’s approach to the pandemic is high. Overall, 70% of Americans back the Democratic president’s handling of the virus response, including 44% of Republicans, according to <a href="https://apnews.com/article/ap-norc-poll-americans-largely-back-biden-virus-response-d365bff571c24f9d3575bcbd051780aa">a new poll </a>from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research.</p>
<p>Biden and Democrats warn that now is not the time to let up on aid, and that it&#8217;s better to risk doing too much than too little. They say the costs of paring back the rescue risk stalling out the economic recovery, as many believe happened in 2009.</p>
<p>“When the house is in flames, you don’t argue about how much of the fire to put out,” said Sen. Patty Murray, D-Wash., during Friday’s session.</p>
<p>“You do whatever it takes until the crisis is over,” she said. “And you do it as fast as you can.”</p>
<p>The debate in Congress reflects a fundamental divide in the country over how to contain and crush the pandemic and get the nation back to normal.</p>
<p>Nearly 10 million <a href="https://apnews.com/article/unemployment-united-states-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-27d58c2e9e2931985e537a08c761507d">jobs </a>have been lost and some 11 million households face evictions. While Democratic leaders generally side with health professionals supporting social distancing restrictions and easing into school and workplace reopenings, congressional Republicans have been more eager to conduct business as close to usual as possible.</p>
<p>The U.S. is not alone in confronting the daunting dilemma that holds serious ramifications about the size and scope of aid that&#8217;s needed to prevent further economic catastrophe.</p>
<p>Senate Republican leader Mitch McConnell, who is leading his minority party toward the &#8220;no&#8221; vote, said <a href="https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-bills-coronavirus-pandemic-ca3816a34f2405c3576251fda95ddbe3">Biden’s 628-page bill</a> is a Democratic “wish list” doesn’t meet the moment because the pandemic is lifting and the economy is ready for a “roaring recovery.&#8221;</p>
<p>“We are already on track to bounce back from the crisis,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Republicans argue Congress has already approved historic sums to counter the pandemic and worry the big spending will overheat the economy, spiking inflationary fears, though economists are mixed on those concerns. They have an opening with voters who the polling shows are skeptical of Biden&#8217;s handling of the economy.</p>
<p>McConnell expressed similar optimism last spring when he hit “pause” on new spending after approval of the initial round of aid. Around that time, then-President Donald Trump pledged that Americans would be all but back to normal by Easter Sunday.</p>
<p>But as Texas announced this past week it would seek to end face-mask wearing requirements, one of the key strategies public health officials say helps stop the spread of the virus, familiar political fault-lines and anxieties are resurfacing. Texas was among the first states to reopen in May, loosening restrictions at the start of the pandemic’s second wave that coursed through summer.</p>
<p>Jason Furman, the former chairman of Obama&#8217;s Council of Economic Advisers who now teaches at Harvard, agrees that parts of Biden’s package are too big, suggesting the $350 billion to states and cities could be reduced or have stricter guardrails against waste. But he said the bigger economic danger is in not doing enough.</p>
<p>Vaccines alone are not enough to ensure a healthy economy, he said. Households are struggling and businesses are confronting changing consumer habits and spending. The Biden package offers $1,400 direct payments to individuals, phased out for those earning $80,000 a year.</p>
<p>“If you add up the financial needs of households and the shortfalls facing states the American Rescue Plan overfills these,” he said by email. “But no legislation is perfect and, as I said, if the downside is families get a little more money in one particular year that is much less bad than if Congress fails to act.”</p>
<p>As Biden embarked on a go-it-alone partisan strategy, relying on Democratic votes for passage, Republicans are in fighting mode.</p>
<p>Senate Republicans forced an all-night reading of the bill Thursday, delaying the start of debate.</p>
<p>On Friday, senators launched an overnight session on amendments, most from Republicans, designed in part to change the bill, but also to highlight costly expenditures and less popular provisions. By early Saturday, most were failing.</p>
<p>Democrats&#8217; own amendment, to reduce extra <a href="https://apnews.com/article/senate-nears-virus-relief-bill-vote-fa965b1b413d811ad10549b3460c6643">jobless benefits from $400 a week to $300</a>, was splitting their ranks and causing further delays, before it eventually was accepted.</p>
<p>Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., who forced the bill reading, used charts and props to help Americans understand the size of the $1.9 trillion package.</p>
<p>“The human mind can&#8217;t really contemplate what a trillion is,” he said, before launching into examples. He suggested a stack of $1 bills would extend the distance halfway to the moon.</p>
<p>GOP Sen. Mike Braun of Indiana said by the time they&#8217;re done they hope to turn public opinion around.</p>
<p>“We’re going to expose every ugly detail of it,” he said.</p>
<p>The White House is well aware of the challenges ahead. Many of Biden&#8217;s staff members are veterans of the 2009 battles.</p>
<p>Press secretary Jen Psaki said Friday that at the time they didn&#8217;t do enough to explain to the American people the benefits in ways &#8220;that people would be talking about at their dinner tables.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877222</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/102419-lindsey-graham.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/102419-lindsey-graham.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/10/102419-lindsey-graham.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">102419 Sen. Lindsey Graham</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man killed after shooting in Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/man-killed-after-shooting-in-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877215</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A man has been killed after bullets fly in Miami, Friday night. Multiple gunshots were fired at a home near Northeast 70th Street and Northeast...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A man has been killed after bullets fly in Miami, Friday night.</p>
<p>Multiple gunshots were fired at a home near Northeast 70th Street and Northeast Third Avenue.</p>
<p>Police said when they arrived, they found the man deceased.</p>
<p>The cause of the shooting is now under investigation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877215</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030621-NE-Miami-Dade-shooting.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2f4c92d0-46e0-47e8-b722-fb4e53a3fd80/3c7895af-b6a9-481b-b129-6ebe5fb99f44/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218302~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2f4c92d0-46e0-47e8-b722-fb4e53a3fd80/3c7895af-b6a9-481b-b129-6ebe5fb99f44/main.mp4*~hmac=2798cea793918a9844a4006b4136e14c38d38ab59d30375d3e597febd07e7a47' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030621-NE-Miami-Dade-shooting.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030621-NE-Miami-Dade-shooting.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030621 NE Miami-Dade shooting</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zoo Miami&#8217;s North American river otter pups turn 1 month old</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/zoo-miamis-north-american-river-otter-pups-turn-1-month-old/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Zoo Miami celebrated a major milestone for three &#8220;otter-ly&#8221; adorable pups, just in time for the weekend. The North American river otters, two male and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zoo Miami celebrated a major milestone for three &#8220;otter-ly&#8221; adorable pups, just in time for the weekend.</p>
<p>The North American river otters, two male and one female, turned 1 month old on Friday.</p>
<p>The pups received their first neonatal exam earlier this week. Zoo officials said they &#8220;appear to be thriving&#8221; and are being well cared for by their first-time mom.</p>
<p>The otters are currently secluded with their mother in an off-exhibit area until they open their eyes and are able to swim.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877101</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_otter_pup_zoo_miami.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8d8f7bef-50c9-4b65-87bf-3fdc899bd59d/a94adfb2-0f5d-4a2f-9d2a-2a2258539aa3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216887~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8d8f7bef-50c9-4b65-87bf-3fdc899bd59d/a94adfb2-0f5d-4a2f-9d2a-2a2258539aa3/main.mp4*~hmac=884226d770317bb3ba1a7270d7bce0d1c2f517560dd6d11b418a0b0c1591d6a8' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_otter_pup_zoo_miami.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_otter_pup_zoo_miami.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_otter_pup_zoo_miami</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rental Ripoff: Woman scammed out of money weeks after moving into apartment</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/rental-ripoff-woman-scammed-out-of-money-weeks-after-moving-into-apartment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Weeks after moving into her new apartment, a Broward County woman was told to get out. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report, &#8220;Rental...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Weeks after moving into her new apartment, a Broward County woman was told to get out. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report, &#8220;Rental Ripoff.&#8221;</p>
<p>The coronavirus pandemic has created financial hardship for millions of Americans, but the scramble to save money can leave the door open to scams.</p>
<p>Jasmine, rented apartment: &#8220;The rent was low. I saw it as an opportunity to be able to save money.&#8221;</p>
<p>This is Jasmine. She asked us not to show her face.</p>
<p>She&#8217;s afraid of crossing paths with the man she says took her money and left her with no place to live.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;I just want him to be locked up or whatever, just to pay for what he did.&#8221;</p>
<p>In January, Jasmine found an ad on Craigslist for a room to rent in Fort Lauderdale. She toured the space with &#8220;Lorenzo,&#8221; the name used by the person who posted the ad.</p>
<p>She liked the apartment, and asked him write up a rental agreement.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a picture of him typing it up.</p>
<p>On Jan. 17, Jasmine gave &#8220;Lorenzo&#8221; a $300 deposit and $800 for the first month&#8217;s rent.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;I was happy. I didn&#8217;t have a problem.&#8221;</p>
<p>But just two weeks after she moved in, Jasmine ran into a big problem.</p>
<p>As she was leaving one morning, she found an eviction notice on her front door. It wasn&#8217;t addressed to her, but to Travis Davis, the man who she thought was her landlord &#8220;Lorenzo.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;We had 24-hour notice with his name on it, to evict the property.&#8221;</p>
<p>She tried calling Davis. He never picked up.</p>
<p>She then called the property manager listed on the notice. They told her the man she gave her money to was no landlord.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;He&#8217;s not the owner. He&#8217;s a tenant behind on rent &#8212; in that place that he&#8217;s renting out to other people.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to Broward court records, Travis Davis owes the actual owner $9,309 in back rent and other fees.</p>
<p>He agreed to pay off the debt through a payment plan, but after he missed his second payment in January, the final eviction notice went up on Jasmine&#8217;s door Feb. 3.</p>
<p>Fort Lauderdale Police detective Jesse Gossman: &#8220;Rental scams have been very common throughout the years.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fort Lauderdale Police detective Jesse Gossman says rental fraud cases like these are rising. He says the delay on eviction cases is adding to the problem.</p>
<p>Detective Jesse Gossman: &#8220;Which has allowed a window of opportunity for people to capitalize on that and purport themselves to be the legitimate owner, and take money from people.&#8221;</p>
<p>He has a warning for people searching online for cheap rent.</p>
<p>Detective Jesse Gossman: &#8220;Often people are going to Craigslist or other online message boards, and unfortunately, those message boards, anyone can go on there and post on them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jasmine was able to convince the property manager to let her lease the apartment. She now has a permanent home.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;I feel like I&#8217;m not going to come home, and I don&#8217;t know if stuff&#8217;s going to be outside, or if somebody&#8217;s going to be waiting for me. I&#8217;m a lot more comfortable now.&#8221;</p>
<p>But she still hopes to recover the money she paid to a fake landlord in a rental ripoff.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877058</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a63a2817-e939-45a6-a64d-9f069175893b/7840f189-30ee-4b92-a473-6e4033b4c095/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219573~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a63a2817-e939-45a6-a64d-9f069175893b/7840f189-30ee-4b92-a473-6e4033b4c095/main.mp4*~hmac=6ba890eae272903e6fcde36be4d6d7d37022acd1497a2c215785e071673550ef' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Driver flees after crashing into cyclist in Brickell</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/driver-flees-after-crashing-into-cyclist-in-brickell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 03:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877015</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bicyclist Michael Hernandez is thankful to be alive after becoming the victim of a hit-and-run in Miami&#8217;s Brickell neighborhood. &#8220;He clipped me probably doing 50,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bicyclist Michael Hernandez is thankful to be alive after becoming the victim of a hit-and-run in Miami&#8217;s Brickell neighborhood.</p>
<p>&#8220;He clipped me probably doing 50, 60 miles an hour,&#8221; Hernandez said.</p>
<p>City of Miami Police said the collision happened near Brickell Avenue and 14th Street, Friday morning.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s an area where Hernandez and his friends meet every day to ride their bikes, but he said at around 6:30 a.m., his ride became dangerous.</p>
<p>&#8220;I hear some screeching tires behind me, and I look back, and all I see is this car just hauling down the road,&#8221; said Hernandez.</p>
<p>The car rammed into the back of his bike leaving him hurt and parts of the bike mangled.</p>
<p>&#8220;It threw my bicycle saddle pretty much straight into my rear butt cheek and right through the rear wheel, went through me, hit a light pole and into a tree,&#8221; said Hernandez.</p>
<p>7News cameras captured an orange cone where the light pole used to be, as well as shattered glass.</p>
<p>Hernandez&#8217;s attorney, Lee Marks, said after causing all the damage, the driver fled the scene.</p>
<p>&#8220;About 35 minutes later, he returned, went into the vehicle and retrieved a knapsack and a small bag, what looked like contraband, and then looked around and took off again,&#8221; Marks said. &#8220;He tried to get into an Uber. The witnesses stopped him, and then he took off up 15th Road westbound.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;At that point, we&#8217;re like, &#8216;All right, this is not really an accident anymore, it&#8217;s probably a crime scene,'&#8221; said Hernandez.</p>
<p>Hernandez was able to take a picture of who, he said, was behind the wheel of the vehicle.</p>
<p>When officers arrived on scene, they found a gun inside the car.</p>
<p>Hernandez said he&#8217;s grateful to be alive.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s what I played in my head every time, and I&#8217;m thankful,&#8221; he said. &#8220;I thank God I walked away from it because the possibility of, best-case scenario in my head, is shattered leg, worst-case scenario, that car could&#8217;ve killed me easily.&#8221;</p>
<p>Hernandez still has some minor bruising and soreness but is OK.</p>
<p>If you have any information on this hit-and-run, call Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a $1,000 reward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877015</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hit-and-run-driver.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/87522198-b3f8-457a-aa99-9b7ae3fbc5dc/2c54428e-f0da-400b-a298-7b0da5e4ea48/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218860~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/87522198-b3f8-457a-aa99-9b7ae3fbc5dc/2c54428e-f0da-400b-a298-7b0da5e4ea48/main.mp4*~hmac=d036c455b9bd6e6fc1eecd06b710232d049e3892b026acd68871a0bf28950a65' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hit-and-run-driver.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hit-and-run-driver.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hit and run driver</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NE Miami-Dade couple&#8217;s food truck stolen from outside apartment complex</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-dade/ne-miami-dade-couples-food-truck-stolen-from-outside-apartment-complex/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 03:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877043</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A South Florida chef and his girlfriend are reeling hours after, they said, they witnessed thieves driving away with their sole source of income: their...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Florida chef and his girlfriend are reeling hours after, they said, they witnessed thieves driving away with their sole source of income: their food truck.</p>
<p>The overnight steal, just after midnight on Friday, has left Chef Bryan Rivas and his girlfriend, Andrea Larrotta, scrambling to find a solution.</p>
<p>&#8220;It hurts us. It hurts a lot, due to the fact that we&#8217;ve got to pay bills, especially during a pandemic, when people nowadays are hurting a lot,&#8221; said Rivas.</p>
<p>The chef said he and Larrotta were out on the balcony of their apartment, located along Northeast 202nd Street, off West Dixie Highway, in Northeast Miami-Dade, at the time of the incident.</p>
<p>Rivas said he bought the food truck, technically a trailer, at the start of the pandemic so he could make a living cooking up what he describes as exclusive cuisine.</p>
<p>&#8220;From Mediterranean cuisine, Indian cuisine, Latin cuisine and American cuisine,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>That is, he said, until he stood on his balcony and watched a crime unfold.</p>
<p>&#8220;I see my truck slowly moving, and I glanced, and for a second, I just paused,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Rivas said he spotted a van towing the 16-foot trailer where he does his work.</p>
<p>Surveillance cameras at a nearby building captured a glimpse of the theft in action.</p>
<p>&#8220;Completely shocked. We didn&#8217;t think this was going to happen to us,&#8221; said Larrotta.</p>
<p>Rivas said he sometimes parks the trailer right outside his community along West Dixie Highway. This time, he was trying to prepare it for a big event in Wynwood this weekend.</p>
<p>Once they spotted the thief, the couple said they rushed to track the trailer down, but it was too late.</p>
<p>&#8220;I jumped in the car and just tried to chase the truck down, but the truck got away,&#8221; said Rivas.</p>
<p>The couple said they may have to cancel upcoming gigs until they figure out where to go from here.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve got to pay our house bills, our rent, water, food to survive,&#8221; said Rivas.</p>
<p>&#8220;We don&#8217;t have a backup plan, so that&#8217;s what makes it even worse,&#8221; said Larrotta. &#8220;It&#8217;s very, very hard.&#8221;</p>
<p>But the couple said they&#8217;re hopeful someone can spot the trailer and call police, so they can get back to work in their mobile kitchen.</p>
<p>Larrotta said she has a message for the thief.</p>
<p>&#8220;If you have any kind of remorse or any kind of conscience in you, please return the trailer back,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The couple said the trailer has a GPS unit, but it only pings once a day, so they are hoping that within the next 24 hours, they&#8217;ll have a better idea of its current location.</p>
<p>If you see the trailer or have any information on this theft, call Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a $1,000 reward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877043</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_stolen_food_truck_trailer_NEMD_surveillance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fca49c9e-30f4-43dd-85b2-f30fdbd5c7a3/3f88982f-d773-40d2-b496-a23e5c3b0c03/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219240~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fca49c9e-30f4-43dd-85b2-f30fdbd5c7a3/3f88982f-d773-40d2-b496-a23e5c3b0c03/main.mp4*~hmac=892b969f5729cb0f3b67dd3a3d44f7f793023f533fdf284a927aac903d08340c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_stolen_food_truck_trailer_NEMD_surveillance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_stolen_food_truck_trailer_NEMD_surveillance.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_stolen_food_truck_trailer_NEMD_surveillance</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>15-year-old arrested after virtual school threat in Pompano Beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/15-year-old-arrested-after-virtual-school-threat-in-pompano-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 02:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Authorities have arrested a 15-year-old after a school scare in Pompano Beach. Investigators said the teen entered a virtual classroom on Thursday and said he...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Authorities have arrested a 15-year-old after a school scare in Pompano Beach.</p>
<p>Investigators said the teen entered a virtual classroom on Thursday and said he was going to commit a shooting before turning on the video camera and dancing.</p>
<p>Pompano Beach Middle School was <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/all-clear-given-at-pompano-beach-middle-school-after-phoned-in-shooting-threat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">placed on lockdown</a> while Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office deputies worked to determine the credibility of the threat.</p>
<p>The teenager was arrested and charged with written threats to kill, false report of a bomb or firearm and disruption of a school function.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877031</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-pompano-beach-middle-school.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b122ff24-287a-447e-80d5-f878be14fc70/b0976616-aa84-47ed-aaca-3cbe48439230/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216974~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b122ff24-287a-447e-80d5-f878be14fc70/b0976616-aa84-47ed-aaca-3cbe48439230/main.mp4*~hmac=9782197e08a2535dfa453a81ad58ceb8eeb316a74f332a9ddc57d0f031b4267c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-pompano-beach-middle-school.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030421-pompano-beach-middle-school.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030421 pompano beach middle school</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senate Dems strike jobless aid deal, COVID relief bill OK in sight</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/senate-dems-strike-jobless-aid-deal-relief-bill-ok-in-sight/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate leaders and moderate Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin struck a deal over emergency jobless benefits, breaking a logjam that had stalled the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate leaders and moderate Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin struck a deal over emergency jobless benefits, breaking a logjam that had stalled the party&#8217;s showpiece $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief bill.</p>
<p>The compromise, announced by the West Virginia lawmaker and a Democratic aide late Friday, seemed to clear the way for the Senate to begin a climactic, marathon series of votes and, eventually, approval of the sweeping legislation.</p>
<p>The overall bill, President Joe Biden’s foremost legislative priority, is aimed at battling the killer pandemic and nursing the staggered economy back to health. It would provide direct payments of up to $1,400 to most Americans and money for COVID-19 vaccines and testing, aid to state and local governments, help for schools and the airline industry and subsidies for health insurance.</p>
<p>The Senate next faced votes on a pile of amendments that were likely to last overnight, mostly on Republican proposals virtually certain to fail but designed to force Democrats to cast politically awkward votes.</p>
<p>More significantly, the jobless benefits agreement suggested it was just a matter of time until the Senate passes the bill. That would ship it back to the House, which was expected to give it final congressional approval and whisk it to Biden for his signature.</p>
<p>White House press secretary Jen Psaki said Biden supports the compromise on jobless payments.</p>
<p>The day&#8217;s lengthy standoff underscored the headaches confronting party leaders over the next two years — and the tensions between progressives and centrists — as they try moving their agenda through the Congress with their slender majorities.</p>
<p>Manchin is probably the chamber’s most conservative Democrat, and a kingmaker in the 50-50 Senate. But the party can’t tilt too far center to win Manchin’s vote without endangering progressive support in the House, where they have a mere 10-vote edge.</p>
<p>Aiding unemployed Americans is a top Democratic priority. But it’s also an issue that drives a wedge between progressives seeking to help jobless constituents cope with the bleak economy and Manchin and other moderates who have wanted to trim some of the bill’s costs.</p>
<p>Biden noted Friday&#8217;s jobs report showing that employers added 379,000 workers — an unexpectedly strong showing. That&#8217;s still small compared to the 10 million fewer jobs since the pandemic struck a year ago.</p>
<p>“Without a rescue plan, these gains are going to slow,&#8221; Biden said. “We can’t afford one step forward and two steps backwards. We need to beat the virus, provide essential relief, and build an inclusive recovery.&#8221;</p>
<p>The overall bill faces a solid wall of GOP opposition, and Republicans used the unemployment impasse to accuse Biden of refusing to seek compromise with them.</p>
<p>“You could pick up the phone and end this right now,” Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., said of Biden.</p>
<p>But in an encouraging sign for Biden, a poll by The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research found that 70% of Americans support his handling of the pandemic, including a noteworthy 44% of Republicans.</p>
<p>The House approved a relief bill last weekend that included $400 weekly jobless benefits — on top of regular state payments — through August. Manchin was hoping to reduce those costs, asserting that level of payment would discourage people from returning to work, a rationale most Democrats and many economists reject.</p>
<p>As the day began, Democrats asserted they&#8217;d reached a compromise between party moderates and progressives extending emergency jobless benefits at $300 weekly into early October.</p>
<p>That plan, sponsored by Sen. Tom Carper, D-Del., also included tax reductions on some unemployment benefits. Without that, many Americans abruptly tossed out of jobs would face unexpected tax bills.</p>
<p>But by midday, lawmakers said Manchin was ready to support a less generous Republican version. That led to hours of talks involving White House aides, top Senate Democrats and Manchin as the party tried finding a way to salvage its unemployment aid package.</p>
<p>The compromise announced Friday night would provide $300 weekly, with the final check paid on Sept. 6, and includes the tax break on benefits.</p>
<p>Before the unemployment benefits drama began, senators voted 58-42 to kill a top progressive priority, a gradual increase in the current $7.25 hourly minimum wage to $15 over five years.</p>
<p>Eight Democrats voted against that proposal, suggesting that Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and other progressives vowing to continue the effort in coming months will face a difficult fight.</p>
<p>That vote began shortly after 11 a.m. EST and was not formally gaveled to a close until nearly 12 hours later as Senate work ground to a halt amid the unemployment benefit negotiations.</p>
<p>Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell chided Democrats, calling their daylong effort to work out the unemployment amendment a “spectacle.&#8221;</p>
<p>“What this proves is there are benefits to bipartisanship when you&#8217;re dealing with an issue of this magnitude,&#8221; McConnell said.</p>
<p>Republicans criticized the overall relief bill as a liberal spend-fest that ignores that growing numbers of vaccinations and signs of a stirring economy suggest that the twin crises are easing.</p>
<p>“Democrats inherited a tide that was already turning.” McConnell said.</p>
<p>Democrats reject that, citing the job losses and numerous people still struggling to buy food and pay rent.</p>
<p>“If you just look at a big number you say, ‘Oh, everything&#8217;s getting a little better,'&#8221; said Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y. “It&#8217;s not for the lower half of America. It&#8217;s not.&#8221;</p>
<p>Friday&#8217;s gridlock over unemployment benefits gridlock wasn&#8217;t the first delay on the relief package. On Thursday Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., forced the chamber&#8217;s clerks to read aloud the entire 628-page relief bill, an exhausting task that took staffers 10 hours and 44 minutes and ended shortly after 2 a.m. EST.</p>
<p>Democrats made a host of other late changes to the bill, designed to nail down support. They ranged from extra money for food programs and federal subsidies for health care for workers who lose jobs to funds for rural health care and language assuring minimum amounts of money for smaller states.</p>
<p>In another late bargain that satisfied moderates, Biden and Senate Democrats agreed Wednesday to make some higher earners ineligible for the direct checks to individuals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877008</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-senate-chamber-floor.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030521 senate chamber floor</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drone captures pod of dolphins, shark together near Miami Beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/drone-captures-pod-of-dolphins-shark-together-near-miami-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876911</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Drone footage in Miami Beach caught a pod of dolphins getting a surprise visitor. The dolphins were swimming near Miami Beach on Friday morning when...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drone footage in Miami Beach caught a pod of dolphins getting a surprise visitor.</p>
<p>The dolphins were swimming near Miami Beach on Friday morning when a shark quickly caught up to them.</p>
<p>They then could be seen swimming off together.</p>
<p>Researchers have said sometimes sharks and dolphins swim together because they&#8217;re all looking for food.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876911</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/dolphins-and-shark.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8060714b-3add-43d1-add2-a163ec6f7f38/a646feed-f82a-42f1-9185-502a7407eb96/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216865~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8060714b-3add-43d1-add2-a163ec6f7f38/a646feed-f82a-42f1-9185-502a7407eb96/main.mp4*~hmac=bf5cd5c119c5da0433f5db84b754b8095f60c5286ef9b8c062b3e2d5567cc211' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/dolphins-and-shark.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/dolphins-and-shark.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">dolphins and shark</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man steals puppy at gunpoint from owner during walk in NW Miami-Dade</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/man-steals-puppy-at-gunpoint-from-owner-during-walk-in-nw-miami-dade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876935</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A woman is desperate to get her dog back after the pup was stolen at gunpoint in Northwest Miami-Dade. Jennifer Spratling walks her dog early...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A woman is desperate to get her dog back after the pup was stolen at gunpoint in Northwest Miami-Dade.</p>
<p>Jennifer Spratling walks her dog early in the morning every day, but she said she never expected what happened on Friday morning.</p>
<p>&#8220;He walked up to me, pointed the gun at me and told me to give him, &#8216;the [expletive] dog,'&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Spratling told 7News it was the scariest moment of her life when she came face to face with a man pointing a gun at her chest.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m just standing there like panicking, I didn&#8217;t know what to do,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I didn&#8217;t have my cellphone on me, no cars were coming up and down the street, so I just didn&#8217;t know what to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Her 4-month-old dog Bella was taken in the area of Northwest 23rd Avenue and 87th Street.</p>
<p>&#8220;At first I was a little hesitant and then he, you know, like, &#8216;I&#8217;m not playing,&#8217; then I dropped the leash, and he grabbed the dog, and he just ran off,&#8221; Spratling said.</p>
<p>Spratling said the gunman was dressed all in black. She believes her dog was a target due to her being an American Bully worth $5,000.</p>
<p>Now she says she&#8217;s hoping her dog is found and not used for constant breeding.</p>
<p>&#8220;She&#8217;s like family,&#8221; said Spratling. &#8220;She&#8217;s like a child to me. I don&#8217;t have any kids. I&#8217;m just real, real sad, and I&#8217;m just wishing I wouldn&#8217;t have went walking this morning.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you have any information on Bella&#8217;s whereabouts, call Miami-Dade Crime Stoppers at 305-471-TIPS. Remember, you can always remain anonymous, and you may be eligible for a $1,000 reward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876935</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/bella-stolen-dog.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8e47e411-7303-43c6-8e86-865b26eb880d/d2225b43-f1ff-4fde-8022-81312722a476/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219161~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8e47e411-7303-43c6-8e86-865b26eb880d/d2225b43-f1ff-4fde-8022-81312722a476/main.mp4*~hmac=2319c25b14bbe1e4713e176d9b1cf682a09ac2e41f3860d88ca421dee2324fa4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/bella-stolen-dog.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/bella-stolen-dog.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">bella stolen dog</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fauci, Gloria Estefan discuss COVID concerns on Instagram Live</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/fauci-gloria-estefan-discuss-covid-concerns-on-instagram-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gloria Estefan and Dr. Anthony Fauci engaged in a conversation about COVID-19 on Instagram Live. Fauci, President Joe Biden&#8217;s chief medical adviser, joined the singer...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gloria Estefan and Dr. Anthony Fauci engaged in a conversation about COVID-19 on Instagram Live.</p>
<p>Fauci, President Joe Biden&#8217;s chief medical adviser, joined the singer virtually for a discussion, Friday.</p>
<p>The two spoke on a range of topics relating to the coronavirus pandemic, including vaccination concerns and the efforts of the scientific community.</p>
<p>&#8220;Even though it took less than a year to get the vaccine, when it usually takes several years, that speed is a reflection of scientific advances,&#8221; said Fauci. &#8220;Safety was not compromised, nor was scientific integrity compromised.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fauci also took questions from commenters on other related topics, such as the benefits of the United States returning to the World Health Organization.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876954</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a132b296-ff67-4b9f-a059-3a456e8a2e1d/13c1e4c6-be28-4847-9770-637c9b5201aa/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217319~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a132b296-ff67-4b9f-a059-3a456e8a2e1d/13c1e4c6-be28-4847-9770-637c9b5201aa/main.mp4*~hmac=532bc40f265b8c202e69c557f21067fe2bf7a131b8108d92295ed5d62cb28313' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
