<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Special Reports &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:14:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Special Reports &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Rental Ripoff: Woman scammed out of money weeks after moving into apartment</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/rental-ripoff-woman-scammed-out-of-money-weeks-after-moving-into-apartment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Weeks after moving into her new apartment, a Broward County woman was told to get out. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report, &#8220;Rental...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Weeks after moving into her new apartment, a Broward County woman was told to get out. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report, &#8220;Rental Ripoff.&#8221;</p>
<p>The coronavirus pandemic has created financial hardship for millions of Americans, but the scramble to save money can leave the door open to scams.</p>
<p>Jasmine, rented apartment: &#8220;The rent was low. I saw it as an opportunity to be able to save money.&#8221;</p>
<p>This is Jasmine. She asked us not to show her face.</p>
<p>She&#8217;s afraid of crossing paths with the man she says took her money and left her with no place to live.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;I just want him to be locked up or whatever, just to pay for what he did.&#8221;</p>
<p>In January, Jasmine found an ad on Craigslist for a room to rent in Fort Lauderdale. She toured the space with &#8220;Lorenzo,&#8221; the name used by the person who posted the ad.</p>
<p>She liked the apartment, and asked him write up a rental agreement.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a picture of him typing it up.</p>
<p>On Jan. 17, Jasmine gave &#8220;Lorenzo&#8221; a $300 deposit and $800 for the first month&#8217;s rent.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;I was happy. I didn&#8217;t have a problem.&#8221;</p>
<p>But just two weeks after she moved in, Jasmine ran into a big problem.</p>
<p>As she was leaving one morning, she found an eviction notice on her front door. It wasn&#8217;t addressed to her, but to Travis Davis, the man who she thought was her landlord &#8220;Lorenzo.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;We had 24-hour notice with his name on it, to evict the property.&#8221;</p>
<p>She tried calling Davis. He never picked up.</p>
<p>She then called the property manager listed on the notice. They told her the man she gave her money to was no landlord.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;He&#8217;s not the owner. He&#8217;s a tenant behind on rent &#8212; in that place that he&#8217;s renting out to other people.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to Broward court records, Travis Davis owes the actual owner $9,309 in back rent and other fees.</p>
<p>He agreed to pay off the debt through a payment plan, but after he missed his second payment in January, the final eviction notice went up on Jasmine&#8217;s door Feb. 3.</p>
<p>Fort Lauderdale Police detective Jesse Gossman: &#8220;Rental scams have been very common throughout the years.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fort Lauderdale Police detective Jesse Gossman says rental fraud cases like these are rising. He says the delay on eviction cases is adding to the problem.</p>
<p>Detective Jesse Gossman: &#8220;Which has allowed a window of opportunity for people to capitalize on that and purport themselves to be the legitimate owner, and take money from people.&#8221;</p>
<p>He has a warning for people searching online for cheap rent.</p>
<p>Detective Jesse Gossman: &#8220;Often people are going to Craigslist or other online message boards, and unfortunately, those message boards, anyone can go on there and post on them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jasmine was able to convince the property manager to let her lease the apartment. She now has a permanent home.</p>
<p>Jasmine: &#8220;I feel like I&#8217;m not going to come home, and I don&#8217;t know if stuff&#8217;s going to be outside, or if somebody&#8217;s going to be waiting for me. I&#8217;m a lot more comfortable now.&#8221;</p>
<p>But she still hopes to recover the money she paid to a fake landlord in a rental ripoff.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877058</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a63a2817-e939-45a6-a64d-9f069175893b/7840f189-30ee-4b92-a473-6e4033b4c095/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219573~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a63a2817-e939-45a6-a64d-9f069175893b/7840f189-30ee-4b92-a473-6e4033b4c095/main.mp4*~hmac=6ba890eae272903e6fcde36be4d6d7d37022acd1497a2c215785e071673550ef' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Rental_Ripoff_Broward_eviction_notice</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost and Found: South Florida filmmaker finds brother believed to have been kidnapped from Colombia</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/lost-and-found-south-florida-filmmaker-finds-brother-believed-to-have-been-kidnapped-from-colombia/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 04:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When a loved one goes missing, a South Florida filmmaker goes on the hunt for answers. His search stretched over two decades and thousands of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a loved one goes missing, a South Florida filmmaker goes on the hunt for answers. His search stretched over two decades and thousands of miles, and now, he&#8217;s turned his story into a movie of inspiration. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has his special assignment report: Lost and Found.</p>
<p>A well-worn Bible serves as a source of inspiration for this South Florida filmmaker.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez keeps it close by as he edits video of his latest project: a story of his own life.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez, filmmaker: &#8220;I have a lot of craziness around, and I grew up in a difficult environment.&#8221;</p>
<p>In 1988, Juan&#8217;s 3-year-old brother, Jhonatan, went missing from outside their home in Bogota, Colombia. Juan was just 5 at the time.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;We were screaming, &#8216;Jhonatan, Jhonatan!&#8217; all around. I remember trying to search under the bed and different places in the house, in the kitchen.&#8221;</p>
<p>They never found Jhonatan and believed he was kidnapped.</p>
<p>Seven years later, their fears were confirmed.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;This guy who took my brother returned and confesses to my mom that he did it. He said because my stepfather ordered him to do it, and he said, &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it. The kid is fine. The kid is good. He&#8217;s with a wealthy family in the United States.'&#8221;</p>
<p>After hearing that, Juan made it a mission to find his brother.</p>
<p>He grew up, became an actor, came to Miami to work, attend film school and search for Jhonatan.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;I need a miracle. It was very difficult. How am I going to find my brother?&#8221;</p>
<p>Every clue Juan uncovered led to dead ends.</p>
<p>He was ready to give up until he came across a magazine article about his favorite actor.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;An interview that they did to Denzel Washington. They ask you, &#8216;What code do you live by?&#8217; And this changed me forever. He said, &#8216;I read from the Bible every day,&#8217; and I was like, &#8216;No!'&#8221;</p>
<p>Juan started doing the same.</p>
<p>He says it gave him faith that he would find the key to locating his brother.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;And from nowhere, I got this email. It was MyHeritage DNA company.&#8221;</p>
<p>In 2018, the company was offering free DNA testing for people looking for long-lost relatives.</p>
<p>Juan was selected to take a test. He took it and waited.</p>
<p>A year later, the company found Jhonatan &#8212; not in the United States, but in Europe.</p>
<p>Early last year, Juan flew from Miami to Norway to be reunited with Jhonatan.</p>
<p>Jhonatan Jimenez: &#8220;Hey, Mama! Hola, Mamita! Que tal?&#8221;</p>
<p>From there, they went to Colombia, so Jhonatan could meet his mother.</p>
<p>We visited with them all together in Bogota via Zoom.</p>
<p>Jhonatan Jimenez: &#8220;All my life, I wanted to find my family, but the need of doing it grew as I got older.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jhonatan grew up in Norway after being adopted from a Colombian orphanage at 3 years old.</p>
<p>Jhonatan Jimenez: &#8220;I had very few memories there and very little knowledge about what had actually happened to me.&#8221;</p>
<p>He tried DNA testing years before, but never found any relatives.</p>
<p>Jhonatan Jimenez: &#8220;Now, I have a brother who&#8217;s protecting me and who&#8217;s always standing up for me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Juan, for you, what&#8217;s it like to be next to him?&#8221;</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;I don&#8217;t have enough words to express what this means for me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Juan says the family is focused on healing.</p>
<p>Part of that includes turning their story into a documentary.</p>
<p>Juan Jimenez: &#8220;It&#8217;s possible. Miracles exist, miracles do exist.&#8221;</p>
<p>Juan hopes by sharing his personal story of a loved one lost and found, he can inspire others to never give up a search for family.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875526</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-Lost-and-Found.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8858b369-44aa-43f5-bfff-8cdc422fe620/a137dafa-494f-4c9d-9a70-6a9adf6c0015/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219664~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8858b369-44aa-43f5-bfff-8cdc422fe620/a137dafa-494f-4c9d-9a70-6a9adf6c0015/main.mp4*~hmac=d0fc3616d737ae62bc3b1a0d008ff32e89a211feb77be16019ee0fe9a2b95c1e' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-Lost-and-Found.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-Lost-and-Found.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030321 Lost and Found</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spotting the Signs: Researchers release pictures of symptom of rare, COVID-linked illness in children</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/spotting-the-signs-researchers-release-pictures-of-symptom-of-rare-covid-linked-illness-in-children/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has been almost a year since experts first identified a mysterious, COVID-linked illness in children. Now, researchers have released pictures of one key symptom....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been almost a year since experts first identified a mysterious, COVID-linked illness in children. Now, researchers have released pictures of one key symptom. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report: Spotting the Signs.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s called Multisystem Inflammatory Syndrome in Children &#8212; or MIS-C.</p>
<p>The illness can appear weeks after a child gets COVID.</p>
<p>Dr. Maria Van Kerkhove, World Health Organization, May 2020: &#8220;It seems to be a very rare syndrome, but we need more information.&#8221;</p>
<p>Experts are learning more.</p>
<p>The CDC says there have been 2,060 reported MIS-C cases in the U.S., and a total of 30 children have died.</p>
<p>Doctors are now providing picture proof of one of the syndrome&#8217;s most common symptoms: rashes.</p>
<p>Dr. Marcos Mestre, Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital: &#8220;In terms of a journal article, that&#8217;s the first time I had seen it kind of summarized in that manner.&#8221;</p>
<p>These pictures are from researchers at Children&#8217;s Hospital of Philadelphia.</p>
<p>The team studied seven MIS-C patients and discovered all of them developed a rash on their lower body, and five out of seven had a rash on their inner thighs.</p>
<p>Some had rashes on their arms, legs and dime-sized circle lesions on their backs and chests.</p>
<p>Dr. Marcos Mestre is the chief medical officer at Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital.</p>
<p>Dr. Marcos Mestre: &#8220;Typically, they&#8217;re going to be these kind of red, flat type rashes that just kind of don&#8217;t have a clear shape around it. It kind of spreads out throughout the body.&#8221;</p>
<p>While there was not one defining rash, researchers hope their work will help other doctors diagnose future cases.</p>
<p>And for parents, rashes are just one sign of possible trouble.</p>
<p>Dr. Marcos Mestre: &#8220;The symptoms we always tell parents to watch for are fevers, sometimes abdominal pain, some redness of the lips, redness of the eyes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;And at that point, nobody had really heard of MIS-C.&#8221;</p>
<p>Melanie Somnitz, mother: &#8220;Correct, correct.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was last April when Melanie Somnitz&#8217;s son Ezra got sick.</p>
<p>The St. Augustine mother says her 6-year-old had a fever, bloodshot eyes and was throwing up.</p>
<p>Melanie Somnitz: &#8220;Both cheeks were very flush. He had the rash on his neck. He had a rash on his torso and on both of his arms.&#8221;</p>
<p>Despite MIS-C, Melanie says Ezra is doing well today.</p>
<p>Dr. Marcos Mestre: &#8220;Over the last month, month and a half, we had seen them pick up a little bit more. Not quite what it was in the summertime.&#8221;</p>
<p>Just how many MIS-C cases have been diagnosed here in South Florida since beginning of the pandemic? Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital says they have seen 50 to 60 patients. At Jackson&#8217;s Holtz Children&#8217;s Hospital, they have treated nine children. Up in Broward, Joe DiMaggio Children&#8217;s Hospital has treated 60 patients with another 20 at Broward Health&#8217;s Salah Foundation Children&#8217;s Hospital.</p>
<p>Dr. Marcos Mestre: &#8220;Just to also ease the mind of families and parents, this is a very rare condition with COVID infection, but at the same time, we always want to make sure families are aware of it.&#8221;</p>
<p>These heartbroken parents in Tennessee also want families to be aware.</p>
<p>Priscilla Morse, mother: &#8220;She was everyone&#8217;s favorite. She was the light of my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>Priscilla and David Morse&#8217;s daughter Gigi is one of COVID&#8217;s youngest victims. The 6-year-old died last summer.</p>
<p>Priscilla Morse: &#8220;She did have a rash on her shoulder, which we found out later is a child sign of COVID. We didn&#8217;t know, so any parents who have kids who are lethargic, throwing up and have a rash, they need to go. That&#8217;s the last photo that I took of her.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gigi&#8217;s case is a reminder that although adults are most at risk from COVID, spotting the signs early on children is key.</p>
<p><strong>MORE INFO: </strong></p>
<p><a href="https://academic.oup.com/ofid/advance-article/doi/10.1093/ofid/ofab074/6138887">Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia study (via Open Forum Infectious Diseases)</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mis-c/index.html">CDC/MIS-C information</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874724</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-multi-inflammatory-syndrom-in-children.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d2a3d8e0-67ed-4c8e-ac30-4775f8b1b55f/b6b92d81-25a7-4a80-ad66-3bf81939e2c5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219654~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d2a3d8e0-67ed-4c8e-ac30-4775f8b1b55f/b6b92d81-25a7-4a80-ad66-3bf81939e2c5/main.mp4*~hmac=00d0a23ee3513057eaee15572066ffc17c67246c871eddf64291e37f6353a407' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-multi-inflammatory-syndrom-in-children.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030221-multi-inflammatory-syndrom-in-children.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030221 Multisystem Inflammatory Syndrome in Children</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scarred and Scared: Police say woman &#8216;intentionally&#8217; poured hot tea on boyfriend, sending him to burn unit for a month</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/scarred-and-scared-police-say-woman-intentionally-poured-hot-tea-on-boyfriend-sending-him-to-burn-unit-for-a-month/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 04:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=873937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A scorned lover is charged in a disturbing criminal case. What started with a Victoria&#8217;s Secret receipt ended with a man in a hospital burn...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A scorned lover is charged in a disturbing criminal case. What started with a Victoria&#8217;s Secret receipt ended with a man in a hospital burn unit for a month. 7&#8217;s Karen Hensel has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report, &#8220;Scarred and Scared.&#8221;</p>
<p>Andy Polo says he had it all: a good job as a pro-body builder and a girlfriend.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I never saw it coming. That woman was my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>That woman is 52-year-old Yvonne Vega.</p>
<p>Andy says they&#8217;ve known each other for 40 years and dated for four.</p>
<p>Until May 3 of last year.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I hate that day. I&#8217;m sorry, I just &#8211; as strong as I am, I&#8217;m not strong enough to overpower that.&#8221;</p>
<p>To understand his very raw and intense pain, we have to go back 10 months, to that day in May.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I was at work, and she called me up and said, &#8216;Can you come down and change the radiator in my car?&#8217; and I said, &#8216;Sure.'&#8221;</p>
<p>While Andy worked on her car, she borrowed his truck.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I said, &#8216;I&#8217;m going in the house. I&#8217;m going to take a shower. I&#8217;m going to lay down. Wake me up when you get back.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Napping naked on his back&#8230;</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I woke up to her throwing boiling hot water on me from across the bed. She used some obscenities and said, &#8216;Who the &#8216;f&#8217; is this for?&#8217; and she had a Victoria&#8217;s Secret gift card and a receipt in her hand.&#8221;</p>
<p>Yvonne had found the gift card and receipt in his truck.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I said, &#8216;Why did you do this to me?&#8217; and she says, &#8221;Cause I love you.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Andy suffered second- and third-degree burns.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;The next thing I know, the whole panel of my back, all my skin came off and fell on the ground, and then I ran for my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>He begged her to call 911.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I said, &#8216;I need to go to the hospital. Call the ambulance, please.&#8217; She says, &#8216;No, you&#8217;ll be all right.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Instead, he says, Yvonne drove to a gas station to buy ice.</p>
<p>Andy then called 911 himself, but when Yvonne returned and heard the ambulance sirens&#8230;</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;She jumped in my truck and fled. I never saw her again.&#8221;</p>
<p>Airlifted to Jackson Memorial Hospital, Andy spent the next month in the Ryder Trauma Burn Unit.</p>
<p>Yvonne was arrested.</p>
<p>The Miami-Dade Police report says Yvonne confronted Andy about what she called his &#8220;infidelity&#8221; and talked of &#8220;&#8230; intentionally throwing the hot tea onto the victim, in self-defense.&#8221;</p>
<p>But when questioned further, she admitted he had never harmed her.</p>
<p>Detectives wrote, &#8220;&#8230;the investigation revealed&#8230;&#8221; the burn was done &#8220;&#8230;intentionally, not accidentally&#8230;&#8221; and it appeared &#8220;&#8230;she had intentionally targeted his genitals.&#8221;</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I&#8217;m in the trauma unit at JMH, and six blocks away is Wynwood. She gets out of jail and goes to Wynwood and parties.&#8221;</p>
<p>The report noted an Instagram picture showing what Andy described to police as &#8220;&#8230;her and her daughters celebrating her accomplishment and freedom.&#8221;</p>
<p>When he was finally released from the hospital, Andy says he turned to his gym to recover.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;That&#8217;s my happy place. Monday morning, I was on a walker, and I went back to the gym. My legs couldn&#8217;t work, but my arms could.&#8221;</p>
<p>A judge has ordered Yvonne to stay away from him.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Andy is working to recover emotionally.</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;I&#8217;ve been diagnosed now with [post-traumatic stress disorder]. I&#8217;m diagnosed with hypervigilance. I walk around like this.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;Why did you want to talk with us?&#8221;</p>
<p>Andy Polo: &#8220;Because it brings awareness that this can happen to anybody and everybody. I knew my woman over 40 years, OK? Forty years. I didn&#8217;t meet her at a gas station. I didn&#8217;t meet her on one of these stupid online dating things.&#8221;</p>
<p>Although his burns have gotten better, doctors say he will be scarred for life. For now, Andy says, he still has thousands of dollars in medical bills and still needs more surgeries.</p>
<p>Yvonne has pleaded not guilty. Her attorney declined to comment, and she is awaiting trial.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">873937</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210301_Adam_Polo_body_burns.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/542f5335-355f-455f-a85d-280a24800ff9/1d4707db-9d84-4af1-a3e1-3bb02d5b6136/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219676~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/542f5335-355f-455f-a85d-280a24800ff9/1d4707db-9d84-4af1-a3e1-3bb02d5b6136/main.mp4*~hmac=ca22108681b9c17ac1ed37f2eb9a8d793a1952e7c94ea9ad0ead665b3f261b5f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210301_Adam_Polo_body_burns.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210301_Adam_Polo_body_burns.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210301_Andy_Polo_body_burns</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami-Dade issues fines, drafts ordinance amid noisy big rig complaints in Redlands</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/miami-dade-issues-fines-drafts-ordinance-amid-noisy-big-rig-complaints-in-redlands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 04:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=872190</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Residents in the Redlands have been complaining for years about big rig trucks paying to park on land that is zoned for agriculture. 7&#8217;s Kevin...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Residents in the Redlands have been complaining for years about big rig trucks paying to park on land that is zoned for agriculture. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek says tensions now are higher than ever, and now the county is taking extra measures to try to stop these trucks from disturbing the peace.</p>
<p>The front of a home in the Redlands doesn&#8217;t look much different than others in the area, but what&#8217;s behind the house has neighbors worried.</p>
<p>Resident (anonymous), upset about trucks: &#8220;All hours of the night, there&#8217;s trucks coming in and out.&#8221;</p>
<p>The 7 Dronecam shows big trucks parking behind the house on Southwest 200th Street and buildings under construction, as well.</p>
<p>Resident: &#8220;I believe they&#8217;re sleeping in their trucks, and maybe other accommodations are becoming available.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;You think they may be building accommodations?&#8221;</p>
<p>Resident: &#8220;Correct.&#8221;</p>
<p>We came to see if we could talk to the property owner and knock on the door. The gate was closed.</p>
<p>So we couldn&#8217;t find the property owner, but look what we did see right here on the gate: two notices from the county for code violations.</p>
<p>Resident: &#8220;They&#8217;re turning it into an industrial zone instead of an agriculture zone.&#8221;</p>
<p>The property owners were fined more than $11,000 after the county said it found an &#8220;estimated eight illegal shed apartments placed behind the house.&#8221;</p>
<p>We spoke to one of the property owners on the phone. She told us, &#8220;Everything is being taken care of,&#8221; anything further will come through her attorney, and then she hung up on us.</p>
<p>Resident: &#8220;The county is stretched thin due to COVID-19, but they need to stay on top of it more.&#8221;</p>
<p>7News <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/disturbing-the-peace-redlands-residents-fed-up-with-disruptive-big-rigs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first reported on the big rig problem</a> in the Redlands two years ago.</p>
<p>Despite residents&#8217; complaints, and fines and liens placed on properties in violation, the trucks keep rolling in.</p>
<p>Louis Lawson, plant nursery owner: &#8220;You listen to impact wrenches every day, compressors, riveting nuts.&#8221;</p>
<p>Farmland turned into truck depots.</p>
<p>Tony Mena, resident: &#8220;I got one about two blocks away. There&#8217;s another one about three blocks away. There&#8217;s another one block to the East. I mean, they&#8217;re all over.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fransico Marilla and his nephew Isidro farm a five-acre field. They said they&#8217;ve had confrontations with the truckers who park next door.</p>
<p>Fransico Marilla, property owner (translation): &#8220;The truckers would throw too much garbage. They would pee in jars and would bombard us with the jars full of urine.&#8221;</p>
<p>The owner of the neighboring property is Larry Cintra-Prieto. Isidro said last March, Cintra-Pietro attacked him with a metal bar after a dispute over the property line.</p>
<p>Isidro Arriaga, farmer (translation): &#8220;He grabbed me with both hands. He grabbed me like this, hit me here. I fell down because I was bleeding.&#8221;</p>
<p>Cintra-Prieto was arrested on five counts of battery. He also has been slapped with thousands of dollars in code violations for unauthorized use of his land.</p>
<p>Incidents like this are why some residents are afraid to complain.</p>
<p>Resident: &#8220;Ugly things can happen in the Redlands.&#8221;</p>
<p>Michael Wanek, resident: &#8220;This is like the Wild West out here.&#8221;</p>
<p>County officials say the current code meant to keep big rig traffic low here is hard to enforce, so now they&#8217;re working on new legislation.</p>
<p>Nathan Kogon, Assistant Director for Development Services: &#8220;We&#8217;re already in the process of crafting the ordinance. We have most of the guts of the ordinance.&#8221;</p>
<p>The new ordinance being hammered out will reduce the number of tractor-trailer trucks allowed per property.</p>
<p>Nathan Kogon: &#8220;I don&#8217;t have a magic number, but I can tell you it&#8217;s definitely going to be significantly smaller.&#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s good news for residents like Michael Wanek, who lives down the street from a truck depot.</p>
<p>Michael Wanek: &#8220;I ended up purchasing the land next door, OK? I didn&#8217;t really want to buy more land, but I bought it because the trucks are going to move in.&#8221;</p>
<p>It could take months before the new ordinance is passed, but residents hope it will finally be what keeps big rig trucks out of this big stretch of farmland.</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Mayor Daniella Levine Cava&#8217;s office also said her office is committed to continuing efforts to contain the illegal tractor-trailer parking lots in the Redlands.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">872190</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_big_rigs_redlands.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e7898396-0a68-46e9-aedd-6dd90f728852/5c38b38c-c338-4bbd-876d-aa1bd2452b59/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219659~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e7898396-0a68-46e9-aedd-6dd90f728852/5c38b38c-c338-4bbd-876d-aa1bd2452b59/main.mp4*~hmac=2947281b689673cd078956fa134f41c0f8e94adcd5b5eb13856eba2c7983fa45' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_big_rigs_redlands.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210226_big_rigs_redlands.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210226_big_rigs_redlands</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taxi Trauma: Miami chef shares emotional, legal ordeal 1 year after Wynwood crash</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/taxi-trauma-miami-chef-shares-emotional-legal-ordeal-1-year-after-wynwood-crash/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 03:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=871494</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A freak accident with a taxi left a Miami woman with mounting medical bills. As 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek tells us, a year later, she&#8217;s still...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A freak accident with a taxi left a Miami woman with mounting medical bills. As 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek tells us, a year later, she&#8217;s still getting hit by &#8220;Taxi Trauma.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey was an up-and-coming chef.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey (in &#8220;MasterChef&#8221; episode): &#8220;I&#8217;m doing a different spin on a <em>tostón</em>.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey, injured by cab: &#8220;I was on &#8216;MasterChef&#8217; and made it to the finale. I represented Miami all the way to the finale.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Ashley&#8217;s culinary career came to a screeching halt in December of 2019.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;We were walking back from dinner, and my life changed.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley was strolling through Wynwood with her cousins when a taxi driver lost control.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;I saw the cab. I saw the reverse lights on. He hit the curb, and then he hit people, and I was one of them.&#8221;</p>
<p>The cab hit Ashley and her Cousin Javon. They were pinned against a glass storefront.</p>
<p>Javon Mincey, injured by cab: &#8220;You could hear people yelling, &#8216;Hey, hey, hey!'&#8221;</p>
<p>Moments later, the cab pulled forward. Ashley collapsed to the sidewalk.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;There was blood everywhere. There was glass, debris inside of my leg.&#8221;</p>
<p>Javon Mincey: &#8220;She just kept saying, &#8216;I can&#8217;t feel my leg. Is my leg there?'&#8221;</p>
<p>The accident report says the taxi driver had stopped the car. He then &#8220;shifted gears&#8221; and &#8220;&#8230; went into reverse, causing him to lose control.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;The impact happened so quickly that parts of my leg separated from my body, and I needed reconstructive surgery on my leg.&#8221;</p>
<p>The driver was not charged in the accident. The report says the taxi &#8220;malfunctioned,&#8221; and witnesses saw him trying to stop the vehicle.</p>
<p>But Ashley and Javon filed a civil suit against him and the cab company, Paloma Transportation LLC.</p>
<p>Paloma Transportation has since dissolved, but a former principal of the company told us in an email that, &#8220;This driver did not pay insurance,&#8221; and, &#8220;This was a practice of some unethical drivers that &#8216;borrowed&#8217; taxi cabs from friends to make a few extra dollars &#8230; We tried our best to stop this from happening. Unfortunately, we could not control it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;It&#8217;s just been trauma after trauma after trauma.&#8221;</p>
<p>Then there was more bad news. Because the driver was uninsured and the taxi company had dissolved, there was no money to be made, so their attorney withdrew from the case.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;I was really devastated, because I&#8217;m in a place right now where I should be wholly focused on physical therapy, rehab, recovery.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley has had four surgeries on her leg and will be in physical therapy for at least another year.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;I&#8217;m going to do some leg extensions.&#8221;</p>
<p>Since chefs spend long hours walking and standing in the kitchen, she&#8217;s nervous about her future, and she&#8217;s frustrated someone was driving a cab without insurance.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;You are told that you have to have insurance to even have that car on the road, so I&#8217;m really baffled as to how we are here a year later.&#8221;</p>
<p>Justin Ziegler, attorney: &#8220;I&#8217;m not shocked for one second that there is a taxi without insurance.&#8221;</p>
<p>Personal injury attorney Justin Ziegler says Ashley and Javon may still be able to seek justice in a court.</p>
<p>Justin Ziegler: &#8220;See if she can get a judgment against the person whose car it was, against the medallion holder, go after the wages of these people and go through that route.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ashley says they will keep fighting.</p>
<p>Ashley Mincey: &#8220;We deserve justice for what happened to me, what happened to my cousin, what happened to my family.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">871494</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210225_Ashley_Mincey.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f67a1c29-a228-45c5-b900-6b0ea306cf6e/606679d1-8b28-4c07-a6a3-892c4d5804b7/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219629~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f67a1c29-a228-45c5-b900-6b0ea306cf6e/606679d1-8b28-4c07-a6a3-892c4d5804b7/main.mp4*~hmac=88bc5b14c989aab7bd2b6c561541d3702ea4c440c4a3ea88641e0abd6a10704a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210225_Ashley_Mincey.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210225_Ashley_Mincey.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210225_Ashley_Mincey</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>‘Nobody in our lifetime has ever experienced this volume of deaths&#8217;: Funeral homes, families overwhelmed, in pain during pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/nobody-in-our-lifetime-has-ever-experienced-this-volume-of-deaths-funeral-homes-families-overwhelmed-in-pain-during-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 04:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870791</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We have seen the toll the coronavirus pandemic has taken on healthcare workers, but if a patient dies, other people take over, and they are...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have seen the toll the coronavirus pandemic has taken on healthcare workers, but if a patient dies, other people take over, and they are suffering, too. 7&#8217;s Karen Hensel has tonight&#8217;s special report: The Pain Behind the Pandemic.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes, son of Gustavo Lazaro Valdes: &#8220;He was a very happy, caring man &#8212; helped everybody that he could.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gustavo Lazaro Valdes was born in Cuba in 1941. He died in December.</p>
<p>Like thousands of South Floridians, the cause was COVID.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes: &#8220;He had just turned 79, so his birthday was on the 17th, and he passed on the 18th, very difficult. He wanted to be cremated. Those were his wishes.&#8221;</p>
<p>His son Gustavo, who shares his name, signed a contract with Miami funeral home Caballero Rivero Little Havana.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes: &#8220;They did say that they were backed up, that they are looking at like one to two weeks out to have my dad cremated.&#8221;</p>
<p>But, one to two weeks turned into three and four.</p>
<p>Gustavo was worried because his father&#8217;s body was not being embalmed and preserved, since he wanted to be cremated.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes: &#8220;I voiced to them my concerns about the body decomposing, and they told me that was not going to be the case, that he was refrigerated. Finally, at four weeks, they finally cremated him.&#8221;</p>
<p>But, Gustavo first had to identify his father after waiting nearly a month.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes: &#8220;It entailed going into basically like a viewing room, a funeral viewing room, and they had my dad there. I don&#8217;t want to talk about that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Citing family privacy, the funeral home would not discuss specifics but told 7News, &#8220;Given the much higher than average death rate in our area and throughout the country, it is currently taking 30-45 days for cremations. We are doing everything possible to serve all families with dignity and respect in extremely difficult circumstances.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;What has it been like for the last responders?&#8221;</p>
<p>Randy Anderson, National Funeral Directors Association President-elect: &#8220;Our caseload has more than doubled since last March when all of this started.&#8221;</p>
<p>Randy Anderson is with the National Funeral Directors Association.</p>
<p>Randy Anderson: &#8220;Nobody in our lifetime has ever experienced this volume of deaths at one time all across the country.&#8221;</p>
<p>A staggering amount of death. The grim milestones passed recently: more than a half a million COVID deaths in the U.S. and more than 30,000 of those are our fellow Floridians.</p>
<p>Randy Anderson: &#8220;I&#8217;ve noted in our staff that many of them have had some compassion fatigue. I&#8217;ve heard from the families that I&#8217;ve served that has been the most difficult is that they say their loved ones died in facilities, a hospital, a nursing home, and they say, &#8216;We didn&#8217;t get to be with them,&#8217; because they were restricted from visiting.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was that way for Gustavo.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes: &#8220;I was only able to see him once a day for 15 minutes through glass.&#8221;</p>
<p>The pandemic&#8217;s pain felt deeply by this grieving son.</p>
<p>Gustavo Valdes: &#8220;I&#8217;ve been terrible. I lost my father. I lost my best friend.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870791</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022421-pain-of-the-pandemic-covid-body-bag.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7fe1f92b-49f1-46a9-ac93-0ca87a8ec0c0/07b59fd4-aba5-4f0c-b076-ebd7b0eb90d5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219611~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7fe1f92b-49f1-46a9-ac93-0ca87a8ec0c0/07b59fd4-aba5-4f0c-b076-ebd7b0eb90d5/main.mp4*~hmac=495889e96fe73fe132ad8921cb1adc4297bacb674d30b483e7be7cf2d099a36b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022421-pain-of-the-pandemic-covid-body-bag.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022421-pain-of-the-pandemic-covid-body-bag.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022421 pain behind the pandemic covid body bag</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Badge Battle: Retired officer, police chief disagree over officer&#8217;s right to honorary badge</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/badge-battle-retired-officer-police-chief-disagree-over-officers-right-to-honorary-badge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 03:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870119</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He retired as a police officer. An honorable officer, he says, but the chief doesn&#8217;t agree. Now, the fight is on over that officer&#8217;s right...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He retired as a police officer. An honorable officer, he says, but the chief doesn&#8217;t agree. Now, the fight is on over that officer&#8217;s right to an honorary badge. The Nightteam&#8217;s Patrick Fraser has this special assignment report: Badge Battle.</p>
<p>When Joe Fleres was a kid, he dreamed of becoming a police officer, and then, he did.</p>
<p>Joe Fleres, retired police officer: &#8220;I loved it. It was the greatest job I ever had.&#8221;</p>
<p>Six years with the Miami Police Department, 15 years with Coral Gables, wrapping up his career as the city&#8217;s community outreach officer.</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;It was the icing on the cake, but other opportunities came. I decided to take it.&#8221;</p>
<p>When Joe decided to retire, he filled out this memo asking for what, he says, retiring officers get: his gun, his current badge and&#8230;</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;You get a promotional ID and your badge to reflect the new rank that you&#8217;re promoted to when you&#8217;re in retirement.&#8221;</p>
<p>The retirement badge would list Joe as a sergeant.</p>
<p>No extra money, just an honor cops like.</p>
<p>Everyone from his sergeant to the police chief signed the request form.</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;It&#8217;s kind of like a gift, a parting gift that you&#8217;ve done your service, you get a promotion and here, here&#8217;s your credentials.&#8221;</p>
<p>But when Joe went to get his honorary badge, he was told the chief changed his mind.</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;At the end of the day, I retired professionally, honorably. I&#8217;m entitled to these items.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;No, you are not,&#8221; says Coral Gables Police Chief Ed Hudak.</p>
<p>Ed Hudak, Coral Gables Police Chief: &#8220;My specific decision to not give him the honorary promotion was the word &#8216;honorary.'&#8221;</p>
<p>And specifically, what does the chief mean when he uses the word honorary?</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;The issue that I&#8217;ve always had with Joseph Fleres throughout the incidents that come across my desk and discipline has been his issue with candor and being forthright all the time.&#8221;</p>
<p>Is it a nice way of saying he lied?</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;On occasion, I have caught him on lies, yes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Joe Fleres doesn&#8217;t think his candor is the problem. It&#8217;s a 60-page complaint he filed last January detailing 19 issues he had over the years with the chief, including the last one a few months before his retirement.</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;I did feel like the time that the chief made a aggressive, unprofessional statement towards me that it was within my right to stand up and actually file that complaint.&#8221;</p>
<p>The chief says his comments came after he heard Fleres talking about him.</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;He was commiserating with another officer about how screwed up, how I was ruining the department, and I said to him, &#8216;You might want to wait until I&#8217;m off the floor before you criticize my job,&#8217; but that was the end of that, as far as I was concerned.&#8221;</p>
<p>Joe is not alone in thinking he deserves the honorary badge.</p>
<p>At least 16 residents sent emails asking that he receive it.</p>
<p>A former city manager texted, &#8220;Thank you again for your exceptional service.&#8221;</p>
<p>Joe&#8217;s mother even wrote an email to make sure her son got the retirement badge.</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;This has everybody baffled.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Chief Hudak says he is not baffled because inside the department, there was a different view of Fleres.</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;It was a tale of two people, I will be honest with you. If you look at his file and you look back at a history of someone, and we have it on paper.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, we went through Joe Fleres&#8217; personnel file. You can find dozens of awards, good scores on his annual evaluations, but he was disciplined a few times and had been investigated by internal affairs several times.</p>
<p>Some complaints were dismissed, some sustained and after looking at everything, Hudak says only he can determine if an officer rises to the level of the honorary badge.</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;I&#8217;m a chief that calls it as I see it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fleres&#8217; reply?</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;It seems like a hissy fit. I stepped on his toe. Now, he wants to step back on mine.&#8221;</p>
<p>Not true, Hudak says. Several officers have retired and not gotten the honorary badge, and he adds by giving it to Joe Fleres, it will be unfair to the men and women who retire in the future.</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;And I owe it to every other officer and employee that leaves this place that that honorary promotion means something.&#8221;</p>
<p>Two men who disagree&#8230;</p>
<p>Joe Fleres: &#8220;Get the police chief to do what&#8217;s right.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ed Hudak: &#8220;It was my decision. This is what I do. I make decisions.&#8221;</p>
<p>Both swore to protect and serve, both did and both also swear they are right about the badge.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870119</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022321-badge-battle-ed-hudak-joe-fleres.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/26109a8b-7d80-4446-92e8-0599aba10136/6b4e3eeb-d394-4e93-9760-8c5877b5cefd/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219676~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/26109a8b-7d80-4446-92e8-0599aba10136/6b4e3eeb-d394-4e93-9760-8c5877b5cefd/main.mp4*~hmac=d561db32450c8a0713abdca844a1801517852a407710e74f6acf8de4374d0def' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022321-badge-battle-ed-hudak-joe-fleres.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022321-badge-battle-ed-hudak-joe-fleres.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022321 badge battle ed hudak joe fleres</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Battle for the Beach: Showdown brewing between Deerfield Beach, resident over beach plots</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/battle-for-the-beach-showdown-brewing-between-deerfield-beach-resident-over-beach-plots/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 03:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In Florida, we often assume beaches are open to the public, but one woman actually owns and lives on one part of Deerfield Beach, and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Florida, we often assume beaches are open to the public, but one woman actually owns and lives on one part of Deerfield Beach, and as Kevin Ozebek explains, she and the city are now literally in a legal &#8220;Battle for the Beach.&#8221;</p>
<p>This stretch of sand near the Deerfield Beach Pier is a true South Florida gem.</p>
<p>Margaret Ferguson, sunbather: &#8220;The beach is beautiful. It is just pristine.&#8221;</p>
<p>But when you walk just north of the pier, there is no missing this taped-off trailer.</p>
<p>Risa Greenberg, sunbather: &#8220;It&#8217;s an eyesore.&#8221;</p>
<p>Scott Ferguson, sunbather: &#8220;It doesn&#8217;t quite fit in with the rest of the neighborhood. I&#8217;ll put it that way.&#8221;</p>
<p>The president of the condo association for these units near the trailer isn&#8217;t thrilled with his neighbor.</p>
<p>Jim D&#8217;Agostino, condo association president: &#8220;She has done nothing but been a nuisance to our community.&#8221;</p>
<p>The woman who calls this trailer home is Kristina Clothier.</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;If I had to choose, this would not be my ideal.&#8221;</p>
<p>Despite living next to a public stretch of beach, Kristina owns two plots of beach property. She inherited them from her father.</p>
<p>Decades ago, private homes dotted the beach. Now most of the beach is public, and Kristina wants to keep it that way. She wants to sell her land to the city, but they&#8217;re not buying.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;What do you want to say to Deerfield Beach?&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;&#8216;Do the right thing, which you should have done years ago.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;And that is?&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;To purchase the property.&#8221;</p>
<p>In 2017, Kristina says the city placed two trash and recycle cans on her property.</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;I am paying a ridiculous amount in taxes, and if the city wants to use the property, then buy the property.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina says she put up &#8220;no trespassing&#8221; signs. Deerfield Beach Code Compliance then fined her for &#8220;unpermitted signs&#8221; and &#8220;unpermitted placement of signs.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;They&#8217;re trying to wear me down. It&#8217;s not going to work.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina racked up $49,880 worth of code violations, which she has not paid.</p>
<p>The city is now suing Kristina, arguing it&#8217;s &#8220;authorized to foreclose on the code enforcement liens.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina&#8217;s attorney disagrees.</p>
<p>Robert Sweetapple, Kristina&#8217;s attorney: &#8220;Instead of buying it, they are attempting to take it through these unfounded, known baseless code violations.&#8221;</p>
<p>In a statement, the city tells 7News, &#8220;Code violation complaints &#8230; are investigated and enforced.&#8221; The city &#8220;would prefer that the property owner address all outstanding violations and bring the property into full compliance.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;You have a government entity saying, &#8216;No, you don&#8217;t own it. We can use it for our gain, for our own property, and you just keep paying those taxes!&#8217; No , that&#8217;s not right, and that&#8217;s not American.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina&#8217;s two sandy plots have a combined market value of more than $761,000, but she has them listed for about double that amount, at nearly $1.5 million. She says that is negotiable.</p>
<p>Kristina says, until they are sold, the beach will remain her home.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;How much of this is principle?&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristina Clothier: &#8220;I would say ALL of it. Absolutely all of it. The problem is, this is everything I own.&#8221;</p>
<p>Jim D&#8217;Agostino: &#8220;She&#8217;s just in this for the big dollar, basically. It&#8217;s pretty obvious why she&#8217;s doing this.&#8221;</p>
<p>So now, the battle for this part of the beach is heading from the sand to the courtroom.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869476</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210222_Deerfield_Beach_plot_of_sand_Ozebek.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/df1e9595-adcb-424b-b999-096be51e3ff7/869215c7-6710-4bf5-aad5-283801f51366/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219640~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/df1e9595-adcb-424b-b999-096be51e3ff7/869215c7-6710-4bf5-aad5-283801f51366/main.mp4*~hmac=73a7f7ae6833a631deda8b010343e6c05eec45d34e92b0d0b310db4ec95995a6' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210222_Deerfield_Beach_plot_of_sand_Ozebek.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210222_Deerfield_Beach_plot_of_sand_Ozebek.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210222_Deerfield_Beach_plot_of_sand_Ozebek</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dialing into Danger: South Florida man speaks out after being targeted with false 911 calls</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/dialing-into-danger-south-florida-man-speaks-out-after-being-targeted-with-false-911-calls/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 04:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=867451</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Imagine this: police are at your door telling you they got a call you were selling guns out of your house, or the next day...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine this: police are at your door telling you they got a call you were selling guns out of your house, or the next day you are bringing young children into the house. Day after day, phony 911 calls. As Patrick Fraser reveals, it&#8217;s what one South Florida family has been facing for months.</p>
<p>When Diego was younger, he admits it: he hung with a tough crowd.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala, victim of false 911 calls: &#8220;Because I used to hang around with people that weren&#8217;t right, and not legit people, man.&#8221;</p>
<p>Of course, like most people, Diego grew up and straightened up.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala: &#8220;I do now, I do now to stay out of trouble.&#8221;</p>
<p>Then trouble returned, with a knock at the door.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala: &#8220;I opened the door, and police were there. They were saying that they were getting phone calls saying that there were minors coming into the house, and I was like, &#8216;Oh, what the hell?'&#8221;</p>
<p>That was the beginning.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala: &#8220;It&#8217;s just uncomfortable. It&#8217;s uncomfortable.&#8221;</p>
<p>The 911 calls sending police to the house kept coming in.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala: &#8220;It was a different claim, that I was being noisy outside of the house, and the music was loud, and there was no music.&#8221;</p>
<p>Each anonymous call came from the same woman.</p>
<p>After accusing Diego of everything from enticing children into his home to selling drugs, the crook then targeted Diego&#8217;s family.</p>
<p>Reina Finchun, Diego&#8217;s mother: &#8220;The two detectives came in, saying that my son was buying arms and I was selling them, and I was being investigated. It&#8217;s very scary.&#8221;</p>
<p>By the time Diego called us, there had been 11 calls to 911 operators.</p>
<p>Reina Finchun: &#8220;Another time that my son has overdosed. Another time that he was being violent, and then the last one, that we&#8217;re selling arms.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Police detective Jacob George: &#8220;We definitely want people to know that this is very much a crime.&#8221;</p>
<p>The crook hopes the calls are creating chaos. The police know the calls are creating danger.</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Police detective Jacob George: &#8220;There&#8217;s always families in need who need our services and genuinely do need that, so every time a bogus call is made, you&#8217;re exhausting those resources from that family in need.&#8221;</p>
<p>Diego has no idea who is doing this to him, but if you listen closely, it appears the woman making the calls is being coached.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala: &#8220;When the operator was asking for information, she was like stuttering and kind of like saying &#8212; you can tell that there was somebody telling her what to say.&#8221;</p>
<p>Whoever was coaching the woman knows Diego well.</p>
<p>Reina Finchun: &#8220;They mentioned the medication that he was taking 15 years ago.&#8221;</p>
<p>Diego says he has no idea why someone from his past would do this to him, but if they&#8217;re trying to upend his family&#8217;s life, he says, they are succeeding.</p>
<p>Reina Finchun: &#8220;This person is so sick to be making up all these phone calls and putting our lives in turmoil.&#8221;</p>
<p>If law enforcement has their way, the person creating the turmoil&#8217;s next call will be for help to bail out of jail.</p>
<p>Miami-Dade Police detective Jacob George: &#8220;We&#8217;re now working directly with the Homeland Security Bureau Cyber Crime Center, so we&#8217;re working hand in hand with them to to solve this and bring this family to peace.&#8221;</p>
<p>Peace from the 911 calls.</p>
<p>Diego Ayala: &#8220;If you were getting phone calls, and police officers were coming to your house saying that you were doing absurd things, you&#8217;d be scared, right? I&#8217;m scared.&#8221;</p>
<p>Scared, and they don&#8217;t even know who to be scared of.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">867451</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218_Diego_Ayala.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a8da105e-e441-4d4d-b45c-5551a054456d/8dee2763-8603-4352-af2f-2da60ad1c36c/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219653~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a8da105e-e441-4d4d-b45c-5551a054456d/8dee2763-8603-4352-af2f-2da60ad1c36c/main.mp4*~hmac=6ee3355add70558a9a37c7917e302effbc7cb0c5eb5d4f101dac5d6d938bc647' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218_Diego_Ayala.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218_Diego_Ayala.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210218_Diego_Ayala</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami homeowner suing to evict couple living on her front porch, upset neighbors say they&#8217;ve been there for years</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/miami-homeowner-suing-to-evict-couple-living-on-her-front-porch-upset-neighbors-say-theyve-been-there-for-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 04:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866813</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This next story is definitely not your typical landlord tenant dispute. A South Florida woman is trying to evict a couple who has made the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This next story is definitely not your typical landlord tenant dispute. A South Florida woman is trying to evict a couple who has made the front yard of her home their living room. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report: Parked on the Porch.</p>
<p>Many of the homes in Miami&#8217;s historic Shenandoah neighborhood still have that old Florida feel, but what&#8217;s happening at one home in particular has neighbors on this street floored.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;This is something we&#8217;ve been living with for many years, and we&#8217;ve had enough.&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbor (in cellphone video): &#8220;Living on the front lawn of a residential home.&#8221;</p>
<p>The neighbors are so concerned about the situation, they do not want to show their faces, but they want something done.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;You find them laying down in the yard. You don&#8217;t know if they&#8217;re alive, if they&#8217;re dead.&#8221;</p>
<p>After a neighbor first contacted us, we went to check out the living conditions.</p>
<p>From the street &#8212; on multiple days &#8212; our camera captured the couple making themselves at home on someone else&#8217;s front lawn.</p>
<p>We saw the woman eat, talk on her cellphone, feed cats, paint and defecate behind plants next to the home.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;They&#8217;re exposing themselves when they urinate and defecate outside in the front yard.&#8221;</p>
<p>The man pushes a shopping cart up and down the sidewalk bringing supplies.</p>
<p>We spotted him on the property waking up, snacking and cleaning up the yard.</p>
<p>We also noticed a school bus stop right in front of the home.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;Since COVID, that area, and it will be a year, that area has not been cleaned.&#8221;</p>
<p>By now, you&#8217;re probably wondering about the actual homeowner.</p>
<p>We saw her, too, but did not see her interact with the people in her yard.</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;There&#8217;s two sides to this story somewhere.&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;Yeah.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;And the front yard is not necessarily the whole story.&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;No, no.&#8221;</p>
<p>It turns out the homeowner and the woman living outside are sisters. This whole ordeal started years ago with the couple living in the backyard. In 2017, the homeowner sued and evicted them, but they came back. This time, moving to the front yard.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;It&#8217;s a major health issue.&#8221;</p>
<p>The homeowner is once again suing to evict the couple, this time from her front porch.</p>
<p>According to court records, after being &#8220;evicted some months ago from a motel,&#8221; the homeowner allowed them to &#8220;put their personal belongings&#8221; on the porch on a &#8220;temporary basis.&#8221; Instead, they started &#8220;squatting.&#8221;</p>
<p>The documents state the homeowner has &#8220;never collected rent&#8221; and has repeatedly asked them to leave.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;The police always says to us that they haven&#8217;t committed a crime.&#8221;</p>
<p>And we discovered the woman living in the front yard is a former attorney disbarred 13 years ago.</p>
<p>In this handwritten court filing, the couple asked a judge to dismiss the case because of the &#8220;temporary halt in evictions&#8221; due to COVID.</p>
<p>The eviction case &#8212; filed in September &#8212; is still pending.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, neighbors say they have repeatedly asked the City of Miami to step in.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;There is anger, there is frustration, a lot of frustration with city officials.&#8221;</p>
<p>Email correspondence shows City of Miami officials have been aware of this problem for years.</p>
<p>In a December email, a member of Mayor Francis Suarez&#8217;s staff called it a &#8220;quality of life&#8221; and &#8220;life safety issue.&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;If this was your street, if this was your neighbors, would they still be out there? If you were a city official? I don&#8217;t think so. I think the answer is absolutely not.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;And what would you like to see happen?&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;I&#8217;d like to see them get the right treatment, and I&#8217;d like to see us, the neighbors, get back to normalcy.&#8221;</p>
<p>But for now, it remains anything but normal.</p>
<p>Neighbor: &#8220;There&#8217;s been times where she just snaps, and she runs out in the street yelling or screaming or taking video or photos.&#8221;</p>
<p>A neighbor recorded this from their own yard.</p>
<p>Woman (in cellphone video): &#8220;Stay away from me. Stay away from me. Stay the [expletive] away from me.&#8221;</p>
<p>When we tried to talk with the woman&#8230;</p>
<p>Woman: &#8220;Please get away from me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;My name is Karen. I&#8217;m with WSVN 7News.&#8221;</p>
<p>She wasn&#8217;t interested.</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;I&#8217;m going to leave my card for you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Woman: &#8220;Get off my property.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;This is not your property.&#8221;</p>
<p>Woman: &#8220;Do not litter on my sidewalk.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami City Commissioner Manolo Reyes says the couple has refused help, including shelter, but they will continue to look for a solution.</p>
<p>The attorney for the homeowner declined to comment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866813</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021721-parked-on-the-porch.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/37e50107-8d64-4cb7-ab63-64f93b853eab/bb7627d0-793c-4cf7-ab66-5db5c36fdfeb/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219713~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/37e50107-8d64-4cb7-ab63-64f93b853eab/bb7627d0-793c-4cf7-ab66-5db5c36fdfeb/main.mp4*~hmac=06ce58e6c1633dce5f9f4ab005efd5615686e77ced9ef4b83170a8e5bff5f3e7' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021721-parked-on-the-porch.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021721-parked-on-the-porch.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021721 parked on the porch</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Problem in the Pipes: West Miramar homeowners frustrated about recent leaks in copper pipes</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/problem-in-the-pipes-west-miramar-homeowners-frustrated-about-recent-leaks-in-copper-pipes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 04:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A leaky pipe is usually a minor problem for homeowners, but for residents in one Broward community, it has turned into a major issue. The...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leaky pipe is usually a minor problem for homeowners, but for residents in one Broward community, it has turned into a major issue. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has his special assignment report: Problem in the Pipes.</p>
<p>Calling a plumber to fix a leaky pipe is a rare occurrence for most homeowners, but Victor Victores calls his plumber every year.</p>
<p>Victor Victores, homeowner: &#8220;Something&#8217;s either wrong with the pipes, or something&#8217;s wrong with the water.&#8221;</p>
<p>Victor moved into his Miramar house after it was built in 1995.</p>
<p>He never had any serious problems until five years ago when a pipe in a bathroom sprung a leak.</p>
<p>Over the next four years, there were three more leaks. The most serious one happened in the kitchen.</p>
<p>Victor Victores: &#8220;Cost about $30,000.&#8221;</p>
<p>The same thing is going on nearby at John Perez&#8217;s house. The first leak happened last summer in the living room.</p>
<p>John Perez, homeowner: &#8220;All the pipes had to be replaced.&#8221;</p>
<p>A few months later in December, another leak. This time in a wall next to their garage.</p>
<p>Eric Misch, homeowner: &#8220;I fear daily that I&#8217;m going to wake up to a massive flood.&#8221;</p>
<p>In the last three years, another neighbor, Eric Misch, has spent thousands fixing leaks in his home.</p>
<p>This was his kitchen just a few weeks ago.</p>
<p>Eric Misch: &#8220;We opened up the ceiling, and in fact, we noticed a big puddle up there. There was a pipe that had several pit marks in it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Eric and the others recently discovered through a neighborhood app they aren&#8217;t the only ones with leaky pipe problems.</p>
<p>John Perez: &#8220;It&#8217;s a big group of people. I&#8217;m saying hundreds of people.&#8221;</p>
<p>The affected houses are here in west Miramar. They all have copper pipes and were built 20 to 25 years ago. The homeowners say the leaks started within the last five to six years.</p>
<p>Victor Victores: &#8220;You can see holes. It looks like somebody took a drill and made little punctures in it.&#8221;</p>
<p>We called several plumbing companies that service Miramar.</p>
<p>They were all familiar with the issue, but split on the source of the problem.</p>
<p>Some say the homes were simply built with thin copper pipes. Others believe the city&#8217;s filtration process could be partially to blame.</p>
<p>Eric Misch: &#8220;The city&#8217;s using a reverse osmosis system.&#8221;</p>
<p>The city tells 7News that it added a reverse osmosis system at the west water treatment plant in 2010.</p>
<p>Some of the plumbers we spoke to say that type of filtration system can make water acidic and accelerate corrosion of copper pipes.</p>
<p>Eric Misch: &#8220;When you start seeing these kinds of patterns, you know there&#8217;s an underlying issue. There&#8217;s a systemic issue.&#8221;</p>
<p>We took the homeowners&#8217; concerns to the city.</p>
<p>They say corrosion and water quality tests were performed and &#8220;Miramar&#8217;s water quality complies with all parameters of Florida Department of Environmental Protection&#8217;s regulations. As a practical matter, pipe leaks can be caused by a myriad of factors other than water quality. Therefore, a pipe leak does not mean that the city should be held responsible&#8230;&#8221;</p>
<p>A homeowner recently filed suit against the city, and &#8220;the court dismissed the resident pipe leak claims with prejudice.&#8221;</p>
<p>Eric Misch: &#8220;I do feel like there needs to be some type of restitution for our loss.&#8221;</p>
<p>The homeowners are faced with a big decision: replace the remaining copper pipes in their homes now or wait until there&#8217;s another leak.</p>
<p>Victor is closely watching this pipe that&#8217;s showing signs of corrosion.</p>
<p>Victor Victores: &#8220;It looks like I have a current leak. Something&#8217;s happening here. I got water.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, he thinks he&#8217;ll be facing yet another big bill to fix the problem in the pipes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866232</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021621-rusted-copper-pipe.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/88cea9b8-0a58-4121-aec0-a1fea3d8d426/77320321-ae30-48b7-b00b-5e3b1568579d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219643~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/88cea9b8-0a58-4121-aec0-a1fea3d8d426/77320321-ae30-48b7-b00b-5e3b1568579d/main.mp4*~hmac=5c0d5ff9ada9de2529b6201e11169be844e5c17fff2238dfa21f658d0400ebe4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021621-rusted-copper-pipe.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021621-rusted-copper-pipe.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021621 rusted copper pipe</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hidden Hazard: South Florida mother warns about dangers of button batteries after daughter swallows one</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/hidden-hazard-south-florida-mother-warns-about-dangers-of-button-batteries-after-daughter-swallows-one/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 03:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=865610</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[They are used to power hearing aids, key fobs and many other small electronics, and if your child gets a hold of one and swallows...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>They are used to power hearing aids, key fobs and many other small electronics, and if your child gets a hold of one and swallows it, it can turn into a matter of life or death. In tonight&#8217;s special report, Kevin Ozebek looks at the &#8220;Hidden Hazard&#8221; of button batteries.</p>
<p>Delany is your typical 3-year-old.</p>
<p>Ysora Waugh, mother: &#8220;She&#8217;s just a joy.&#8221;</p>
<p>She loves her parents, can play with her brother for hours and is shy around strangers.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Delany, do you have a favorite cartoon?&#8221;</p>
<p>But the day after Christmas, Ysora Waugh says her usually vibrant little girl started acting strangely.</p>
<p>Ysora Waugh: &#8220;All of the sudden, she started crying. I had turned my back just for a second, and when she started crying, I ran to her. She was saying &#8216;ouchy&#8217; and pointing to her throat.&#8221;</p>
<p>Her big brother Keoni was home with his mom and sister and tried to help.</p>
<p>Keoni Waugh, brother: &#8220;I was basically just playing my Xbox, and then I just heard her saying, &#8216;Ouchy, ouchy, ouchy,&#8217; so I ran over. I tried getting her a candy cane, an ice cream.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;She didn&#8217;t want it?&#8221;</p>
<p>Keoni Waugh: &#8220;Yeah.&#8221;</p>
<p>Delany started drooling, so Ysora called 911.</p>
<p>Ysora Waugh: &#8220;I knew at that point something had to be lodged in there to be causing that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ysora had paramedics rush Delany to an ER.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;If you did not take her to the hospital that day, what would have happened to her, do you think?&#8221;</p>
<p>Ysora Waugh: &#8220;She probably wouldn&#8217;t be with us today.&#8221;</p>
<p>Doctors took this X-ray and the source of Delany&#8217;s pain became clear.</p>
<p>She had swallowed a small button battery.</p>
<p>Ysora Waugh: &#8220;I was in shock. We don&#8217;t own watches like that. We don&#8217;t have those kind of batteries around that I knew of.&#8221;</p>
<p>In just the four hours from the time Delany ingested the battery to when doctors were able to remove it, the battery began corroding.</p>
<p>Delany&#8217;s doctor is Neil Tucker of Broward Health.</p>
<p>Dr. Neil Tucker, Broward Health: &#8220;The battery is lodged between the walls of the esophagus, and it creates a current. Then the battery will start to corrode, and its contents will come out. It&#8217;s something that can become a life or death situation.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you suspect your child has swallowed a button battery, it&#8217;s recommended you give him or her honey while en route to the ER if they are over the age of 1.</p>
<p>It may coat the battery and prevent corrosion, but Dr. Tucker says this is his best advice for parents.</p>
<p>Dr. Neil Tucker: &#8220;They just need to safety proof their homes and make sure that these things are not sitting around.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ysora and her husband found out the battery Delany swallowed came from a remote that controls a ring light.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Did you even know you had a button battery in any device in your home?&#8221;</p>
<p>Chris Waugh, father: &#8220;No.&#8221;</p>
<p>I didn&#8217;t think I had any of these button batteries in my home either, until I was cooking one day and noticed the battery slot in the back of my kitchen scale. There is no screw holding the cover in place, so there is very easy access to the battery.</p>
<p>Ysora Waugh: &#8220;Look over all your toys, all of your remotes. Look for any loose batteries. Make sure the covering on the battery part is something that is safe. It either has a screw, or if it doesn&#8217;t, place a piece of tape on it, or just get rid of it altogether, because I will never allow one of those batteries back in my house.&#8221;</p>
<p>Good advice from a mother whose child is just one of the nearly 2,500 kids under the age of 7 who swallowed a button battery last year, and a mother who now knows first hand the hidden hazard they pose.</p>
<p>Some battery makers like Duracell are putting bitter-tasting coatings on their button batteries, so if a child does put it in their mouth, they&#8217;re more likely to spit it out.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">865610</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210215_Hidden_Hazard_special_report_Ozebek.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/547060a8-2cbb-4009-8bc5-a92a861f1e9a/3429520b-5652-4a2b-af5e-fc0619795cc7/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219652~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/547060a8-2cbb-4009-8bc5-a92a861f1e9a/3429520b-5652-4a2b-af5e-fc0619795cc7/main.mp4*~hmac=358cb56d9d28b196630f0f7f221c30200270c1162651b3a2c54f7bb530ae658f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210215_Hidden_Hazard_special_report_Ozebek.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210215_Hidden_Hazard_special_report_Ozebek.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210215_Hidden_Hazard_special_report_Ozebek</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sound Relief: Baptist Health neurosurgeon provides breakthrough treatment for essential tremors</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/sound-relief-baptist-health-neurosurgeon-provides-breakthrough-treatment-for-essential-tremors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 04:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=864294</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is the most common movement disorder, and it can make day-to-day tasks nearly impossible, but now a revolutionary procedure being done in South Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is the most common movement disorder, and it can make day-to-day tasks nearly impossible, but now a revolutionary procedure being done in South Florida is proving to be a savior for those suffering from a type of tremor. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has our special assignment report, &#8220;Sound Relief.&#8221;</p>
<p>For some people, whar are thought of as simple tasks can be nearly impossible. like pouring and drinking a glass of water.</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez, essential tremors patient: &#8220;There are some people that are very cruel, and they make fun of you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Or lifting food into the microwave.</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;When I was making coffee or helping my wife with breakfast, I mean, my hand would shake so much that I just didn&#8217;t want to do it.&#8221;</p>
<p>And even signing your name&#8230;</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;It looked like it was a little kid writing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Seventy-two-year-old Roberto Rodriguez is one of the millions of Americans who suffer from essential tremors. Doctors aren&#8217;t sure of the cause, but they think it&#8217;s hereditary.</p>
<p>Roberto says the shaking in his left dominant hand started 15 years ago and continued to get worse.</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;I could not carry my granddaughter because I was afraid that I might drop her.&#8221;</p>
<p>But look at his hand now.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;If you could, Roberto, show me your left hand. So it&#8217;s as steady as a rock?&#8221;</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;Yes.&#8221;</p>
<p>The incredible change is thanks to a breakthrough treatment Roberto received in December.</p>
<p>Dr. Justin Sporrer, Baptist Health neurosurgeon: &#8220;High-frequency focused ultrasound is a treatment where we&#8217;re aiming up to 1,000 small ultrasonic waves at a very particular target deep inside the brain.&#8221;</p>
<p>Baptist Health neurosurgeon, Dr. Justin Sporrer, says the treatment involves a special ring placed on the patient&#8217;s head.</p>
<p>From a control room, he operates the ring as it emits ultrasonic beams.</p>
<p>Dr. Justin Sporrer: &#8220;We are able to, with good accuracy, aim those ultrasonic beams at a very specific point in the brain, that point that is causing an abnormal circuit. By doing that, we are able to stop that abnormal circuit and stop that tremor.&#8221;</p>
<p>In other words, the beams kill just the brain cells causing the tremors.</p>
<p>In Roberto&#8217;s brain scan, you can see the exact spot Dr. Sporrer targeted.</p>
<p>Dr. Sporrer&#8217;s assistant: &#8220;That&#8217;s spectacular.&#8221;</p>
<p>As soon as the procedure was over, Dr. Sporrer had Roberto draw a spiral.</p>
<p>Look at the spiral he drew on the left before the procedure, and the one on the right a few hours later, after the prcedure.</p>
<p>Relative: &#8220;How is it? Is it good?&#8221;</p>
<p>Roberto was given a spoon and a bowl of soup after the treatment.</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;Soup!&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;And could you eat it this time?&#8221;</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;Yes, yes, yes. I could eat it, with no problem whatsoever. Chicken soup! For the first time I could eat chicken soup. So good!&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Are you even amazed at the results you see from this?&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Justin Sporrer: &#8220;It&#8217;s bordering on science fiction, but it&#8217;s not fiction anymore, because we&#8217;re doing it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Sporrer says high-frequency ultrasound can also stop tremors in some forms of Parkinson&#8217;s disease, and he believes the treatment&#8217;s potential is extraordinary.</p>
<p>Dr. Justin Sporrer: &#8220;Think of a brain problem, from schizophrenia to depression, in some forms of obesity, etcetera. There&#8217;s some abnormal circuit that is causing these abnormal thoughts or abnormal urges or abnormal movements, and so, if we can disrupt that abnormal circuit, then we might have a beneficial effect on the patient.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s complex science, but for Roberto, it&#8217;s now back to enjoying the simple things in life.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;What do you really appreciate now that the steadiness is back in your hand?</p>
<p>Roberto Rodriguez: &#8220;Being able to carry my granddaughter. That was the big thing.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">864294</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210212_high_frequency_ultrasound_treatment_sound_relief.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/83e1c76f-bd01-40a5-a8ae-bfecd270c795/9ed5f69c-b490-4e52-a05e-1ee309b73a48/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219661~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/83e1c76f-bd01-40a5-a8ae-bfecd270c795/9ed5f69c-b490-4e52-a05e-1ee309b73a48/main.mp4*~hmac=61b7fda4f512f5e6651b459dc9ca73e5b41261c9dcad58b32c4c2b3fbaaab45e' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210212_high_frequency_ultrasound_treatment_sound_relief.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210212_high_frequency_ultrasound_treatment_sound_relief.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210212_high_frequency_ultrasound_treatment_sound_relief</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Florida steps up to help woman after car crashed into yard, dog killed in traffic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/south-florida-steps-up-to-help-woman-after-car-crashed-into-yard-dog-killed-in-traffic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 04:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=863684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has been a rough couple of months for a Miami woman after a car crash left a hole in her fence and her heart,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been a rough couple of months for a Miami woman after a car crash left a hole in her fence and her heart, but immediately after her story aired on 7News, South Florida stepped up in a big way. 7&#8217;s Karen Hensel has our special assignment report.</p>
<p>When we first met Marilyn Gore, we learned the retired Miami-Dade Public Schools teacher grows most of her food in her yard.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore, homeowner: &#8220;Papaya, coconuts, more mangoes.&#8221;</p>
<p>We also heard about her deep connection with her beloved Belgian Malinois, Max.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;I talked to Max like you talk to a person.&#8221;</p>
<p>But on the night of Dec. 3, a two-car accident put into motion months of frustration and desperation.</p>
<p>The crash report found a woman &#8220;failed to stop&#8221; at a red light, sending a car driven by a police officer into Marilyn&#8217;s fence.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;I heard, &#8216;Plank da plank.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Because it was the other driver&#8217;s fault, Miami-Dade County concluded it did not have to pay for the damage, and the other driver&#8217;s insurance company wouldn&#8217;t pay up.</p>
<p>Weeks later, with the fence down. Max ran into the street, was hit by a car and killed.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;That day he died, he didn&#8217;t get to eat, and I was so heartbroken.&#8221;</p>
<p>But after <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/investigations/car-crash-involving-police-officer-leaves-hole-in-womans-fence-and-heartbreak-after-her-dog-later-escapes-and-dies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">our story aired a little more than a week ago</a>, South Floridians immediately started reaching out to us, wanting to help Marilyn.</p>
<p>They emailed:</p>
<ul>
<li>&#8220;I was distraught by this woman&#8217;s plight&#8230;&#8221;</li>
<li>&#8220;My heart is so compelled to try and help to do something.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>And they called.</p>
<ul>
<li>7News viewer voicemail 1: &#8220;I was trying to get involved and perhaps help this woman who had the fence problem, and her dog got killed.&#8221;</li>
<li>7News viewer voicemail 2: &#8220;She was just heartbroken, and your story touched my heart.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>Dozens of calls and emails.</p>
<p>There were offers of money to help fix the yard and the hole in her fence, but also offers to make Marilyn&#8217;s family whole again.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;Hello. Sweetheart, I love you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marilyn&#8217;s family became whole thanks to Miami Canine Training, who donated a 2-year old German shepherd named Kat.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;I love her, and she loves me, too. Thank you so much!&#8221;</p>
<p>Officer: &#8220;You&#8217;re welcome, you&#8217;re welcome.&#8221;</p>
<p>The rain did nothing to dampen this heartwarming moment.</p>
<p>We can&#8217;t show you who brought the dog because he&#8217;s an undercover officer with the North Miami Beach Police Department.</p>
<p>Officer: &#8220;One of my co-workers saw Karen&#8217;s video, and she was like, &#8216;Oh, we&#8217;ll start a potluck to get her a dog,&#8217; and I was like, &#8216;No, I have one.&#8217; We&#8217;re going to take it to you.&#8221;</p>
<p>One wet dog &#8212; and a new lifelong friendship.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;I hugged her after I dried her off. I pat my leg, and she came on my lap, and we bonded like that. (snaps fingers) It was very special, and when it was time to go to bed, guess where she went: straight to my room. She slept in my room. I was so, so happy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marilyn says she&#8217;s humbled by total strangers who have offered to help her.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;There are a lot of people who have reached out, don&#8217;t even know me. To take their time and effort and pour their concern into someone who is a total stranger, that tells you about their humanity.&#8221;</p>
<p>The hole in the fence &#8212; and the hole in her heart &#8212; now filled.</p>
<p>Marilyn Gore: &#8220;It was a story made in heaven.&#8221;</p>
<p>One angel is a generous man who mailed us a check for Marilyn to cover the loan she took out to fix the fence. He said he was including a few extra dollars for a &#8220;nice dinner&#8221; and to &#8220;buy the new doggie some treats.&#8221;</p>
<p>A fellow schoolteacher of Marilyn&#8217;s has set up a GoFundMe page to help cover some of the other expenses from the crash and cleanup.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFO:</strong><br />
<a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-marilyn-gore-pay-for-damages-to-her-property?qid=913f1844753979cd7ef6347ef6f0fc47" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GoFundMe page for Marilyn Gore</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">863684</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210211_Marilyn_Gore_and_dog_Special_Report.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f57a7414-ee6d-409f-b387-640697002add/933f4839-ac01-48ac-b51b-be10a8d0e5cb/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219655~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f57a7414-ee6d-409f-b387-640697002add/933f4839-ac01-48ac-b51b-be10a8d0e5cb/main.mp4*~hmac=5417960f1e1187434ceceddde335f3ccf4003df33ff66b11583574c8b3076b18' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210211_Marilyn_Gore_and_dog_Special_Report.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210211_Marilyn_Gore_and_dog_Special_Report.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210211_Marilyn_Gore_and_dog_Special_Report</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Police Response: Officers surprise boy not allowed into school when mask fell off during seizure</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/police-response-officers-surprise-boy-not-allowed-into-school-when-mask-fell-off-during-seizure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 04:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=862988</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A little boy who dreams of becoming a police officer suffers from seizures, and then, he was told he could not come to school. What...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A little boy who dreams of becoming a police officer suffers from seizures, and then, he was told he could not come to school. What happened next is stunning. The Nightteam&#8217;s Patrick Fraser has this special assignment report: Police Response.</p>
<p>They came down the street flashing lights with their guns and badges and one more thing: enormous hearts.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;I just love it. I love it so much.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;These are all your friends, and they are here for you whenever you need &#8217;em.&#8221;</p>
<p>Let me back up a second. His name is Justin, and his parents called Help Me Howard after he was <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/help-me-howard/10-year-old-not-allowed-in-school-after-seizure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">not allowed into school</a> for violating the mandatory mask policy. Yes, his mask did fall off while he was having a seizure.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd Sr., Justin&#8217;s father: &#8220;I can&#8217;t even count how many seizures he has a month.&#8221;</p>
<p>As our story wrapped up, Justin told us why he wanted to be in school: because he has a goal.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;I want to be a police because police help people.&#8221;</p>
<p>He wants to be a police officer.</p>
<p>South Florida&#8217;s law enforcement community was watching Channel 7.</p>
<p>Maj. Rosanna Cordero-Stutz, Miami-Dade Police: &#8220;I saw, and I cried. That little boy had the hardest day a little boy has ever had in his life, and at the end of the video, the one thing that made him smile and jump up was, &#8216;I want to be a police officer.'&#8221;</p>
<p>And so, police from across South Florida came to show Justin they cared.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;I can&#8217;t believe what&#8217;s happening.&#8221;</p>
<p>Justin stood in amazement. Notice the Band-Aid. He had a seizure, fell and hit his head the day before, but all that was forgotten as the motormen from the North Miami Police Department came rolling up.</p>
<p>Officer: &#8220;Now you are part of us, and the Miami Dolphins sent some gifts for you here, too.&#8221;</p>
<p>Patrol cars from Miami-Dade Police were in the parade for Justin.</p>
<p>Two mounted officers stopped in. Justin had never seen a horse.</p>
<p>Mounted officer: &#8220;Horses love peppermint.&#8221;</p>
<p>His face after feeding a horse a peppermint would make anyone smile, especially his parents.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd Sr.: &#8220;Thank you, God bless you all.&#8221;</p>
<p>Joetta Robinson, Justin&#8217;s mother: &#8220;I&#8217;m so speechless!&#8221;</p>
<p>Justin Floyd Sr.: &#8220;A helicopter just came down our street!&#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s right. Justin is fascinated by police helicopters, and Miami-Dade brought one.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;I can&#8217;t believe it man! I can&#8217;t believe it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Along with Miami-Dade and North Miami Police, the PBA and Police Community Relations Foundation wanted to see Justin.</p>
<p>A bus pulled up filled with police explorers bringing bags of food and gifts for Justin and his sister.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;I can&#8217;t believe so much police are over here giving me stuff.&#8221;</p>
<p>As we looked over, we saw Justin&#8217;s father. There were tears in his eyes.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd Sr.: &#8220;Yeah, it did change my perspective of the police.&#8221;</p>
<p>Joetta Robinson: &#8220;They have come through for one little kid who has a dream of doing what they do.&#8221;</p>
<p>The kindness of the officers left Justin in awe as the little man got to meet the men and women he adores.</p>
<p>Officer: &#8220;Can I get a hug? Thank you so much.&#8221;</p>
<p>Justin: &#8220;Thank you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Officer: &#8220;Just want you to know that you are our little hero.&#8221;</p>
<p>The law enforcement community showed a little boy they don&#8217;t just enforce the law in his neighborhood. They help people like him in the neighborhood.</p>
<p>Rosanna Cordero-Stutz: &#8220;We want him to know that he is not alone, and it&#8217;s the same way for us. We are not alone. We lean on each other, and we want to show that to Justin.&#8221;</p>
<p>And they told Justin what he was hoping to hear: one day, his dream can come true.</p>
<p>Rosanna Cordero-Stutz: &#8220;This is your official junior police badge. I expect to see a real one one day on you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;Yeehaww!&#8221;</p>
<p>Before the officers left, they had one more surprise for Justin. They gave him a bike.</p>
<p>He had never ridden one before, but an officer was there for him.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;Holy moly!&#8221;</p>
<p>Joetta Robinson: &#8220;I would just like to say thank you to Miami-Dade Police Department. Thank you to Help Me Howard, to Channel 7, for coming through for our tiny little family.&#8221;</p>
<p>Justin&#8217;s heart was broken that day when he was kicked out of the school, but now, the kind hearts of police officers made him forget all that.</p>
<p>Justin Floyd: &#8220;Best day I&#8217;ve ever had.&#8221;</p>
<p>What a day, Justin. What a day.</p>
<p>After Channel 7 contacted the Miami-Dade school district, they did allow Justin to return to the classroom.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">862988</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021021-police-response.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/810d5ffc-1b01-4aaa-8765-6ad5e5a2a1f2/94684c00-1b40-4192-b304-865c8dc70e4a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219701~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/810d5ffc-1b01-4aaa-8765-6ad5e5a2a1f2/94684c00-1b40-4192-b304-865c8dc70e4a/main.mp4*~hmac=43f1f393e6e8a4921439b4f58b957de0a53d62b59b5767fd5d5296b596f04058' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021021-police-response.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021021-police-response.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021021 police response</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BSO investigating shooting incident outside holiday party hosted by Pompano Beach school for at-risk youth</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/bso-investigating-shooting-incident-outside-holiday-party-hosted-by-pompano-beach-school-for-at-risk-youth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 03:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=862382</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What started as a holiday celebration inside a South Florida school turned chaotic when gunfire erupted outside. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has her special assignment...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What started as a holiday celebration inside a South Florida school turned chaotic when gunfire erupted outside. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has her special assignment special report: Party Panic.</p>
<p>You can hear the urgency in her voice.</p>
<p>911 caller: &#8220;Hi, I don&#8217;t know. I&#8217;m in Pompano Beach. I&#8217;m inside a party in a room, and they&#8217;re shooting inside the building. I&#8217;m stuck in the bathroom.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was Dec. 25, Christmas night, around 11 p.m.</p>
<p>While huddled inside a bathroom, callers told 911 they believed there was a shooter in the building.</p>
<p>911 caller: &#8220;Hi, I don&#8217;t know the address of where I&#8217;m at, but I&#8217;m at a party, and they&#8217;re shooting inside the building.&#8221;</p>
<p>911 dispatcher: &#8220;Did you see anyone shooting or no?&#8221;</p>
<p>911 caller: &#8220;No, I didn&#8217;t see no one shooting. When they started shooting, I ran and hide myself in the bathroom with me and my friends.&#8221;</p>
<p>One caller said she heard 12 shots.</p>
<p>The other said there were more than 15.</p>
<p>911 dispatcher: &#8220;You don&#8217;t know the name of the club?&#8221;</p>
<p>911 caller: &#8220;Powerline, I think.&#8221;</p>
<p>But, it wasn&#8217;t a club.</p>
<p>Instead, the panicked 911 calls were coming from inside a school for at-risk youth in Pompano Beach.</p>
<p>911 caller: &#8220;Can you make officers come inside, please? Please, please, please.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dispatcher: &#8220;I&#8217;m letting them know.&#8221;</p>
<p>911 caller: &#8220;The police are inside.&#8221;</p>
<p>Deputies: &#8220;Hey, Sheriff&#8217;s Office! Open the door!&#8221;</p>
<p>911 callers: &#8220;We called! We called! We called! We called! We called! We called! We called! We called! We called!&#8221;</p>
<p>Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office deputies responded to the Youth Under Construction Youth Center.</p>
<p>Delvin King, school principal: &#8220;They walked around the building because they thought it was an active shooter within the building, which it wasn&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>Delvin King is the principal and confirms his school did hold the Christmas party, but he would not tell us how many people were there or whether they even attend the school.</p>
<p>7News Producer: &#8220;Were they students?&#8221;</p>
<p>Delvin King: &#8220;I don&#8217;t have that information.&#8221;</p>
<p>7News Producer: &#8220;How do you not have it? It&#8217;s your school.&#8221;</p>
<p>Delvin King: &#8220;It was hosted by the school, but as far as who was there, I don&#8217;t have that information.&#8221;</p>
<p>The principal believes the shots were fired outside on the north side of the building.</p>
<p>Delvin King: &#8220;It must have been in the air because nobody was shot.&#8221;</p>
<p>The day after the shooting incident, the principal posted what he called a &#8220;warning&#8221; to parents on Facebook: &#8220;Your children are also out here with loaded guns shooting in parking lots at parties. This madness has to stop!&#8221;</p>
<p>Delvin King: &#8220;Eventually, something bad is going to happen. Thank God nothing bad happened that night.&#8221;</p>
<p>This isn&#8217;t the first time the youth center has hosted a party during the pandemic.</p>
<p>The principal posted a video on Facebook the day after Thanksgiving.</p>
<p>It shows people dancing &#8212; no social distancing &#8212; and only some wearing masks.</p>
<p>He called it a &#8220;successful party,&#8221; and then, last summer, wearing a school shirt, he shared this video&#8230;</p>
<p>Delvin King singing in video posted on Facebook: &#8220;I&#8217;m takin&#8217; this b**** back to when I was in elementary school. We gettin&#8217; outta here! F*** ya!&#8221;</p>
<p>King wrote, &#8220;When you know the COVID-19 cases are rising and still have a party with no mask and all, then BSO come knocking at the door.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s unclear from the post where that party took place.</p>
<p>BSO tells 7News they continue to investigate the Christmas night shooting and are asking anyone with information to call Broward County Crime Stoppers at 954-493-TIPS or BSO detectives at 954-786-4201.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">862382</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020921-pompano-beach-shooting-incident.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8682fbd7-f177-4154-a2c6-28ee318b5c11/7b6e0580-228b-4a51-9036-3d0389edac5a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219632~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8682fbd7-f177-4154-a2c6-28ee318b5c11/7b6e0580-228b-4a51-9036-3d0389edac5a/main.mp4*~hmac=b900fbb983bea7d1ee809829f36ba44ce5585ff23fce4dee8ec27fa482daa5bf' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020921-pompano-beach-shooting-incident.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020921-pompano-beach-shooting-incident.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">020921 pompano beach shooting incident</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Million</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/missing-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 03:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=861491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When her husband was accidentally killed, she received over $1.5 million in a settlement. But now, the money is gone, taken, she says, from her...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When her husband was accidentally killed, she received over $1.5 million in a settlement. But now, the money is gone, taken, she says, from her bank account. How did this happen? Here is 7&#8217;s Patrick Fraser with this special assignment report, &#8220;Missing Million.&#8221;</p>
<p>He was at a neighbor&#8217;s house and wanted an avocado. It cost Eliseo his life.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez (translation of): &#8220;And he went up the tree, and it had electricity, and it killed him immediately.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was 2013. Magaly&#8217;s life with her husband Eliseo ended that day, and her struggles to survive began.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;I was poor and homeless, and I would sleep in a car.&#8221;</p>
<p>Magaly sued in Broward Circuit Court and settled.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;It was $1,520,000.&#8221;</p>
<p>Magaly had no idea what to do with the enormous check. Her attorney had to show her.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;So he rode me to the Bank America, and I deposited the check.&#8221;</p>
<p>Her first acts with her newfound wealth: give each of her three children $50,000, then homes for them.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;I bought two houses, one for $250,000, and the other one for $160,000.&#8221;</p>
<p>Magaly says she was now left with more than a million dollars in the bank, spread out through 10 accounts.<br />
Enough money to last a lifetime &#8212; till it started disappearing.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;I didn&#8217;t understand anything about accounts or account numbers.&#8221;</p>
<p>As we went through hundreds of pages of bank records, we discovered withdrawals from her accounts began right after she deposited the money.</p>
<p>In 2016, someone withdrew $100,000, and $22,000 on the same day from another of Magaly&#8217;s accounts.</p>
<p>The withdrawals kept on coming, days and months apart.</p>
<p>$3,000&#8230;</p>
<p>$2,000&#8230;</p>
<p>$10,000&#8230;</p>
<p>Here is a $50,000 withdrawal in 2019.</p>
<p>Patrick Fraser: &#8220;So you didn&#8217;t know for <em>four</em> years that someone was stealing your money?&#8221;</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;No. I never had money in my life, so I didn&#8217;t put too much attention.&#8221;</p>
<p>Magaly would get monthly bank statements that could have revealed the thefts, but she didn&#8217;t read them.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;The letter I would get, I would store them. I wouldn&#8217;t open them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Then, in 2020, Magaly got a letter from Bank of America that she did open and did understand.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;That is when I notice all the transactions, and I almost had a heart attack.&#8221;</p>
<p>The million dollars she had in her accounts, down to nearly nothing.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;[There&#8217;s] $3,000 right now. That&#8217;s it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Left with $3,000 after she says $997,000 was stolen from her.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;It&#8217;s terrible, terrible. I&#8217;m still &#8230; I can&#8217;t sleep.&#8221;</p>
<p>Who was able to take so much money from Magaly&#8217;s accounts? She says she has no idea, that she didn&#8217;t tell anyone her account numbers.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;Nobody knew anything. Not even my kids.&#8221;</p>
<p>A Bank of America spokesman wrote, &#8220;We have thoroughly investigated this case and confirmed that appropriate procedures were followed in these banking transactions.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office said, because the case is under investigation, they can&#8217;t talk about it, but Magaly, understandably, can&#8217;t stop talking about it.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;The person who did this has to pay for it. I have to find out who did this.&#8221;</p>
<p>Eight years ago, Magaly lost her husband. Now she has lost nearly all her money.</p>
<p>Magaly Terry-Gonzalez: &#8220;I have to find out who did this.&#8221;</p>
<p>Who did this? Who has her missing million?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">861491</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020821-Missing-Million.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d0cf9544-c072-456e-8af4-fbbd1a96b652/2124b733-fc5d-4c17-8879-75f95dcab04b/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219637~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d0cf9544-c072-456e-8af4-fbbd1a96b652/2124b733-fc5d-4c17-8879-75f95dcab04b/main.mp4*~hmac=e47d650b286b21d228dc9e6e83f14a7fb3e81ca845c0e1a21f0a727151ec1828' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020821-Missing-Million.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020821-Missing-Million.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">020821 Missing Million</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breath of Hope: South Florida doctors lead way against treating severe lung damage caused by COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/breath-of-hope-south-florida-doctors-lead-way-against-treating-severe-lung-damage-caused-by-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 04:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=858628</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[South Florida is leading the way in the fight against one of the most fatal effects of the coronavirus: severe lung damage. As 7&#8217;s Karen...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>South Florida is leading the way in the fight against one of the most fatal effects of the coronavirus: severe lung damage. As 7&#8217;s Karen Hensel reports, the treatment is giving patients a &#8220;Breath of Hope.&#8221;</p>
<p>It has been seven months since Alberto Diaz was in the fight for his life.</p>
<p>Alberto Diaz: &#8220;I collapsed in the door of the hospital.&#8221;</p>
<p>Alberto went to the emergency room at Mount Sinai Medical center on July 3.</p>
<p>He had coronavirus and spent the next month in the ICU.</p>
<p>Alberto Diaz: &#8220;I could not move in the bed because if I moved in the bed, the oxygen would go down.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Seth Gottlieb, Mount Sinai Medical Center: &#8220;He was very bad. His oxygen levels were low, and without the supplemental oxygen that we had, as much as we could push it through his nose and around his face, he would not have survived. He was very bad.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Seth Gottlieb showed us two sets of X-rays.</p>
<p>The dark lungs on the right are normal.</p>
<p>Alberto&#8217;s lungs are on the left. The white cloudiness shows the damage left by COVID.</p>
<p>Dr. Seth Gottlieb: &#8220;We have fluid and proteins and perhaps blood that have filled the airways and fill the air sacs, and that&#8217;s why you had this haziness in the lungs.&#8221;</p>
<p>It took two months in the hospital for Alberto to beat COVID, but the virus left him with severe scarring in his lungs.</p>
<p>Dr. Seth Gottlieb: &#8220;Once you get to that point where the lungs are scarred, many times it doesn&#8217;t go away. It can leave you with permanent deficits.&#8221;</p>
<p>Alberto never smoked and despite being diabetic, was generally in good health, but to this day, he still needs oxygen.</p>
<p>Alberto Diaz: &#8220;My lung is enough to sit down here and talk to you, but if I walk back to the street I begin to&#8230;&#8221;</p>
<p>Alberto is not the only patient struggling. Doctors from across South Florida are treating COVID patients suffering from COVID&#8217;s long lasting effects.</p>
<p>Dr. Jose Suarez, Westchester General Hospital: &#8220;So, they&#8217;re recovering from the disease, and they still have findings for weeks, for months, so we called those post-COVID syndrome and long haulers.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Jose Suarez of Westchester Hospital says long hauler patients can experience everything from hair loss to the worst symptom: lung problems.</p>
<p>Dr. Jose Suarez: &#8220;It looks actually worse than smoker&#8217;s lungs on some patients. It has to do with the scarring that they are developing, and it&#8217;s not just the lungs, but we&#8217;re finding it in other organs &#8212; kidneys, livers.&#8221;</p>
<p>But there is hope. Westchester is among a few hospitals around the world studying a new drug.</p>
<p>Dr. Jose Suarez: &#8220;So we&#8217;re doing a trial with Algernon, a medication called Ifenprodil, which has been around since the &#8217;70s, and we&#8217;re starting to use it on COVID patients, and it&#8217;s a potent anti-inflammatory.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s hoped the drug will reduce the scarring of lung tissue which has led to so many long term problems.</p>
<p>Right now, it&#8217;s only being used on critically ill patients, and Dr. Suarez says the results are looking good.</p>
<p>Dr. Jose Suarez: &#8220;These patients are not getting that scarring that we usually see with the COVID patients, and their reactions to the treatment is phenomenal.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Suarez says 10 patients who have received the drug have recovered from COVID without the scarring, and he believes studies like this one provide hope for future COVID patients.</p>
<p>Dr. Jose Suarez: &#8220;I do see hope. I am so happy that we now have the vaccine. I am seeing a lot of great, cutting edge medications that are about to come out into the market, which is going to be great.&#8221;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this drug won&#8217;t work for Alberto, but he still sees every day as a reason to celebrate.</p>
<p>He says he will continue to fight because from the moment he walked into the hospital, he knew he would win against COVID.</p>
<p>Alberto Diaz: &#8220;I never had in my mind that I would have lost my life there. Never. I see a lot of people pass by there, you know?&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;That didn&#8217;t make it?&#8221;</p>
<p>Alberto Diaz: &#8220;That didn&#8217;t make it. I&#8217;m telling you the truth.&#8221;</p>
<p>And for him, every breath he takes is a breath of hope for a long life with his family and a full recovery.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">858628</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020521-lung-damage.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5b13a269-99bd-4f70-8719-2ec3602e0764/2935dd19-d445-43c8-87df-3b612865d061/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217804~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5b13a269-99bd-4f70-8719-2ec3602e0764/2935dd19-d445-43c8-87df-3b612865d061/main.mp4*~hmac=3f6b04d456474f3e0e838465dad34d735d6e47dc4f32a9b6ca48a8559930980e' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020521-lung-damage.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020521-lung-damage.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">020521 lung damage</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Roof Ripoff: 2 men claiming to be contractors pour substance onto Deerfield Beach home&#8217;s roof</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/roof-ripoff-2-men-claiming-to-be-contractors-pour-substance-onto-deerfield-beach-homes-roof/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 04:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=857481</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A South Florida homeowner just had her roof repaired, so you can imagine her anger when she stepped outside and saw her roof wrecked. The...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Florida homeowner just had her roof repaired, so you can imagine her anger when she stepped outside and saw her roof wrecked. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report: Roof Ripoff.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson loves her Deerfield Beach home she bought back in 1969.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson, homeowner: &#8220;I watched them build it. I was 20 years old when we moved in. My husband was in Vietnam.&#8221;</p>
<p>But now&#8230;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;You don&#8217;t like being in your own backyard anymore?&#8221;</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;I don&#8217;t. I don&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>And that&#8217;s because from here, you can really see the massive black mess on her roof.</p>
<p>Shirley thinks it&#8217;s tar.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;It was terrible. It smelled like tar, and I know what tar smells like.&#8221;</p>
<p>Last month, Shirley needed her roof patched.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;There was a drip-drip, and there was a leak.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, she called a trusted contractor she has known for 30 years.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;They had to match that shingle. They matched it pretty good, so the job looked like it never even happened. I was really happy.&#8221;</p>
<p>One week later, the doorbell rang. Her son answered the door.</p>
<p>Shirley&#8217;s son: &#8220;Yeah.&#8221;</p>
<p>Man: &#8220;Let me show you something.&#8221;</p>
<p>He says this man, as well as a second man seen here, claimed they work for the contractor who wrapped up the job just seven days earlier.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t understand why they were coming back, but I&#8217;m thinking maybe they just want to touch up on the wood.&#8221;</p>
<p>Soon, Shirley&#8217;s husband stepped out.</p>
<p>The two men told him they wanted money.</p>
<p>Shirley then came out enraged.</p>
<p>&#8220;But who are you?!?!?&#8221;</p>
<p>By the time Shirley spoke to them, the damage was done.</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;The guy goes, &#8216;We put eight buckets of this stuff up there, eight gallons. It&#8217;s going to cost you anywhere from $2,000 to $3,000.&#8217; I said, &#8216;Are you crazy? You just destroyed my roof. You think I am going to pay you?'&#8221;</p>
<p>Shirley told the men she was calling her contractor.</p>
<p>As she ran back inside her home to get her phone, the two men bolted in a white pickup.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Do you have any reason to believe these are legitimate contractors?&#8221;</p>
<p>Lt. Brian Montgomery, Broward Sheriff&#8217;s Office: &#8220;Absolutely not.&#8221;</p>
<p>Montgomery says BSO wants these two men identified.</p>
<p>One was wearing a white shirt and black cap.</p>
<p>His face is hard to see because of the face mask, but we do have a better view of the second man who has a white beard.</p>
<p>Lt. Brian Montgomery: &#8220;We want to talk to them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Lt. Montgomery says if anyone comes to your home unannounced for repair work, call police right away.</p>
<p>Lt. Brian Montgomery: &#8220;If they&#8217;re legitimate, they&#8217;re not going to leave. They&#8217;re going to wait for law enforcement to show up. Why? Because they have nothing to hide.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;What do you think their motivation was?&#8221;</p>
<p>Shirley Johnson: &#8220;Money.&#8221;</p>
<p>The two men told Shirley what they sprayed was going to dry clear.</p>
<p>Clearly, that didn&#8217;t happen.</p>
<p>If you have any information on these two men, call BSO at 954-490-4287.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">857481</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020421-roof-ripoff-bso.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d2cba019-4ba4-4fdd-b80d-98a846a16792/2148e337-6ce0-4bc4-b194-aa827595518e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219604~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/d2cba019-4ba4-4fdd-b80d-98a846a16792/2148e337-6ce0-4bc4-b194-aa827595518e/main.mp4*~hmac=dbcf9e92c5d4a4b5486bace0963e6642866208615167ba2d4407fe0404e74778' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020421-roof-ripoff-bso.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020421-roof-ripoff-bso.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">020421 roof ripoff bso</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money for Nothing: Police arrest man accused of defrauding customers out of kitchen, closet renovations</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/money-for-nothing-police-arrest-man-accused-of-defrauding-customers-out-of-kitchen-closet-renovations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=855995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[They thought the extra time at home during the pandemic was the perfect time to renovate. In his special assignment report, Kevin Ozebek investigates why...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>They thought the extra time at home during the pandemic was the perfect time to renovate. In his special assignment report, Kevin Ozebek investigates why they say they shelled out their money for nothing.</p>
<p>They had big dreams of fancy kitchens.</p>
<p>Daisy Salazar: &#8220;I can&#8217;t eat at home. I can&#8217;t cook at home.&#8221;</p>
<p>Walter Martinez: &#8220;I just felt taken, violated.&#8221;</p>
<p>All of these South Florida homeowners hired the same person to renovate their homes, paid big money but were left with big messes.</p>
<p>Jessica Chirino, former customer: &#8220;I have six children in my house without closets and without a kitchen!&#8221;</p>
<p>In May 2020, Michael and Jessica Chirino paid Junior Gonzalez Montes de Oca of Elite Custom Kitchens and Closets, Inc., a $10,800 deposit to update their kitchen cabinets and bedroom closets.</p>
<p>Measurements were made, rooms were ripped out, but after that, not much else happened.</p>
<p>Michael Chirino, former customer: &#8220;As soon as he receives the money, there&#8217;s automatically a disconnection, and then, that&#8217;s when the excuses begin.&#8221;</p>
<p>They were left with a stripped kitchen and bare closets.</p>
<p>They demanded their money back but have only received a fraction of it, and they are not alone.</p>
<p>Daisy Salazar is living out of boxes after paying thousands last year to have her kitchen renovated.</p>
<p>Daisy Salazar, former customer: &#8220;The estimate was for $7,200, and I paid him $4,300. After that, everything was, &#8216;Yes, everything&#8217;s going to be done in a few weeks.&#8217; Weeks, months came and went and nothing.&#8221;</p>
<p>After posting online reviews, Daisy and the Chirinos found even more unhappy customers like Fahim Siddiqui and Walter Martinez.</p>
<p>Walter paid a $7,500 deposit to renovate his kitchen.</p>
<p>Walter Martinez, former customer: &#8220;It took him two weeks just to come and rip out the kitchen, and it was three missed appointments.&#8221;</p>
<p>He says after texting back and forth for months, he asked for a refund but never got a dime.</p>
<p>Walter Martinez: &#8220;My insurance cancelled on me because they consider my house a construction zone.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fahim hired the company to update his kitchen cabinets.</p>
<p>This is what he had to deal with for weeks.</p>
<p>Fahim Siddiqui, former customer: &#8220;All my bottom cabinets, which happens to be the chemicals and all the unsafe stuff, have no doors. No doors, no front covers for my drawers so it&#8217;s just open.&#8221;</p>
<p>We wanted to speak to Gonzalez Montes de Oca, so we stopped by his Miami-Dade warehouse.</p>
<p>No answer, but we tracked him down not far away.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Junior, can we talk to you just for a second?&#8221;</p>
<p>He quickly sped off.</p>
<p>Gonzalez Montes de Oca later agreed to an interview but cancelled.</p>
<p>Then Tuesday, he was arrested, charged with grand theft, contracting without a license and a scheme to defraud.</p>
<p>His attorney tells 7 Investigates his client &#8220;has spent the last 20 years providing quality craftsmanship at affordable prices. Unfortunately, my client&#8217;s business has been in decline and short staffed due to COVID. He had been struggling to fulfill his customer&#8217;s orders due to some personal hardships and has already issued thousands in refunds.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Do you feel justice is being done?&#8221;</p>
<p>Jessica Chirino: &#8220;Partly, I definitely will be looking up his mug shot.&#8221;</p>
<p>Investigators believe that there may be additional victims. Anyone victimized by Gonzalez is asked to call the Economic Crimes Bureau at 305-994-1000.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">855995</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020321-junior-gonzalez-montes-de-oca.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/619ba7b9-f3bd-460f-8613-6f44e7b08492/0392aba8-2a33-452d-aa33-83a3a6ed8545/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217572~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/619ba7b9-f3bd-460f-8613-6f44e7b08492/0392aba8-2a33-452d-aa33-83a3a6ed8545/main.mp4*~hmac=533ec1f7e1bc710fb8bf2fea486946b3237cab94567a4b6b26dff7ca57f9e268' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020321-junior-gonzalez-montes-de-oca.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/020321-junior-gonzalez-montes-de-oca.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">020321 junior gonzalez montes de oca</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami restaurant gifts money &#8212; and a meal &#8212; to local seniors reeling from Alaska trip cancellation</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/miami-restaurant-gifts-money-and-a-meal-to-local-seniors-reeling-from-alaska-trip-cancellation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 06:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=812274</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Help is on the way for a group of seniors who lost thousands of dollars when their trip to Alaska was cancelled. After waiting two...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Help is on the way for a group of seniors who <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/out-in-the-cold-seniors-demand-refund-from-city-of-miami-for-cancelled-alaskan-cruise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lost thousands of dollars</a> when their trip to Alaska was cancelled. After waiting two years with no answers, a local business now has a gift for them this holiday season. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has an update to our special assignment report, &#8220;Out in the Cold.&#8221;</p>
<p>This Miami restaurant serves up a menu that keeps customers coming back for more.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;How&#8217;s the food?&#8221;</p>
<p>Batuka Williams: &#8220;Oh, good. Awesome!&#8221;</p>
<p>Eric Van Dyke, co-owner, iKrave: &#8220;I would say it&#8217;s a mixture of everything. You got soul food, you got a mixture of Spanish how we wanna do it. It&#8217;s a mixture of everything.&#8221;</p>
<p>The owners of iKrave restaurant, Eric and Sheena Van Dyke, decided to open on a day they&#8217;re usually closed, for some very important guests.</p>
<p>Sheena Van Dyke (greeting guests): &#8220;How you doing?&#8221;</p>
<p>They are welcoming members of a group called Seniors on the Move. Before the pandemic, they would meet at Charles Hadley Park in Miami.</p>
<p>When the 7News team met the seniors earlier this year, they were frustrated with the city&#8217;s Parks and Recreation Department.</p>
<p>Katherine Ellis: &#8220;Give us our money back. We deserve &#8212; we&#8217;ve worked hard all our lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>In 2018, they each paid thousands of dollars for an Alaskan cruise. The money was collected by Charles Hadley Park director and trip organizer, Antavius Howell.</p>
<p>When the trip was cancelled, some received partial refunds, but others got nothing.</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;We&#8217;ve been waiting two years to get the money.&#8221;</p>
<p>And they&#8217;re still waiting.</p>
<p>When Howell died unexpectedly in June, the seniors reached out to 7News for help. They grew angry at the lack of answers from the city &#8230; and lack of a refund.</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;Shame on you! Two to three thousand dollars. That&#8217;s a lot of money for no one to say anything.&#8221;</p>
<p>When our report aired in November, Eric and Sheena were watching.</p>
<p>Sheena Van Dyke, co-owner, iKrave: &#8220;To lose that type of money in this pandemic is truly, truly heartbreaking, so, if we can help them in some aspect to getting some of their money back, that&#8217;s what we&#8217;re here to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Van Dykes gave the seniors a free meal here at their restaurant, but they wanted to do even more.</p>
<p>Sheena Van Dyke: &#8220;When we seen your story, my husband, the first thing he said was, &#8216;We have to do something,&#8217; and when he say that, guess what we&#8217;re gonna do? We&#8217;re gonna do something! We do want to give each and every one of you $500 for what you all went through.&#8221;</p>
<p>Five hundred dollars to help each of the seniors through the holiday season.</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;I&#8217;m so overwhelmed. I mean, this is beautiful.&#8221;</p>
<p>Batuka Williams: &#8220;There are good people in the world, and for them to see this and stand up and do something for us, I mean, that ain&#8217;t nothing but God in them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Around the same time 7News started investigating the seniors&#8217; story, the Miami Police Department&#8217;s public corruption task force also started an investigation. The case is still open.</p>
<p>But the seniors are not hopeful Parks and Rec will give them their money back.</p>
<p>Katherine Ellis: &#8220;The city needs to do better as far as the seniors are concerned. Have an open heart. Look at the situation.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, they are extremely thankful for Eric and Sheena&#8217;s kindness.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">812274</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201225_Hadley_Park_seniors_at_iKrave.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ebf20dcf-63c3-4fff-9d09-877e828ad31c/79763148-58d1-48af-a1c3-93ab5b87fc11/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217750~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ebf20dcf-63c3-4fff-9d09-877e828ad31c/79763148-58d1-48af-a1c3-93ab5b87fc11/main.mp4*~hmac=1902b4f14624933f7da9d3505cd1f39e180b0a9c16ae1a8154f5a33f75e228ce' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201225_Hadley_Park_seniors_at_iKrave.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201225_Hadley_Park_seniors_at_iKrave.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201225_Hadley_Park_seniors_at_iKrave</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sweet Dreams: Owner of Night Owl Cookies, 29, turns baked treats into big business</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/sweet-dreams-owner-of-night-owl-cookies-29-turns-baked-treats-into-big-business/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=791651</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The holiday season is here, and with that comes Christmas cookies. One South Florida entrepreneur is baking up big business. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows us...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The holiday season is here, and with that comes Christmas cookies. One South Florida entrepreneur is baking up big business. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows us how he is turning his &#8220;Sweet Dreams&#8221; into a reality.</p>
<p>They are covered in sprinkles. Coated in cereal.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez, owner, Night Owl Cookies: &#8220;How much fun is that?&#8221;</p>
<p>Stuffed with guava. Saturated with chocolate chips.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Can we talk about how much chocolate is on that cooke?&#8221;</p>
<p>And racking up thousands of &#8220;likes&#8221; on Instagram.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;How many calories are in this, Andrew?&#8221;</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;You shouldn&#8217;t be asking.&#8221;</p>
<p>At just 29 years old, Andrew Gonzalez is the brains &#8212; and the master baker &#8212; behind Night Owl Cookies.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;I&#8217;d rather not have lunch and dinner and just go straight for the cookies.&#8221;</p>
<p>While many businesses are struggling, Andrew&#8217;s is thriving.</p>
<p>He just expanded his South Florida chain by opening a cookie shop in North Miami. Later this month, he&#8217;s opening stores in Wynwood and Pembroke Pines.</p>
<p>Since the pandemic, his sales have surged on the Postmates delivery app.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;People love desserts, and &#8216;stressed&#8217; spelled backward is &#8216;desserts.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Andrew can bake upwards of 10,000 cookies a day from his commercial kitchen in Miami.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;What goes through your head as you just look at what you&#8217;ve created? This is yours.&#8221;</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;It&#8217;s difficult to comprehend, honestly. I still sometimes don&#8217;t believe it.&#8221;</p>
<p>To many, Night Owl Cookies may seem like an overnight success, but Andrew started the company 9 years ago while he was a student at Miami Dade College.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;The only time I had to bake cookies was nighttime, so Night Owl Cookies came to be.&#8221;</p>
<p>His first big break was being <a href="https://wsvn.com/entertainment/miamis-own-night-owl-cookies-draws-national-attention-with-help-from-deco/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">featured on Deco Drive</a> in 2013. Back then &#8230;</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;It was a one-man show.&#8221;</p>
<p>He took the orders and did the deliveries himself.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;I was a lost college student. I didn&#8217;t know what I wanted to do with my life, and I feel like a lot of people today feel the same waym especially with the pandemic, but when you don&#8217;t give up and you have this dream and you reach for it, you can make it happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now, he has around 60 employees.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;You&#8217;re going to make me cry, and I don&#8217;t want to cry. Come on, man. Yeah, I never thought &#8212; I am literally emotional.&#8221;</p>
<p>After just one bite, you&#8217;ll taste what makes these cookies special.</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;It all goes back to the dough. The dough is our prized possession.&#8221;</p>
<p>The recipe is so secret, employees here don&#8217;t even know it. For the dry ingredients, they just mix what&#8217;s labeled &#8220;Bag #1&#8221; with what&#8217;s labeled &#8220;Bag #2.&#8221;</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;Our recipe is located in one spot. I handwrote it myself, sealed it. It&#8217;s actually in a safety deposit box.&#8221;</p>
<p>Though his team does know how to make the cookies perfect for instagram &#8230; and he taught me, too.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;So you kind of roll it like this, and then you put it right into the chocolate?&#8221;</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;You got it!&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Look at this chocolate chip cookie! It&#8217;s like half chocolate, half dough!&#8221;</p>
<p>After waiting patiently while the cookies baked for 12 minutes&#8230;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Look at that!&#8221;</p>
<p>Finally, it&#8217;s time to taste.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;This is phenomenal. Talk about the best day on the job ever, in 15 years of being a reporter.&#8221;</p>
<p>It may be messy&#8230;</p>
<p>Andrew Gonzalez: &#8220;If it doesn&#8217;t make a mess on your hands when you&#8217;re eating it, it&#8217;s not a chocolate chip cookie.&#8221;</p>
<p>But dreams sure are sweet when they look like this.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">791651</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201204_Andrew_Gonzalez_Night_Owl_Cookies_owner.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0e1f6dfe-1182-4e7c-87b6-8f9d82320719/be488a7f-52f3-4362-a9f8-c550099c4d41/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219625~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0e1f6dfe-1182-4e7c-87b6-8f9d82320719/be488a7f-52f3-4362-a9f8-c550099c4d41/main.mp4*~hmac=c73244ad6a7472d102642204877e2efcd79cc41790a9f9788469bf882a610dbc' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201204_Andrew_Gonzalez_Night_Owl_Cookies_owner.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201204_Andrew_Gonzalez_Night_Owl_Cookies_owner.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201204_Andrew_Gonzalez_Night_Owl_Cookies_owner</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Born without arms, Afghan refugee swimmer trains in Fort Lauderdale for Tokyo Paralympics in 2021</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/born-without-arms-afghan-refugee-swimmer-trains-in-fort-lauderdale-for-tokyo-paralympics-in-2021/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 04:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=785738</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For some, this Thanksgiving will be like no other with the pandemic bringing big celebrations to a holiday halt. Tonight, we want to give you...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For some, this Thanksgiving will be like no other with the pandemic bringing big celebrations to a holiday halt. Tonight, we want to give you a moment to remember all we do have through the eyes of a young athlete who has found a new home in South Florida. 7&#8217;s Karen Hensel has our special assignment report: Winning Spirit.</p>
<p>Lap after lap after lap, under the early morning South Florida sun, swimmers glide through the lanes at the Carter Aquatic Complex in Fort Lauderdale.</p>
<p>Their arms propelling their bodies forward, except for one swimmer, though he&#8217;s still making waves.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi, training for Paralympics: &#8220;My father used to say, &#8216;God took your arms from you, but instead, he give you the talent and skill in your legs and your feet.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Meet Abbas Karimi, an elite swimmer who was born without arms.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;Everything was very challenging to do with my feet and learn everything.&#8221;</p>
<p>Abbas grew up in war-torn Afghanistan.</p>
<p>Now, he&#8217;s training here in South Florida for the 2021 Paralympic games in Japan.</p>
<p>The 23-year-old&#8217;s journey to get here has been filled with pain and perseverance.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;They was always calling me armless, &#8216;Oh, look at this guy, doesn&#8217;t have arms&#8217; and trying to make fun of me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bullied as a boy, he discovered something that soothed him &#8212; a love of the water.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;When I learned swimming, I was not believing in myself almost a year, like, &#8216;Wow, I learned swimming without arms.'&#8221;</p>
<p>As a teenager, he made the difficult decision to leave home.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;It&#8217;s tough to leave your family, your father, your mother at the very young age of 16, but I wanted to get out of that world.&#8221;</p>
<p>He first went to Iran before his brother helped smuggle him across the border into neighboring Turkey.</p>
<p>It was a dangerous gamble.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;If the police capture you on the border, they can do anything to you. They can kill you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Abbas lived in Turkey as a refugee.</p>
<p>Then, he came to the United States under the United Nations&#8217; refugee program.</p>
<p>After a few years living and training in Portland, this summer, Abbas moved to South Florida.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s now part of the Swim Fort Lauderdale program.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;It feels right to be here because I found the right coach.&#8221;</p>
<p>Working to help Abbas achieve his goal is Fort Lauderdale swim coach Marty Hendrick.</p>
<p>Marty Hendrick, coach: &#8220;Our arms in swimming helps us turn our body into a position to get air. He doesn&#8217;t have that. To get on the podium, he knows he&#8217;s got to really work.&#8221;</p>
<p>And work he does. In the pool six days a week, sometimes training twice a day.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;My family is so happy for me. I lost my father last year. The last time that my father talked to me, he said that you put my name in the top of the world. He said that you made me very proud.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coach Marty is also very proud of Abbas, who he&#8217;s not simply guiding in the pool, but in life.</p>
<p>Abbas Karimi: &#8220;I&#8217;m living with him. I call him dad at home.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marty Hendrick: &#8220;I feel completely blessed that I have this kid at home.&#8221;</p>
<p>Abbas and Coach Marty will travel next summer to Tokyo for the 2021 Paralympic Games, where the swimmer is set to compete in several events. We will, of course, update you on their journey.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">785738</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112520-abbas-karimi.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/894f10e1-666d-402b-b9ad-d412bc1c8b5c/5ce76dcc-9a72-4bc5-8141-0683a9986de9/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219635~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/894f10e1-666d-402b-b9ad-d412bc1c8b5c/5ce76dcc-9a72-4bc5-8141-0683a9986de9/main.mp4*~hmac=8c683ad7c9d0297e445cd834972ec3afb483e4f84e59fc12b4316fe812427347' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112520-abbas-karimi.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112520-abbas-karimi.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">112520 abbas karimi</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Masking the Problem: Is there harm in wearing a mask a few days in a row?</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/masking-the-problem-is-there-harm-in-wearing-a-mask-a-few-days-in-a-row/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 04:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=785168</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since we use them so often, we&#8217;re probably all guilty of not washing or disposing of our masks daily, so is there any harm in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since we use them so often, we&#8217;re probably all guilty of not washing or disposing of our masks daily, so is there any harm in wearing for a mask a few days in a row? 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek answers that question in tonight&#8217;s special report: Masking the Problem.</p>
<p>Masks are the defining symbol of the new normal, and we know they work at limiting the spread of COVID-19.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant, Florida Atlantic University: &#8220;I would say it is the most effective thing we can do.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Dr. Patrick Grant, a biomedical scientist at Florida Atlantic University, has made an alarming discovery about what can be living on your mask.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;I&#8217;d like to think I have pretty good hygiene. That was my assumption, so I was pretty disturbed to see how much was growing on this.&#8221;</p>
<p>Masks act as a roadblock against aerosol, the tiny droplets we release when we breathe, cough, sneeze and talk.</p>
<p>These droplets can carry bacteria and viruses like COVID-19.</p>
<p>We tested different masks this summer with Dr. Grant&#8217;s colleague Dr. Nwadiuto.</p>
<p>Dr. Nwadiuto Esiobu, Florida Atlantic University: &#8220;Each time we do this experiment, we find that 100% of the time, we got no aerosols passed through the KN-95s.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Dr. Grant says take all that aerosol, add in the germs on our hands, which we use to adjust our masks, and they quickly get very dirty</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;You have to make sure you are not cross contaminating other surfaces, or other people, more problematically, with that same mask.&#8221;</p>
<p>To see what micro-organisms can be on well-worn masks, I brought these two into Dr. Grant&#8217;s lab.</p>
<p>This cloth one, I used for one full day.</p>
<p>This surgical-style mask also got a full day&#8217;s use, which included a morning workout.</p>
<p>Dr. Grant took a sample from each masks, and then, swabbed a petri dish.</p>
<p>It incubated all weekend.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;This is the surgical mask.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Oh, gross!.&#8221;</p>
<p>And then, we came back to see the eye-popping results.</p>
<p>The petri dish with the sample from the surgical mask was loaded with bacteria and likely yeast colonies.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;Yeah, this is alive. This came off your mask.&#8221;</p>
<p>The petri dish with the cloth mask sample hosted even more colonies.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;That is horrifying to see, I have to say. I did not expect that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;I think even more troubling, at the moment, during the pandemic is viruses, such as coronavrius, is also likely trapped on our mask if we are exposed to it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Not all of the micro-organisms festering in these petri dishes are dangerous.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;Some of them can be quite beneficial to us, but occasionally, some of them are not.&#8221;</p>
<p>Some of the potentially bad bacteria Dr. Grant has found on masks include e-coli and staph. He&#8217;s also found types of fungi, and while his lab cannot detect viruses like coronavirus, he has little doubt they&#8217;re on masks too.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;If you&#8217;re infected with it, you&#8217;re breathing it onto your mask.&#8221;</p>
<p>We can also transfer germs onto our masks by touching them and by touching contaminated surfaces like bathroom door handles, which is why it&#8217;s best to start every day with a fresh mask.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;If you&#8217;re not confident about how clean your mask might be and you don&#8217;t have any way to clean it, it&#8217;s probably best to dispose of it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Grant has created this patent pending mask disinfector. It uses a specific type of UV light to damage the genetic material of micro-organisms and viruses, including COVID-19.</p>
<p>Dr. Patrick Grant: &#8220;That kind of damage at a significant level isn&#8217;t sustainable for life.&#8221;</p>
<p>But for now, your best bet is running cloth masks through the wash, and these surgical masks should be tossed out after wearing them for one day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">785168</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112420-petri-dish.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ffecf4e9-11e0-4ce8-8a04-307a1b8bfeb0/edb84779-ce2e-49d3-aff4-b909f0242a42/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219657~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ffecf4e9-11e0-4ce8-8a04-307a1b8bfeb0/edb84779-ce2e-49d3-aff4-b909f0242a42/main.mp4*~hmac=b4ce5cd4da3f712930510a878f859dc269caada7ffabfdde19e9d9ea234e8dd0' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112420-petri-dish.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112420-petri-dish.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">112420 petri dish</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Driving Down Business? Chick-fil-A drive-thru traffic blocks access to small businesses in Pompano Beach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/driving-down-business-chick-fil-a-drive-thru-traffic-blocks-access-to-small-businesses-in-pompano-beach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=784338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Some South Florida small businesses say they are literally being cut off and worry if they&#8217;ll be able to survive, and they are pointing the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some South Florida small businesses say they are literally being cut off and worry if they&#8217;ll be able to survive, and they are pointing the finger at a fast food giant. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has tonight&#8217;s special assignment report, &#8220;Driving Down Business?&#8221;</p>
<p>For more than 20 years, Virginia O&#8217;Neil has been cutting hair.</p>
<p>Virginia O&#8217;Neil, barbershop owner: &#8220;It has afforded me a modest, nice lifestyle.&#8221;</p>
<p>She owns TFS Hair Stylings in Pompano Beach, but right now, it&#8217;s her business that&#8217;s being cut.</p>
<p>Virginia says she has gone from an average of 14 cuts a day to just seven, and she says it&#8217;s not just because of the pandemic.</p>
<p>Customer: &#8220;I&#8217;m trying to go home!&#8221;</p>
<p>Virginia says her barbershop is being affected by this fast food drive-thru that sometimes snakes right past her front window.</p>
<p>Virginia O&#8217;Neil: &#8220;Here comes the Chick-fil-A parade. It saddens me that so many people who I have been cutting their hair for over 20 years, I don&#8217;t see anymore.&#8221;</p>
<p>Virginia says at times her clients physically cannot get to her, and the view from 7Skyforce helps explain why.</p>
<p>Here is Virginia&#8217;s barbershop, off Federal Highway, and her two parking lots. Next door is the Chick-fil-A, and look how drivers waiting for the drive-thru can block off access to Virginia&#8217;s parking spots.</p>
<p>As one of Virginia&#8217;s customers describes it&#8230;</p>
<p>Jane Eisdorfer, barbershop customer: &#8220;It&#8217;s like an accident waiting to happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>The congestion can be frustrating for those trying to come&#8230;</p>
<p>Jack Owens, barbershop customer: &#8220;I&#8217;ve actually come by, and it was backed up so far on Federal Highway that I just had to go past.&#8221;</p>
<p>And go.</p>
<p>Bernard Kelley, in car trying to leave Virginia&#8217;s barbershop: &#8220;You expect to just get out and go, but you have to sit here for 5 to 10 minutes trying to just to leave the business.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, we&#8217;re trying to leave Virginia&#8217;s barbershop now, but we&#8217;re stuck now, too, because we&#8217;re essentially in the Chick-fil-A drive-thru.</p>
<p>Aly Arnold, Jimmy John&#8217;s franchise owner: &#8220;Monday thru Friday we are in war. I mean, I apologize to all our customers.&#8221;</p>
<p>Aly Arnold co-owns a Jimmy John&#8217;s in the same plaza as Virginia&#8217;s barbershop. She says, since the pandemic, the popularity of the Chick-fil-A drive-thru has surged, but with customers now sometimes struggling to get to her sub shop, she says, her sales have been sliced in half.</p>
<p>Aly Arnold: &#8220;We&#8217;re here to work with you. We&#8217;re not against you. We&#8217;re neighbors, so if you&#8217;re willing to come to a compromise and we can solve this as adults, let&#8217;s do it.&#8221;</p>
<p>At the Chick-fil-A, they are trying to make this line move. You can see staff walking car by car grabbing orders.</p>
<p>The operator of this Chick-fil-A franchise tells us, &#8220;We recognize that there are traffic concerns surrounding our drive-thru, and we have been working diligently with the city of Pompano Beach, local law enforcement and Chick-fil-A, Inc. to implement a permanent solution to improve traffic flow. Our goal is to ensure that &#8230; those in close proximity to our restaurant are safe, and we can assure you that additional changes are in progress.&#8221;</p>
<p>Virginia O&#8217;Neil: &#8220;Well, I would be very grateful, because like I said, I know Chick-fil-A is not going, nor do I wish them to go. The only thing I&#8217;m asking is to move the drive-thru over to the left hand lane.&#8221;</p>
<p>But since drive-thru traffic sometimes still blocks access to her barbershop, Virginia decided to force the drive-thru into that left hand lane herself.</p>
<p>Virginia O&#8217;Neil: &#8220;Let their customers feel like my customers.&#8221;</p>
<p>For one day, she strategically parked her SUV so her customers could easily maneuver around. It was a quick, but not permanent fix, for this jammed parking lot.</p>
<p>Pompano Beach Commissioner Andrea McGee tells 7News the city&#8217;s building department is looking into whether it has the power to help solve the problem. If so, McGee says, she&#8217;d like to see a solution in which all sides are left happy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">784338</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201123_Pompano_Beach_Chick_fil_A_drive_thru_aerial.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0fa3dd1b-20ca-401a-affe-7afd5bf0a734/6b395773-4723-4b1c-996b-7b48cfcffa27/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219702~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0fa3dd1b-20ca-401a-affe-7afd5bf0a734/6b395773-4723-4b1c-996b-7b48cfcffa27/main.mp4*~hmac=5c52f8bd1e73777115f4fd3a8460bca124e569c68fec2e2fbf1e2c8eba439855' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201123_Pompano_Beach_Chick_fil_A_drive_thru_aerial.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201123_Pompano_Beach_Chick_fil_A_drive_thru_aerial.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201123_Pompano_Beach_Chick_fil_A_drive_thru_aerial</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Safe Travels: What to expect at airports as millions prepare to travel for Thanksgiving</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/safe-travels-what-to-expect-at-airports-as-millions-prepare-to-travel-for-thanksgiving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 03:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=783132</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With COVID cases spiking across the country, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is now urging people to stay home this Thanksgiving, but still,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With COVID cases spiking across the country, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is now urging people to stay home this Thanksgiving, but still, it&#8217;s expected millions will be hopping on a plane for the first time since the pandemic. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows us how to have safe travels.</p>
<p>Airports again are getting busy! So, before take off, the new safety protocols start here on the ground at the airport.</p>
<p>Greg Chin, Miami International Airport: &#8220;Facial coverings are required in the airport, so once you step foot inside the airport, you must have some sort of facial covering on.&#8221;</p>
<p>And that applies to both MIA and FLL.</p>
<p>At check-in, you&#8217;ll now see Plexiglas shields separating you from the agent, but doctors say to be extra safe, check in online at home and use mobile boarding passes.</p>
<p>Dr. Terry Adirim, Florida Atlantic University: &#8220;I would really look into doing as much as you can hands free.&#8221;</p>
<p>At TSA checkpoints, agents are now behind barriers, and there are new procedures.</p>
<p>You may be asked to insert your passport or driver&#8217;s license into one of these scanners.</p>
<p>Daniel Ronan, Transportation Security Administration: &#8220;We want passengers to do that themselves, so they don&#8217;t have to hand their ID to somebody else.&#8221;</p>
<p>7News was given rare access inside a check point, so we could see how cleaning crews are constantly wiping down all the bins and surfaces.</p>
<p>Agents also have 3D baggage screeners, so they don&#8217;t have to hand search as much luggage.</p>
<p>Now, it&#8217;s time to board!</p>
<p>Field Sutton, Spirit Airlines: &#8220;Once you get on the aircraft, my advice is just try and stay calm. If you haven&#8217;t flown recently, it is going to feel strange.&#8221;</p>
<p>Experts say wipe your seat with disinfectant before sitting down.</p>
<p>Dr. Terry Adirim: &#8220;The airlines are doing a very good job at cleaning their planes before people board, but it can give you a sense of confidence that at least your area is clean, and once you sit down in your seat, reach overhead and turn the vent so the airflow is at maximum. It pulls the air all the way down. It keeps it vertical.&#8221;</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s why that vertical airflow on board is crucial.</p>
<p>The Department of Defense fitted jets with this particle spitting mannequin and particle detecting sensors in every seat.</p>
<p>With a downward airflow and efficient filtration system, the study found you&#8217;d have to sit next to an infectious person for at least 54 hours to receive a dangerous dose of COVID-19.</p>
<p>Dr. Terry Adirim: &#8220;They found the particles didn&#8217;t really go very far, and if people wear masks, it is really a safe environment while you&#8217;re flying.&#8221;</p>
<p>And to further boost passenger confidence, American Airlines is deep cleaning with a virus killing electro-static spray.</p>
<p>Spirit Airlines is fogging aircraft so all surfaces are left with a coating that protects passengers from microorganisms.</p>
<p>Frontier Airlines is hand cleaning every single seat in-between flights, and on all airlines, masks are mandatory.</p>
<p>Jake Filene, Frontier Airlines: &#8220;We&#8217;ve denied boarding to a number of people because they don&#8217;t want to wear a mask.&#8221;</p>
<p>Field Sutton: &#8220;At this point, we have banned nearly 300 people from flying Spirit because it is not worth it to us. We don&#8217;t want you on our plane if you are not going to wear a mask.&#8221;</p>
<p>And once you land, doctors say keep that mask on when you hop into a taxi or Uber.</p>
<p>Dr. Terry Adirim: &#8220;Always wear a mask. Don&#8217;t crowd in the car, especially with other people that are not part of your family unit.&#8221;</p>
<p>And as travel picks up, so will the measures to stop the virus from spreading.</p>
<p>At Tampa International Airport, you can now get a rapid COVID test before you board.</p>
<p>MIA will offer the same service next month.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s all to make sure you have safe travels.</p>
<p>TSA still only allows 3.4 ounce liquid bottles in carry-ons, but now with one exception. You are allowed to travel with up to 12 ounces of hand sanitizer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">783132</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112020-airport-check-in.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/974dad8b-40ad-4181-a9a5-8b74dfd6bff9/d2aeec4c-2c11-4e5d-8f43-2c1f00818fb0/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219671~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/974dad8b-40ad-4181-a9a5-8b74dfd6bff9/d2aeec4c-2c11-4e5d-8f43-2c1f00818fb0/main.mp4*~hmac=2e8fd760eefdf833564f5c0ca46a6122e7c94104eda5e72da1f919d54286df7a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112020-airport-check-in.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112020-airport-check-in.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">112020 airport check in</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Scammer Wasn&#8217;t a Porn Star, She Was A &#8230;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/the-scammer-wasnt-a-porn-star-she-was-a/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 03:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=781941</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He thought he found the person he wanted to spend the rest of his life with, but as the Nightteam&#8217;s Patrick Fraser shows us, it...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He thought he found the person he wanted to spend the rest of his life with, but as the Nightteam&#8217;s Patrick Fraser shows us, it turns out all he found was love and lies, which cost him big time.</p>
<p>Gary and Kathy were married for 56 years until she passed away in 2018.</p>
<p>Gary Buckley, scammed: &#8220;I hate to talk about that because we&#8217;ll get too emotional.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley, Gary&#8217;s daughter: &#8220;I&#8217;m sure that this stems from loneliness and boredom.&#8221;</p>
<p>Very lonely, very vulnerable and then he met a person on the internet.</p>
<p>Gary Buckley: &#8220;A person that I could enjoy the remainder of my life with.&#8221;</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s back up and let Gary&#8217;s daughter Kristine pick up the story.</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley: &#8220;He left his phone in my car, and I snooped and realized he&#8217;s been talking to this woman.&#8221;</p>
<p>The woman said she was Jelena Jensen, a former porn star.</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley: &#8220;I learned that they had been talking. They were in love. They are getting married.&#8221;</p>
<p>The woman said she had to go by the name Daniola Wilsonz because she was in hiding.</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley: &#8220;She says that she is the real Jelena Jensen, but she had to escape her ex-boyfriend, who was forcing her to do porn.&#8221;</p>
<p>As Kristine followed the texts, she saw her father had been sending the person money.</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley: &#8220;He sent her $500 at one time, $300 another time.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gary Buckley: &#8220;I&#8217;ve sent her just under $5,000.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gary also sent flowers to a Utah address and then got excited when the person said she wanted to move to South Florida.</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley: &#8220;They have talked about her moving in for a little while. Then, they&#8217;re going to get their own house and have a baby.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristine and her brother tried to talk to their father to explain the person was a scammer. The crook, in turn, convinced Gary his kids were trying to break them up.</p>
<p>Linda Buckley, Gary&#8217;s sister: &#8220;She turns him against the kids. She&#8217;s already saying things like, &#8216;Don&#8217;t listen to the kids and don&#8217;t tell them these things because they&#8217;re going to turn you against me.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Gary believed the conniving scammer, quit talking to his children, sent the person he thought he loved his class ring, a plane ticket to come live with him and more cash.</p>
<p>Kristine Buckley: &#8220;My dad, right now, just took an Uber to FedEx. He&#8217;s on his way to send her more money.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kristine gave up trying to convince her father he was being scammed and asked us to help to find the proof to show Gary what was going on.</p>
<p>We went to work to track the person down. It was interesting.</p>
<p>This is the address where Gary sent the person cash and presents. A house in Utah that, court records show, is owned by a man.</p>
<p>The con artist was using the name Daniola Robinson Wilsonz.</p>
<p>The last name of the man who owns the house is Robinson. That explained something Gary had told us.</p>
<p>Linda Buckley: &#8220;He&#8217;s never heard her voice, just these lines and lines and lines of text of how much she loves him.&#8221;</p>
<p>We are convinced the so-called woman that texted she loved Gary is a man.</p>
<p>We texted him. He said he was too smart for our stupid questions, and the former porn star Jelena Jensen didn&#8217;t want to go on camera with us but wrote on Twitter they are &#8220;using my photos. They are lying. Don&#8217;t get catfished.&#8221;</p>
<p>We took all the information to Gary. It was now clear to him what was going on.</p>
<p>Gary Buckley: &#8220;Yes, I have been taken, taken me for an emotional ride.&#8221;</p>
<p>Of course, Gary knows why he got scammed. He was vulnerable.</p>
<p>Gary Buckley: &#8220;I wanted a companion again, and I just didn&#8217;t want to sit around, wilt and die. I wanted something else to happen to give me a reason to live.&#8221;</p>
<p>But, while Gary&#8217;s spirits are crushed, he still has hope for a legitimate girlfriend.</p>
<p>Gary Buckley: &#8220;I won&#8217;t turn it down. I would still like to have a companion, even if it&#8217;s only for nine years, 10 years, 12 years.&#8221;</p>
<p>More love, no lies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">781941</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111820-jelena-jensen.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/56ca79af-0c57-4c8c-96e5-d864651bb4b9/42384265-d0b4-449a-b6c9-ee4c653543c8/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219672~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/56ca79af-0c57-4c8c-96e5-d864651bb4b9/42384265-d0b4-449a-b6c9-ee4c653543c8/main.mp4*~hmac=02789ea82b47ce519871dee38793cf32400c86dddc9682c60ce5a30abf0dfdfc' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111820-jelena-jensen.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111820-jelena-jensen.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">111820 jelena jensen</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Firefighters sound alarm about toxic chemicals in protective suits, potential health risks</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/firefighters-sound-alarm-about-toxic-chemicals-in-protective-suits-potential-health-risks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 04:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=780670</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s a story that could affect every firefighter in Florida and across the country. It&#8217;s about their gear, their health and why they&#8217;re sounding the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a story that could affect every firefighter in Florida and across the country. It&#8217;s about their gear, their health and why they&#8217;re sounding the alarm. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has this special assignment report: Fighting More Than Fire.</p>
<p>Palm Beach County firefighter Ric Jorge had been living his dream.</p>
<p>Ric Jorge: &#8220;I&#8217;ve always wanted to be a fireman for as far back as I can remember.&#8221;</p>
<p>His helmet carries visible scars of his fire fights, but now, he suspects the gear designed to protect him could have actually hurt him.</p>
<p>Ric Jorge: &#8220;It was not about if I get cancer, it&#8217;s when I get cancer.&#8221;</p>
<p>Firefighters have known for years they have higher cancer rates.</p>
<p>Ric was diagnosed with colon cancer last year.</p>
<p>Ric Jorge, retired Palm Beach County firefighter: &#8220;You see the statistics and the different types of cancer. I just looked at it realistically and said, &#8216;All right, it&#8217;s just a matter of time.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Diane Cotter, husband is a retired Worcester, MA firefighter: &#8220;Paul was an amazing firefighter, truly a fireman&#8217;s firefighter.&#8221;</p>
<p>When Diane Cotter&#8217;s husband was diagnosed with prostate cancer in 2014, she was determined to find out why, even though she had no medical training.</p>
<p>Diane Cotter: &#8220;I have barely a 12th grade education, and I have an expired hair dresser&#8217;s license.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, she researched, started asking questions, then zeroed in on the protective suits known as turnout gear that firefighters wear to every call.</p>
<p>She asked manufacturers what was in the gear.</p>
<p>Diane Cotter: &#8220;&#8216;Well, we can&#8217;t tell you because it&#8217;s proprietary.'&#8221;</p>
<p>But she didn&#8217;t give up.</p>
<p>She found Notre Dame nuclear physicist Graham Peaslee, who agreed to test the suits.</p>
<p>Graham Peaslee: &#8220;I had not seen anything that high before, and so that&#8217;s what made me concerned.&#8221;</p>
<p>Peaslee&#8217;s test found the gear was soaked in a toxic chemical called polyfluoroalkyl substances, or PFAS.</p>
<p>Graham Peaslee: &#8220;The amount of it there is actually not miniscule. It&#8217;s a large amount compared to how toxic these chemicals are.&#8221;</p>
<p>Peaslee says when firefighters sweat, their pores open, creating an avenue for the chemicals to possibly enter the body.</p>
<p>Graham Peaslee: &#8220;Specifically, underarms and the groin, where the skin is thinner, where there&#8217;s more exposure to chemicals known to get through there.&#8221;</p>
<p>In June, after a peer review by fellow scientists, his study was published.</p>
<p>Graham Peaslee: &#8220;Previous to this article coming out, it was discounted that there was any risk associated with this.&#8221;</p>
<p>But the dangers of PFAS have been known for years.</p>
<p>Rob Bilott, attorney: &#8220;What&#8217;s the impact of the potential that those chemicals were there and could be getting into the blood of the firefighters?&#8221;</p>
<p>Attorney Rob Bilott sued and won after PFAS was found in drinking water in West Virginia.</p>
<p>Last year, Hollywood turned his court battle into the movie &#8220;Dark Waters.&#8221;</p>
<p>Actor Mark Ruffalo portrayed Bilott in the film.</p>
<p>Rob Bilott: &#8220;A lot was known about the toxicity of these PFAS chemicals going back many many decades, and when I say known, it was known by the manufacturers.&#8221;</p>
<p>And that knowledge is the basis of a new lawsuit.</p>
<p>Two dozen California firefighters are suing manufacturers, including 3M and DuPont, over the PFAS chemical being used in their gear and firefighting foam.</p>
<p>The lawsuit alleges the companies &#8220;for decades &#8230; were aware of the harmful impact these substances have on human health,&#8221; and they sold it &#8220;without ever informing firefighters.&#8221;</p>
<p>3M sent a statement to 7News: &#8220;3M acted responsibly in connection with products containing PFAS and will vigorously defend our record of environmental stewardship.&#8221;</p>
<p>DuPont has not yet responded.</p>
<p>Ed Kelly, International Association of Fire Fighters Union: &#8220;Obviously, we are very upset.&#8221;</p>
<p>The country&#8217;s largest firefighter&#8217;s union is now calling for change.</p>
<p>Ed Kelly: &#8220;As a union, we&#8217;re going to fight like hell to make sure we have gear that protects us, not makes us sick.&#8221;</p>
<p>For now, despite knowing about the potential dangers, firefighters across the country still have to put on this gear every day.</p>
<p>Some firefighters want the manufacturers to pay to replace it with safer gear, so they don&#8217;t have to fight more than fires.</p>
<p>The Broward Firefighter&#8217;s Union says they&#8217;re researching new gear technology.</p>
<p>Miami Fire Rescue tells us they don&#8217;t have enough information about the issue to comment yet.</p>
<p>3M released the following statement to 7News:</p>
<p>“3M is committed to supporting first responders, including firefighters. 3M acted responsibly in connection with products containing PFAS and will vigorously defend our record of environmental stewardship.”</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">UNIVERSITY OF NOTRE DAME:</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://fightingfor.nd.edu/2019/fighting-to-protect-the-brave/">https://fightingfor.nd.edu/2019/fighting-to-protect-the-brave/</a></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">ND STUDY ON PFAS:</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.0c00410">https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.0c00410</a></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">EPA BASICS ON PFAS:</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://www.epa.gov/pfas/basic-information-pfas#:~:text=Per%2D%20and%20polyfluoroalkyl%20substances%20(PFAS)%20are%20a%20group%20of,United%20States%20since%20the%201940s">https://www.epa.gov/pfas/basic-information-pfas#:~:text=Per%2D%20and%20polyfluoroalkyl%20substances%20(PFAS)%20are%20a%20group%20of,United%20States%20since%20the%201940s</a>.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">NIH BASICS ON PFAS:</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><a href="https://www.niehs.nih.gov/health/topics/agents/pfc/index.cfm">https://www.niehs.nih.gov/health/topics/agents/pfc/index.cfm</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">780670</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111620-firefighter-clothing.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c776c365-6dc1-425c-b09a-e41baf65bb78/6903f062-98ce-45d1-aafd-c0074526d57e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219700~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/c776c365-6dc1-425c-b09a-e41baf65bb78/6903f062-98ce-45d1-aafd-c0074526d57e/main.mp4*~hmac=0b6c89d4ab0ccb1143b53c88fcf8a24fe9e4d94358b1b430e08b69da32d7890f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111620-firefighter-clothing.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111620-firefighter-clothing.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">111620 firefighter clothing</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Home for the Holidays: South Floridians share how they&#8217;re preparing for Thanksgiving amid pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/home-for-the-holidays-south-floridians-share-how-theyre-preparing-for-thanksgiving-amid-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 03:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=778815</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Thanksgiving is just a couple of weeks away, and even though COVID-19 numbers are starting to climb, many are still planning holiday get togethers. The...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thanksgiving is just a couple of weeks away, and even though COVID-19 numbers are starting to climb, many are still planning holiday get togethers. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek looks at how you can stay safe when you have friends and family home for the holidays.</p>
<p>Abby Siegel is a sophomore at Cornell University in New York. She checks in for mandatory COVID testing on campus every week.</p>
<p>Abby Siegel, South Florida student: &#8220;Everyone&#8217;s being very safe. We&#8217;re getting tested twice a week.&#8221;</p>
<p>Abby&#8217;s sister, Allison, is a senior at University of Michigan.</p>
<p>Allison Siegel, South Florida student: &#8220;I had COVID back in March when I was studying abroad, and so I got retested and tested positive again for the antibodies.&#8221;</p>
<p>Both girls look forward to coming home to Miami for the holidays.</p>
<p>Rich Siegel: &#8220;In our family, Thanksgiving has always been kind of our holiday.&#8221;</p>
<p>But the virus is changing the way they will celebrate.</p>
<p>Rich Siegel, Abby and Allison&#8217;s dad: &#8220;As long as we can remember, our families would travel from around the country, from the West Coast, Nebraska, from Colorado. We&#8217;re not having family coming from out of town, so that&#8217;s a big difference.&#8221;</p>
<p>They will also trade their more formal indoor dining to an outdoor Thanksgiving meal at the patio table.</p>
<p>Jackie Siegel, Abby and Allison&#8217;s mom: &#8220;It&#8217;s not going to be the same, but we&#8217;re going to carry on, carry on the traditions that we have established over the years, and if we need to FaceTime my mother with help in making the pie crust, we will.&#8221;</p>
<p>Traditions are important, but so is safety.</p>
<p>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says in addition to outdoor dining, you should wear masks when not eating and continue to social distance, even when you&#8217;re hosting family members.</p>
<p>Dr. Aileen Marty, FIU: &#8220;If you&#8217;re having family members come into your home who have been living elsewhere, you want to know what they&#8217;ve been doing. Have they been pretty much in quarantine themselves? Have they been isolating all this time? Or have they been in a situation that&#8217;s more risky?&#8221;</p>
<p>And if you are at increased risk because of illness or preexisting conditions, it is best to avoid gathering with people you don&#8217;t live with.</p>
<p>Dr. Aileen Marty: &#8220;Just do not forget that people who have recovered may still be shedding enough virus to cause problems for others. People who have recovered are also retesting positive, so this is a very tricky virus with a lot of problems.&#8221;</p>
<p>Because we&#8217;re in another surge, many South Florida families are now rethinking holiday plans.</p>
<p>Mary Jo Shore, planning Thanksgiving: &#8220;This year, we&#8217;ve gone back and forth, as I&#8217;m sure many people have.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mary Jo Shore&#8217;s family gatherings have always been huge, with some 50 people coming to dinner, but this year, her sister will host the meal in two different shifts.</p>
<p>Mary Jo Shore: &#8220;Her husband&#8217;s family will come over. I believe it&#8217;s like 2 to 4, and then, our shift is like 5 to 7. They&#8217;re going to set up outside. They have some really nice tents that they bought.&#8221;</p>
<p>And heaping platters of food will be replaced by individual servings to lessen the possibility of spreading the disease.</p>
<p>Mary Jo Shore: &#8220;Instead of making the big soufflé platter, I&#8217;m actually going to make it in, like, muffin tins, and so everyone can just grab their own. I&#8217;m a big proponent of not cancelling. We&#8217;ve been living with this for more than seven months, and to me, the important thing is to be able to continue to live your life, but to live it safely.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for the Siegel girls, Allison has a plan for when she gets off the plane.</p>
<p>Allison Siegel: &#8220;Whenever I get home, I shower immediately and unpack and wash all my clothes.&#8221;</p>
<p>To make sure she doesn&#8217;t have COVID, Abby will get tested at school the day before she leaves. She&#8217;ll get double protection by wearing two masks on the plane, and she&#8217;ll wipe down the seats with a disinfectant.</p>
<p>Abby Siegel: &#8220;I&#8217;m definitely taking all the precautions possible, so that I don&#8217;t catch it on the plane or bring it home to my family.&#8221;</p>
<p>Precautions designed to keep everyone as safe as possible during the holidays.</p>
<p>If you would like to learn more about the CDC&#8217;s COVID-19 precautions for holiday gatherings, click <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/daily-life-coping/holidays.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">778815</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111320-socially-distant-thanksgiving.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f7e3f148-d848-456a-98b9-06be2b8632df/558348fb-3bb1-4041-affa-a8e64f08a4ca/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217795~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f7e3f148-d848-456a-98b9-06be2b8632df/558348fb-3bb1-4041-affa-a8e64f08a4ca/main.mp4*~hmac=4c66450cd16f35d0a5eb9d91bb1852903c5e18c02850cb189c6a17a72f254ddf' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111320-socially-distant-thanksgiving.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111320-socially-distant-thanksgiving.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">111320 socially distant thanksgiving</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami-Dade Police officers under internal affairs investigation after dog tased, shot and killed</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/miami-dade-police-officers-under-internal-affairs-investigation-after-dog-tased-shot-and-killed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=777547</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A South Florida man called 911 about a burglary in his neighborhood, but that emergency phone call left him broken-hearted and two Miami-Dade police officers...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Florida man called 911 about a burglary in his neighborhood, but that emergency phone call left him broken-hearted and two Miami-Dade police officers under investigation. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel takes us inside the deadly call.</p>
<p>Sylvan Plowright spent more than a decade in the 1980s and &#8217;90s as a professional boxer.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s him at the 5th Street Gym on South Beach made famous by Muhammad Ali.</p>
<p>Sylvan Plowright: &#8220;I kind of relate to him a lot because I trained also at the 5th Street Gym on Miami Beach and was using the same locker room that he had.&#8221;</p>
<p>As a young boxer, Sylvan was used to taking punches to the gut, but now older, at 67, he just took a big punch to the heart.</p>
<p>Officer on police radio: &#8220;We&#8217;re going to need a supervisor here, shots fired.&#8221;</p>
<p>The shots fired by police are the gunshots that killed Sylvan&#8217;s dog Niles.</p>
<p>It was Oct. 5 when Sylvan called 911.</p>
<p>911 call: &#8220;Calling about a burglary taking place. They have a saw cutting through a door, a barred door of an open, unoccupied residence.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dispatcher: &#8220;And it&#8217;s behind your address?&#8221;</p>
<p>Plowright: &#8220;Yes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Although Sylvan did not know the exact address, he told the dispatcher details about the house where the burglary was taking place.</p>
<p>911 call (Plowright to dispatcher): &#8220;It&#8217;s a corner lot. It&#8217;s a white car parked in front of the place, a white SUV.&#8221;</p>
<p>Instead, two officers showed up at his home, and that&#8217;s where things took a deadly turn.</p>
<p>Sylvan Plowright, dog was shot and killed: &#8220;I looked up and seen the flashlights &#8212; it had just got dusk &#8212; shining in the dog&#8217;s face, so I ran out and said &#8216;Hey, hey, I&#8217;m the one who called, you know? Please don&#8217;t tase my dog. What do you want me to do?&#8217; I kept repeating those three things.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sylvan says when he came outside, Niles was barking, and the officers were in his driveway, weapons drawn.</p>
<p>He says the two officers yelled two different commands.</p>
<p>Sylvan Plowright: &#8220;At this point, he&#8217;s telling me, &#8216;Get on the ground, get on the ground.&#8217; This one here is saying, &#8216;Get your dog, get your dog,&#8217; so I get on the ground to get my dog. At this point, he is saying &#8216;Shoot him.&#8217; I was hoping he didn&#8217;t mean for him to shoot me.&#8221;</p>
<p>The dog was tased by one officer.</p>
<p>Sylvan Plowright: &#8220;He made a squeal and went on his back.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sylvan says he had his hand on Niles when the second officer fired his gun.</p>
<p>Sylvan Plowright: &#8220;Two seconds after he tased him, he shot from over there and shot the dog three times. There&#8217;s still his blood right there. I saw the dog&#8217;s last breath. That&#8217;s when my girlfriend came out.&#8221;</p>
<p>Remnants of police tape remain, along with questions about that night.</p>
<p>The incident report offers few details about why officers fired, only that they discharged their weapons &#8220;toward the listed animal &#8230; while in the performance of their duties.&#8221;</p>
<p>There is no mention of the dog being aggressive, but the report does describe Sylvan Plowright as &#8220;very distraught and uncooperative.&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbors I spoke with say the dog was friendly. We requested the officers&#8217; body camera footage, but that won&#8217;t be released until after the internal affairs investigation is over.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Sylvan is still waiting to bury Niles. The dog&#8217;s body is being held by Animal Services, now considered evidence.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">777547</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111120-niles-the-dog.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/35623401-b662-448b-a592-d281348b3c37/4278a68a-5dc6-4aaf-96d5-94daa877f9da/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219645~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/35623401-b662-448b-a592-d281348b3c37/4278a68a-5dc6-4aaf-96d5-94daa877f9da/main.mp4*~hmac=f60f48e35d712325e9041b4bfc56cde91ae5b6c91ee73d8609bec83aeb2502da' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111120-niles-the-dog.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111120-niles-the-dog.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">111120 niles the dog</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could some body bags burned during COVID pandemic pose a health risk? State set to notify human crematories of the problem</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/could-some-body-bags-burned-during-covid-pandemic-pose-a-health-risk-state-set-to-notify-human-crematories-of-the-problem/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 03:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=776954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are coronavirus deaths possibly affecting some of the air we breathe? It&#8217;s a question tonight as the number of COVID-19 cases in Florida rise. 7&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are coronavirus deaths possibly affecting some of the air we breathe? It&#8217;s a question tonight as the number of COVID-19 cases in Florida rise. 7&#8217;s Karen Hensel has our special report: Air of Trouble?</p>
<p>In August, 7 Investigates <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/county-launches-investigation-after-7news-documents-black-smoke-billowing-from-miami-funeral-homes-crematory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">documented thick black smoke</a> billowing out of the crematory at Maspons Funeral Home in Little Havana.</p>
<p>Since then, more black smoke rising into the air from two other South Florida crematories.</p>
<p>An expert on air quality told us it can be a health risk.</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar, University of Miami, September: &#8220;Those concentrations are alarmingly high.&#8221;</p>
<p>After seeing our video from Little Havana, a Miami-Dade inspector went to the funeral home and saw &#8220;no visible emissions&#8221; and found &#8220;no violations,&#8221; but the investigation of what caused the smoke continues.</p>
<p>An investigation that now includes state environmental officials, and the focus is on body bags.</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya, Miami-Dade County Environmental Specialist Supervisor: &#8220;You don&#8217;t want to have this burning into the environment. The standard is that we don&#8217;t want to have, pretty much any of it in the environment.&#8221;</p>
<p>It is polyvinyl chloride, or PVC, a plastic the National Institutes of Health says is associated with an &#8220;increased risk&#8221; of a number of cancers.</p>
<p>In Florida, body bags are not allowed to be burned if they contain more than 0.5% of the chemical.</p>
<p>In the case of Maspons, the inspector wrote the funeral home&#8217;s &#8220;own body bags&#8221; &#8230; &#8220;do not contain PVC,&#8221; but &#8220;the facility does not have any data sheets on body bags that are received from hospitals,&#8221; and 7News has learned Maspons is not alone.</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya: &#8220;At this time, no one has the information because, like I said, the hospitals, the suppliers and the vendors just don&#8217;t have it, so that&#8217;s what we encountered immediately.&#8221;</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya, an environmental specialist with the county, says there&#8217;s a coronavirus connection to this chemical confusion.</p>
<p>There has been an increase in cremations, and Bedoya says people who die of COVID are being transported from hospitals to funeral homes in thicker body bags.</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya: &#8220;So, the bags they normally use are a bit thinner, but these thicker bags are pretty much what&#8217;s being used now to wrap the bodies, so it&#8217;s something new that we&#8217;re encountering with the pandemic.&#8221;</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;Do you think those thicker bags potentially contain more PVC?&#8221;</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya: &#8220;At this point in time, we&#8217;re not sure.&#8221;</p>
<p>There are 205 permitted human crematories statewide. We were told the Florida Department of Environmental Protection was set to alert them of this potential problem by the end of October. That hasn&#8217;t happened yet, but Miami-Dade is not waiting on the state.</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya: &#8220;As soon as we find issues like this, we go ahead and address it head on.&#8221;</p>
<p>Which is why county officials immediately notified all 11 crematories about the potential health risk with the body bags.</p>
<p>With no official guidance yet from the state, Miami-Dade has told crematories in the county not to burn the thicker bags and to either use their own or cremate bodies without bags.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">776954</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111020-maspons-funeral-home-black-smoke.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a4d9edfd-c3cf-4301-ba31-c894045943e1/c1acba36-eef2-474e-ba1c-854b3fdf8c39/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219607~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a4d9edfd-c3cf-4301-ba31-c894045943e1/c1acba36-eef2-474e-ba1c-854b3fdf8c39/main.mp4*~hmac=011658e17c38d9ef9c6a11c1a36e2958f13707970e1dbe00f1f034253cb7bdc7' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111020-maspons-funeral-home-black-smoke.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/111020-maspons-funeral-home-black-smoke.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">111020 maspons funeral home black smoke</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trashing the Neighborhood: Miami residents look to block off streets to deter prostitution, littering</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/trashing-the-neighborhood-miami-residents-look-to-block-off-streets-to-deter-prostitution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 04:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=776242</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A group of homeowners are fed up with what they say is a nasty problem. They say they have a solution, but no one is...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A group of homeowners are fed up with what they say is a nasty problem. They say they have a solution, but no one is willing to help. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek looks at what&#8217;s trashing the neighborhood.</p>
<p>Anyone taking a walk around this Miami neighborhood has to make sure to watch his or her step.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;This is not something you want to step on.&#8221;</p>
<p>Aurora Linares: &#8220;No, and the thing is you don&#8217;t even want to see it!&#8221;</p>
<p>But this is what people are seeing outside their homes: used condoms and broken liquor bottles.</p>
<p>Aurora Linares and her neighbors say they find this kind of trash on every block.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Raise your hand if you have seen a condom along your neighborhood swales?&#8221;</p>
<p>They took 7News for a walk in their Flagami neighborhood to show us the problem.</p>
<p>They say the trash is coming from unwanted late night visitors.</p>
<p>Emily Maza, homeowner: &#8220;People park to conduct, uh, sexual activities, and they leave behind the items that they use to conduct their sexual activities.&#8221;</p>
<p>Prostitutes work this strip of motels along Southwest Eighth Street and make their way into Aurora&#8217;s neighborhood.</p>
<p>Aurora Linares, homeowner: &#8220;They&#8217;ve exposed themselves. They opened up their shirt and exposed their breasts to me!&#8221;</p>
<p>After the prostitutes are picked up, neighbors say the men drive onto their streets, where they find plenty of dark and quiet places.</p>
<p>Aurora Linares: &#8220;They can easily access our neighborhood streets because they&#8217;re not blocked off from where the motels are.&#8221;</p>
<p>This is the area where the motels are, and it&#8217;s a quick drive into this quiet family neighborhood. People who live here want the city to block these five avenues that meet the back of the motels.</p>
<p>Emily Maza: &#8220;I would love to see some of the avenues closed off to deter people from coming into our neighborhood.&#8221;</p>
<p>Neighbors hope that by blocking traffic, it will keep illegal activity off their streets, and this kind of trash off their swales.</p>
<p>Aurora Linares: &#8220;We&#8217;ve emailed multiple times on what needs to be done. Right now, we have not been given any clarity or any understanding of who we need to speak with, who can we work with to get this completed.&#8221;</p>
<p>Aurora says her attempts to get help from the City of Miami have left her frustrated.</p>
<p>Aurora Linares: &#8220;Somebody to tell us what the process is, and we will do all the leg work that we need to make this process happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>7News did some legwork, too.</p>
<p>We reached out to the city and spoke to District 4 Commissioner Manolo Reyes.</p>
<p>Commissioner Manolo Reyes: &#8220;They want to stop the traffic, but there&#8217;s a process. I welcome that process. I welcome that they start the process.&#8221;</p>
<p>To start the process, they have to get neighbors to sign a petition.</p>
<p>Once that&#8217;s done, a traffic study would have to be completed.</p>
<p>The city would also ask all residents in the neighborhood to vote on the idea, and then, even if the city approves the plan, it still has to go to the county.</p>
<p>Manolo Reyes: &#8220;The transportation department in Miami-Dade County, they are the ones that have the last word.&#8221;</p>
<p>The neighbors welcome the challenge.</p>
<p>Aurora Linares: &#8220;It may take a long time, like he says, but if we don&#8217;t start it now, it will never happen.&#8221;</p>
<p>They say the time and effort are worth it to keep people from trashing their neighborhood.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">776242</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110920-used-condom.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/30c5ce6c-5a45-47aa-ad10-ab1fdb45ed31/f88c634a-5e55-4a50-99f4-7842c6b6c74d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217743~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/30c5ce6c-5a45-47aa-ad10-ab1fdb45ed31/f88c634a-5e55-4a50-99f4-7842c6b6c74d/main.mp4*~hmac=88d9096646d499d7398f894a0d5636128411e71ba2929a96a967ca283d84c96c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110920-used-condom.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110920-used-condom.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">110920 used condom</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Last Wish: Widow left fuming after late husband&#8217;s dying wish was not granted</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/last-wish-widow-left-fuming-after-late-husbands-dying-wish-was-not-granted/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 04:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=774595</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A South Florida couple thought they had everything in order for when their time came. They didn&#8217;t want to be resuscitated and suffer, so they...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Florida couple thought they had everything in order for when their time came. They didn&#8217;t want to be resuscitated and suffer, so they signed legal documents, but as the Nightteam&#8217;s Patrick Fraser reports, their last wish was not granted, leaving a widow fuming about how the love of her life was treated.</p>
<p>When Barbara says God sent Robert to her, she is serious because she prayed for a man like him at church the Sunday before she met him.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis, Robert&#8217;s wife: &#8220;And I ordered him, and he showed up at my open house on Wednesday morning. That&#8217;s how we met.&#8221;</p>
<p>They shared 31 wonderful years together, and as they got older, shared several health scares.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;We had both very severe life-threatening medical conditions.&#8221;</p>
<p>Conditions so severe they both made a promise to let each other go peacefully when their time came.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;No resuscitation for either one, ever.&#8221;</p>
<p>They went to an attorney and filled out a living will, marking no ventilator, feeding tube or cardiac resuscitation.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;We signed living wills, which is basically no DNR, and it&#8217;s on a white sheet.&#8221;</p>
<p>Then in September, Robert didn&#8217;t feel great, and they decided to go to the hospital. As they were leaving, Robert faltered.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;I could hardly hold him, and I knew.&#8221;</p>
<p>Instinctively, Barbara dialed 911, and while she was speaking to the operator, it happened.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;She said, &#8216;Do you have a pulse?&#8217; I said, &#8216;No,&#8217; and at the same time, this very large amounts of brown liquid came from his nose, his mouth.&#8221;</p>
<p>Barbara said Robert was dead, and a few minutes later, the paramedics arrived.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;And I said to them, &#8216;Please don&#8217;t resuscitate this man, don&#8217;t touch him.'&#8221;</p>
<p>They asked Barbara for proof Robert did not want them to attempt to restart his heart. She ran and got their living will.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;They pushed it aside, and they said, &#8216;Do you have a yellow paper?&#8217; &#8216;What freaking yellow paper? What are you talking about?'&#8221;</p>
<p>Barbara says when she couldn&#8217;t show the yellow paper, they went to work.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;They put this mechanical machine on him, smacking like this, and I screamed at them several times, &#8216;Stop.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Barbara says a deputy told her if she didn&#8217;t stop hollering at the paramedics, she would be taken away, and so she grew quiet.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;I sat and watched them torture my husband, torture.&#8221;</p>
<p>They couldn&#8217;t restart Robert&#8217;s heart. He was officially dead, but Barbara&#8217;s anger at what he went through did not end.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;It tears me up. It tears me up, all because I don&#8217;t have a yellow form. Who knows about a yellow form?&#8221;</p>
<p>This is the yellow form the paramedics were talking about &#8212; a do not resuscitate order signed by the patient and their physician, so even if you have a living will that says do not resuscitate, without the yellow form, the paramedics are required to try to resuscitate you, exactly what Robert and Barbara did not want.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;His wishes were not respected.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kenneth Scheppke, State EMS Medical Director: &#8220;Yeah, the DNR order is very specific.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Kenneth Scheppke is with the Florida Health Department and says the living will is normally used in a hospital, but if you are at home or outside, paramedics need to see the yellow DNR form.</p>
<p>Kenneth Scheppke: &#8220;Once properly filled out, it allows EMTs and paramedics to withhold cardiopulmonary resuscitation. That&#8217;s the reason why it&#8217;s yellow, so it&#8217;s easily spotted.&#8221;</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;I&#8217;m so traumatized.&#8221;</p>
<p>Barbara will never forget what she went through simply because she had no idea about a yellow piece of paper.</p>
<p>Barbara Lewis: &#8220;I think it&#8217;s a big injustice to those that are very sick and do not know about this yellow form.&#8221;</p>
<p>Robert wanted to die peacefully.</p>
<p>Instead, Barbara was left tormented that she wasn&#8217;t able to grant his last wish.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">774595</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/untitled-25.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4c48d560-e5d8-4407-8053-d6a39334ed22/ba861b2a-78ac-48ad-a174-c07238ee183b/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217635~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4c48d560-e5d8-4407-8053-d6a39334ed22/ba861b2a-78ac-48ad-a174-c07238ee183b/main.mp4*~hmac=0cad2245aec993d03f0a0d2219f7e379f145e226e2d3d6a569ac677c32ecd020' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/untitled-25.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/untitled-25.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">untitled (25)</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exotic Invaders: Rising tegu, iguana population in South Florida threaten native wildlife</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/exotic-invaders-rising-tegu-iguana-population-in-south-florida-threaten-native-wildlife/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=773403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Signs are pointing to an explosion of iguanas and other invasive lizards living in South Florida and, as the Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek reports, these exotic...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Signs are pointing to an explosion of iguanas and other invasive lizards living in South Florida and, as the Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek reports, these exotic invaders are doing serious damage.</p>
<p>They are scaly, cold blooded invasive reptiles from South America, and they are now overrunning South Florida.</p>
<p>Rodney Irwin, lizard hunter: &#8220;They&#8217;re just going to overwhelm us by sheer numbers.&#8221;</p>
<p>Iguanas and tegu lizards are taking over businesses, backyards and South Florida habitats.</p>
<p>Rodney Irwin: &#8220;They&#8217;ve gone from being, &#8216;Oh, there&#8217;s a pretty colorful animal, and the tourists love them!&#8217; That has now progressed to the point where everyone is tired of seeing them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Lizard hunter Rodney Irwin says he has seen a huge increase in the black and white tegu population since we went hunting with him last year.</p>
<p>Another trapper, Carlos Michaelsen, says the tegu population is now spreading from rural Southwest Miami-Dade into more urban areas like Doral.</p>
<p>So, we have only been out here for 10 minutes. Three traps have been checked, and we already have found two tegus.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;How many tegus have you trapped this year?&#8221;</p>
<p>Carlos Michaelsen, tegu trapper: &#8220;Easily over 1,800 tegus just this year.&#8221;</p>
<p>For Carlos, the hunt is personal.</p>
<p>Carlos Michaelsen: &#8220;We created this albino, which is a world&#8217;s first.&#8221;</p>
<p>He breeds exotically colored tegus unlike the ones running wild in South Florida.</p>
<p>Carlos Michaelsen: &#8220;This isn&#8217;t something that could live in the wild. &#8221;</p>
<p>He knows irresponsible tegu owners are to blame for releasing them here.</p>
<p>Now, they&#8217;re eating the eggs of native wildlife.</p>
<p>Carlos spends more than 20 hours a week trapping tegu on the outskirts of Everglades National Park to protect the threatened reptiles and birds inside.</p>
<p>Carlos Michaelsen: &#8220;I feel as a breeder and a keeper of the species, I have a moral obligation.&#8221;</p>
<p>Despite his hard work, a record 34 tegus were found in the park this year, but when it comes to numbers, the iguana population is out of control.</p>
<p>Carlos Michaelsen: &#8220;They have one defense mechanism, and that is run like hell.&#8221;</p>
<p>In the past two months, Rodney has removed nearly 500 iguanas from the wild.</p>
<p>Just a tiny fraction of the nearly 20,000 reported to the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission over the past few years.</p>
<p>&#8220;Without a doubt, the iguana population is exploding.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;For every one that you see, there might be 30 of them within a half mile that you don&#8217;t see.&#8221;</p>
<p>They are not just annoying. Iguanas threaten our infrastructure.</p>
<p>The South Florida Water Management District says iguanas dig deep burrows which can weaken canal walls, and the problem is spreading.</p>
<p>Michelle Miller, University of Florida: &#8220;The warmer it gets, the further north these animals should be able to disperse.&#8221;</p>
<p>Iguanas here have abundant food and few predators.</p>
<p>They were first spotted in South Florida back in the 1960s. Cold snaps would kill many and keep their numbers in check.</p>
<p>Michelle Miller: &#8220;It definitely helps if we have a hard frost.&#8221;</p>
<p>But we have not experienced cold enough temperatures to kill iguanas in five years.</p>
<p>Combine that with the fact they can lay up to 70 eggs a year, and you have a recipe ripe for a reptile boom.</p>
<p>FWC is looking for ways to reduce the number of both lizards.</p>
<p>Carol Lyn Parrish, FWC: &#8220;I would say FWC is considering all options right now. Non-native species are a priority for us.&#8221;</p>
<p>The agency could impose strict requirements for people who own or breed the lizards or potentially go as far as an all out ban.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s for sure is, right now, we&#8217;re living in an invasive lizard hotspot!</p>
<p>Rodney Irwin &#8220;For every one you see now is going to be four next year.&#8221;</p>
<p>And you can expect to keep seeing even more of these exotic invaders.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">773403</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110420-tegu.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fa581274-0e3e-4f22-bb28-0c5b99453e22/4dd1f2cf-99a7-4da3-812d-c3e8574212eb/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219677~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/fa581274-0e3e-4f22-bb28-0c5b99453e22/4dd1f2cf-99a7-4da3-812d-c3e8574212eb/main.mp4*~hmac=4ea5a68b098eea07b79fbc1e941b3883ab8f47c2cc5a955c01d62b0da2f95438' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110420-tegu.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110420-tegu.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">110420 tegu</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out in the Cold: Seniors demand refund from Miami employee for cancelled Alaskan cruise</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/out-in-the-cold-seniors-demand-refund-from-city-of-miami-for-cancelled-alaskan-cruise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 03:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=772013</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[They paid thousands of dollars to a Miami city employee for a dream vacation. The trip, though, never happened. Now a group of seniors are...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>They paid thousands of dollars to a Miami city employee for a dream vacation. The trip, though, never happened. Now a group of seniors are begging the city for both answers and their money. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek investigates in this special assignment report, &#8220;Out in the Cold.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was supposed to be the trip of a lifetime.</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;I was just so excited when the Alaska trip came up. I couldn&#8217;t wait.&#8221;</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb and Batuka Williams took jobs as security guards to pay for an Alaskan cruise. The trip was organized by the leader of a senior program at Miami&#8217;s Charles Hadley Park called Seniors on the Move.</p>
<p>Batuka Williams, Seniors on the Move member: &#8220;I&#8217;ve always wanted to go to Alaska. We went shopping. We went to get our winter clothes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Katherine and Joseph Ellis were going to celebrate their 50th wedding anniversary on the trip.</p>
<p>Katherine Ellis, Seniors on the Move member: &#8220;I was excited, and we wanted to make sure it was special.&#8221;</p>
<p>The group was supposed to cruise around Alaska last year, well before the pandemic hit.</p>
<p>But Antavius Howell, the director of Charles Hadley Park and leader of the Seniors on the Move program, told them the trip was off.</p>
<p>According to the seniors, Howell said some people backed out of the trip, leaving the group too small.</p>
<p>Katherine Ellis: &#8220;I was very disappointed, and in fact, I went home, and I cried.&#8221;</p>
<p>Batuka Williams: &#8220;I was so disappointed. I was hurt.&#8221;</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;We were all heartbroken, but he said, &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry. We will get our money, we will be refunded our money.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The seniors thought they would be quickly refunded the more than $2,000 they each paid for the trip. That&#8217;s because they bought added insurance for $229.</p>
<p>But they were never given a travel insurance policy, or any documents from a cruise line or travel agency.</p>
<p>All they have are handwritten receipts signed by Howell&#8217;s assistant, Robin Benyard, who is a City of Miami Recreation aide.</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;We&#8217;ve been waiting two years to get the money, and all we&#8217;ve been told when we asked him about it was, he&#8217;s working on it. &#8216;I&#8217;m working on it.&#8217; I mean, we have been more than patient.&#8221;</p>
<p>Some of the seniors did get partial refunds, but the money didn&#8217;t come from a company. Instead, Howell either handed them cash or transferred money from his bank account into theirs.</p>
<p>Then in July, Howell unexpectedly died, which is now forcing the seniors to take their fight directly to the city.</p>
<p>Katherine Ellis: &#8220;Give us our money back. We deserve &#8212; we&#8217;ve worked hard all our lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>To find out where their money went, we tried to speak to Robin Benyard, who signed those receipts.</p>
<p>Kevin Ozebek: &#8220;Robin, can we just ask you a few questions? Please?&#8221;</p>
<p>But she bolted into a park building when she learned we work for 7News.</p>
<p>We pushed the city for answers, but the only thing a city spokesperson would tell us is, &#8220;Due to an ongoing investigation, we cannot provide any comments about this case at this time.&#8221;</p>
<p>Charlean Cobb: &#8220;Shame on you! Two-thousand to $3,000. That&#8217;s a lot of money for no one to say anything.&#8221;</p>
<p>Around the time we started asking the city questions, the Miami Police Department&#8217;s Public Corruption Task Force started investigating.</p>
<p>But since these seniors still don&#8217;t have answers or their money, their anger keeps growing toward the Parks and Recreation Department.</p>
<p>Batuka Williams: &#8220;I need that money, especially right now, so stand up and do something about it for us seniors at Hadley Park.&#8221;</p>
<p>7News will stay on top of this, and we&#8217;ll keep pushing to get them at least an answer to what happened to their money.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">772013</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201102_Out_in_the_Cold_senior_travelers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6db582fa-c0e6-46ee-bc8d-785cebe8d0a3/18c6cadc-dc99-4e89-a6ec-aa7ccafa0f41/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219640~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6db582fa-c0e6-46ee-bc8d-785cebe8d0a3/18c6cadc-dc99-4e89-a6ec-aa7ccafa0f41/main.mp4*~hmac=e3d623b9590332afb97b240dd335500e8f9c86d61beedf062a3cb03fb8c91673' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201102_Out_in_the_Cold_senior_travelers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/201102_Out_in_the_Cold_senior_travelers.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201102_Out_in_the_Cold_senior_travelers</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tide of Trash: Amid COVID-19 pandemic, masks, gloves endanger marine life</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/tide-of-trash-amid-covid-19-pandemic-masks-gloves-endanger-marine-life/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 02:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=770515</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Litter on beaches is not a new problem, but now, COVID is making things worse with masks and gloves endangering marine life. Kevin Ozebek has...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litter on beaches is not a new problem, but now, COVID is making things worse with masks and gloves endangering marine life. Kevin Ozebek has this special assignment report, &#8220;Tide of Trash.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s supposed to protect us, but now it is endangering the environment.</p>
<p>Orsi Zoltanfi, volunteer: &#8220;Single use masks and gloves, this is the new trend.&#8221;</p>
<p>Personal protective equipment is trending in a very bad way.</p>
<p>Sophie Ringel, founder, Clean Miami Beach: &#8220;The amount of PPE I&#8217;m seeing, not just in the streets but also in the canal right here, is alarming and shocking.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sophie Ringel and volunteers with Clean Miami Beach go out twice a month to pick up trash.</p>
<p>They started seeing masks and gloves in the water after the pandemic reached South Florida in March.</p>
<p>Sophie Ringel: &#8220;Plastic pollution has been a problem for a very long time, but now, it gets topped with PPE, especially masks.&#8221;</p>
<p>When PPE is tossed on the street, it can blow into the water or get washed into the ocean through storm drains.</p>
<p>Rafaela D&#8217;Almeida, volunteer: &#8220;Something that&#8217;s supposed to keep us safe now is hurting the environment, so it&#8217;s kind of counterproductive for people to not care about the environment and care so much about their health. I think they should go hand in hand.&#8221;</p>
<p>In just one hour, the group picked up 84 pounds of trash, including 88 masks. They record their haul on Clean Swell, an app that keeps track of all the trash picked up by volunteers.</p>
<p>Maria Algarra, Clean This Beach Up: &#8220;I would say at least 35% of what we pick up is PPE nowadays. That includes gloves, masks, wipes&#8230;&#8221;</p>
<p>Environmental activist Maria Algarra was so alarmed at the flood of PPE trash, she started The Glove Challenge.</p>
<p>The idea is simple. If you see a glove on the ground or in the water, snap a picture, post it and tag it, and, of course, pick it up and throw it in the trash. #TheGloveChallenge went viral.</p>
<p>Maria Algarra: &#8220;It was crazy because it started here in Miami. It started locally, then it moved to Canada, South America. It went to Europe, and people were mad.&#8221;</p>
<p>To date, more than 18,000 carelessly tossed gloves have been tagged by people in countries around the world.</p>
<p>John Hocevar, Greenpeace: &#8220;We&#8217;re using about 200 billion pieces of PPE each month, and none of this is recyclable, so it&#8217;s all either ending up in a landfill or an incinerator or just into the environment.&#8221;</p>
<p>From South Florida to South America, marine animals are suffering.</p>
<p>A puffer fish caught in a mask recently washed up on Miami Beach.</p>
<p>Maria Algarra: &#8220;I was extremely upset. I honestly couldn&#8217;t believe that I was seeing it. Seeing the puffer fish strangled by a mask was just horrifying.&#8221;</p>
<p>In Brazil, a penguin died after swallowing a mask.</p>
<p>Now, it seems anywhere in the world where there is a beach, PPE litter is a problem.</p>
<p>Gary Stokes, Oceans Asia: &#8220;In Hong Kong, come down to the beach and still finding lots of these.&#8221;</p>
<p>Gary Stokes is with Oceans Asia Marine Conservation Group. He hopes these shocking images will teach people to be more careful.</p>
<p>Gary Stokes: &#8220;The effect this is going to have on the natural world besides us is quite terrifying, and we&#8217;re only at the start of this, so we&#8217;re going to see how bad it&#8217;s going to get in the coming years.&#8221;</p>
<p>And with the pandemic still here and masks remaining a must, environmentalists will keep pounding this message: If you don&#8217;t throw these out properly, they will become part of the tide of trash.</p>
<p>If you would like to get involved in local clean up efforts, click the links below.</p>
<p><a href="https://cleanmiamibeach.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Clean Miami Beach</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/cleanthisbeachup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Clean This Beach Up</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.volunteercleanup.org/find" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.volunteercleanup.org</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">770515</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/103020-ppe-pollution.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/33955d21-e41e-4e1f-8345-0150e4857f6b/e671de12-19ee-4230-833f-e7ee68afbcba/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217806~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/33955d21-e41e-4e1f-8345-0150e4857f6b/e671de12-19ee-4230-833f-e7ee68afbcba/main.mp4*~hmac=ef3617b72eaea9c1603bbc3c6a3a061218b128c01e758331dcd35d334e638b76' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/103020-ppe-pollution.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/103020-ppe-pollution.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">103020 ppe pollution</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>From raising the minimum wage, to changing the Florida Primary process: A look at the 6 proposed amendments on 2020 ballot</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/from-raising-the-minimum-wage-to-changing-the-florida-primary-process-a-look-at-the-6-proposed-amendments-on-2020-ballot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 13:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=761612</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The presidential race may be the marquee matchup, but Florida voters will also decide on issues that hit closer to home. On the ballot are...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The presidential race may be the marquee matchup, but Florida voters will also decide on issues that hit closer to home.</p>
<p>On the ballot are six proposed amendments to the state&#8217;s constitution.</p>
<p>Nova Southeastern Unversity Law Professor Richard Grosso: &#8220;Don&#8217;t treat these as an afterthought.&#8221;</p>
<p>First up is Amendment One: Should only U.S. Citizens who are permanent Florida residents be allowed to vote in a Florida election?</p>
<p>While the proposal may sound significant, Grosso says it&#8217;s not.</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;That&#8217;s already the law that only United States citizens can vote.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amendment Two is a different story.</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;This would be a meaningful substantive change to the Florida Constitution.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amendment Two: Should the Florida minimum wage be gradually raised to $15 per hour?</p>
<p>Right now, the minimum wage in Florida is $8.56.</p>
<p>A YES vote would raise it to $10 in 2021 and add a dollar a year until 2026.</p>
<p>According to Grosso, supporters would argue, &#8220;Minimum wage workers are them who are most likely to spend that money again out and fuel the economy with it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;Opponents say that it will be a burden on business.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amendment Three: Should all registered voters be allowed to vote in state primary elections regardless of political party affiliation.</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;Everybody votes in one primary.&#8221;</p>
<p>This means all voters would cast ballots for statewide candidates in the same primary. The top two vote-getters would then face off in the general election.</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;The proponents say that this amendment would tend to result in more mainstream candidates with broader appeal.&#8221;</p>
<p>Those against the amendment would counter the argument.</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;It would water down and drown out the voting power of minorities.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amendment Four: Should all proposed amendments or revisions to the state constitution be approved in two elections instead of one in order to take effect?</p>
<p>Grosso believes it would have been unlikely an initiative like medical marijuana would have passed if this amendment had been in place in 2016.</p>
<p>Grosso: &#8220;Amendment Four would severely limit the power of the citizens in Florida to decide what they want in their constitution.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for those supporting a YES vote, Grosso said, &#8220;The argument is that the constitution should only be amended infrequently.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amendment Five and Six both involved property tax breaks.</p>
<p>Amendment Five: Florida residents will have three years to transfer homestead exemption instead of the current two years.</p>
<p>Amendment Six: Should the spouse of a deceased veteran, who suffered from a combat-related disability, continue to receive the homestead property tax discount?</p>
<p>Constitutional amendments in Florida require at least 60% of voter support to pass.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400"><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Florida Division of Elections</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Proposed constitutional amendments: <a href="https://dos.elections.myflorida.com/Initiatives/">https://dos.elections.myflorida.com/Initiatives/</a></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Broward County Supervisor of Elections</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Sample ballot: <a href="https://www.browardsoe.org/Portals/Broward/Documents/2020Elections/2020-General-Election-Sample-Ballot.pdf">https://www.browardsoe.org/Portals/Broward/Documents/2020Elections/2020-General-Election-Sample-Ballot.pdf</a></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Miami-Dade County Elections Department</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400">Sample ballot:  <a href="https://www.miamidade.gov/elections/library/sample-ballots/2020-11-03-general.pdf">https://www.miamidade.gov/elections/library/sample-ballots/2020-11-03-general.pdf</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">761612</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/6-proposed-amendments-e1602854284174.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/6-proposed-amendments-e1602854284174.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/6-proposed-amendments-e1602854284174.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">6 proposed amendments</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doctor&#8217;s Orders: South Florida doctor hosts Instagram cooking show every Tuesday</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/doctors-orders-south-florida-doctor-hosts-instagram-cooking-show-every-tuesday/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=753424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He&#8217;s a doctor by day, but by night, he shows a completely different side. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek introduces us to a front line hero...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He&#8217;s a doctor by day, but by night, he shows a completely different side. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek introduces us to a front line hero who is cooking up a storm on social media. It&#8217;s our special assignment report: Doctor&#8217;s Orders.</p>
<p>Dr. Alex Morizio (in Instagram Live): &#8220;Salute, everyone, salute!&#8221;</p>
<p>He&#8217;s whipping up everything from the classics&#8230;</p>
<p>Alex Morizio (in Instagram Live): &#8220;Eggplant Parmesan!&#8221;</p>
<p>To more complex gourmet Italian dishes, like saffron-infused homemade tagliatelli.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio (in Instagram Live): &#8220;See the sauce and how it is coming together? Beautiful!&#8221;</p>
<p>Every Tuesday night at 8 o&#8217;clock, Dr. Alex Morizio hits the live button on Instagram and streams Cooking with Al from his South Beach home.</p>
<p>Boom!</p>
<p>Alex Morizio, Italian chef: &#8220;Italians, we find a lot of joy and love in cooking and especially eating.&#8221;</p>
<p>This Brooklyn born, second generation Italian American was raised in the kitchen.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;You always have to give credit to mom. Mom is always the base of your cooking life, but I learned from dad, too.&#8221;</p>
<p>For the past 15 years, Doctor Alex did weekly stand-up comedy gigs as an escape.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;They call me &#8216;Chef Al Dente.&#8217; First name is &#8216;Al,&#8217; &#8216;Chef Al Dente.'&#8221;</p>
<p>He hasn&#8217;t lost his sense of humor, but he did lose his venue once clubs were closed because of the pandemic, so he turned to his Amalfi Coast roots and his love of food.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;I still wanted to have fun. I wanted to entertain. I wanted to stay connected with people, so I said let me put Instagram Live on and start cooking.&#8221;</p>
<p>Alex Morizio (in Instagram Live): &#8220;Let it swim, put it right in there.&#8221;</p>
<p>Whether he&#8217;s frying up calamari or making meatballs&#8230;</p>
<p>Alex Morizio (in Instagram Live): &#8220;Holy Trinity: ground beef, ground pork, ground veal. Get ready!&#8221;</p>
<p>Doctor Alex says the aim is to boost his viewers&#8217; confidence in the kitchen.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;As long as they&#8217;re enjoying it, I&#8217;ll keep doing it.&#8221;</p>
<p>But no one may get more out of this Instagram show than Doctor Alex himself.</p>
<p>His day job is leading the intensive care unit at Palmetto General Hospital.</p>
<p>The past six months have been grueling because of COVID-19.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;The patients, obviously when they come into the ICU, they&#8217;re really sick. There&#8217;s a decent chance, unfortunately, of them passing away. They stay on life support for extended periods of time. It&#8217;s rough to watch.&#8221;</p>
<p>So once the scrubs can come off and Instagram can be set to stream&#8230;</p>
<p>Alex Morizio (in Instagram Live): &#8220;Here&#8217;s to love!&#8221;</p>
<p>Doctor Alex gets the mental breather he desperately needs after a 60-hour work week in the ICU.</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;My mind is completely clear when I am doing the cooking show. I am not thinking of anything else but how much I am enjoying cooking the food, talking to people on Instagram.&#8221;</p>
<p>So for now, ICU rounds will still be his day job.</p>
<p>Tuesday nights&#8230;</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m just stirring up my penne al la vodka!&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8230;He&#8217;ll devote to Instagram Live, but he definitely has a taste for more!</p>
<p>Alex Morizio: &#8220;If Food Network is listening, I&#8217;m here! I&#8217;m ready!&#8221;</p>
<p>Click <a href="https://www.instagram.com/dralexmorizio/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a> to check out Dr. Alex Morizio&#8217;s Instagram page!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">753424</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/100220-alex-morizio.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/55aae58b-1d6b-48d8-b88a-cdd48baf3de6/8da550e4-9b29-4ac9-8c98-c9b26d3724c0/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219632~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/55aae58b-1d6b-48d8-b88a-cdd48baf3de6/8da550e4-9b29-4ac9-8c98-c9b26d3724c0/main.mp4*~hmac=943331ac63bb16f924b53d68b2f674cc6945a5ba77d7f5b0c8ebc69f61e1175d' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/100220-alex-morizio.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/100220-alex-morizio.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">100220 alex morizio</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feeding a Need: South Florida woman uses old refrigerator to help underprivileged families</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/feeding-a-need-south-florida-woman-uses-old-refrigerator-to-help-underprivileged-families/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 03:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=747477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When you see an old refrigerator sitting on the side of the road, it&#8217;s usually headed for the trash, but 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows how...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you see an old refrigerator sitting on the side of the road, it&#8217;s usually headed for the trash, but 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows how a South Florida woman is using them to help feed her community.</p>
<p>So many people across South Florida are going through tough times. The pandemic has made it even harder for them to feed their families.</p>
<p>Sherina Jones, Village (FREE)DGE organizer: &#8220;People are losing their jobs, kids are home more than ever, and the cost of food is rising on a day-to-day basis.&#8221;&#8216;</p>
<p>According to the U.S. Census, South Florida has a huge number of people who say they don&#8217;t have enough to eat. It&#8217;s one of the highest rates in the country.</p>
<p>Sherina Jones wanted to help fill the gap, starting with those living in Liberty City.</p>
<p>Sherina Jones: &#8220;People definitely need the help that we&#8217;re giving right now.&#8221;</p>
<p>She wasn&#8217;t sure how to help &#8230; until she came across a video on social media.</p>
<p>Sherina Jones: &#8220;The next video that was loading, it said &#8216;community refrigerator,&#8217; and I&#8217;m like, &#8216;What is a community refrigerator?'&#8221;</p>
<p>A few weeks later, she bought a refrigerator from a local repair store. She plugged in it, and filled it with food.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s called the Village (FREE)DGE.</p>
<p>Sherina Jones: &#8220;We load it in the morning with breakfast, so in the morning, most people come get breakfast or either a lunch item, and in the afternoon, we put lunch items, and in the evening, we put dinner things in there.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sherina and her family work to keep the shelves stocked with fruits, vegetables and other foods. Anyone who needs something to eat is welcome to take what they need.</p>
<p>And it&#8217;s all free.</p>
<p>Danny Agnew, Roots Black House: &#8220;I thought it made sense, because we know that we needed to fill a void in the community.&#8221;</p>
<p>Danny Agnew and Isaiah Thomas run Roots Black House print shop on Northwest Seventh Avenue. They offered to let Sherina keep her refrigerator at their store.</p>
<p>Isaiah Thomas, Roots Black House: &#8220;There&#8217;s times where us ordinary citizens can be a real village to help each other out, so I decided we&#8217;d get behind family and behind a great initiative.&#8221;</p>
<p>Along with providing the electricity for the fridge, the print shop also serves as a base where people can drop off food or cash donations.</p>
<p>Danny Agnew: &#8220;There&#8217;s a wide network of people who have been donating every single day. It&#8217;s really heartening to see the effects and the reach this thing has spread through our communities.</p>
<p>To help reach needy residents in other parts of town, Sherina teamed up with Blossom Beauty Salon in Northwest Miami and Sweet Boutique in Opa-Locka to set up two more Village (FREE)DGES.</p>
<p>Sherina Jones: &#8220;I&#8217;m interacting with people, and they&#8217;re telling me how grateful they are. I feel very good to know that I&#8217;m helping someone, especially during a time like this.&#8221;</p>
<p>Sherina is grateful for the positive response her project has received, because it truly does take a village in these tough times.</p>
<p><strong>DONATION INFO:</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/community-refrigerator-miami-edition?utm_source=customer&amp;utm_medium=copy_link&amp;utm_campaign=p_cf+share-flow-1"><span class="s1">GoFundMe</span></a></p>
<p class="p2">CashApp $villagepantry</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Email: </span>free.oge.miami@gmail.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">747477</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/200925_Liberty_City_Village_FREEDGE.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9212fdaf-8102-4709-b5bc-5b49304d0991/9bbf0122-d988-4a49-9814-390d0b7d5e53/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217712~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9212fdaf-8102-4709-b5bc-5b49304d0991/9bbf0122-d988-4a49-9814-390d0b7d5e53/main.mp4*~hmac=9bdf17fb452f8d132321e683c592f6adb3086c3ad3c32b5c5d7d622b665132eb' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/200925_Liberty_City_Village_FREEDGE.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/200925_Liberty_City_Village_FREEDGE.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200925_Liberty_City_Village_FREEDGE</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>County launches investigation after 7News documents black smoke billowing from Miami funeral home’s crematory</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/county-launches-investigation-after-7news-documents-black-smoke-billowing-from-miami-funeral-homes-crematory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 02:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=743662</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What we found, and where we found it, was so concerning to county environmental officials, they immediately launched an investigation. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What we found, and where we found it, was so concerning to county environmental officials, they immediately launched an investigation. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel has our special assignment report, &#8220;Air of Trouble?&#8221;</p>
<p>Thick black smoke billowing into the air, not in an industrial park, but in busy Little Havana, and the smoke you&#8217;re seeing is from the burning of human bodies.</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar, Associate Professor of Environmental Health at University of Miami: &#8220;Those concentrations are alarmingly high.&#8221;</p>
<p>It started with a tip from a 7News viewer describing a &#8220;big black cloud&#8221; from Maspons Funeral Home on Southwest Eighth Street in Miami, so we went to check it out for ourselves.</p>
<p>On four separate days in August, we saw this black smoke coming from the funeral home&#8217;s crematory stack.</p>
<p>We also watched one day as the plume crossed the street toward people eating outside at Café Versailles.</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar: &#8220;Casket, body when they are incinerated at a high temperature, the very first thing that will be happening is it will be evaporating all the smoke coming out from the chimney.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar is an environmental scientist at the University of Miami who studies air quality. After seeing our video&#8230;</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar: &#8220;Wow&#8230;&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8230;Kumar says he&#8217;s concerned for those outdoor diners.</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar: &#8220;Some of the particles even can be dropped in the water, on the hand, or when you&#8217;re eating, for example. You&#8217;re ingesting some of them.&#8221;</p>
<p>So, what&#8217;s in the black smoke?</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar: &#8220;Some of them are even considered to be carcinogenic.&#8221;</p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5931459/">study published in 2018</a> by the National Institutes of Health found &#8220;&#8230;corpse cremation generates numerous harmful air pollutants&#8230;&#8221; that &#8220;&#8230;could have severe effects on the surrounding environment and human health.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar: &#8220;When you&#8217;re breathing them, they directly become part of your respiratory tract system, and from there, they become part of your circulatory system, so they go to your heart and circulating throughout the body.&#8221;</p>
<p>Inspection reports obtained by 7 Investigates show Maspons&#8217; crematory passed inspection in both 2016 and 2018 with no violations.</p>
<p>Funeral homes are required to report so-called &#8220;upsets&#8221; of black smoke, but Miami-Dade County&#8217;s Division of Environmental Resources Management told us the funeral home has done &#8220;no self-reporting of issues or concerns for the site.&#8221;</p>
<p>We showed our video to Steven Bedoya, an environmental specialist with the county.</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;So on a scale of 1-10, 10 being the worst, what&#8217;s the potential impact? How bad is this?&#8221;</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya, environmental specialist supervisor of Miami-Dade County: &#8220;So, I would put it at around a 7 or 8. It&#8217;s a high priority for us.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Naresh Kumar: &#8220;I will say definitely 10. It shouldn&#8217;t be at all near a dining facility or a residential facility.&#8221;</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya: &#8220;That&#8217;s very thick. We haven&#8217;t seen it that badly. This is a first for us. We definitely have to investigate.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bedoya says they have never seen smoke in the thickness we documented at any facility they regulate, so they immediately launched an investigation and sent an inspector to Maspons Funeral Home.</p>
<p>And on that visit, the inspector saw &#8220;no visible emissions&#8221; and found &#8220;no violations.&#8221;</p>
<p>The inspector&#8217;s report reveals a possible coronavirus connection. The funeral home noted &#8220;an increase in crematory workload due to the COVID-19 pandemic,&#8221; including more &#8220;cremation of heavy bodies (~200+ lbs).&#8221;</p>
<p>But the inspector found they did not appear to overload their crematory unit on the four days we documented black smoke.</p>
<p>Karen Hensel (on the phone): &#8220;Hi, this is Karen Hensel with 7News, could I talk to someone about the black smoke that is coming out of your chimney right now?&#8221;</p>
<p>Maspons Funeral Home turned down our request for an interview.</p>
<p>Café Versailles did not comment.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, documents show Maspons Funeral Home is planning to add a second crematory unit at their Little Havana location. The county says they already have a construction permit for the new machine.</p>
<p>Steven Bedoya: &#8220;So they&#8217;re going to be adding another unit on-site. That&#8217;s going to be added emissions that they&#8217;re going to have on-site, so it&#8217;s going to be two units overall.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bottom line: He says no one should see any black smoke coming from any of the county&#8217;s 11 human crematories.</p>
<p>The investigation into what we saw continues.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p>Miami-Dade County DERM Environmental Complaints: EnvironmentalComplaints@miamidade.gov</p>
<p>305-372-6955</p>
<p><a href="http://www.miamidade.gov/environment" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">http://www.miamidade.gov/environment</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">743662</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/092220-7inv-black-smoke.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/46941b95-02aa-4758-bf74-37c0fe71b1a2/d16d954a-31c3-4bda-b23c-a2913cfe608e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217652~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/46941b95-02aa-4758-bf74-37c0fe71b1a2/d16d954a-31c3-4bda-b23c-a2913cfe608e/main.mp4*~hmac=3cad398c1eaff69b4b82a5c71f43f68c62f37ce43aac2a13ca3dc81fc787174f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/092220-7inv-black-smoke.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/092220-7inv-black-smoke.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">092220 7inv black smoke</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terror and Trauma: COVID-19 presents health problems for 9/11 first responders, volunteers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/terror-and-trauma-covid-19-presents-health-problems-for-9-11-first-responders-volunteers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 02:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=732345</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As we commemorate the 19th anniversary of the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks, many of the first responders and volunteers who worked at Ground Zero now...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we commemorate the 19th anniversary of the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks, many of the first responders and volunteers who worked at Ground Zero now find themselves facing another threat. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has more on how COVID-19 is presenting new problems for them.</p>
<p>Sept. 11, 2001 started as a bright, beautiful day in New York City.</p>
<p>Douglas Bush, Ground Zero volunteer: &#8220;I remember driving to work that morning noticing how clear the skies were.&#8221;</p>
<p>But at 8:46 a.m., our world changed forever.</p>
<p>Before the day was over, almost 3,000 people would die in the worst terror attack in our nation&#8217;s history.</p>
<p>Douglas Bush: &#8220;I thought to myself, &#8216;This can&#8217;t be happening.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Douglas Bush could see the Twin Towers burning from his office.</p>
<p>He joined other volunteers in removing debris, and for 21 days, he served meals to Ground Zero workers.</p>
<p>Douglas Bush: &#8220;You could smell what smelled like death in the air. This can&#8217;t be healthy, for anyone to be working down here.&#8221;</p>
<p>He was right. Seven years later, Douglas developed non-Hodgkin&#8217;s lymphoma and then melanoma.</p>
<p>Annie O., Ground Zero volunteer: &#8220;While we were down there, we were all coughing. We called it &#8216;Trade Center cough.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Annie O. was also at Ground Zero. She worked for the Red Cross and the Salvation Army for 10 months.</p>
<p>Annie O.: &#8220;About three years ago, I got sick and just did not get better, and they kept saying, &#8216;It&#8217;s pneumonia.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Now Annie has scarring on her lungs and a condition called Barrett&#8217;s esophagus, which can develop into cancer.</p>
<p>Douglas Bush: &#8220;I could not think of any reason other than being there during that time after 9/11 that this would have happened.&#8221;</p>
<p>With already compromised immune systems, they and other 9/11 survivors now face a great threat from COVID-19.</p>
<p>Michael Barasch, attorney: &#8220;I&#8217;ve lost nearly 100 of my clients as a result of COVID.&#8221;</p>
<p>Michael Barasch is an attorney whose firm represents some 20,000 9/11 survivors, first responders and volunteers.</p>
<p>All, like Annie and Douglas, are recipients of a victim compensation fund for 9/11 survivors.</p>
<p>Michael Barasch: &#8220;They&#8217;ve linked 68 cancers to the World Trade Center toxins, and if you&#8217;ve been through chemotherapy or radiation, your immune system is shot, and that makes you particularly vulnerable to COVID-19.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fifteen hundred of his clients left New York and moved here to South Florida.</p>
<p>Annie now volunteers with a food distribution program in Miami but keeps in mind her weakened immune system.</p>
<p>Annie O.: &#8220;I don&#8217;t leave the house if I&#8217;m not well, and I take my temperature. I wash my hands, and I try to keep positive.&#8221;</p>
<p>Douglas is even more careful. He survived two different cancers. Now, he only leaves his condo complex once a week for fresh air.</p>
<p>Douglas Bush: &#8220;Given the conditions and circumstances, I don&#8217;t know when my immune system could be further compromised, making it easier for me and susceptible to actually picking up a disease that I don&#8217;t need and no one else needs.&#8221;</p>
<p>Douglas and Annie say they&#8217;ll never forget that terrible day when so many lost their lives.</p>
<p>Douglas Bush: &#8220;If I had it to do over again, I would do absolutely nothing different than what I chose to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Annie O.: &#8220;It&#8217;s so good for the soul, being the solution.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you were in the New York Ground Zero area and exposed to toxins, there is a one-time-only extension to sign up for the September 11th Victim Compensation Fund.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.vcf.gov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">September 11th Victim Compensation Fund</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.911victims.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Barasch &amp; McGarry</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">732345</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/200911_Ground_Zero_September_11_first_responders.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a49199b8-f267-4826-aec4-50577219edb1/7147bc05-be13-4b7d-87a0-1021cf5dd043/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219675~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a49199b8-f267-4826-aec4-50577219edb1/7147bc05-be13-4b7d-87a0-1021cf5dd043/main.mp4*~hmac=b45f3080b18b091a48b31bbe9164cb24fe85cd08ff02de47bcc2ba10c55678a5' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/200911_Ground_Zero_September_11_first_responders.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/200911_Ground_Zero_September_11_first_responders.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200911_Ground_Zero_September_11_first_responders</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Shot at Protection: South Florida woman takes part in COVID-19 vaccine trial</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/a-shot-at-protection-south-florida-woman-takes-part-in-covid-19-vaccine-trial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 03:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=715505</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We hear a lot about the efforts of front line workers in the fight against COVID, but there are others who are quietly helping in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We hear a lot about the efforts of front line workers in the fight against COVID, but there are others who are quietly helping in the background. Kevin Ozebek tells us some are volunteering their bodies to give us all a shot at protection.</p>
<p>She takes her temperature every day, but Erica Rodriguez Hylton isn&#8217;t sick. She&#8217;s recording her body&#8217;s reaction to a potential COVID vaccine candidate.</p>
<p>Erica Rodriguez Hylton, participant in vaccine trial: &#8220;I have to check myself, check my temperature, check the injection mark, and yeah, I mean, I just have to keep up with it. I have to call if I have any health problems.&#8221;</p>
<p>Erica is part of a vaccine clinical trial.</p>
<p>Pfizer Pharmaceutical Company teamed up with the German Company BioNTech to recruit volunteers between the ages of 18 to 85. Erica applied online and was selected to take part in the study.</p>
<p>Erica Rodriguez Hylton: &#8220;I was nervous. I was like, &#8216;Well, what if there&#8217;s side effects? What if it&#8217;s not safe?&#8217; And, you know, the whole time I just had to remind myself, my friends, my family, everyone that I love, I&#8217;m doing this for them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Erica got her first vaccine injection on Aug. 8.</p>
<p>Erica Rodriguez Hylton: &#8220;It&#8217;s just like a quick pinch, and like afterwards, like for the first two days, I only had like a bit of a little bit of a headache and fatigue.&#8221;</p>
<p>Participants are paid for their efforts &#8212; $118 per injection.</p>
<p>After her first shot, Erica was given a device to measure any swelling or redness at the injection site on her arm.</p>
<p>She puts all observations into an app and sends in the information daily. Erica was also given a COVID test kit, just in case she starts to experience symptoms.</p>
<p>Erica Rodriguez Hylton: &#8220;It&#8217;s just like any other swab test that they&#8217;ve been doing at Walgreens or with public health. You call the lab, and they send somebody to come pick it up.&#8221;</p>
<p>Erica is one of some 30,000 people taking part in the vaccination trial at 120 locations around the world. Pfizer and BioNTech says the goal is &#8220;to bring a well-tolerated, highly effective vaccine to the market as quickly as possible.&#8221;</p>
<p>Erica says she feels good about doing her part to help.</p>
<p>Erica Rodriguez Hylton: &#8220;This whole pandemic has just been horrible, and I just think that we kind of have to just throw down our politics and just do what it takes to fight this thing because people are dying. I want people I love to be safe, so when it came down to it, that&#8217;s all, like, to think about, is other people.&#8221;</p>
<p>She goes for her second and final trial injection on Aug. 24 and will continue to do follow ups and report any possible side-effects.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">715505</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/082120-covid-vaccine-trial-erica.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/06153618-3a5a-4850-b169-d17dcb9ec095/dd5487d3-eb73-4ce9-941f-a237b819427d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217718~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/06153618-3a5a-4850-b169-d17dcb9ec095/dd5487d3-eb73-4ce9-941f-a237b819427d/main.mp4*~hmac=7a5bb987c7ac5cf41d58e8787d622d632966804e2ec8ed8476fd0c12eda7b0b8' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/082120-covid-vaccine-trial-erica.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/082120-covid-vaccine-trial-erica.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">082120 covid vaccine trial erica</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Florida woman on a mission to clean up Miami Beach, one early morning at a time</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/south-florida-woman-on-a-mission-to-clean-up-miami-beach-one-early-morning-at-a-time/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=711134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One South Florida woman is a beach cleaning machine using her time and energy to protect our oceans. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel shows us what&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One South Florida woman is a beach cleaning machine using her time and energy to protect our oceans. The Nightteam&#8217;s Karen Hensel shows us what&#8217;s got her beach bummed in this special assignment report.</p>
<p>Victoria Player: &#8220;I spend so much time in the ocean snorkeling, kayaking, paddle boarding, diving, and when you see the destruction to the wildlife out there that have ingested trash, I mean, it&#8217;s suicide for the animals. It&#8217;s a death sentence. My name is Victoria Player, and pretty much, I&#8217;d say, for the last nine years, I have been coming to the beach every morning to walk, watch the sunrise and pick up trash.&#8221;</p>
<p>Before the sun comes up, Victoria Player is on Miami Beach working, though she&#8217;s not getting paid.</p>
<p>Victoria spends the early mornings picking up what others have left behind.</p>
<p>Victoria Player, picks up trash on the beach: &#8220;Karen, I just literally just got on the beach over there at South Pointe, and I walked to here, which is, what, not even a quarter of a mile, and you can see I&#8217;ve picked up this already, including a dirty diaper.&#8221;</p>
<p>On the day we tagged along, Victoria had already collected two bags of trash in the dark.</p>
<p>Victoria Player: &#8220;I typically walk up to 14th Street, and in that walk, I can pick up close to four or five bags of debris or trash.&#8221;</p>
<p>With the sun rising, we see even more that this is what thrown away looks like to some beachgoers.</p>
<p>Karen Hensel: &#8220;How much trash do you think you have picked up in all the years you have been out here doing this?&#8221;</p>
<p>Victoria Player: Tons. Even today, sometimes I can&#8217;t do it all, and I have to leave it because I don&#8217;t have time to pick it all up. I have to get to work.&#8221;</p>
<p>Work, Victoria&#8217;s paying job, is owning a luxury flooring business.</p>
<p>Victoria Player: &#8220;I work with very high-net-worth individuals. I wear Chanel shoes and Chanel handbag. I am just trying to now do my part. It&#8217;s not enough. How can one person make enough of an impact? They can&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s why Victoria is taking her concerns to South Beach hotels before the beaches become packed during snowbird season.</p>
<p>A time when her typical five bags of trash collected grows to 10 or even 15.</p>
<p>Her goal is to meet with hotel managers on an initiative to help educate tourists.</p>
<p>Victoria Player: &#8220;Every hotel room around the world now there is a notice when you enter the rooms about conserving water, conserving energy. Why can&#8217;t we put some sort of notice in the hotel rooms to educate the tourists to limit their plastic that they bring to the beach? There&#8217;s a trash can every 30 feet at the top of the beach. There&#8217;s also trash cans at every single exit off the beach.&#8221;</p>
<p>Victoria just started a change.org petition to keep Miami Beach clean.</p>
<p>As for the hotels&#8230;</p>
<p>Victoria Player: &#8220;I am just going to keep calling, smiling and dialing and just turn up. Hotels aren&#8217;t busy right now, right? You saw what we collected from there to here. Imagine what the rest of this beach looks like.&#8221;</p>
<p>Victoria Player lives by a simple rule: if you bring something to the beach, take it with you, and pick up three pieces of trash left behind by someone else, and for all of us, leave only our footprints in the sand.</p>
<p><a href="http://chng.it/HQSVfhq4Gt" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Victoria Player’s “Keep Miami Beach Clean” petition</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">711134</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/081420-miami-beach-cleanup.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6db70a69-099e-41a0-9004-fb4ce23bc050/f3d8df1c-5f2c-4a3e-a6f8-b028b25f5956/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217767~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6db70a69-099e-41a0-9004-fb4ce23bc050/f3d8df1c-5f2c-4a3e-a6f8-b028b25f5956/main.mp4*~hmac=fb1f72bc587754b12879f3a0ea2beacf3c7ea45c649bde555191f96b5b71f79b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/081420-miami-beach-cleanup.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/081420-miami-beach-cleanup.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">081420 miami beach cleanup</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feeding Families: Adopt A Family Miami helps residents in need during pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/feeding-families-adopt-a-family-miami-helps-residents-in-need-during-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 02:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=706355</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The coronavirus pandemic has left thousands of hospitality and service industry workers without jobs and struggling to feed their families. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows us...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The coronavirus pandemic has left thousands of hospitality and service industry workers without jobs and struggling to feed their families. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek shows us how one group of friends is on a mission to keep families fed and their refrigerators filled.</p>
<p>The coronavirus pandemic has affected nearly every aspect of life in South Florida. For some, it has taken away their ability to care for their own families.</p>
<p>Mabel De Beunza, Adopt A Family Miami volunteer: &#8220;These are people that don&#8217;t receive government aid. They don&#8217;t get a government check. They don&#8217;t receive a stimulus.&#8221;</p>
<p>This group of women wants to help fill the gap and provide much-needed support for some of Miami Beach&#8217;s most vulnerable residents.</p>
<p>Mabel De Beunza: &#8220;We are Adopt A Family Miami, also known as Fill the Fridge. Really, connecting people with people, and people who have a great deal of need.&#8221;</p>
<p>Adopt A Family Miami started in April after founder Mytyl Simancas saw an online post about a family that needed food.</p>
<p>Mytyl Simancas, founder, Adopt A Family Miami: &#8220;I saw that dropping off food one time was not going to solve any issues, so I decided to do it more frequently, and I started getting friends, asking them to help me.&#8221;</p>
<p>Her wish was granted in the form of donations and dozens of volunteers.</p>
<p>They are focused on helping low-income families with parents who work in hotels and restaurants in Miami Beach.</p>
<p>Many have been out of work for months.</p>
<p>Roberto Inoa, Adopt A Family Miami recipient: &#8220;Nobody was working, and they came, and just in time.&#8221;</p>
<p>Army veteran Roberto Inoa was laid off from his hotel restaurant job four months ago. He says the program has eased some of the financial burden.</p>
<p>Roberto Inoa: &#8220;Not only have I made friends, but friends are very involved, like, &#8216;What does your family need?'&#8221;</p>
<p>Families are visited several times a month by an assigned member.</p>
<p>Not only do members keep the refrigerator stocked; they also help in other ways.</p>
<p>Leslie Cooper, Adopt A Family volunteer: &#8220;We&#8217;ve had some pro bono medical work done and pro bono legal work done to help our families.&#8221;</p>
<p>Adopt A Family Miami started out with one family in April. They are now helping more than 150.</p>
<p>According to member Mabel De Beunza, that shows the impact the coronavirus pandemic has had in South Florida.</p>
<p>Mabel De Beunza: &#8220;Just when we think that we were graduating some of our families &#8212; their fridges didn&#8217;t need to be filled as much as necessary &#8212; then the closures of indoor restaurants happened.&#8221;</p>
<p>The plan is to never turn away a family in need, but the group also needs help.</p>
<p>Mabel De Beunza: &#8220;The resources need to be there, and that&#8217;s what we&#8217;re trying to do, is to raise as much money as possible.&#8221;</p>
<p>They&#8217;ve launched an online fundraising effort in the hopes of raising $100,000.</p>
<p>Even if they don&#8217;t reach their goal, they plan to keep helping families, even if the money comes out of their own wallets.</p>
<p>Mytyl Simancas: &#8220;It&#8217;s very moving, and when we are delivering, and every time we see them, we only get blessings and gratitude.&#8221;</p>
<p>They say that gratitude and the ability to make a difference is worth every penny.</p>
<p><strong>FOR MORE INFORMATION:</strong><br />
Adopt A Family Miami<br />
<a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/operation-fill-the-fridge-and-beyond?utm_source=customer&amp;utm_medium=copy_link&amp;utm_campaign=p_cf+share-flow-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Operation Fill the Fridge and Beyond</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">706355</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200807_adopt_a_family_miami_special_report.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f1472a94-6191-424c-947b-73da94ce4531/c0da530b-9420-4b72-b2a1-92663601654f/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219630~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f1472a94-6191-424c-947b-73da94ce4531/c0da530b-9420-4b72-b2a1-92663601654f/main.mp4*~hmac=63d662e047cf52e4e78f07af612807a571d161150fa0aa1cb5c90f22b3d24753' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200807_adopt_a_family_miami_special_report.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200807_adopt_a_family_miami_special_report.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200807_Adopt_A_Family_Miami_Special_Report</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helping Hands: Roofing community teams up to repair Fort Lauderdale family&#8217;s damaged roof</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/helping-hands-roofing-community-teams-up-to-repair-fort-lauderdale-familys-damaged-roof/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 03:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=697158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Fort Lauderdale family is sleeping soundly tonight after years of struggling. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has the exclusive story of how helping hands changed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fort Lauderdale family is sleeping soundly tonight after years of struggling. The Nightteam&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has the exclusive story of how helping hands changed their lives.</p>
<p>When Hurricane Irma hit South Florida in September 2017, the Walters family knew their roof was in trouble.</p>
<p>Annette Walters, homeowner: &#8220;As it rained, it just got heavier and heavier, and we knew soon it was just going to collapse.&#8221;</p>
<p>Clayton Walters, homeowner: &#8220;It was very bad, real bad. It started caving in.&#8221;</p>
<p>The roof collapsed in the bedroom. Then, mold started growing, making the family sick.</p>
<p>Annette Walters: &#8220;I stayed in the hospital constantly, and I knew it was because of the mold. All four of us move to the den. We sleep in the den, mattress in the den. That&#8217;s where we had to stay because everything had just fallen apart.&#8221;</p>
<p>With no insurance, there wasn&#8217;t any money for a new roof, but one day, after almost three years of misery, neighbors saw a woman fixing a roof nearby. They reached out to her and discovered a group called National Women in Roofing.</p>
<p>MaryBeth Reed, National Women in Roofing: &#8220;We reached out to the construction and roofing community and said, &#8216;Hey, we&#8217;ve got this family seriously in need. What can we do to help them?&#8217; And really, it was the power of all these women. We have well over 120 members here in South Florida and nearly 2,000 throughout the country.&#8221;</p>
<p>With their urging, it didn&#8217;t take long for local businesses to get involved.</p>
<p>Sandy Giel, National Women in Roofing: &#8220;We literally had probably 10 people within the first three hours, and it&#8217;s just snowballed from there. It&#8217;s just an amazing, amazing thing.&#8221;</p>
<p>In all, 37 South Florida companies stepped up offering labor, materials or donations for an estimated $45,000.</p>
<p>Colin Kepley, Skilcon Roofing and Waterproofing: &#8220;It&#8217;s a nice thing to be able to help out somebody that&#8217;s in need and just bringing the communities together in Fort Lauderdale. We&#8217;re a hard-hit area with COVID-19, and it&#8217;s great to see everybody collaborating to do this.&#8221;</p>
<p>When they started the project, volunteers were shocked at the condition of the house.</p>
<p>Worker: &#8220;The wood, you can see, has already been damaged. It has mold, and the water damage has come in. The family has not been able to sleep here because of this mold.&#8221;</p>
<p>Soon, it was out with the old roof, stripping it off and fixing the carpentry, trusses and putting on a new flat roof and shingles.</p>
<p>Woman volunteer: &#8220;Are you going to flash pretty much the perimeter area?&#8221;</p>
<p>Volunteer: &#8220;Yes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Inside, the mold is being removed, and new drywall for the ceiling is going up.</p>
<p>Clay Thomas, Advanced Roofing: &#8220;The fact that we can come in and not only stop the problem but improve that immediate environment, I think that&#8217;s huge.&#8221;</p>
<p>For the volunteers, it was a labor of love.</p>
<p>Marlene Contreras, National Women in Roofing: &#8220;This is what National Women in Roofing is all about!&#8221;</p>
<p>For the Walters family, it&#8217;s a gift they&#8217;ll never forget.</p>
<p>Annette Walters: &#8220;If they hadn&#8217;t came into my life, my family and I would literally be homeless. They are amazing. They are my angels.&#8221;</p>
<p>The roofing industry coming together, their many helping hands making a difference for a family in need.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">697158</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/073120-helping-hands-damaged-roof.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/89b70443-2d8a-47ec-86ab-d313150bd15e/8abf9b63-6d64-4b87-8656-644de49873ed/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217749~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/89b70443-2d8a-47ec-86ab-d313150bd15e/8abf9b63-6d64-4b87-8656-644de49873ed/main.mp4*~hmac=21b92a49dab3d91c912c74f51084d9ace60b17025d5e1865704bda3c7f56ec7b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/073120-helping-hands-damaged-roof.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/073120-helping-hands-damaged-roof.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">073120 helping hands damaged roof</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frontline Fighters: 2 South Florida frontline workers return to work following bout with COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/frontline-fighters-2-south-florida-frontline-workers-return-to-work-following-bout-with-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 03:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=691318</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are countless medical workers across the country fighting against COVID-19, both professionally and personally. Tonight, we meet two of them here in South Florida...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are countless medical workers across the country fighting against COVID-19, both professionally and personally. Tonight, we meet two of them here in South Florida who have battled back from the virus. 7&#8217;s Kevin Ozebek has this special assignment report: &#8220;Frontline Fighters.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maria Sulayman and Keith Martin have two things in common.</p>
<p>The ICU nurse and firefighter paramedic have both been on the frontline of the coronavirus pandemic, and both caught and survived COVID-19 themselves.</p>
<p>Maria Sulayman, ICU Nurse, Jackson Health System: &#8220;The most terrifying thing I&#8217;ve ever encountered in medicine.&#8221;</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin, Broward Sheriff Fire Rescue: &#8220;It was like the flu on steroids. I mean, just something you can never imagine.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maria is a critical care nurse at Jackson Memorial Hospital.</p>
<p>She deals directly with COVID patients.</p>
<p>Maria Sulayman: &#8220;It was heartbreaking. The patients were very scared.&#8221;</p>
<p>In June, it was Maria who was scared.</p>
<p>The nurse tested positive herself.</p>
<p>Maria Sulayman: &#8220;I didn&#8217;t know if I was going to make it a couple of days out of it. I didn&#8217;t know if I had to go to the intensive care unit myself. When it was very severe, I could not breathe. I could not get a breath in.&#8221;</p>
<p>Maria monitored her oxygen levels and says her symptoms included headaches, body aches and a persistent sore throat.</p>
<p>It took her a month to fully recover.</p>
<p>Sadly, the Jackson Health System lost three members of its family due to COVID-19. ICU nurse Araceli Buendia Ilagan, Dr. Luis Caldera-Nieves and radiology technician Devin Francis all died of complications from the virus.</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin: &#8220;It is something that crossed our mind quite often losing a brother and sister here at the agency.&#8221;</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin works for Broward Sheriff Fire Rescue and is based at the airport.</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin: &#8220;We respond to all types of emergency medical calls, and we&#8217;re always cautious, and we&#8217;re ready. When you throw a pandemic on top of that, for us, it&#8217;s like we don&#8217;t know what to expect.&#8221;</p>
<p>Because of precautions he took, Keith was not expecting to test positive.</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin: &#8220;When you hear the news, your heart stops for a second almost. You feel like your heart stops, and you have a sense of anxiety &#8217;cause you don&#8217;t know if this is the end for you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Keith quarantined at home.</p>
<p>He stayed in one bedroom or outside on the patio away from his wife and two daughters.</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin: &#8220;They were very terrified to know that daddy was exposed to COVID. Through the sliding glass doors, we would touch hands, and we would talk and communicate, but it was definitely not a pleasurable experience.&#8221;</p>
<p>Keith had a throbbing headache and his fever spiked to almost 102 degrees, but he says by day 14, he felt great and was back to work after testing negative twice.</p>
<p>Lt. Keith Martin: &#8220;I mean, I love this profession. I love my career. I love my job, so for me, this is who I am, so I mean, hey, if being exposed to COVID is part of the job, it&#8217;s what we signed up for.&#8221;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Thursday was Maria&#8217;s first day back at Jackson and is once again in the ICU caring for critically ill COVID patients.</p>
<p>Maria Sulayman: &#8220;I&#8217;m actually very excited to go back and help my coworkers. I&#8217;m really happy that I got my strength back, and I know how much they&#8217;ve been suffering and how desperate they are.&#8221;</p>
<p>Frontline fighters working around the clock to help others.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">691318</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/072420-frontline-fighters-return-to-work.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5ac6cd0b-3764-4e4a-9cd2-8e76dd7d2b0d/cb8490ee-b3a4-4b66-b343-89bfba278056/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219605~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/5ac6cd0b-3764-4e4a-9cd2-8e76dd7d2b0d/cb8490ee-b3a4-4b66-b343-89bfba278056/main.mp4*~hmac=1cdb3c5fd626c392ce3a0f7cbe574e5662ee880dcbc97152b05b676483f3e2fb' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/072420-frontline-fighters-return-to-work.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/072420-frontline-fighters-return-to-work.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">072420 frontline fighters return to work</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New temperature-checking device being deployed to front lines of pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/new-temperature-checking-device-being-deployed-to-front-lines-of-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Evan Siegel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 02:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=682684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many people are worried about going out in the middle of the pandemic, whether it&#8217;s to head to work or go shopping. But now, there&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many people are worried about going out in the middle of the pandemic, whether it&#8217;s to head to work or go shopping.</p>
<p>But now, there&#8217;s new technology that&#8217;s designed to give peace of mind by keeping those who are sick out of offices and stores.</p>
<p>Getting your temperature checked before entering a business is the new normal, but now, instead of people coming face-to-face using handheld thermometers, there&#8217;s a new way to find out if someone is sick.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s called the iDISPLAY thermometer, and it was created by a company named Outform.</p>
<p>Chris Brandewie, Outform: &#8220;It uses thermal body scanners to scan the body temperature and that includes even if you&#8217;re wearing a mask, so even if you have a mask or some obstruction of your face this will still actually be able to scan the body temperature and then it will give an approved sign or a decline sign.&#8221;</p>
<p>The machine tells you where to stand. It takes your temperature, and if it detects a fever, an alarm goes off.</p>
<p>The device can also be synched to automatic doors, keeping them closed to the person trying to enter if they have a temperature.</p>
<p>Eddie Gonzalez, CEO of i-payout: &#8220;That&#8217;s a good thing for the employees.&#8221;</p>
<p>I-payout is a software company in Fort Lauderdale. Gonzalez said his company started using the iDISPLAY thermometer last month.</p>
<p>Eddie Gonzalez: &#8220;First thing in the morning when they come out. We have signs all over. They&#8217;ll sign in, take the temperature on the block. If, for some reason, the temperature is elevated, there&#8217;s an exit right there that we would exit them out of the building.&#8221;</p>
<p>Employees say the no-touch unit creates a safer work environment.</p>
<p>Natalia Yenatska, i-payout employee: &#8220;We come up, we scan, you are sure that the temperature is good. It makes me feel better about coming into work and that makes me feel better because I know my family is safe.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also being used in retail businesses.</p>
<p>Elisa Massa, store owner: &#8220;I decide for the security of the staff, me and the customers.&#8221;</p>
<p>Massa is the owner of Botanica San Lazarus in Pompano Beach.</p>
<p>Elisa Massa: &#8220;When people walk in, I tell the customer, &#8216;Come and get the temperature. Let me see if you&#8217;re OK.'&#8221;</p>
<p>Hospitals are also looking into using the units. At Nicklaus Children&#8217;s Hospital, the iDISPLAY is currently being tested.</p>
<p>Chris Brandewie, iDISPLAY thermometer: &#8220;Basically someone walks up to it, they have a fever, it gets notified to the front desk and you can actually isolate that person coming into the hospital.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said 40% of the virus&#8217;s transmission occurs before someone has symptoms like fever.</p>
<p>The many people who have COVID-19 without showing any symptoms can still spread it. But new technology like iDISPLAY does give people peace of mind and adds one more tool in the fight against the virus.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">682684</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/2007010_idisplay_thermometer.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4c08ab47-c1ea-4858-8ff7-49440eeecb32/d5c79cd4-edef-44d3-b313-98b875772d34/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217092~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4c08ab47-c1ea-4858-8ff7-49440eeecb32/d5c79cd4-edef-44d3-b313-98b875772d34/main.mp4*~hmac=00cf496fc30123603790d9a91cb78dab7842e29942d004c2fdf997e78052bb59' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/2007010_idisplay_thermometer.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/2007010_idisplay_thermometer.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200710_iDisplay_thermometer</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weston teen, self-professed &#8216;Bird Nerd,&#8217; raising thousands for Pelican Harbor Seabird Station</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/weston-teen-self-professed-bird-nerd-raising-thousands-for-pelican-harbor-seabird-station/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Evan Siegel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 02:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=674139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[He calls himself a &#8220;Bird Nerd,&#8221; but one Weston teen&#8217;s passion for birds is serious business in the world of wildlife conservation. Oskar Garcia: &#8220;I&#8217;ve...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He calls himself a &#8220;Bird Nerd,&#8221; but one Weston teen&#8217;s passion for birds is serious business in the world of wildlife conservation.</p>
<p>Oskar Garcia: &#8220;I&#8217;ve always had a fascination with birds. It&#8217;s been a key part of my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>Oskar rescued his first bird when he was just 4 years old. Then, when he was 6, the Deepwater Horizon oil rig exploded, gushing oil into the Gulf of Mexico, killing and crippling an estimated one million birds.</p>
<p>Astrid Garcia, Oskar&#8217;s mom: &#8220;He was devastated. He saw the pictures, you saw the images of the birds all covered in oil, and he was beside himself. He just wanted to know what can we do, what can we do?&#8221;</p>
<p>With help from his classmates, Oskar collected 169 bottles of Dawn dish washing liquid.</p>
<p>The donated soap was used to clean birds covered in oil.</p>
<p>Oskar Garcia: &#8220;People that I didn&#8217;t know, they all wanted to help the cause. Yes, it was just nice to see that I had a voice even at such a young age.&#8221;</p>
<p>Oskar discovered his voice for change and his talent for art. He started designing T-shirts when he was 7. When he was 11, a bird calendar project earned him more than $1,000.</p>
<p>He took all the pictures himself and donated the proceeds to Pelican Harbor Seabird Station, which rehabilitates then releases sick and injured wildlife.</p>
<p>Sarah Curry, Pelican Harbor Seabird Station: &#8220;He brings his passion of wildlife combined with his passion for making art and provides a really unique way to support Pelican Harbor.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now at 16, Oskar is Pelican Harbor&#8217;s youngest major donor, giving more than $14,000 over the past six years.</p>
<p>Sarah Curry: &#8220;That&#8217;s a significant amount of money for someone at that age or any age to contribute, I&#8217;m sure, so we&#8217;re so thankful for his contributions, and it&#8217;s literally saving lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>Now, Oskar has a new fundraising project for the Seabird Station. He has designed a line of pelican gear and is selling it online.</p>
<p>Astrid Garcia: &#8220;His designs can be customized into anything you want and all the profit goes to Pelican Harbor. Several people have approached him to match the profit that he makes, so hopefully he&#8217;ll get matches for those so that his donation is significant to Pelican Harbor.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Seabird Station is closed to the public right now because of the COVID-19 pandemic, but the work to treat and save South Florida&#8217;s native birds continues.</p>
<p>Oskar said he&#8217;s making it his mission to help.</p>
<p>Oskar Garcia: &#8220;You need all the organisms to keep balance, and it&#8217;s a beautiful thing for everyone to enjoy.&#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s why he&#8217;s on a mission to help, so future generations can enjoy birding in the future.</p>
<p>You can learn more about Oskar&#8217;s work <a href="https://www.pelicanharbor.org/oskar-garcia" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">674139</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/unknown-1-14.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/unknown-1-14.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/unknown-1-14.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Unknown-1</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandemic forcing kids to adjust to revamped summer camps</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/special-reports/pandemic-forcing-kids-to-adjust-to-revamped-summer-camps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Evan Siegel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 02:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Special Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=665141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[School is finally over for thousands of South Florida students. The next step for many is summer camp, but the coronavirus pandemic is forcing camp...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>School is finally over for thousands of South Florida students. The next step for many is summer camp, but the coronavirus pandemic is forcing camp directors to make big changes to keep kids healthy. 7&#8217;s Brian Entin has more about summer safety.</p>
<p>Kids at Fight Sports Summer Camp in Coral Springs spend a few hours every day learning about jujitsu.</p>
<p>Instead of sparring with each other, they practice their moves on dummies and keep their distance from their friends.</p>
<p>Felipe Amarante, Fight Sports owner: &#8220;I had to find a way for them to practice jujitsu, especially for the parents that are not ready for contact at all.&#8221;</p>
<p>South Florida camp directors were afraid they would not be able to open this summer, but were finally given the green light last week.</p>
<p>Amarante said things are a lot different this year.</p>
<p>&#8220;Maybe more cleaning, right? More hand washing.&#8221;</p>
<p>Camps had to make major changes in order to open, and kids will see it the minute they walk through the door.</p>
<p>Felipe Amarante: &#8220;As the kids come in, we check their temperature, we have multiple hand sanitizers. We do have the social distancing, we clean everything. Everything is nice and organized.&#8221;</p>
<p>You won&#8217;t see as many kids at area camps, either.</p>
<p>Last summer, the program at Fight Sports had 40 campers enrolled.</p>
<p>But because of social distancing rules, they could only accept 18.</p>
<p>Mike Nieves, APT trainer: &#8220;OK, what&#8217;s the steps that we need to take to make sure our athletes and their families are safe?&#8221;</p>
<p>APT soccer camp in Coconut Creek is also operating below normal numbers.</p>
<p>Because soccer is a high contact sport, Nieves said his staff had to figure out how to run their camp without anyone actually playing soccer.</p>
<p>Mike Nieves: &#8220;We have to be able to put together games that are social distanced, keeping these kids six feet or more apart.&#8221;</p>
<p>The kids spend their time brushing up on technique and form, guided by their instructors who all wear masks.</p>
<p>If parents still aren&#8217;t comfortable bringing their kids to camp, APT has come up with virtual training sessions.</p>
<p>Djems Lima, APT owner: &#8220;We basically do the exercise, show them and we have our screen turned so we can see them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Camps have hand washing and CDC reminders posted throughout their facilities.</p>
<p>They are also bringing in extra help to make sure everything is clean.</p>
<p>Mike Nieves: &#8220;One of our main things is making sure we keep the contact with surfaces in our facility as minimal as possible for our players.&#8221;</p>
<p>Even with all the new measures to keep things safe, they say it&#8217;s OK if parents don&#8217;t jump at the chance to send their kids to camp.</p>
<p>Djems Lima: &#8220;It&#8217;s completely understandable, because we don&#8217;t know what the long-term effects of this is.&#8221;</p>
<p>There is no doubt that camp will definitely be different this year, but the goal is for kids to still have a good time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">665141</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/unknown-5-3.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/unknown-5-3.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/unknown-5-3.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Unknown-5</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
