<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>US &amp; World &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:38:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>US &amp; World &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Over 166,000 hens die in Arizona farm fire</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/over-166000-hens-die-in-arizona-farm-fire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 01:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Over 166,000 laying hens died on Saturday after a fire broke out at a bird warehouse in Arizona. Flames engulfed three massive warehouses...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Over 166,000 laying hens died on Saturday after a fire broke out at a bird warehouse in Arizona.</p>
<p>Flames engulfed three massive warehouses containing chickens and hens at Hickman&#8217;s Family Farms in Arlington, about 50 miles west of Phoenix, according to the Maricopa County Sheriff&#8217;s Office (MCSO).</p>
<p>The fire broke out when a piece of equipment malfunctioned and caught fire, Hickman&#8217;s Family Farms spokesperson Sharman Hickman told CNN.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re just trying to get back to business,&#8221; Hickman said. &#8220;We&#8217;re still mourning the loss of all those chickens and hens.&#8221;</p>
<p>There is no indication of foul play, said Sgt. Joaquin Enriquez of the MCSO.</p>
<p>Farm employees reported a fire at one of their bird warehouses around 1 p.m. But by the time first responders arrived at the scene two more warehouses had caught fire.</p>
<p>One adult was transported to a local hospital for smoke inhalation and is in stable condition, Buckeye Valley Fire District spokesperson Sarah Mendoza told CNN.</p>
<p>Hickman&#8217;s Family Farms has been in business for over 70 years, and the farm has been run by the same family for four generations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878034</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/192e3189-b603-40bb-97e4-1fdbc2a60a8f/708a617f-e81c-4cf1-942a-b057c1cd1040/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216599~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/192e3189-b603-40bb-97e4-1fdbc2a60a8f/708a617f-e81c-4cf1-942a-b057c1cd1040/main.mp4*~hmac=c6bc1c915d725f3191972c845c55839078c08b3b6735fefda9d8497b14aa5dc0' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_c4b48ef2627f856e55433e37eca80b70-h_cee999bec64b6eb9314617bc31930c0b</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian disinformation campaign working to undermine confidence in COVID-19 vaccines used in US</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/russian-disinformation-campaign-working-to-undermine-confidence-in-covid-19-vaccines-used-in-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 01:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=878015</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Online platforms directed by Russian intelligence are spreading disinformation about two of the coronavirus vaccines being used in the US, a State Department spokesperson confirmed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Online platforms directed by Russian intelligence are spreading disinformation about two of the coronavirus vaccines being used in the US, a State Department spokesperson confirmed to CNN on Sunday.</p>
<p>The agency&#8217;s Global Engagement Center identified three Russian outlets &#8212; News Front, New Eastern Outlook and Oriental Review &#8212; that are spreading not only misinformation about the virus, but also regarding &#8220;international organizations, military conflicts, protests; and any divisive issue that they can exploit,&#8221; according to the spokesperson.</p>
<p>&#8220;These sites all vary in their reach, tone, and audience &#8212; but they all are spreading Russian propaganda and disinformation. The State Department&#8217;s finding of a link between these sites and Russian Intelligence is a result of a joint interagency conclusion,&#8221; the spokesperson said.</p>
<p>The GEC leads efforts &#8220;to recognize, understand, expose, and counter foreign state and non-state propaganda and disinformation efforts aimed at undermining or influencing the policies, security, or stability of the United States, its allies, and partner nations,&#8221; according to its website.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/russian-disinformation-campaign-aims-to-undermine-confidence-in-pfizer-other-covid-19-vaccines-u-s-officials-say-11615129200" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Wall Street Journal </a>first reported on the disinformation.</p>
<p>The campaign comes as the US and other countries race to vaccinate people using three vaccines developed in record time by the drug makers Pfizer/BioNTech, Moderna and Johnson &amp; Johnson. US officials have been working to increase confidence in the drugs in recent months as studies showed a concerning level of vaccine hesitancy among some people, though that has decreased as the rollout has progressed.</p>
<p>A spokesman for the Kremlin denied to the Journal that the country&#8217;s intelligence services were spearheading the disinformation campaign.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s nonsense. Russian special services have nothing to do with any criticism against vaccines,&#8221; the spokesman, Dmitry Peskov, told the newspaper.</p>
<p>The Journal reported that, &#8220;Russian state media and Russian government Twitter accounts have made overt efforts to raise concerns about the cost and safety of the Pfizer vaccine in what experts outside the US government say is an effort to promote the sale of Russia&#8217;s rival Sputnik V vaccine.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;The emphasis on denigrating Pfizer is likely due to its status as the first vaccine besides Sputnik V to see mass use, resulting in a greater potential threat to Sputnik&#8217;s market dominance,&#8221; a forthcoming report by the Alliance for Securing Democracy says, according to the Journal.</p>
<p>One outlet in the disinformation campaign, News Front, used international reports to play &#8220;up the risk that a person who receives the Pfizer or Moderna Inc. vaccines could contract Bell&#8217;s palsy, in which facial muscles are paralyzed,&#8221; according to the Journal, which noted that while a small number of side effects have been reported by vaccine recipients, the shots are overwhelmingly safe and effective.</p>
<p>Pamela Eisele, a spokeswoman for Pfizer, told the newspaper that so far, &#8220;millions of people have been vaccinated with our vaccine following the endorsement of regulators in multiple countries.&#8221;</p>
<p>A spokeswoman for Moderna didn&#8217;t immediately respond to the Journal&#8217;s request for comment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">878015</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_COVOD19_vaccines_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Floyd&#8217;s cause of death, ex-cop&#8217;s force will be keys at trial</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/floyds-cause-of-death-ex-cops-force-will-be-keys-at-trial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877997</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis police officer was swiftly fired and charged with murder after bystander video showed him pressing his knee into George Floyd&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis police officer was swiftly fired and charged with murder after bystander video showed him pressing his knee into George Floyd&#8217;s neck, ignoring the Black man&#8217;s cries that he couldn&#8217;t breathe. But even with that powerful footage, legal experts say the case isn&#8217;t a slam dunk.</p>
<p>Jury selection begins Monday in Derek Chauvin&#8217;s trial, which is expected to come down to two key questions: Did Chauvin&#8217;s actions cause Floyd&#8217;s death, and were his actions reasonable?</p>
<p>“It’s hard not to watch the video and conclude that the prosecutors will not have any trouble with this case,” said Susan Gaertner, the former head prosecutor in neighboring Ramsey County. “But it’s not that simple.”</p>
<p>Floyd was declared dead May 25 after Chauvin, who is white, pressed his knee against Floyd’s neck <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/prosecutors-officer-was-on-floyds-neck-for-about-9-minutes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">for about nine minutes</a>, holding his position even after Floyd went limp as he was handcuffed and lying on his stomach. Floyd’s death sparked sometimes violent protests in Minneapolis and beyond, and led to a nationwide reckoning on race.</p>
<p>Chauvin is charged with second-degree unintentional murder and second-degree manslaughter, and a panel of appeals court judges ruled Friday that the judge must consider reinstating a third-degree murder charge that he dismissed last fall. Three other officers, all of whom also were fired, face trial in August on charges of aiding and abetting the second-degree murder and manslaughter counts.</p>
<p>The second-degree murder charge requires prosecutors to prove Chauvin caused Floyd&#8217;s death while committing or trying to commit a felony — in this case, third-degree assault. The manslaughter charge has a lower bar, requiring proof that Chauvin caused Floyd&#8217;s death through negligence that created an unreasonable risk, and consciously took the chance of causing severe injury or death.</p>
<p>Exactly how Floyd died is shaping up as a major flashpoint of the trial.</p>
<p>Chauvin&#8217;s attorney, Eric Nelson, argues in court documents that Floyd likely died from fentanyl he consumed, or a combination of fentanyl, methamphetamine and underlying health conditions — not as a result of Chauvin&#8217;s knee on his neck.</p>
<p>But Hennepin County Judge Peter Cahill wrote last fall that for the second-degree murder charge, prosecutors don&#8217;t have to prove that Chauvin was the sole cause of Floyd&#8217;s death — only that his conduct was a “substantial causal factor.”</p>
<p>Still, defense attorneys who aren&#8217;t connected to the case say all Nelson has to do is raise reasonable doubt in a single juror&#8217;s mind.</p>
<p>“Although he had him pinned under his knee and he’s yelling ‘I can’t breathe! I can’t breathe!’ there’s an argument that (Chauvin) wasn’t exerting pressure and his inability to breathe was due to the drugs in his system or something to that effect, or his anxiety,” said F. Clayton Tyler, a prominent local defense attorney.</p>
<p>Defense attorneys say it also may not be easy to establish that Chauvin was committing the felony of assault — as required for the second-degree murder charge in this case. That&#8217;s because Chauvin is authorized to use force as a police officer, and his attorneys will argue that his use of force against Floyd was reasonable.</p>
<p>Gaertner said the defense will face a challenge of trying to move the jury’s focus off of the video and the strong emotion it generates. They&#8217;ll instead try to focus on the medical evidence and Floyd’s underlying conditions while trying to portray the circumstances of the arrest as “justifiable consistent with police norms,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>Brandt and Tyler said Chauvin will likely have to take the stand to explain why he felt he had to hold Floyd down for so long. Brandt said he’ll likely say he followed his training, and that it was necessary because his experience with other suspects under the influence of drugs shows that things can suddenly become erratic and dangerous.</p>
<p>Prosecutors, however, have submitted a list of previous instances in which Chauvin used chokeholds or similar restraints on the job. Cahill ruled they can admit only one as evidence: a 2017 arrest in which Chauvin restrained a female by placing his knee on her neck while she was prone on the ground.</p>
<p>Cahill also ruled that prosecutors can tell jurors about a 2015 incident in which Chauvin saw other officers place a suicidal, intoxicated male in a side-recovery position after using a stun gun on him. Cahill said prosecutors can introduce that if they can show Chauvin was present when a medical professional said that the male could have died if officers had prolonged the detention.</p>
<p>Brandt said telling the jury about those events will allow prosecutors to show that Chauvin knew the proper way to restrain someone and provide relief, and that he had done it wrong before.</p>
<p>Brandt said the third-degree murder charge could be easier for prosecutors to prove if it&#8217;s reinstated because they wouldn&#8217;t have to show Chauvin intended to commit assault. Instead, they must prove his actions caused Floyd&#8217;s death, and that they were reckless and without regard for human life.</p>
<p>The second-degree manslaughter count alleges Chauvin took a risk that a reasonable person would have known could cause death. To defend against that, Brandt said, Chauvin could argue that he had used the same hold in the past and didn&#8217;t think it would cause a problem.</p>
<p>However, Brandt said “the whole case” against Chauvin is the video capturing the amount of time he restrained Floyd.</p>
<p>“You hear on the video the passersby, the onlookers saying, ‘Dude, he can’t breathe. Let him up. What are you doing? You are killing him,’” Brandt said. “I mean, it’s almost like they are giving a play-by-play.”</p>
<p>Tyler said if he were a prosecutor, he’d use a still shot of Chauvin’s expressionless face from that video and keep it in view for the jury to see.</p>
<p>“I mean, the look on his face,” Tyler said. “If I was prosecuting this case, I have to say, I’d have that picture up there. You want to show indifference? Just look at him.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877997</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Chauvin_Floyd.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/812320ba-7b39-4d87-9d03-61bf4e9e286e/a2aa5109-fcd6-4826-a8f2-436b2fe8f6b3/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218149~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/812320ba-7b39-4d87-9d03-61bf4e9e286e/a2aa5109-fcd6-4826-a8f2-436b2fe8f6b3/main.mp4*~hmac=51392e00d99577f9bcc5a3941bbf1c06d3a51f7ce330b9bdd539d63d79dc13fd' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Chauvin_Floyd.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Chauvin_Floyd.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Chauvin_Floyd</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Authorities to seek charges after violent Boulder party that left 3 officers injured</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/authorities-to-seek-charges-after-violent-boulder-party-that-left-3-officers-injured/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; Authorities promised Sunday to pursue criminal charges after a massive party near the University of Colorado in Boulder devolved into a violent confrontation...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; Authorities promised Sunday to pursue criminal charges after a massive party near the University of Colorado in Boulder devolved into a violent confrontation with police that left three officers injured.</p>
<p>Hundreds of people flooded the streets in an area known as the Hill on Saturday night and when told to leave threw bottles, rocks and other objects at police and firefighters, police said.</p>
<p>At least one car was damaged when the mob flipped it over, and police brought in a SWAT team and used tear gas to break up the crowd that numbered 500 to 800 people at its peak, said Boulder Police Chief Maris Herold.</p>
<p>Images shared by local media showed no social distancing and most without masks despite the coronavirus pandemic. Fireworks were set off in the middle of the street and a law enforcement armored vehicle and a fire truck were damaged, according to police and local media.</p>
<p>At one point Herold said a “tactical decision” was made to withdraw some officers when a group of about 100 people started to rush them. It took more than three hours to disperse the crowd, according to a timeline she provided.</p>
<p>Boulder County District Attorney Michael Dougherty described the rowdy behavior amid the coronavirus pandemic as “shameful.”</p>
<p>“I hear people refer to it as a party. I don&#8217;t regard flipping over a car as a party and I don&#8217;t regard people who throw bottles and rocks at firefighters and police as a party,” he said. “Those are criminal acts and will be treated as such.”</p>
<p>No arrests were made at the scene, police said.</p>
<p>Officers were reviewing officer body camera footage and shared social media videos and photos to identify the individuals involved. They also set up a <a href="https://bouldercopd.evidence.com/axon/citizen/public/hill-disturbance">portal </a>on the city&#8217;s website to allow the public to submit additional video footage or other evidence from the disturbance.</p>
<p>Herold said it was a calculated call not to make any arrests immediately, out of worry that sending in officers would agitate the large crowd. She added that the department had “excellent” video to help it pursue those responsible for the violence.</p>
<p>The three injured officers were recovering, including one who was struck in the hand and another who was hit in the face but was wearing a gas mask, Herold said. City vehicles suffered thousands of dollars in damages and private property also was harmed, she said.</p>
<p>The Hill neighborhood has been known for decades for sometimes raucous parties and there have been previous confrontations that resulted in violence, including 12 officers injured in a 1997 riot near the school.</p>
<p>But city officials said during a Sunday press conference that the stakes from Saturday&#8217;s events are particularly high amid the pandemic, with potentially dire consequences. Health officials advised anyone who participated to quarantine for at least 10 days and to get tested for COVID-19.</p>
<p>CU Boulder students returned to campus for hybrid and in-person learning in mid-February.</p>
<p>University officials apologized to Boulder residents who live near the school and said students who were involved in violence, property damage or failing to disperse would be held accountable.</p>
<p>“If they can&#8217;t meet our expectation, they are not welcome at the university,” said CU Boulder Chief Operating Officer Patrick O&#8217;Rourke. He added that the university knows its students were involved and “We are not going to try to shift the blame.”</p>
<p>After the party broke up, other students came to the scene with garbage bags to pick up the large amounts of trash left behind.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877987</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f0ac3c7d-d4b9-475c-87ab-57cf56beeb48/b938ccf4-2b96-4ebb-bd50-79e12e68fa1e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615216973~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f0ac3c7d-d4b9-475c-87ab-57cf56beeb48/b938ccf4-2b96-4ebb-bd50-79e12e68fa1e/main.mp4*~hmac=d7fb1ac3dfc0b05f751a8b927c5081729880641d35fd78cce67b47200e8e3b97' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Boulder_Colorado_college_party_aftermath</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk lost $27 billion last week</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/elon-musk-lost-27-billion-last-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 22:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Elon Musk&#8217;s net worth plunged last week as tech stocks got hammered and Tesla shares&#8217; stunning rise quickly unraveled. Wall Street is growing increasingly nervous...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Elon Musk&#8217;s <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/investing/elon-musk-pay-wealth-tesla-stock-options/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">net worth</a> plunged last week as tech stocks got hammered and Tesla shares&#8217; stunning rise quickly unraveled.</p>
<p>Wall Street is growing increasingly nervous about rising bond yields, which could make borrowing more expensive. That could eat into corporate profits, which is why investors have begun to reverse some of the positions they took over the past year in high-growth but risky tech stocks like Tesla.</p>
<p>Tesla&#8217;s stock fell 11.5% last week. Musk, who owns nearly 18% of Tesla&#8217;s shares, bore most of the brunt of that massive sell-off.</p>
<p>Musk&#8217;s wealth fell by $27 billion last week, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/billionaires/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg&#8217;s Billionaires Index</a>. The decline in his net value is roughly equal to the entire fortune held by Dyson founder James Dyson &#8212; the 52nd richest person in the world, according to Bloomberg.</p>
<p>Musk and Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos have been swapping places atop Bloomberg&#8217;s list of richest people in the world since January. But Musk now sits in a distant second place: $157 billion, compared to Bezos&#8217; net worth of $177 billion. Musk remains $21 billion ahead of Microsoft founder Bill Gates, who remains the third-richest person on the planet.</p>
<p>Tesla&#8217;s stock gained 743% in 2020, propelling it to No. 5 on the list of most valuable companies on the stock market. After losing 15% this year, Tesla&#8217;s stock has since fallen to No. 7, behind Facebook and Berkshire Hathaway but ahead of JPMorgan Chase.</p>
<p>Even if Tesla&#8217;s stock continues to sink, Musk still stands to become much richer in 2021 and beyond.</p>
<p>He received four grants to buy 8.4 million Tesla shares in 2020. Each of those was worth $5 billion at Friday&#8217;s closing price, although some of that will be shaved off because Musk will have to pay the exercise price. Musk will probably receive three additional options grants this year, each as large and as lucrative as those he received in 2020.</p>
<p>Musk has not exercised any of his options. Executives typically exercise them when they are due to expire, or to free up cash. Musk has never sold Tesla shares.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877948</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Elon_Musk.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Elon_Musk.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210307_Elon_Musk.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210307_Elon_Musk</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amid the rubble of Mosul, Pope Francis declares hope &#8216;more powerful than hatred&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/amid-the-rubble-of-mosul-pope-francis-declares-hope-more-powerful-than-hatred/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 16:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877829</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Standing amid the rubble left behind by the now-defeated ISIS terrorists in the Iraqi city of Mosul, Pope Francis on Saturday declared hope to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Standing amid the rubble left behind by the now-defeated ISIS terrorists in the Iraqi city of Mosul, <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/05/middleeast/iraq-pope-francis-visit-arrival-baghdad-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pope Francis</a> on Saturday declared hope to be &#8220;more powerful than hatred and peace more powerful than war.&#8221;</p>
<p>Francis called for &#8220;harmonious coexistence&#8221; of people from different backgrounds and cultures while leading a prayer at a square overlooking the ruins of the Syro-Catholic Church in Mosul&#8217;s Old City. Once an ISIS stronghold, the whole city has been completely destroyed in 2017, during the nine-months-long battle over its control.</p>
<p>&#8220;Here in Mosul, the tragic consequences of war and hostility are all too evident,&#8221; Francis said. &#8220;How cruel it is that this country, the cradle of civilization, should have been afflicted by so barbarous a blow, with ancient places of worship destroyed and many thousands of people &#8212; Muslims, Christians, Yazidis and others &#8212; forcibly displaced or killed!&#8221;</p>
<p>Thousands of people were killed during the battle to recapture Mosul from ISIS, which controlled the city between 2014 and 2017.</p>
<p>The visit to Mosul came on the third day of the <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/04/middleeast/iraq-pope-christians-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pope&#8217;s tour of the war-ravaged nation</a>, the first-ever papal visit to Iraq and Francis&#8217; first trip outside Italy since the coronavirus pandemic began. He has repeatedly denounced religious extremism and called for friendship between religions during the trip.</p>
<p>After leaving Mosul, Francis traveled to the Qaraqosh, the largest Christian city in Iraq. Like Mosul, Qaraqosh was also controlled by the ISIS terrorist group for more than two years.</p>
<p>The Pope visited the city&#8217;s Church of the Immaculate Conception, where he gave a speech and led a prayer. He was greeted by thousands of people there &#8212; a marked difference from his visits to other locations across Iraq. The government has imposed a total curfew for the entirety of the four-day papal visit to minimize health and security risks.</p>
<p>Late on Sunday, the Pope was scheduled to hold celebrate Mass at the Franso Hariri Stadium in Erbil, according to Iraq state-run Iraqiya TV. Some 8,000 people have gathered at the stadium to welcome the Pope there, security officials told CNN. The plan had been to have the 35,000 seats stadium at some 50% capacity with an empty seat between each of the attendees to allow for social distancing, according to officials. However, images from the stadium showed swathes of the stadium stands filled with people seated closely together without social distancing.</p>
<p>Earlier Sunday, Francis met with Nechirvan Barzani, the president of the Kurdish Regional Government, the semi-autonomous region in northern Iraq.</p>
<p>The Pope is believed to have long wished to go to Iraq, which figures heavily in the Old Testament, and whose dwindling Christian minority has suffered greatly from the country&#8217;s long cycles of violence.</p>
<p>Thought to be one of the oldest Christian communities in the world, prior to the 2003 US invasion, there were 1.5 million Christians in Iraq. Around 80% of them have since fled, according to leading Christian clerics there.</p>
<p>He touched down in Baghdad on Friday, where he was met by Iraqi Prime Minister Mustafa al-Kadhimi. Francis later met with clerics and other officials at a Baghdad church that was the site of a bloody 2010 massacre.</p>
<p>On Saturday, the Pope held a historic meeting with revered Shia Muslim cleric <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/06/middleeast/pope-francis-nayaf-grand-ayatollah-intl-hnk/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani</a> in the holy city of Najaf before visiting Ur, the ancient Iraqi city where Jews, Christians and Muslims believe their common patriarch Abraham was born.</p>
<p>Francis then returned to Baghdad on Saturday afternoon and celebrated Mass at the Chaldean Cathedral of Saint Joseph. He is scheduled to leave Iraq on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877829</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180825_pope_francis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180825_pope_francis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/180825_pope_francis.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180825_Pope_Francis</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Workers worry about safety, stress as states ease mask rules</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/workers-worry-about-safety-stress-as-states-ease-mask-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 14:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[JACKSON, Mississippi (AP) — Leo Carney worries that bigger crowds and mask-less diners could endanger workers at the Biloxi, Mississippi, seafood restaurant where he manages...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>JACKSON, Mississippi (AP) — Leo Carney worries that bigger crowds and mask-less diners could endanger workers at the Biloxi, Mississippi, seafood restaurant where he manages the kitchen. Maribel Cornejo, who earns $9.85 an hour as a McDonald&#8217;s cook in Houston, can&#8217;t afford to get sick and frets co-workers will become more lax about wearing masks, even though the fast food company requires them.</p>
<p>As more jurisdictions join Texas, Mississippi and other states in <a href="https://apnews.com/article/texas-other-states-ease-covid-19-restrictions-af9fc214690270fe617864abc772ecce">lifting mask mandates</a> and easing restrictions on businesses, many essential workers — including bartenders, restaurant servers and retail workers — are relieved by changes that might help the economy but also concerned they could <a href="https://apnews.com/article/rochelle-walensky-coronavirus-pandemic-fe2e65c19506b99ebdb8f1e0badc846b">make them less safe</a> amid a pandemic that health experts warn is far from over.</p>
<p>Many business owners on the Mississippi Gulf Coast were glad Gov. Tate Reeves decided to eliminate mask requirements, limits on seating in restaurants and most other binding restrictions. “But the workers themselves&#8230; especially ones that have pre-existing conditions, they’re scared right now,” Carney said.</p>
<p>“This just puts us back in a situation where we’re on the frontlines, under the gun again,” said Carney, who sees Black Mississippians facing the greatest risks from the decision that took effect Wednesday. COVID-19 has disproportionately affected Black and Latino people in the United States, and many Gulf Coast restaurants have a significant number of Black employees.</p>
<p>Public health experts tracking the trajectory of more contagious virus variants have warned that lifting restrictions too soon could lead to another lethal wave of infections. Although vaccination drives are accelerating as drug manufacturers ramp up production, many essential workers are not yet eligible for COVID-19 vaccines in Mississippi and other states.</p>
<p>Alabama’s state health officer on Friday advised residents to keep following standard infection-prevention recommendations even though the governor is letting the state’s <a href="https://apnews.com/article/kay-ivey-extends-alabama-mask-order-coronavirus-bd11f67b77915a7cd9320b714f222869">mask mandate expire </a>next month.</p>
<p>“There is nothing magical about the date of April 9. We don’t want the public to think that’s the day we all stop taking precautions,” State Health Officer Scott Harris said.</p>
<p>The governors of Iowa, Montana, North Dakota also have ended mask requirements or plan to suspend them soon. The governor of South Carolina on Friday lifted an executive order requiring face coverings in government office buildings and restaurants, leaving it up to state administrators and restaurant operators to develop their own guidelines.</p>
<p>Governors in several other states, including Michigan and Louisiana, eased the operating limits for bars, restaurants and other businesses in recent days.</p>
<p>The National Retail Federation, the largest retail trade association in the U.S., issued a statement Wednesday encouraging shoppers to wear masks. Some retail chains, including Target and supermarket operator Albertson&#8217;s, plan to continue requiring them for both customers and workers in states that no longer make them mandatory.</p>
<p>Texas Retailers Association President and CEO George Kelemen said he thinks many members will continue to require workers — but not necessarily customers — to wear masks and other protective gear.</p>
<p>“Retailers know their customers best,” he said.</p>
<p>McDonald’s cook Cornejo, 43, said the end of Texas’ mask mandate next week alarms her because several of her co-workers already were lax about keeping their faces covered. She said co-workers she has asked to pull their masks back over their noses politely acquiesced, but not always for long.</p>
<p>“There are just different attitudes,” said Cornejo, whose 19-year-old son began working as a cashier at the same restaurant to help pay the family’s bills. “Some say it’s just too difficult to keep it on for eight hours, especially when it gets hot.”</p>
<p>The director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Dr. Rochelle Walensky, encouraged Americans to “do the right thing” by continuing to abide by recommendations for routine mask use and social distancing &#8211; even if their states lift restrictions.</p>
<p>Dr. William Schaffner, a professor of preventive medicine at Vanderbilt University in Tennessee, said individuals who wear masks still risk infection from unmasked shoppers and diners. He called Texas Gov. Greg Abbott’s decision to lift COVID-19 restrictions starting March 10 “entirely too soon and entirely too carefree.”</p>
<p>While deaths and new confirmed cases have plummeted from their January peaks nationwide, they’re still running at high levels, while outbreak indicators in some states have risen in recent weeks. In Mississippi, for example, the 7-day rolling average of the virus positivity rate rose from 11.47% on Feb. 19 to 12.14% on March 5, and the state&#8217;s 7-day rolling average of daily deaths increase during the same period from 15 per day to 20.71 per day.</p>
<p>Workers in cities that still have mask mandates or jobs at businesses that maintain their own virus-prevention rules anticipate defiance from customers emboldened by their governors’ actions and weary of taking precautions.</p>
<p>Molly Brooks, 25, a barista at a Farmers Branch, Texas, coffee shop, said she has regularly dealt with customers who walked out or bullied her and her colleagues when they were asked to wear a mask. Brooks worries how they&#8217;re going to enforce the rule, which the coffee shop plans to keep in place, now that Texas&#8217; governor lifted the statewide mask mandate.</p>
<p>“We are gearing up for the emotional toll that this is going to take,” said the 25-year-old barista, who started working for the coffee shop in November while looking for a job in education. “The people who don&#8217;t want to wear them are still going to fight&#8230;and now they are going to have even more ammunition.”</p>
<p>Square Books in Oxford, Mississippi, home of the University of Mississippi, will require masks and allow only eight customers at a time. Although General Manager Lyn Roberts believes the rules will make many customers feel safe, bookstore employee Paul Fyke said he observed a change in Oxford almost as soon as the Board of Aldermen chose to follow the governor&#8217;s lead and did away with the college town&#8217;s mask mandate.</p>
<p>“I mean, really, even on the drive home, you can kind of already see there were places where, for a lot of people, it was triumph,” he said on Thursday, the day after Oxford&#8217;s mask requirement ended. “They were happy to be removing them.”</p>
<p>Still, some workers are cautiously hopeful that fewer restrictions will bring more customers, tips and job security after a year short on all three.</p>
<p>In San Francisco, where the mayor last week announced the return of indoor dining and the reopening of movie theaters and gyms, Dino Keres had no qualms about serving drinks to customers bellying up to the bar inside Sam&#8217;s Grill.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s partly because he was about to get his second vaccine dose, but also because nobody on staff was infected when indoor dining was briefly permitted last fall. What’s more, masks are required unless people are eating, and indoor seating is limited to 25% of capacity.</p>
<p>“We have already went through this once, and now the timing feels about right to try it again,” Keres said Thursday.</p>
<p>Ro Hart, an assistant general manager and hostess at Tony’s Pizza Napoletana in San Francisco, said the return of indoor dining in the city provoked a mixture of joy and anxiety.</p>
<p>“We are happy to be bringing in more revenue, but we are little nervous, too, because we have to be more stringent about making sure everyone keeps their masks on when they’re not eating,” Hart said, adding that she would be far more worried if San Francisco didn&#8217;t require masks.</p>
<p>“We feel for our brothers and sisters at all those restaurants in Texas,” she said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877775</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/07/200710_disney_employees_face_masks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200710_Disney_employees_face_masks</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bloody Sunday memorial honors late civil rights giants</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/bloody-sunday-memorial-honors-late-civil-rights-giants/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 13:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877771</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SELMA, Ala. (AP) — Activists who gathered virtually and in person to commemorate a pivotal day in the civil rights struggle that became known as...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SELMA, Ala. (AP) — Activists who gathered virtually and in person to commemorate a pivotal day in the civil rights struggle that became known as Bloody Sunday called on people to continue the fight for voting rights as they also honored giants of the civil rights movement, including the late U.S. Rep. John Lewis, who died last year.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.selmajubilee.com/">Selma Bridge Crossing Jubilee</a> marks the 56th anniversary of Bloody Sunday — the day on March 7, 1965, that civil rights marchers were brutally beaten by law enforcement officers on Selma’s Edmund Pettus Bridge. Lewis, the Rev. Joseph Lowery, the Rev. C.T. Vivian, and attorney Bruce Boynton were the late civil rights leaders honored on Sunday.</p>
<p>The day became a turning point in the fight for voting rights. Footage of the beatings helped galvanize support for passage of the Voting Rights Act of 1965.</p>
<p>This year’s commemoration comes as some states seek to roll back expanded early and mail-in voting access and efforts have been unsuccessful to restore a key section of the Voting Rights Act that required states with a history of discrimination to get federal approval for any changes to voting procedures.</p>
<p>Many speakers throughout the day&#8217;s events emphasized the need for continued activism to protect voting access.</p>
<p>“Voter suppression is still alive and well,&#8221; said U.S. Rep. Teri Sewell, a Democrat who represents the 7th Congressional District which includes Selma. “It reminds us that progress is elusive and every generation must fight and fight again.”</p>
<p>Sewell spoke during a video that featured comments from activists, mayors, members of Congress and others about the historic anniversary. Later, organizers played video footage of activists, many who had been part of the original Bloody Sunday events in 1965, crossing the bridge once again. They wore masks and in keeping with social distancing requirements designed to stop the coronavirus, spread out across the bridge as they walked.</p>
<p>The event typically brings thousands of people to Selma. However, most of the events were held virtually this year because of the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
<p>The annual <a href="http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?oeidk=a07ehmlomcwef65374d&amp;llr=jlhbevkab">Martin &amp; Coretta King Unity Breakfast</a> was held as a drive-in event. The outdoor event included some in-person speakers such as Rev. Bernard LaFayette, and the founders of the group Black Voters Matter. Cliff Albright, one of the group&#8217;s founders, spoke about the continued need to fight for voter access.</p>
<p>“The movement is not over,&#8221; he said as people in their cars honked in support. “What we are asking folks today is for us to commit to that moment, for us to commit to this movement.”</p>
<p>Others spoke via video link or in prerecorded messages. President Joe Biden appeared via a prerecorded message, in which he announced an executive order aimed at promoting voting access.</p>
<p>“Every eligible voter should be able to vote and have that vote counted,” Biden said. “If you have the best ideas, you have nothing to hide. Let the people vote.”</p>
<p>Lowery, a charismatic and fiery preacher, is often considered the dean of the civil rights veterans and led the Southern Christian Leadership Conference.</p>
<p>Vivian began organizing sit-ins against segregation in the 1940s and later joined forces with the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. In 1965, Vivian led dozens of marchers to a courthouse in Selma, confronting the local sheriff on the courthouse steps and telling him the marchers should be allowed to register to vote. The sheriff responded by punching Vivian in the head.</p>
<p>Boynton was arrested for entering the white part of a racially segregated bus station in Virginia, launching a chain reaction that ultimately helped to bring about the abolition of Jim Crow laws in the South. Boynton contested his conviction, and his appeal resulted in a U.S. Supreme Court decision that prohibited bus station segregation.</p>
<p>His case inspired the Freedom Riders of 1961 — a group of young activists who went on bus rides throughout the South to test whether court-ruled desegregation was actually being enforced. They faced violence from white mobs and arrest by local authorities.</p>
<p>Organizers acknowledged the fallen civil rights leaders and planned to lay wreaths at the bridge in their honor.</p>
<p>The march across the Selma bridge was sparked by events in nearby Marion, where a Black man had been killed by a white Alabama state trooper during peaceful protests for voting rights. Jimmie Lee Jackson, a 26-year-old church deacon, was shot while trying to protect his mother from being hurt and died eight days later. In response, activists in Marion and Selma gathered for a march on March 7, their goal the state capital in Montgomery.</p>
<p>Although the Jackson case occurred in 1965, it has particular resonance in 2021 as the state of Minnesota prepares to try former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin in the death of George Floyd, an African American. Floyd died after Chauvin, who is white, pressed his knee onto Floyd’s neck while Floyd was held face-down on the ground in handcuffs, saying he couldn’t breathe. Body camera footage indicates Chauvin’s knee was on Floyd’s neck for about nine minutes. Floyd was later pronounced dead at a hospital.</p>
<p>Jury selection begins Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877771</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/200301_rep_john_lewis_selma.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/200301_rep_john_lewis_selma.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/03/200301_rep_john_lewis_selma.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200301_Rep_John_Lewis_Selma</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>12-year-old arrested for 4 carjacking incidents in Washington, DC</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/12-year-old-arrested-for-4-carjacking-incidents-in-washington-dc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 22:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; A 12-year-old boy was arrested Thursday evening after a series of attempted armed carjackings and one successful one in Washington, DC. All four...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; A 12-year-old boy was arrested Thursday evening after a series of attempted armed carjackings and one successful one in Washington, DC.</p>
<p>All four incidents happened in the span of one hour, according to a Metropolitan Police Department (MPD) <a href="https://mpdc.dc.gov/release/arrest-made-and-additional-suspect-sought-armed-carjacking-gun-offenses-fifth-district" target="_blank" rel="noopener">news release.</a></p>
<p>The boy was arrested by the MPD on the same day and charged with four counts of armed carjacking, the news release said. Police are still searching for a second suspect who was seen on a surveillance camera.</p>
<p>The incidents began around 6:30 p.m., when a rideshare driver was picking up a customer and was approached by the two suspects. One of the suspects pointed a gun at him from the driver&#8217;s side door and ordered him to get out of the vehicle, according to an incident report. The other suspect grabbed the victim&#8217;s phone.</p>
<p>The driver refused to exit the car and was able to drive away.</p>
<p>About 45 minutes later, the suspects approached another rideshare driver, according to an incident report. One suspect opened the front passenger door and waved a handgun at the driver, demanding his car keys. The driver managed to drive away, and the suspects once again fled the scene, according to the incident report.</p>
<p>At around 7:20 p.m., the two suspects approached a man who was walking toward his car. One suspect pointed a handgun at the man and demanded the car keys. The other suspect pulled out a bag from the car and took a laptop before the pair fled the scene, according to an incident report.</p>
<p>Less than 10 minutes after the third carjacking, the suspects approached a woman who was sitting in her car. One suspect opened the driver&#8217;s side of the car, pointed a handgun at the woman and ordered her to get out of her car, according to police.</p>
<p>The woman said she was unable to understand due to a language barrier, an incident report said. A suspect then motioned to the woman to exit her car. The suspects drove away in the car, which was eventually recovered, police said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877466</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/180110-new-police-lights.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/180110-new-police-lights.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/02/180110-new-police-lights.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180110-new-police-lights</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pope, top Iraq Shiite cleric deliver message of coexistence</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/pope-top-iraq-shiite-cleric-deliver-message-of-coexistence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 18:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877352</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[PLAINS OF UR, Iraq (AP) — Pope Francis walked through a narrow alley in Iraq’s holy city of Najaf for a historic meeting with the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PLAINS OF UR, Iraq (AP) — Pope Francis walked through a narrow alley in Iraq’s holy city of Najaf for a historic meeting with the country’s top Shiite cleric, and together they delivered a powerful message of peaceful coexistence in a country still reeling from back-to-back conflicts over the past decade.</p>
<p>In a gesture both simple and profound, Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani welcomed Francis into his spartan home. Afterward, he said religious authorities have a role in protecting Iraq’s Christians, and that Christians should live in peace and enjoy the same rights as other Iraqis. The Vatican said Francis thanked al-Sistani for having “raised his voice in defense of the weakest and most persecuted” during some of the most violent times in Iraq’s recent history</p>
<p>Al-Sistani, 90, is one of the most senior clerics in Shiite Islam, and <a href="https://apnews.com/article/iraq-ali-al-sistani-pope-francis-saddam-hussein-59818e71b874766877b951f332bfeb8b">his rare but powerful political interventions have helped shape present-day Iraq</a>. He is a deeply revered figure in Shiite-majority Iraq and his opinions on religious and other matters are sought by Shiites worldwide.</p>
<p>Later in the day, the pope met with Iraqi religious leaders in the shadow of a symbol of the country’s ancient past — the 6,000-year-old ziggurat in the Plains of Ur, also the traditional birthplace of Abraham, the biblical patriarch revered by Jews, Christians and Muslims.</p>
<p>Such interfaith forums are a staple of Francis’ international trips. But in strife-torn Iraq the televised gathering of figures from across the country’s religious spectrum was nearly unheard of: From Shiite and Sunni Muslims to Christians, Yazidis and Zoroastrians and tiny, lesser known, ancient and esoteric faiths like the Kakai, a sect among ethnic Kurds, Mandaeans and Sabaean Mandaeans. Missing from the picture was a representative of Iraq’s once thriving, now nearly decimated Jewish community, though they were invited, the Vatican said.</p>
<p>Together, the day’s two main events gave symbolic and practical punch to the central message of Francis’ visit, calling for Iraq to embrace its diversity. It is a message he hopes can preserve the place of the thinning Christian population in the tapestry.</p>
<p>Still, it faces a tough sell in a country where every community has been traumatized by sectarian bloodshed and discrimination and where politicians have tied their power to sectarian interests.</p>
<p>In al-Sistani, Francis sought the help of an ascetic, respected figure who is immersed in those sectarian identities but is also a powerful voice standing above them.</p>
<p>Their meeting in al-Sistani’s humble home, the first ever between a pope and a grand ayatollah, was months in the making, with <a href="https://apnews.com/article/pope-ayatollah-meeting-preparation-iraq-6ebc225f98c0f711f4e86227df34d517">every detail painstakingly negotiated beforehand</a>.</p>
<p>Early Saturday, the 84-year-old pontiff, travelling in a bullet-proof Mercedes-Benz, pulled up along Najaf’s narrow and column-lined Rasool Street, which culminates at the golden-domed Imam Ali Shrine, one of the most revered sites in Shiite Islam.</p>
<p>He then walked the few meters (yards) down an alley to al-Sistani’s home. As a masked Francis entered the doorway, a few white doves were released in a sign of peace. He emerged just under an hour later, still limping from an apparent flare-up of sciatica nerve pain that makes walking difficult.</p>
<p>A religious official in Najaf called the 40-minute meeting “very positive.” He spoke on condition of anonymity because he was not authorized to brief media.</p>
<p>The official said al-Sistani, who normally remains seated for visitors, stood to greet Francis at the door of his room — a rare honor. The pope removed his shoes before entering al-Sistani’s room and was served tea and a plastic bottle of water.</p>
<p>Al-Sistani and Francis sat close to one another, without masks. Al-Sistani spoke for most of the meeting, the official said. Al-Sistani, who rarely appears in public or even on television, wore black robes and a black turban, in simple contrast to Francis’ all-white cassock.</p>
<p>The official said there was some concern about the fact that the pope had met with so many people the day before. Francis has received the coronavirus vaccine but al-Sistani has not. The aging ayatollah, who underwent surgery for a fractured thigh last year, looked tired.</p>
<p>After the meeting ended, Francis paused before leaving the room to have a last look, the official said.</p>
<p>In a statement issued by his office afterward, al-Sistani affirmed that Christians should “live like all Iraqis, in security and peace and with full constitutional rights.” He pointed out the “role that the religious authority plays in protecting them, and others who have also suffered injustice and harm in the events of past years.”</p>
<p>Al-Sistani wished Francis and the followers of the Catholic Church happiness and thanked him for taking the trouble to visit him in Najaf, the statement said.</p>
<p>Iraqis cheered the meeting, and the prime minister responded to it by declaring March 6 a National Day of Tolerance and Coexistence in Iraq.</p>
<p>”We welcome the pope’s visit to Iraq and especially to the holy city of Najaf and his meeting with Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani,” said Najaf resident Haidar Al-Ilyawi. “It is a historic visit and hope it will be good for Iraq and the Iraqi people.”</p>
<p>Iraq’s Christians, battered by violence and discrimination, hope a show of solidarity from al-Sistani will help secure their place in Iraq and ease intimidation from Shiite militiamen against their community.</p>
<p>Al-Sistani’s voice is a powerful one, often for moderation.</p>
<p>After the 2003 U.S.-led invasion, his opinions forced American administrators to alter their transition plans, and his approval opened the way for Iraq’s Shiites to participate in force in post-Saddam Hussein elections. In 2019, as anti-government demonstrations gripped the country, his sermon led to the resignation of then-prime minister Adil Abdul-Mahdi.</p>
<p>But his word is not law. After 2003, he repeatedly preached calm and restraint as the Shiite majority came under attack by Sunni extremists. Yet brutal Shiite reprisals against Sunni civilians fed a years-long cycle of sectarian violence.</p>
<p>His 2014 fatwa, or religious edict, calling on able-bodied men to join the security forces in fighting the Islamic State group helped ensure the extremists’ defeat. But it also swelled the ranks of Shiite militias, many closely tied to Iran and now blamed for discrimination against Sunnis and Christians.</p>
<p>Later, Pope Francis evoked the common reverence for Abraham to speak against religious violence at the inter-faith gathering at the Plains of Ur, near the southern city of Nasiriyah.</p>
<p>“From this place, where faith was born, from the land of our father Abraham, let us affirm that God is merciful and that the greatest blasphemy is to profane his name by hating our brothers and sisters,” Francis said. “Hostility, extremism and violence are not born of a religious heart: they are betrayals of religion.”</p>
<p>The Vatican said Iraqi Jews were invited to the event but did not attend, without providing further details. Iraq’s ancient Jewish community was decimated in the 20th century by violence and mass emigration fueled by the Arab-Israeli conflict, and only a handful remain.</p>
<p>Ali Thijeel, a Nasiriyah resident who attended the event, said he hoped the pope’s visit would encourage investment in the area to attract pilgrims and tourists. “This is what we were waiting for,” he said. “This is a message to the government and politicians. They should take care of this city and pay attention to our history.”</p>
<p>Francis’ visit — his first international trip since the start of the coronavirus pandemic — comes amid a surge in COVID-19 cases in Iraq. Despite concern about infections, Francis celebrated Mass in a packed, stuffy Chaldean Catholic Cathedral later Saturday in Baghdad that featured chanted Scripture readings and a maskless choir singing hymns.</p>
<p>“Love is our strength, the source of strength for those of our brothers and sisters who here too have suffered prejudice, indignities, mistreatment and persecutions for the name of Jesus,” Francis told the faithful, who did wear masks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877352</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/AP21065258719098.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/AP21065258719098.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/AP21065258719098.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">APTOPIX Iraq Pope</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>California OKs reopening of ball parks, Disneyland</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/california-oks-reopening-of-ball-parks-disneyland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877338</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California has cleared a path for fans to hit the stands at opening-day baseball games and return to Disneyland nearly a year after coronavirus restrictions shuttered major entertainment spots.</p>
<p>The state on Friday relaxed guidelines for reopening outdoor venues as a fall and winter surge seemed to be ending, with COVID-19 infection rates, hospitalizations and deaths plummeting and vaccination rates rising.</p>
<p>New public health rules would allow live concerts at stadiums and sports arenas to reopen with limited attendance April 1. Amusement parks also will be permitted to reopen in counties that have fallen from the state&#8217;s purple tier — the most restrictive — to the red tier.</p>
<p>In all cases, park capacities will be limited, and COVID-19 safety rules such as mask-wearing requirements will apply.</p>
<p>The move followed a week of milestones, with California ramping up vaccinations for the poorest neighborhoods, counties reopening more businesses and Gov. Gavin Newsom passing a measure aimed at encouraging schools that have restricted students to online learning to reopen classrooms this month.</p>
<p>“Steady opening is consistent with the data. As cases decline, we want to return to work and school,” said Dr. Jeffrey Klausner, clinical professor of preventive medicine at the University of Southern California. “Outdoor activities in particular have always been low risk. Opening these sites makes sense.”</p>
<p>The reopening can&#8217;t come too soon for Kenny King Jr., a resident of Pleasant Hill in the San Francisco Bay Area who became an annual Disneyland passholder a decade ago. He typically takes his family to the Southern California park five times a year, but the last visit was just over a year ago for his birthday.</p>
<p>King, 38, said he&#8217;s excited to return with his 8-year-old daughter, who had just started enjoying rides such as Big Thunder Mountain Railroad and Space Mountain, and to take his 2-year-old son, who was mesmerized by the lights and sounds when he visited last year.</p>
<p>“That’s something that we just made our family thing — Disney trips,” King said. “We’ll sit there at the house sometimes and we’ll be like ‘man, I just miss Disneyland.&#8217; ”</p>
<p>Also applauding were the thousands of workers who were laid off by Disneyland, Universal Studios Hollywood, Knott&#8217;s Berry Farm and other big locations. Ten thousand lost their jobs alone at Disneyland and its related attractions in Orange County, not to mention the knock-on effect to nearby restaurants and hotels.</p>
<p>Andrea Zinder, president of the local United Food and Commercial Workers Union that represents Disney workers, said employees are “excited to go back to work and provide Californians with a bit more magic in their lives.”</p>
<p>Most of the major theme parks are in Southern California, which is still in the purple category. However, Los Angeles, Orange and San Diego counties were expecting to reopen within the next few weeks as their COVID-19 numbers fall.</p>
<p>Only 16 of 58 counties currently are in the red tier, and two small counties are in the orange tier. None are yet in the yellow tier, the lowest and least restrictive.</p>
<p>Theme parks in the red tier will be limited to 15% capacity.</p>
<p>Outdoor sports will be limited to 100 people in the purple tier but will increase up to 67% in the yellow tier.</p>
<p>The San Diego Padres, Los Angeles Angels and Oakland Athletics all announced they will have fans in the stands for opening day April 1. The Los Angeles Dodgers and San Francisco Giants both start their seasons on the road and said they would announce their plans later.</p>
<p>Teams and event organizers can only sell tickets regionally in the purple tier. In the other tiers, teams and organizers can sell tickets to anyone living in California. No concessions will be allowed in the purple tier, while in others, concession sales will only be available at seats.</p>
<p>Richard Haick of San Pablo, California, already bought ticket vouchers for the Oakland A’s return and hopes to take his 10-year-old son to a game soon. His son plays Little League baseball and is very excited to attend games.</p>
<p>“It’s nice to have, even in a reduced capacity, some sense of normal,” said Haick, a 45-year-old photographer.</p>
<p>The quicker pace of reopening is tied to a new plan to vaccinate California’s most vulnerable residents. Once 2 million people across 400 ZIP codes in the most disadvantaged neighborhoods receive at least one vaccine dose, it will be easier for counties to exit the state’s most restrictive tier. Once 4 million people in those neighborhoods are vaccinated, counties will be able to open up even more.</p>
<p>It all puts California in a drastically different position than a year ago, when Gov. Gavin Newsom imposed the statewide stay-at-home order that restricted travel, shuttered businesses and forced millions of people onto unemployment. California still has among the most severe restrictions of any state and continues to discourage out-of-state visitors.</p>
<p>The state is pinning its hopes of a full reopening on inoculating enough of its 40 million residents to halt widespread COVID-19 infections.</p>
<p>More than 10 million doses had been given only three months since the first shot was given, the Department of Public Health said.</p>
<p>Just over 3 million people have been fully vaccinated, or about 10% of the population 16 and older.</p>
<p>There are hopeful signs. This week, the seven-day average rate of positive results from tests dropped this week to 2.2%, a record low.</p>
<p>Although pressure has been building to reopen the economy, health officials said the changes in guidelines were a cautious and measured rather than a wholesale approach.</p>
<p>“We will &#8230;. keep our foot on the brake, not the gas, our eyes on the road, hands on the wheel and navigate based on data and science,” said Dr. Mark Ghaly, secretary of the state Health and Human Services Agency.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877338</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219189~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/69ce6077-0525-4857-99c8-c24583775e15/86fda1f8-73b9-4fa2-869f-c1cc14165bf5/main.mp4*~hmac=9db0e975a924b2cb465a0111975a103e3c17569f6dd83db5e8e6be277872acd9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/08/sleeping-beauty-castle-disneyland.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">sleeping beauty castle disneyland</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Father arrested in India for beheading his 17-year-old daughter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/father-arrested-in-india-for-beheading-his-17-year-old-daughter-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 17:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Police in India&#8217;s northern Uttar Pradesh state have arrested a man who confessed to beheading his teenage daughter. Sarvesh Kumar was arrested as he was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Police in India&#8217;s northern <a href="https://cnn.com/2020/09/29/asia/india-dalit-woman-gang-rape-murder-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Uttar Pradesh</a> state have arrested a man who confessed to beheading his teenage daughter.</p>
<p>Sarvesh Kumar was arrested as he was walking toward a police station in Hardoi district on Wednesday night, carrying the severed head of his 17-year-old daughter.</p>
<p>&#8220;He was making his way on foot to the police station to confess what he had done,&#8221; a spokesperson for Hardoi Police told CNN on Friday.</p>
<p>&#8220;He told police he had seen his daughter with a young man that he believes she was seeing, which made him angry as he was against it,&#8221; the spokesperson added.</p>
<p>As Kumar, a vegetable seller from Pandetara village, made the one-mile walk from his home to the police station, local passersby alerted the police, who stopped him and began to film him.</p>
<p>During this time, according to the police spokesperson, Kumar told authorities about his daughter&#8217;s relationship, saying he had found her alone at home, locked her in a room and severed her head using a knife.</p>
<p>&#8220;Considering the situation, he was calm. He wasn&#8217;t crying or hysterical. When the policemen were speaking to him, they asked him to place his daughter&#8217;s head on the ground and to sit down, which he listened to without arguing back,&#8221; the police spokesperson told CNN.</p>
<p>Kumar is currently in custody where he continues to be questioned, the spokesperson added. A list of charges will be compiled once the investigation has been completed. He will have access to a public lawyer once he has been formally charged, and he will remain in custody until the trial, police said.</p>
<p>India reported 24 so-called &#8220;<a href="https://cnn.com/2020/05/18/asia/pakistan-honor-killing-hnk-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">honor killings</a>&#8221; in 2019, according to statistics from the country&#8217;s National Crime Records Bureau.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877334</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_016d0742c0ff0ffc22baa7b9427273b3-h_18cca017ffe6a0a2b1c6a9bad8954c75.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_016d0742c0ff0ffc22baa7b9427273b3-h_18cca017ffe6a0a2b1c6a9bad8954c75.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_016d0742c0ff0ffc22baa7b9427273b3-h_18cca017ffe6a0a2b1c6a9bad8954c75.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Hardoi, India</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;We&#8217;re walking into the mouth of the monster&#8217; by loosening Covid-19 restrictions, expert says</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/were-walking-into-the-mouth-of-the-monster-by-loosening-covid-19-restrictions-expert-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877317</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; More states are relaxing measures to protect against Covid-19 as variants circulate in the United States &#8212; a combination that means &#8220;we&#8217;re walking into the mouth of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; More states are<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/05/health/us-coronavirus-friday/index.html"> relaxing measures</a> to protect <a href="https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2020/health/coronavirus-us-maps-and-cases/">against Covid-19</a> as variants circulate in the United States &#8212; a combination that means &#8220;we&#8217;re walking into the mouth of the monster,&#8221; an infectious disease expert said.</p>
<p>A variant first identified in the UK has now been reported in 2,672 cases in 46 states as of Thursday, according to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. And it is spreading quickly.</p>
<p>&#8220;We literally are sitting on top of that, at a time when instead of actually getting better prepared for it, we&#8217;re opening up and inviting the virus in,&#8221; said Michael Osterholm, director of the Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy at the University of Minnesota.</p>
<p>&#8220;Right now, that (UK variant) is about to take off the United States,&#8221; Osterholm told <a href="https://www.cnn.com/shows/the-lead">CNN&#8217;s Jake Tapper.</a> &#8220;A number of states have seen it go from 1 or 2% of the viruses identified, to now over 20 to 30%.&#8221;</p>
<p>This week, <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/03/politics/greg-abbott-texas-criticism-coronavirus-handling/index.html">Texas </a>and Mississippi joined the list of states to remove mandates for citizens to wear masks and expanded capacity for businesses.</p>
<p>With vaccine eligibility opening up to most US adults by the summer, support for measures to protect against the virus is waning, according to a new survey.</p>
<p>Although less than a third of people said there should be fewer measures, support for additional restrictions has been on the decline since November, according to new research from the Pew Research Center.</p>
<p>But health experts say the road to herd immunity still has a long way ahead, and masks and other restrictions are still crucial to managing the pandemic.</p>
<p>A new CDC study demonstrates &#8220;that masks work,&#8221; CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said during a White House Covid-19 briefing on Friday.</p>
<p>&#8220;You have decreases in cases and deaths when you wear masks and you have increases in cases and deaths when you have in-person restaurant dining, and so we would advocate for policies &#8212; certainly while we&#8217;re at this plateau of a high number of cases &#8212; that would listen to that public health science,&#8221; Walensky said.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>States range on loosening restrictions</h3>
<p>As the US moves closer to widespread vaccinations, many states are changing their policies around Covid-19 restrictions.</p>
<p>In Maine, Gov. Janet Mills said Friday the state will continue to require masks, but she announced a new framework to slowly reopen the state. By March 26, capacity for indoor gatherings in the state will increase to 50% and outdoor will increase to 75%.</p>
<p>And in West Virginia, beginning Saturday, some businesses including restaurants, bars, gyms and museums can open with 100% seating capacity, but social distancing will still be required, Gov. Jim Justice said Friday.</p>
<p>In Texas, any business will be allowed to open 100% beginning March 10, and the order for residents to wear masks has been lifted.</p>
<p>Not all state leaders feel comfortable with the changes.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m deeply concerned about states that lift the mask mandate because what you&#8217;re doing is sending a signal that it&#8217;s not important anymore, and that is not true. In fact, it is just as important as ever,&#8221; North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper said.</p>
<p>&#8220;I would encourage my fellow governors and local officials who are making decisions in some states to keep the mask mandate, to show good examples and to continue doing responsible things.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Detroit mayor declines Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine allocation</h3>
<p>Many experts have celebrated the authorization of the third coronavirus vaccine: Johnson &amp; Johnson&#8217;s, which is a single shot and is stored at temperatures more convenient for transportation and storage.</p>
<p>But there has been some pushback.</p>
<p>Detroit Mayor <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/04/health/detroit-mayor-johnson-and-johnson-vaccine/index.html">Mike Duggan on Thursday said the city declined</a> an initial allocation of the newly authorized vaccine.</p>
<p>Duggan turned down the shipment because the city is able to meet current demand with its supply of the Pfizer/BioNTech and Moderna vaccines &#8212; even as his administration expanded vaccine eligibility Thursday to residents ages 50 and older with chronic medical conditions.</p>
<p>All three vaccines are highly effective at preventing serious illness from Covid-19, and health officials have urged people to take any Covid-19 vaccine they are offered.</p>
<p>&#8220;The day may come in March or April when every single Moderna and Pfizer is committed, and we still have people who need a vaccine. And at that point we will set up a Johnson &amp; Johnson center. I don&#8217;t see that in the next couple of weeks,&#8221; Duggan said.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>CDC guidance for the vaccinated</h3>
<p>CDC guidance for people who have been vaccinated is coming soon, Walensky said. The guidance had been expected to release this week.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our goal and what is most important is that people who have been vaccinated and those not yet vaccinated are able to understand the steps they can take to protect themselves and their loved ones,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>More than 82 million vaccine doses have been given out in the US, and after a year of life turned upside down, many want to know what the future holds.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think people need practical advice about how to go about their everyday lives,&#8221; said Julia Marcus, an infectious disease epidemiologist at Harvard. &#8220;I think without guidance, people may make decisions that are not informed.&#8221;</p>
<p>While the guidelines will not give the vaccinated permission to start living like it&#8217;s 2019 again, according to a Biden administration official, the guidelines do offer some hope that the end of total social isolation is near.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877317</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/coronavirus.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">coronavirus</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York cinemas reopen, brightening outlook for theaters</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/new-york-cinemas-reopen-brightening-outlook-for-theaters/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — After growing cobwebs for nearly a year, movie theaters in New York City reopen Friday, returning film titles to Manhattan marquees...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — After growing cobwebs for nearly a year, movie theaters in New York City reopen Friday, returning film titles to Manhattan marquees that had for the last 12 months instead read messages like “Wear a mask” and “We’ll be back soon.”</p>
<p>Shortly after noon at the Angelika Film Center on Houston Street, Holly Stillman was already feeling emotional coming out of the first New York showing of Lee Isaac Chung’s tender family drama “Minari.” “My mask is drenched,” she said.</p>
<p>But she was equally overwhelmed by being back in a cinema. Though Stillman feared the experience would be too restrictive because of COVID-19 protocols, she instead found it euphoric.</p>
<p>“It was just you and the movie screen,” said Stillman. “It was wonderful to smell the popcorn as soon as I got into the theater — even though I don’t eat popcorn.”</p>
<p>Less than half of movie theaters are open nationwide, but reopenings are quickening. Theaters in many other areas reopened last summer around the release of Christopher Nolan’s “Tenet,” but that attempted comeback fizzled. Throughout, theaters remained shut in the five boroughs. For a year almost to the date, one of the world’s foremost movie capitals stayed dark.</p>
<p>For a theatrical business that has been punished by the pandemic, the resumption of moviegoing in New York — is a crucial first step in revival.</p>
<p>“It’s a symbolic moment,” said Michael Barker, co-president of the New York-based Sony Pictures Classics, which on Friday released the Oscar contenders “The Father” and “The Truffle Hunters” in Manhattan theaters. “It says that there is hope for the theatrical world to reactivate itself.”</p>
<p>For some moviegoers who consider the big screen the only way to see a movie, the long-in-coming day had almost religious significance.</p>
<p>“Moviegoing for me is like going to church,” said JM Vargas, who had tickets Friday to “Minari,” “The Last Dragon” and “Chaos Walking.” “I’ve been waiting a year to go back to church.”</p>
<p>Cinemas in the city are currently operating at only 25% capacity, with a maximum of 50 per each auditorium. As in other places, mask wearing is mandatory, seats are blocked out and air filters have been upgraded.</p>
<p>Many theaters were caught off guard when Gov. Andrew Cuomo said cinemas could, under those conditions, reopen. Some of the city’s prominent theaters, including the Film Forum, the Alamo Drafthouse, the Metrograph and Regal Cinemas were targeting openings in the coming weeks. Some needed more time to prepare. After sitting dormant all winter, the Cinema Village in Manhattan two weeks earlier burst a pipe, flooding the lobby — one last bit of bad luck in a grueling year.</p>
<p>“This was the worst horror movie. I don’t think any Hollywood director could have dreamed it up,” said Nicolas Nicolaou, owner of the Cinema Village and theaters in Queens and New York. “We didn’t realize we’d be 100% shutdown for this long.”</p>
<p>New York, along with Los Angeles (where theaters are still closed), is one of the top movie markets. For smaller films, it’s a vital epicenter of word-of-mouth. For blockbusters, it’s a lucrative necessity. Without New York or Los Angeles open, Hollywood studios have pushed most of their larger productions until more theaters are open, or they’ve steered films to streaming services.</p>
<p>“The New York opening is very significant to the theater business in New York, in the nation and in the globe,” says John Fithian, president of the National Association of Theater Owners. “We in the movie theater business live off of movies that play all around the country and all around the world. We keep seeing those movies leave the theatrical release schedule to move to later dates because there just haven’t been enough markets. New York is the most important of those markets.”</p>
<p>Lately, with President Biden’s prediction that every adult can be vaccinated by the end of May, the outlook for theaters has been brightening for the first time in a long time. Last weekend, “Tom &amp; Jerry” overperformed at the box office with $14.1 million in ticket sales, even while it streamed on HBO Max. Though Universal Pictures pushed the “Fast &amp; Furious” sequel “F9” from late May to late June, other movies have moved up on the calendar, reversing the postponement tide.</p>
<p>Sony Pictures said it will release “Peter Rabbit 2: The Runaway” in May. Paramount Pictures’ “A Quiet Place II” moved into the May 28 date vacated by “F9.” The Walt Disney Co.’s “Black Widow” currently remains slated for May 7. Adding to the optimism: Southern California theaters are expected to reopen over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>“It’s not that we’re going back to record-breaking business this summer,” said Fithian. “We’re going to crawl, then we’re going to walk and then we’re going to run. It’s going to take into 2022 before sustained profitability comes back into the business.”</p>
<p>But at least on Friday, New York’s cinema lobbies were, if not crowded, again bustling. Sold-out signs for the evening adorned box-office windows. Even a little star power returned. Liam Neeson was to stop by the AMC at Lincoln Square to introduce “The Marksman.”</p>
<p>At the IFC Center in Greenwich Village, masked moviegoers flocked to films to play catch up — even if the movies were streaming. IFC is hosting a four-week “What’d We Miss?” series of movies the theater couldn’t play over the last 12 months, including “First Cow” and “MLK/FBI.”</p>
<p>“We’re used to being present for the birth of these movies for New York audiences when they move into the public realm,” said John Vanco, senior vice president of the IFC Center. The circumstances, he granted, weren’t ideal. But they were better than nothing. “I don’t look at 25% as being not good enough,” said Vanco. “I look at it as better than 0%.”</p>
<p>At the IFC, Tykon Herman settled in for “Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom,” and had tickets for a 5 p.m. of “The Trial of the Chicago 7.”</p>
<p>“I’m one of the very few that don’t have Netflix,” said Herman, laughing. “I’m just old-fashioned. I’ve loved the theater experience from the time I saw ‘E.T.’ It’s not going to be the same but sitting down in front of this screen makes me feel like things may be getting back to normal soon.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877232</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/09/150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">150724_movie_theater_auditorium_graphic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Europe staggers as infectious variants power virus surge</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/europe-staggers-as-infectious-variants-power-virus-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In a matter of just days, 45 children and 14 staff members had tested positive.</p>
<p>Genetic analysis confirmed what officials already suspected: The highly contagious coronavirus variant first identified in England was racing through the community, a densely packed city of nearly 40,000 with a chemical plant and a Pirelli bicycle tire factory a 15-minute drive from the heart of Milan.</p>
<p>“This demonstrates that the virus has a sort of intelligence. &#8230; We can put up all the barriers in the world and imagine that they work, but in the end, it adapts and penetrates them,’’ lamented Bollate Mayor Francesco Vassallo.</p>
<p>Bollate was the first city in Lombardy, the northern region that has been the epicenter in each of Italy’s three surges, to be sealed off from neighbors because of virus variants that the World Health Organization says are powering another uptick in infections across Europe. The variants also include versions first identified in South Africa and Brazil.</p>
<p>Europe recorded 1 million new COVID-19 cases last week, an increase of 9% from the previous week and a reversal that ended a six-week decline in new infections, WHO said Thursday.</p>
<p>“The spread of the variants is driving the increase, but not only,’’ said Dr. Hans Kluge, WHO regional director for Europe, citing “also the opening of society, when it is not done in a safe and a controlled manner.”</p>
<p>The variant first found in the U.K. is spreading significantly in 27 European countries monitored by WHO and is dominant in at least 10 countries: Britain, Denmark, Italy, Ireland, Germany, France, the Netherlands, Israel, Spain and Portugal.</p>
<p>It is up to 50% more transmissible than the virus that surged last spring and again in the fall, making it more adept at thwarting measures that were previously effective, WHO experts warned. Scientists have concluded that it is also more deadly.</p>
<p>“That is why health systems are struggling more now,” Kluge said. “It really is at a tipping point. We have to hold the fort and be very vigilant.”</p>
<p>In Lombardy, which bore the brunt of Italy’s spring surge, intensive care wards are again filling up, with more than two-thirds of new positive tests being the UK variant, health officials said.</p>
<p>After putting two provinces and some 50 towns on a modified lockdown, Lombardy&#8217;s regional governor announced tightened restrictions Friday and closed classrooms for all ages. Cases in Milan schools alone surged 33% in a week, the provincial health system&#8217;s chief said.</p>
<p>The situation is dire in the Czech Republic, which this week registered a record-breaking total of nearly 8,500 patients hospitalized with COVID-19. Poland is opening temporary hospitals and imposing a partial lockdown as the U.K. variant has grown from 10% of all infections in February to 25% now.</p>
<p>Two patients from hard-hit Slovakia were expected to arrive Saturday for treatment in Germany, where authorities said they had offered to take in 10 patients.</p>
<p>Kluge cited Britain’s experience as cause for optimism, noting that widespread restrictions and the introduction of the vaccine have helped tamp down the variants there and in Israel. The vaccine rollout in the European Union, by comparison, is lagging badly, mostly because of supply problems.</p>
<p>In Britain, the emergence of the more transmissible strain sent cases soaring in December and triggered a national lockdown in January. Cases have since plummeted, from about 60,000 a day in early January to about 7,000 a day now.</p>
<p>Still, a study shows the rate of decline slowing, and the British government says it will tread cautiously with plans to ease the lockdown. That process begins Monday with the reopening of schools. Infection rates are highest in people ages 13 to 17, and officials will watch closely to see whether the return to class brings a spike in infections.</p>
<p>While the U.K. variant is dominant in France, forcing lockdowns in the French Riviera city of Nice and the northern port of Dunkirk, the variant first detected in South Africa has emerged as the most prevalent in France&#8217;s Moselle region, which borders Germany and Luxembourg. It represents 55% of the virus circulating there.</p>
<p>Austria&#8217;s health minister said Saturday the U.K. variant is now dominant in his country. But the South Africa variant is also a concern in a district of Austria that extends from Italy to Germany, with Austrian officials announcing plans to vaccinate most of the 84,000 residents there to curb its spread. Austria is also requiring motorists along the Brenner highway, a major north-south route, to show negative test results.</p>
<p>The South Africa variant, now present in 26 European countries, is a source of particular concern because of doubts over whether the current vaccines are effective enough against it. The Brazilian variant, which appears capable of reinfecting people, has been detected in 15 European countries.</p>
<p>WHO and its partners are working to strengthen the genetic surveillance needed to track variants across the continent.</p>
<p>The mayor of Bollate has appealed to the regional governor to vaccinate all 40,000 residents immediately, though he expects to be told the vaccine supply is too tight.</p>
<p>Bollate has recorded 3,000 positive cases and 134 deaths — mostly among the elderly — since Italy was stricken a year ago. It took the brunt in the resurgence in November and December, and was caught completely off guard when the U.K. variant arrived, racing through school-age children before hitting families at home.</p>
<p>“People are starting to get tired that after a year there is no light at the end of the tunnel,” Vassallo said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877227</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/01/010221-coronavirus_UK-variant_B117.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">010221 coronavirus_UK variant_B117</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fauci, Gloria Estefan discuss COVID concerns on Instagram Live</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/fauci-gloria-estefan-discuss-covid-concerns-on-instagram-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gloria Estefan and Dr. Anthony Fauci engaged in a conversation about COVID-19 on Instagram Live. Fauci, President Joe Biden&#8217;s chief medical adviser, joined the singer...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gloria Estefan and Dr. Anthony Fauci engaged in a conversation about COVID-19 on Instagram Live.</p>
<p>Fauci, President Joe Biden&#8217;s chief medical adviser, joined the singer virtually for a discussion, Friday.</p>
<p>The two spoke on a range of topics relating to the coronavirus pandemic, including vaccination concerns and the efforts of the scientific community.</p>
<p>&#8220;Even though it took less than a year to get the vaccine, when it usually takes several years, that speed is a reflection of scientific advances,&#8221; said Fauci. &#8220;Safety was not compromised, nor was scientific integrity compromised.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fauci also took questions from commenters on other related topics, such as the benefits of the United States returning to the World Health Organization.</p>
<p>Anyone with questions and concerns about the coronavirus can call the Florida Department of Health&#8217;s 24-hour hotline at 1-866-779-6121.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876954</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a132b296-ff67-4b9f-a059-3a456e8a2e1d/13c1e4c6-be28-4847-9770-637c9b5201aa/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217319~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a132b296-ff67-4b9f-a059-3a456e8a2e1d/13c1e4c6-be28-4847-9770-637c9b5201aa/main.mp4*~hmac=532bc40f265b8c202e69c557f21067fe2bf7a131b8108d92295ed5d62cb28313' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Estefan_Fauci_Instagram_Live</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four sisters in their 80s and 90s reunited to get their COVID-19 vaccines together</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/four-sisters-in-their-80s-and-90s-reunited-to-get-their-covid-19-vaccines-together/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 23:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Four elderly sisters in New Jersey haven&#8217;t been able to have their regular get-togethers during the coronavirus pandemic, but they made an exception...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Four elderly sisters in New Jersey haven&#8217;t been able to have their regular get-togethers during the coronavirus pandemic, but they made an exception to get their Covid-19 vaccinations.</p>
<p>Edith Camp, 96, Bernice Cecil, 92, Nora McDonald, 86, and 84-year-old Rose Ramsey &#8212; got their second doses of the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine on Tuesday at Inspira Medical Center Mullica Hill, south of Philadelphia.</p>
<p><figure id="attachment_876939" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-876939" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color"><img loading="lazy" class="size-full wp-image-876939" src="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?quality=60&amp;strip=color" alt="" width="1024" height="630" srcset="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg 3000w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?resize=300,185 300w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?resize=768,473 768w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?resize=1024,630 1024w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?resize=1536,945 1536w, https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?resize=2048,1260 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-876939" class="wp-caption-text">[Courtesy: Inspira Health]</figcaption></figure>As children, they were known as the Langley sisters, and the four wore buttons with pictures of their other sisters &#8212; Pauline Taylor, who wasn&#8217;t able to come, and Doris Papiano, who died in 2011.</p>
<p>It was Cecil&#8217;s idea for them to get their shots together, according to Ramsey&#8217;s daughter Lori Goldsmid.</p>
<p>It &#8220;was my aunt Bernice&#8217;s idea to have them together, you know, for a little bit of support for each other because it&#8217;s scary,&#8221; Goldsmid told CNN.</p>
<p>It took some doing, but Goldsmid was able to arrange for them all to get their first dose at the same time.</p>
<p>&#8220;I was glad and relieved to get it over with and I wasn&#8217;t nervous at all,&#8221; Ramsey told Goldsmid.</p>
<p>They didn&#8217;t get much of a chance to talk on Tuesday because of all the media attention, but they agreed that the staff was all very nice.</p>
<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t believe so many people care about four old ladies getting their shots,&#8221; Camp said to her niece.</p>
<p>Before the pandemic, the five sisters saw each other regularly and they would all have lunch at least once a month.</p>
<p>Goldsmid said they&#8217;re excited to see each other in about 10-14 days once the vaccine has been in their systems long enough to give them the most protection.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re already trying to make plans at this point, whether we&#8217;re going to do it at someone&#8217;s house or see if we can get a room at a restaurant for lunch,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>They&#8217;ve been able to talk on the phone and on FaceTime, but they haven&#8217;t been able to get together or see other members of their large family since February of last year.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think the hardest part for some of them was not seeing their grandchildren at the same time as not being able to see their sisters,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I think it&#8217;s heartbreaking at that age not to be able to see any of your family.&#8221;</p>
<p>Goldsmid said the five sisters have more than 100 grandchildren, great-grandchildren and great-great-grandchildren between them.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876937</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_a16aaa635f7409864e384ff635af6faf-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76-e1614987404995.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_a16aaa635f7409864e384ff635af6faf-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76-e1614987404995.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_a16aaa635f7409864e384ff635af6faf-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76-e1614987404995.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_a16aaa635f7409864e384ff635af6faf-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76</media:title>
		</media:content>

		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_ac18fe2c32eba4591757f6e71b28c481-h_c70c64acdd6f58411fa593fd5904eb76.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image" />
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>3rd-degree murder count could be reinstated in Floyd&#8217;s death</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/3rd-degree-murder-count-could-be-reinstated-in-floyds-death/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 21:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The Minnesota Court of Appeals on Friday ordered a judge to reconsider adding a third-degree murder charge against a former Minneapolis police...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The Minnesota Court of Appeals on Friday ordered a judge to reconsider adding a third-degree murder charge against a former Minneapolis police officer charged in George Floyd’s death, handing a potential victory to prosecutors, but setting up a possible delay to a trial set to start next week.</p>
<p>A three-judge panel said Hennepin County District Judge Peter Cahill erred last fall when he rejected a prosecution motion to reinstate the third-degree murder charge against Derek Chauvin. The panel said Cahill should have followed the precedent set by the appeals court last month when it affirmed the third-degree murder conviction of former officer Mohamed Noor in the 2017 shooting death of Justine Ruszczyk Damond. The unarmed Australian woman had called 911 to report a possible sexual assault.</p>
<p>The appeals court sent the case back to Cahill for a ruling consistent with its ruling in the Noor case, giving the judge some leeway to consider other arguments that the defense might make against reinstating the charge.</p>
<p>&#8220;This court’s precedential opinion in Noor became binding authority on the date it was filed. The district court therefore erred by concluding that it was not bound by the principles of law set forth in Noor and by denying the state’s motion to reinstate the charge of third-degree murder on that basis,&#8221; the appeals court wrote.</p>
<p>It was not immediately clear if Friday&#8217;s ruling would force a delay in jury selection for Chauvin’s case, which is due to start Monday. He&#8217;s currently charged with second-degree murder and manslaughter. Prosecutors did not immediately return a message seeking comment on whether they would seek a delay. Chauvin’s attorney had no comment.</p>
<p>Chauvin has the option of appealing the ruling to the Minnesota Supreme Court, which would force Cahill to delay the trial, said Ted Sampsell-Jones, a criminal law expert at the Mitchell Hamline School of Law. But if Chauvin decides not to appeal, the professor added, “then Judge Cahill will almost certainly reinstate the third-degree charge.&#8221;</p>
<p>And if Chauvin decides not to appeal, Sampsell-Jones said, Cahill could still begin jury selection Monday, then decide in the next three weeks — before opening arguments — whether to reinstate the charge.</p>
<p>A reinstated third-degree murder count could increase the prosecution’s odds of getting a murder conviction.</p>
<p>“We believe the Court of Appeals decided this matter correctly,&#8221; Minnesota Attorney General Keith Ellison said in a statement. &#8220;We believe the charge of 3rd-degree murder, in addition to manslaughter and felony murder, reflects the gravity of the allegations against Mr. Chauvin. Adding this charge is an important step forward in the path toward justice. We look forward to presenting all charges to the jury in Hennepin County.”</p>
<p>Floyd, who was Black, died May 25 after Chauvin, who is white, pressed his knee on Floyd’s neck while he was handcuffed and pleading that he couldn’t breathe. In the wake of his death, civil unrest spiraled into violence locally. Protests spread worldwide and forced a painful reckoning on racial justice in the U.S.</p>
<p>With tensions growing over the looming trial, authorities have already surrounded the courthouse and nearby buildings in downtown Minneapolis with tall barriers of chain-link fencing and razor wire in case protests anticipated before, during and after the trial turn violent.</p>
<p>Cahill ruled last October that third-degree murder under Minnesota law requires proof that someone’s conduct was “eminently dangerous to others,” plural, not just to Floyd. Cahill said there was no evidence that Chauvin endangered anyone else and threw out the charge. But the Court of Appeals rejected similar legal reasoning in Noor’s case, ruling that a third-degree murder conviction can be sustained even if the action that caused a victim’s death was directed at just one person.</p>
<p>The appeals court rejected the argument by Chauvin&#8217;s attorney that the Noor ruling shouldn&#8217;t have the force of law unless and until it’s affirmed by the Minnesota Supreme Court, which will hear oral arguments in Noor’s appeal in June.</p>
<p>Three other former officers — Thomas Lane, J. Kueng and Tou Thao — are charged with aiding and abetting second-degree murder and manslaughter. They’re scheduled for trial in August. Prosecutors want to add charges of aiding and abetting third-degree murder against them, but that question will be resolved later.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876838</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Derek-Chauvin.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ae4778a5-0696-41d6-82d6-bb85bdee7ec5/a42a6f9a-c71b-46de-a12b-36d2cdada2f7/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219323~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ae4778a5-0696-41d6-82d6-bb85bdee7ec5/a42a6f9a-c71b-46de-a12b-36d2cdada2f7/main.mp4*~hmac=eb96fe34a8a4518537c60663ea93cc9047b320f56dbe0b39d332e2017c9dabbe' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Derek-Chauvin.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Derek-Chauvin.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Derek Chauvin</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Texas school district removes &#8216;chivalry&#8217; assignment that called for girls to dress &#8220;to please men&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/texas-school-district-removes-chivalry-assignment-that-called-for-girls-to-dress-to-please-men/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876812</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, Texas (AP) &#8212; A Texas school district has removed an assignment that called for girls to follow the &#8220;Rules of Chivalry,&#8221; including dressing &#8220;in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) &#8212; A Texas school district has removed an assignment that called for girls to follow the &#8220;Rules of Chivalry,&#8221; including dressing &#8220;in a feminine manner to please men&#8221; and to &#8220;not complain or whine.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.everythinglubbock.com/news/local-news/chivalry-homework-assignments-gains-negative-attention-online/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">KLBK-TV</a>, the assignment was to be completed this week by students at Shallowater High School and was shared in a private Facebook group. The assignment sparked online criticism of the district.</p>
<p>According to an image of the assignment, it was intended to &#8220;demonstrate to the school how the code of chivalry and standards set in the medieval concept of courtly love carries over into the modern day.&#8221;</p>
<p>The instructions said &#8220;ladies deemed worthy of the honor by the gentlemen&#8221; would receive 10 points for every signature they received as they completed each task. The tasks also included cooking for the boys in their class, walking &#8220;behind men daintily as if their feet were bound,&#8221; cleaning up after the boys and outside of the classroom, not &#8220;show intellectual superiority if it would offend the men around them.&#8221;</p>
<p>Shallowater Independent School District did not immediately respond to calls from The Associated Press for comment.</p>
<p>In a statement to the station, the school district said the assignment had been reviewed and &#8220;despite its historical context, it does not reflect our district and community values.&#8221; The assignment was addressed with the teacher and removed, according to the district&#8217;s statement.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876812</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/05/180501_dark_classroom_desks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/05/180501_dark_classroom_desks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/05/180501_dark_classroom_desks.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180501_dark_classroom_desks</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jeep boss says it may might drop Cherokee name</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/jeep-boss-says-it-may-might-drop-cherokee-name/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 19:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876752</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Jeep&#8217;s new boss says the company is open to dropping the name &#8220;Cherokee&#8221; from its vehicles in response to objections from the Cherokee...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Jeep&#8217;s new boss says the company is open to dropping the name &#8220;Cherokee&#8221; from its vehicles in response to objections from the Cherokee Nation.</p>
<p>The company is engaged in talks with officials from the Native American tribe, according to Carlos Tavares, CEO of Stellantis, the <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/01/04/cars/fiat-chrysler-psa-merger-approval/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recently merged automaker</a> that includes the Jeep brand. Tavares made the comment in an interview with the <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/jeep-owner-stellantis-is-open-to-dropping-cherokee-name-ceo-says-11614799301" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wall Street Journal</a> and his comments were confirmed by the company.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are ready to go to any point, up to the point where we decide with the appropriate people and with no intermediaries,&#8221; he said when asked about dropping the name. &#8220;At this stage, I don&#8217;t know if there is a real problem. But if there is one, well, of course we will solve it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The <a href="https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/chief-of-cherokee-nation-asks-jeep-to-stop-using-tribes-name/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">objections to the name</a> were raised by Chuck Hoskin Jr., principal chief of the Cherokee Nation.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think we&#8217;re in a day and age in this country where it&#8217;s time for both corporations and team sports to retire the use of Native American names, images and mascots from their products, team jerseys and sports in general,&#8221; he said in a statement last month.</p>
<p>The Grand Cherokee is one of the best-selling models any of Stellantis&#8217; brands in terms of global sales. It is No. 2 in the company&#8217;s US sales, behind only the Ram pickup, and the Cherokee is No. 4 in US sales. The Cherokee name was first used on a Jeep SUV in 1974, and has been in use by Jeep on either the Cherokee or Grand Cherokee ever since.</p>
<p>The discussion around the Cherokee name comes as many sports teams and companies are rethinking logos that rely on racist or stereotypical representations of minorities.</p>
<p>The Washington Football team last summer dropped its &#8220;<a href="http://www.cnn.com/2020/07/13/us/washington-redskins-nickname-change-spt/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Redskins</a>&#8221; name, and the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/12/13/us/cleveland-indians-mlb-name-change-spt-trnd/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cleveland Indians baseball team</a> followed suit a few months later. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/04/17/us/landolakes-logo-change-trnd/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Land O&#8217; Lakes</a> butter last year removed an image of a Native American woman from its label. Other food brands including &#8220;<a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/02/09/business/aunt-jemima-new-name/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Aunt Jemima</a>,&#8221; have also begun rebranding amid a national reckoning over institutional racism.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876752</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/hypatia-h_801ba4b2be82cc5e2bcc79b924625385-h_b78436ef209c5d1121503afbd5e37a81.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/hypatia-h_801ba4b2be82cc5e2bcc79b924625385-h_b78436ef209c5d1121503afbd5e37a81.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/hypatia-h_801ba4b2be82cc5e2bcc79b924625385-h_b78436ef209c5d1121503afbd5e37a81.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">All-new 2021 Jeep® Grand Cherokee L Overland</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter is testing an &#8216;undo&#8217; option after sending tweets</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/twitter-is-testing-an-undo-option-after-sending-tweets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 18:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Twitter is working on a feature that could offer users a short window of time to rethink posting a tweet even after they hit send....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>(CNN) &#x2014; Twitter is working on a feature that could<strong>&#xC2;&#xA0;</strong>offer users a short window of time to rethink<strong>&#xC2;&#xA0;</strong>posting a tweet even after they hit send.<p>The company confirmed to CNN Business on Friday it is testing an undo option that would potentially let users retract or correct a<strong>&#xC2;&#xA0;</strong>tweet before it&#x2019;s officially posted on the platform.</p><p>The feature was discovered by Jane Manchun<strong>&#xC2;&#xA0;</strong>Wong, an app developer who has a&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/22/tech/jane-wong-app-features/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">strong track record</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;of uncovering new tools on social networks before they&#x2019;re released. Wong posted&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://twitter.com/wongmjane/status/1367704041942179841" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a GIF</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;on Twitter that shows a blue &#x201C;undo&#x201D; bar appearing beneath the words &#x201C;Your Tweet was sent.&#x201D; (It&#x2019;s possible the feature could change before it formally rolls out &#x2014; if it ever does.)</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/wongmjane/status/1367704041942179841</embed></div><p>It&#x2019;s not quite&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/1/15/21066815/twitter-edit-button-jack-dorsey-says-no" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the edit button</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;users have long requested, but it&#x2019;s a step toward helping users<strong>&#xC2;&#xA0;</strong>proactively catch errors and slow down before sending impulse tweets.</p><p>The feature is reminiscent of Gmail&#x2019;s existing&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://support.google.com/mail/answer/2819488?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&amp;hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recall tool</a>, which allows users up to 30 seconds to retract sending<strong>&#xC2;&#xA0;</strong>an email.</p><p>Last year, Twitter told investors it was mulling a subscription service and was evaluating exclusive options for paying users, including an &#x201C;undo send&#x201D; feature. At the time, the company said it&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/07/31/twitter-survey-reveals-the-subscription-options-its-eyeing-including-an-undo-send-option/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">asked users in a survey</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;to evaluate which options were most or least important to them.</p><p>&#x201C;Over the course of this year, you&#x2019;ll see us test subscription products in public,&#x201D; the company&#x2019;s investor relations&#x2019; Twitter account&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://twitter.com/TwitterIR/status/1366821636712722432" target="_blank" rel="noopener">teased&#xC2;&#xA0;</a>earlier this week. &#x201C;You&#x2019;ll hear more about them. And hopefully, you&#x2019;ll see some of these products roll out as well.&#x201D;</p><p>Last month, Twitter&#xC2;&#xA0;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/25/tech/twitter-super-follow-investor-day/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>&#xC2;&#xA0;it is exploring other subscription opportunities, such as a way for users to become paid subscribers to Twitter accounts they like to receive additional content such as exclusive announcements and newsletters. The company has also set an ambitious goal to double its annual revenue by the end of 2023.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876709</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_299150113f866b7b50be4b7a47119b8f-h_b11f633b0f9cc12134529e551424b8e0.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_299150113f866b7b50be4b7a47119b8f-h_b11f633b0f9cc12134529e551424b8e0.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_299150113f866b7b50be4b7a47119b8f-h_b11f633b0f9cc12134529e551424b8e0.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_299150113f866b7b50be4b7a47119b8f-h_b11f633b0f9cc12134529e551424b8e0</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prince Philip transferred back to private hospital</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/prince-philip-transferred-back-to-private-hospital/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 17:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LONDON (AP) — Prince Philip has been transferred from a specialist cardiac hospital to a private facility to continue his recovery after a heart procedure,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LONDON (AP) — Prince Philip has been transferred from a specialist cardiac hospital to a private facility to continue his recovery after a heart procedure, Buckingham Palace said Friday.</p>
<p>The palace said the 99-year-old husband of Queen Elizabeth II underwent a successful procedure for a pre-existing heart condition at St Bartholomew’s Hospital on Wednesday.</p>
<p>He was moved to King Edward VII&#8217;s hospital on Friday and is “expected to remain in hospital for continuing treatment for a number of days,&#8221; the palace said.</p>
<p>Philip was admitted to the private London hospital on Feb. 16, where he was treated for an infection. On Monday he was transferred to the specialized cardiac care hospital.</p>
<p>Philip’s illness is not believed to be related to the coronavirus. Both Philip and the monarch received COVID-19 vaccinations in January and chose to publicize the fact in order to encourage others to also take the vaccine.</p>
<p>Philip, also known as the Duke of Edinburgh, retired in 2017 and rarely appears in public. Before his hospitalization, he had been isolating at Windsor Castle, west of London, with the queen.</p>
<p>Although he enjoyed good health well into old age, Philip has had heart issues in the past. In 2011, he was rushed to a hospital by helicopter after suffering chest pains and was treated for a blocked coronary artery.</p>
<p>The longest-serving royal consort in British history, Philip married the then-Princess Elizabeth in 1947. He and the queen have four children, eight grandchildren and nine great-grandchildren.</p>
<p>His illness comes as the royal family braces for the broadcast on Sunday of an interview conducted by Oprah Winfrey with Meghan, Duchess of Sussex.</p>
<p>Meghan and husband Prince Harry quit royal duties last year and moved to California, citing what they said were the unbearable intrusions and racist attitudes of the British media.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876676</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-prince-philip.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9bae34d2-2afa-48b1-b439-11c3a0faa950/0319b844-c55a-4dbc-b812-39a19c34f47f/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219205~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/9bae34d2-2afa-48b1-b439-11c3a0faa950/0319b844-c55a-4dbc-b812-39a19c34f47f/main.mp4*~hmac=42ac7ab772b909b54624f39327f703cb18fe2a56eb775aac46499ce6d23cb6c7' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-prince-philip.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030521-prince-philip.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030521 prince philip</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney is closing 60 stores in the US and Canada</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/disney-is-closing-60-stores-in-the-us-and-canada/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876557</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; The Disney Store, once a mall mainstay, is drastically reducing the number of locations it has in the United States and Canada. Disney said it&#8217;s closing...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; The Disney Store, once a mall mainstay, is drastically reducing the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/12/12/business/retailers-restaurants-bankrupt-2020/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">number of locations</a> it has in the United States and Canada.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/media/disney-earnings-q1-2021/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Disney</a> said it&#8217;s closing at least 60 stores in North America, amounting to about 35% of its locations in the region. Moving forward, Disney is placing a larger emphasis on its e-commerce business rather than its brick-and-mortar footprint.</p>
<p>&#8220;While consumer behavior has shifted toward online shopping, the global pandemic has changed what consumers expect from a retailer,&#8221; said Stephanie Young, president of Disney&#8217;s consumer products, games and publishing unit, in a press release.</p>
<p>Disney said that it&#8217;s focusing on making its shopDisney platform a more &#8220;seamless&#8221; and &#8220;personalized&#8221; experience. That online revamp will be &#8220;complemented by greater integration with Disney Parks apps and social media platforms.&#8221;</p>
<p>Covid-19 has <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/10/11/investing/stocks-week-ahead/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">spurred more people to move their shopping habits online.</a> Research firm eMarketer recently said e-commerce sales across the world grew nearly 28% in 2020, surpassing $4 trillion.</p>
<p>Fans can still buy Mickey merchandise at theme park stores, third-party retailers and Disney shop-in-shops. In 2019, Target <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/04/business/target-disney-store/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opened mini-Disney stores</a> in 25 of its locations.</p>
<p>Disney, which didn&#8217;t release a list of stores that will close, has about 300 locations worldwide. It had nearly 800 locations globally at its peak in 1999.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876557</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_28abee9ad818315d990cba0b6ae2dd4c-h_92fe9ca139c5c5d3b7a5c9927e52d38d.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1e17159f-58cf-48a7-9ae7-5f218dc95e08/3069efac-81bf-44b1-b7c4-ecdf9600fd31/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217294~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/1e17159f-58cf-48a7-9ae7-5f218dc95e08/3069efac-81bf-44b1-b7c4-ecdf9600fd31/main.mp4*~hmac=04e8c7fc0abf82ff9b964a3326badddac1299704f58765fd5672ffc678454c22' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_28abee9ad818315d990cba0b6ae2dd4c-h_92fe9ca139c5c5d3b7a5c9927e52d38d.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_28abee9ad818315d990cba0b6ae2dd4c-h_92fe9ca139c5c5d3b7a5c9927e52d38d.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Disney Store seen in Times Square, New York</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former police chief is facing charges over fires authorities say were linked to people he had disagreements with</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/former-police-chief-is-facing-charges-over-fires-authorities-say-were-linked-to-people-he-had-disagreements-with/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876532</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; A former Maryland police chief is facing multiple arson and attempted murder charges in connection with 11 fires spanning from 2011 to 2020,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; A former Maryland police chief is facing multiple arson and attempted murder charges in connection with 11 fires spanning from 2011 to 2020, according to a news release from the Prince George&#8217;s County Fire/EMS Department.</p>
<p>Authorities determined the homes, garages and vehicles that were set on fire were all connected to people with whom David M. Crawford had previous disagreements, according to the release.</p>
<p>&#8220;The victims include a former City of Laurel official, three former law enforcement officials including a former City of Laurel Police Chief, two relatives, two of Crawford&#8217;s former physicians, and a resident in his neighborhood,&#8221; the release said.</p>
<p>Crawford, 69, was arrested Wednesday, according to the release. He is being held without bond, according to Howard County Police Chief Lisa Myers</p>
<p>Crawford last served as a law enforcement official in 2010, when he resigned as the chief of the City of Laurel Police Department, the release said. Before that, Crawford was the chief of the District Heights Police Department and a major with Prince George&#8217;s County police, it added.</p>
<p>The 11 fires took place in several Maryland counties, including Prince George&#8217;s County, Montgomery County, Howard County and Frederick County, and had previously been investigated separately.</p>
<p>A 12th fire, in Charles County, is still under investigation and Crawford is a suspect in the case, the release said. No charges have so far been filed.</p>
<p>Robert Bonsib, Crawford&#8217;s lawyer, told CNN Thursday that &#8220;Dave Crawford has a long history of serving his community as a police officer for a large local department and then as Chief of Police for a municipal department. The allegations in the criminal complaint are inconsistent with his long history of public service.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>How investigators tied the incidents together</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>In each case where surveillance video was discovered, the arsonist&#8217;s identity was hidden, the release said, oftentimes by a hooded sweatshirt drawn tightly around their face.</p>
<p>The arsonist also had a pattern of using gallon gasoline jugs and a stick wrapped in cloth to set the fires. And all of the fires were set at night, the release said.</p>
<p>And in several cases, there were similar vehicle descriptions: a silver sedan.</p>
<p>The big break in the case came after the last-known fire, in 2020, when investigators discovered a link between the victims, and found out they had been in disagreements with Crawford, the release said.</p>
<p>The attempted murder charges stem from the fact that in several cases, there were clear signs the victims and their families were inside their homes at the time Crawford set the fires.</p>
<p>In January, investigators executed a search warrant at Crawford&#8217;s home and found &#8220;several critical items of evidence,&#8221; the release said, including a target list of the known victims that linked him to the fires.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876532</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_33d090bec0fa58904c9abfaa111e8b23-h_53d49b4d10cd814164e15e2a90f61ac3.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/bdbc2edd-cc58-4cfc-8547-2b41aa411421/94abb28b-9469-4575-9fc2-9d1c6c58d440/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217397~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/bdbc2edd-cc58-4cfc-8547-2b41aa411421/94abb28b-9469-4575-9fc2-9d1c6c58d440/main.mp4*~hmac=ab8b511798483214b2ee7754272c3683b251a9196aac962cc4839448e76a4ac9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_33d090bec0fa58904c9abfaa111e8b23-h_53d49b4d10cd814164e15e2a90f61ac3.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_33d090bec0fa58904c9abfaa111e8b23-h_53d49b4d10cd814164e15e2a90f61ac3.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MD Serial Arsonist Arrested</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pope urges Iraq to embrace its Christians on historic visit</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/pope-urges-iraq-to-embrace-its-christians-on-historic-visit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 12:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BAGHDAD (AP) — Pope Francis opened the first-ever papal visit to Iraq on Friday with a plea for the country to protect its centuries-old diversity,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BAGHDAD (AP) — Pope Francis opened the first-ever papal visit to Iraq on Friday with a plea for the country to protect its centuries-old diversity, urging Muslims to embrace their Christian neighbors as a precious resource and asking the embattled Christian community &#8212; “though small like a mustard seed” &#8212; to persevere.</p>
<p>Francis brushed aside the coronavirus pandemic and security concerns to resume his globe-trotting papacy after a yearlong hiatus spent under COVID-19 lockdown in Vatican City. His primary aim over the weekend is to encourage Iraq’s dwindling Christian population, which was violently persecuted by the Islamic State group and still faces discrimination by the Muslim majority, to stay and help rebuild the country devastated by wars and strife.</p>
<p>“Only if we learn to look beyond our differences and see each other as members of the same human family,&#8221; Francis told Iraqi authorities in his welcoming address, &#8220;will we be able to begin an effective process of rebuilding and leave to future generations a better, more just and more humane world.”</p>
<p>The 84-year-old pope donned a facemask during the flight from Rome and throughout all his protocol visits, as did his hosts. But the masks came off when the leaders sat down to talk, and social distancing and other health measures appeared lax at the airport and on the streets of Baghdad, despite the country’s worsening COVID-19 outbreak.</p>
<p>The government is eager to show off the relative stability it has achieved after the defeat of the IS “caliphate.” Nonetheless, security measures were tight.</p>
<p>Francis, who relishes plunging into crowds and likes to travel in an open-sided popemobile, was transported around Baghdad in an armored black BMWi750, flanked by rows of motorcycle police. It was believed to be the first time Francis had used a bulletproof car — both to protect him and keep crowds from forming.</p>
<p>Iraqis, though, seemed keen to welcome Francis and the global attention his visit brought. Some lined the road to cheer his motorcade. Banners and posters in central Baghdad depicted Francis with the slogan “We are all Brothers.”</p>
<p>Some hoping to get close were sorely disappointed by the heavy security cordons.</p>
<p>“It was my great wish to meet the pope and pray for my sick daughter and pray for her to be healed. But this wish was not fulfilled,” said Raad William Georges, a 52-year-old father of three who said he was turned away when he tried to see Francis during his visit to Our Lady of Salvation Cathedral in the Karrada neighborhood.</p>
<p>“This opportunity will not be repeated,&#8221; he said ruefully. “I will try tomorrow, I know it will not happen, but I will try.”</p>
<p>Francis told reporters aboard the papal plane that he was happy to be resuming his travels again and said it was particularly symbolic that his first trip was to Iraq, the traditional birthplace of Abraham, revered by Muslims, Christians and Jews.</p>
<p>“This is an emblematic journey,” he said. “It is also a duty to a land tormented by many years.”</p>
<p>Francis was visibly limping throughout the afternoon in a sign his sciatica nerve pain, which has flared and forced him to cancel events recently, was possibly bothering him. He nearly tripped as he climbed up the steps to the cathedral and an aide had to steady him.</p>
<p>At a pomp-filled gathering with President Barham Salih at a palace inside Baghdad&#8217;s heavily fortified Green Zone, Francis said Christians and other minorities in Iraq deserve the same rights and protections as the Shiite Muslim majority.</p>
<p>“The religious, cultural and ethnic diversity that has been a hallmark of Iraqi society for millennia is a precious resource on which to draw, not an obstacle to eliminate,” he said. “Iraq today is called to show everyone, especially in the Middle East, that diversity, instead of giving rise to conflict, should lead to harmonious cooperation in the life of society.”</p>
<p>Salih, a member of Iraq&#8217;s ethnic Kurdish minority, echoed his call.</p>
<p>“The East cannot be imagined without Christians,” Salih said. “The continued migration of Christians from the countries of the east will have dire consequences for the ability of the people from the same region to live together.”</p>
<p>The Iraq visit is in keeping with Francis’ long-standing effort to improve relations with the Muslim world, which has accelerated in recent years with his friendship with a leading Sunni cleric, Sheikh Ahmed el-Tayeb. It will reach a new high with his meeting Saturday with Iraq’s leading Shiite cleric, Grand Ayatollah Ali al-Sistani, a figure revered in Iraq and beyond.</p>
<p>In Iraq, the pontiff bringing his call for tolerance to a country rich in ethnic and religious diversity but deeply traumatized by hatreds. Since the 2003 U.S. invasion that toppled Saddam Hussein, it has seen vicious sectarian violence between Shiites and Sunni Muslims, clashes and tensions between Arabs and Kurds, and militant atrocities against minorities like Christians and Yazidis.</p>
<p>The few Christians who remain harbor a lingering mistrust of their Muslim neighbors and face discrimination that long predated IS.</p>
<p>Iraq&#8217;s Christians, whose presence here goes back nearly to the time of Christ, belong to a number of rites and denominations, with the Chaldean Catholic the largest, along with Syriac Catholics, Assyrians and several Orthodox churches. They once constituted a sizeable minority in Iraq, estimated at around 1.4 million. But their numbers began to fall amid the post-2003 turmoil when Sunni militants often targeted Christians.</p>
<p>They received a further blow when IS in 2014 swept through northern Iraq, including traditionally Christian towns across the Nineveh plains. Their extremist version of Islam forced residents to flee to the neighboring Kurdish region or further afield.</p>
<p>Few have returned — estimates suggest there are fewer than 300,000 Christians still in Iraq and many of those remain displaced from their homes. Those who did go back found homes and churches destroyed. Many feel intimidated by Shiite militias controlling some areas.</p>
<p>There are practical struggles, as well. Many Iraqi Christians cannot find work and blame discriminatory practices in the public sector, Iraq’s largest employer. Public jobs have been mostly controlled by Shiite political elites.</p>
<p>For the pope, who has often traveled to places where Christians are a persecuted minority, Iraq’s beleaguered Christians are the epitome of the “martyred church” that he has admired ever since he was a young Jesuit seeking to be a missionary in Asia.</p>
<p>At Our Lady of Salvation Cathedral, Francis prayed and honored the victims of one of the worst massacres of Christians, the 2010 attack on the cathedral by Islamic militants that left 58 people dead.</p>
<p>Speaking to congregants, he urged Christians to persevere in Iraq to ensure that its Catholic community, &#8220;though small like a mustard seed, continues to enrich the life of society as a whole” — using an image found in both the Bible and Quran.</p>
<p>On Sunday, Francis will honor the dead in a Mosul square surrounded by shells of destroyed churches and meet with the small Christian community that returned to the town of Qaraqosh, where he will bless their church that was vandalized and used as a firing range by IS.</p>
<p>Iraq is seeing a new spike in coronavirus infections, with most new cases traced to the highly contagious variant first identified in Britain. Francis, the Vatican delegation and travelling media have been vaccinated; most Iraqis have not, raising questions about the potential for the trip to fuel infections.</p>
<p>The Vatican and Iraqi authorities have downplayed the threat and insisted that social distancing, crowd control and other health care measures will be enforced.</p>
<p>To some degree they were, but that didn’t diminish the happiness of ordinary Iraqis — Christians and Muslims alike — that Francis had come to their home.</p>
<p>”We cannot express our joy because this for sure is a historic event which we will keep remembering,” said Rafif Issa. “All Iraqis are happy, not just the Christians. We hope it will be a blessed day for us and for all the Iraqi people.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876506</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Pope_Francis_Iran.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/06858fee-af41-4bba-b226-888c7e556f3d/4dd9b813-ab80-45d3-a8d3-b66e7a01ad70/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217393~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/06858fee-af41-4bba-b226-888c7e556f3d/4dd9b813-ab80-45d3-a8d3-b66e7a01ad70/main.mp4*~hmac=bd2e92fa24d57b0bd8b97ecef1c8b8e9fe5ad208de69fd639d9d12a16881fcc2' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Pope_Francis_Iran.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/210305_Pope_Francis_Iran.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210305_Pope_Francis_Iran</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>World&#8217;s first space hotel scheduled to open in 2027</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/worlds-first-space-hotel-scheduled-to-open-in-2027/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 11:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876495</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; If you&#8217;re daydreaming of future travels while stuck at home during the pandemic, why fantasize about the beaches of Bali or the canals...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; If you&#8217;re daydreaming of future travels while stuck at home during the pandemic, why fantasize about the beaches of Bali or the canals of Venice when vacationing in space could be in your future?</p>
<p><a href="https://cnn.com/travel/article/space-hotel-designs-von-braun-station-scn/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Back in 2019</a>, Californian company the Gateway Foundation released plans for a cruise ship-style hotel that could one day float above the Earth&#8217;s atmosphere.</p>
<p>Then called the Von Braun Station, this futuristic concept &#8212; comprised of 24 modules connected by elevator shafts that make up a rotating wheel orbiting the Earth &#8212; was scheduled to be fully operational by 2027.</p>
<p>Fast forward a couple years and the hotel has a new name &#8212; Voyager Station &#8212; and it&#8217;s set to be built by Orbital Assembly Corporation, a new construction company run by former pilot John Blincow, who also heads up the Gateway Foundation.</p>
<p>In a recent interview with CNN Travel, Blincow explained there had been some Covid-related delays, but construction on the space hotel is expected to begin in 2026, and a sojourn in space could be a reality by 2027.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re trying to make the public realize that this golden age of space travel is just around the corner. It&#8217;s coming. It&#8217;s coming fast,&#8221; said Blincow.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>A hotel like no other</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Renderings of what the hotel might look like suggest an interior not dissimilar to a luxury Earth-bound hotel, just with some pretty specatcular out-of-this-world views.</p>
<p>When the initial designs premiered a couple years ago, Tim Alatorre, senior design architect at Orbital Assembly Corporation<a href="https://cnn.com/travel/article/space-hotel-designs-von-braun-station-scn/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> told CNN Travel </a>the hotel&#8217;s aesthetic was a direct response to the Stanley Kubrick movie &#8220;2001: A Space Odyssey&#8221; &#8212; which he called &#8220;almost a blueprint of what not to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I think the goal of Stanley Kubrick was to highlight the divide between technology and humanity and so, purposefully, he made the stations and the ships very sterile and clean and alien.&#8221;</p>
<p>Instead, Alatorre and his team want to bring a slice of earth to space via warm suites and chic bars and restaurants. Guests might be in space, but they can still enjoy regular beds and showers.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s not to say the hotel will ignore the novelty of being in space altogether. There are plans to serve traditional &#8220;space food&#8221; &#8212; like freeze dried ice cream &#8212; in the hotel&#8217;s restaurant.</p>
<p>Plus there will be recreational activities on offer that &#8220;highlight the fact that you&#8217;re able to do things that you can&#8217;t do on Earth,&#8221; according to Alatorre.</p>
<p>&#8220;Because of the weightlessness and the reduced gravity, you&#8217;ll be able to jump higher, be able to lift things, be able to run in ways that you can&#8217;t on Earth.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>How does it work?</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>So how exactly would the physics of a space hotel work?</p>
<p>Alatorre told CNN Travel that the rotating wheel would work to create a simulated gravity.</p>
<p>&#8220;The station rotates, pushing the contents of the station out to the perimeter of the station, much in the way that you can spin a bucket of water &#8212; the water pushes out into the bucket and stays in place,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Near the center of the station there&#8217;s no artificial gravity, Alatorre explained, but as you move down the outside of the station, the feeling of gravity increases.</p>
<p>The hotel&#8217;s original name was chosen because the concept was inspired by 60-year-old designs from Wernher von Braun, an aerospace engineer who pioneered rocket technology, first in Germany and later in the US.</p>
<p>While living in Germany, von Braun was involved in the Nazi rocket development program, so naming the space hotel after him was a controversial choice.</p>
<p>This was partly why the name&#8217;s been changed, Blincow told CNN Travel.</p>
<p>&#8220;The station is not really about him. It&#8217;s based on his design, and we like his contributions towards science and space,&#8221; Blincow said. &#8220;But you know, Voyager Station is so much more than that. It is the stuff in the future. And we want a name that doesn&#8217;t have those attachments to it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Space tourism is becoming an increasingly hot topic, and there are several companies trying to make it happen &#8212; from Virgin Galactic to Elon Musk&#8217;s SpaceX.</p>
<p>SpaceX&#8217;s StarShip system could help get Voyager Station off the ground.</p>
<p>&#8220;We cannot call SpaceX our partner, but in the future we look forward to working with them,&#8221; Blincow told a recent <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m50A-3OLGd0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">live event promoting Orbital Assembly,</a> advising viewers to &#8220;hang tight.&#8221;</p>
<p>For now, the space hotel isn&#8217;t advertising a room rate, but expect it to come with a pretty hefty price tag attached.</p>
<p>Virgin Galactic, for example, plans to launch passengers into sub-orbital space at $250,000 per person, per trip.</p>
<p>However the team behind Voyager Station have said they&#8217;re hoping to eventually make a stay at the hotel equivalent to &#8220;a trip on a cruise or a trip to Disneyland.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>&#8220;Starship culture&#8221;</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Voyager Station is perhaps the flashiest of Orbital&#8217;s designs, it&#8217;s actually just one facet of their space ambitions.</p>
<p>The team is also hoping to build research stations, and spark space tourism and commerce opportunities.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re designing the tools and machines right now that can build these structures very quickly,&#8221; Blincow told CNN Travel.</p>
<p>The team imagine government or private companies might use modules for training crews &#8220;heading to Mars, the Moon and beyond,&#8221; as Alatorre outlined at the 2021 live event.</p>
<p>The next stage in getting the Voyager Station off the ground is bringing more investors into the mix, and continuing with tests on the ground.</p>
<p>The eventual goal, as Alatorre put it back in 2019, is &#8220;to create a starship culture where people are going to space, and living in space, and working in space and they want to be in space. And we believe that there&#8217;s a demand for that.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876495</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_e1abdbb4a7bad3ba07f88337a0bf66c6-h_114ccf79c4a834222533f6762c9c5b94.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_e1abdbb4a7bad3ba07f88337a0bf66c6-h_114ccf79c4a834222533f6762c9c5b94.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_e1abdbb4a7bad3ba07f88337a0bf66c6-h_114ccf79c4a834222533f6762c9c5b94.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">20-0522 Voyager - Animations-Scene 3a</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prosecutors: Officer was on Floyd&#8217;s neck for about 9 minutes</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/prosecutors-officer-was-on-floyds-neck-for-about-9-minutes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 11:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876468</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — As the trial approaches for a white Minneapolis police officer charged with murder in the death of George Floyd, prosecutors are putting...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — As the trial approaches for a white Minneapolis police officer charged with murder in the death of George Floyd, prosecutors are putting the time Derek Chauvin’s knee was on the Black man&#8217;s neck at about nine minutes.</p>
<p>The time has fluctuated before. It was recorded as 8 minutes, 46 seconds in an initial criminal complaint — a <a href="https://apnews.com/article/d39cf4e1460fa14f0e339d85f21ad3c2">figure that became symbolic</a> to many in the weeks after Floyd’s death — before a math error was corrected to make it 7:46. But filings since then, citing time-stamped police body-camera video, now make it at least nine minutes.</p>
<p>The fact that the figure has evolved probably won&#8217;t matter at Chauvin’s trial, which begins Monday with jury selection. One former prosecutor says it’s common for such details to be fine-tuned as prosecutors build a case. A support group for victims of police violence says the discrepancies won&#8217;t have any impact.</p>
<p>“He was obviously on there enough time to think about what he was doing. He heard the man pleading that he couldn’t breathe,” said Toshira Garraway, founder of Families Supporting Families Against Police Violence. “If it was two minutes or if it was five minutes or if it was 10 minutes, he was fully aware … Once he said, ‘I cannot breathe’ … he was supposed to remove his knee.”</p>
<p>Floyd died May 25. He had been handcuffed and was pleading that he couldn&#8217;t breathe, but Chauvin kept his knee on Floyd&#8217;s neck even after he stopped moving and speaking.</p>
<p>Chauvin is charged with second-degree murder and manslaughter. Three other officers — Thomas Lane, J. Kueng and Tou Thao — are charged with aiding and abetting second-degree murder and manslaughter and are scheduled for trial in August.</p>
<p>The narrative in the initial complaint filed May 29 by the Hennepin County Attorney’s Office says Chauvin held his knee to Floyd’s neck for 8 minutes, 46 seconds. But the time stamps cited in that charging document indicate it was actually 7 minutes, 46 seconds.</p>
<p>The Associated Press began asking about the error the day after the initial charges were filed, but prosecutors repeatedly declined to address it. The 8:46 detail was repeated in <a href="https://apnews.com/article/b33f9d6420d570ab3f3f7afece67b6bb">an amended complaint filed days later </a>by the Attorney General’s Office.</p>
<p>In the weeks that followed Floyd’s death, some demonstrators staged “die-ins” that lasted 8 minutes, 46 seconds, some lawmakers knelt for that amount of time in the U.S. Senate, and mourners at a memorial service for Floyd stood in silence for 8:46 to reflect on the final moments of his life.</p>
<p>In mid-June, <a href="https://apnews.com/article/0b4714f6a42b362b0e2c0cd701c6392b">prosecutors acknowledged the one-minute error</a>, but said it would have no impact on the case.</p>
<p>Documents filed by prosecutors in September and October changed the timing yet again. These documents contain the most detailed picture of what happened, citing time stamps from Lane, Keung and Thao&#8217;s body camera videos.</p>
<p>The documents don’t list an exact time for when Chauvin began kneeling on Floyd, but instead provide a narrative for when Floyd was first pressed to the ground. Time stamps on video from Lane’s body camera — recorded in 24-hour-clock format — show that began at some point from 20:19:14 to 20:19:45, meaning from 14 to 45 seconds after 8:19 p.m.</p>
<p>But the documents cite a clear moment when Chauvin removed his knee, when a stretcher was ready to take Floyd away. Lane’s body camera time-stamp read 20:28:45.</p>
<p>This means Chauvin had his knee on Floyd’s neck for at least nine minutes flat, but possibly for as long as 9 minutes, 31 seconds. Documents filed by prosecutors characterize the timing as “approximately nine minutes,” though in at least one document it is characterized as “more than nine minutes and twenty seconds.”</p>
<p>John Stiles, the spokesman for the Attorney General’s Office, said the length of time of Chauvin’s restraint will be evidence presented at trial. He declined further comment.</p>
<p>Tom Heffelfinger, a former U.S. attorney for Minnesota who is not connected to this case, said it’s normal for prosecutors to fine-tune details as they build a case and that the length of Chauvin’s restraint won’t become essential until a prosecutor presents it to the jury.</p>
<p>But at trial, he said, the timing will become extremely relevant as both sides argue about Floyd’s cause of death. Heffelfinger also said it points to Chauvin’s state of mind and can be used by prosecutors to show willfulness, and that Chauvin had Floyd under his control and held his position for too long.</p>
<p>“You can see from the bystander video, Chauvin had Floyd under control for that entire period,” Heffelfinger said. “He didn’t need to have his knee to the neck in order to maintain that … control.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876468</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/bhdn_na-100fr_mn_-george-floyd_-officer-derek-chauvin-booking-_cnna-st1-1000000005cedc3f_174_0_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ea12a69a-a42f-4356-9a9e-5cae135901a1/ba156d03-cd09-4c3a-b1f6-05ea05026639/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219215~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ea12a69a-a42f-4356-9a9e-5cae135901a1/ba156d03-cd09-4c3a-b1f6-05ea05026639/main.mp4*~hmac=3cf6c6de9acb68f6213a6082764d34dab4230ac30fc2c805bdc6f297878123e9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/bhdn_na-100fr_mn_-george-floyd_-officer-derek-chauvin-booking-_cnna-st1-1000000005cedc3f_174_0_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/bhdn_na-100fr_mn_-george-floyd_-officer-derek-chauvin-booking-_cnna-st1-1000000005cedc3f_174_0_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Derek Chauvin mugshot</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Zealand downgrades tsunami warning after 8.1-magnitude earthquake</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/new-zealand-downgrades-tsunami-warning-after-8-1-magnitude-earthquake/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 02:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Extreme]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; New Zealand has downgraded its tsunami warning after a powerful earthquake struck the Kermadec Islands region early Friday, sparking fears of a tsunami. The 8.1-magnitude quake was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; New Zealand has downgraded its tsunami warning after a powerful<a href="https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us7000dflf/executive" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> earthquake struck the Kermadec Islands</a> region early Friday, sparking fears of a tsunami.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us7000dflf/executive" target="_blank" rel="noopener">8.1-magnitude quake</a> was the third to strike the area on Friday morning local time, according to the New Zealand National Emergency Management Agency.</p>
<p>Residents in some areas received emergency alerts on their phones urging them to &#8220;EVACUATE NOW,&#8221; as tsunami sirens rang out. The emergency agency issued a <a href="https://www.civildefence.govt.nz/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">temporary evacuation order</a> for people near the coast, warning them, &#8220;Do not stay at home&#8221; as a &#8220;damaging tsunami is possible.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Kermadec Islands are 500 to 620 miles northeast of New Zealand&#8217;s North Island. The East Coast of the North Island from the Bay of Islands to Whangarei, from Matata to Tolaga Bay including Whakatane and Opotiki and Great Barrier Island are all included in the Pacific nation&#8217;s tsunami warning.</p>
<p>On Friday afternoon, the agency downgraded its warning from a &#8220;land and marine threat&#8221; to &#8220;beach and marine threat,&#8221; meaning all residents who evacuated can now return to their homes.</p>
<p>It added that strong currents and unpredictable surges may continue for several hours, and that people should stay away from beaches, shores and rivers.</p>
<p>The earthquake came &#8220;without any significant warning,&#8221; seismologist Bill Fry said in a press conference Friday. He added in his 13 years responding to earthquakes and tsunamis in New Zealand, &#8220;this is the first time we&#8217;ve had this particular sequence.&#8221;</p>
<p>In Russell, New Zealand, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CMAvox3gJso/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rita Baker</a> told CNN that she had evacuated with other residents to a hill overlooking the Bay of Islands.</p>
<p>When the first alerts came about earthquakes in New Zealand, Baker wasn&#8217;t too worried, she wrote to CNN. Then the first Kermadec quake struck with little warning.</p>
<p>&#8220;An hour after that, the tsunami siren went off and for a split second I went into panic mode,&#8221; Baker added. &#8220;Just hearing that sound made me get a bit anxious.&#8221;</p>
<p>Baker&#8217;s home sits 10 meters (32 foot) from the water&#8217;s edge. &#8220;Next thing my husband called me from his work in town and told me to get out ASAP and go to higher ground, as this was no drill and they were evacuating the hotel (he works at a hotel right on the waterfront),&#8221; she wrote.</p>
<p>&#8220;So I grabbed the cat (hiding under the bed) and literally with shaking hands put her in her carry cage and grabbed my handbag and computer hard-drive and got down to the car and drove up the local landmark hill.&#8221;</p>
<p>The quake also triggered warnings in Hawaii and in American Samoa, which were later canceled. Australia&#8217;s Bureau of Meteorology reported observations of a 64 centimeter (approximately 2 foot) tsunami wave at its remote Norfolk Island.</p>
<p>Thursday&#8217;s earthquake was the largest to strike anywhere in the world since August of 2018, when an 8.2-magnitude quake struck much deeper underground, also in the South Pacific, near Fiji.</p>
<p>Only around one or fewer earthquakes of 8.0-magnitude or greater occur each year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876299</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_a1503d6522f01aa5d28d4bdda0c6f9cc-h_ddd862e6b8463c79438cdaebc8bef958.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_a1503d6522f01aa5d28d4bdda0c6f9cc-h_ddd862e6b8463c79438cdaebc8bef958.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_a1503d6522f01aa5d28d4bdda0c6f9cc-h_ddd862e6b8463c79438cdaebc8bef958.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_a1503d6522f01aa5d28d4bdda0c6f9cc-h_ddd862e6b8463c79438cdaebc8bef958</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dallas police officer charged with 2 counts capital murder</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/dallas-police-officer-charged-with-2-counts-capital-murder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876233</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DALLAS (AP) — A Dallas police officer was arrested Thursday on two counts of capital murder, more than a year and a half after a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DALLAS (AP) — A Dallas police officer was arrested Thursday on two counts of capital murder, more than a year and a half after a man told investigators that he kidnapped and killed two people at the officer&#8217;s instruction in 2017, authorities said.</p>
<p>Bryan Riser, a 13-year veteran of the force, was arrested Thursday morning and taken to the Dallas County Jail for processing, according to a statement from the police department. A lawyer for him couldn&#8217;t immediately be identified.</p>
<p>Riser was arrested in the unconnected killings of Liza Saenz, 31, and Albert Douglas, 61, after a man came forward in August 2019 and told police he had kidnapped and killed them at Riser&#8217;s direction, police Chief Eddie Garcia said during a news conference. He said investigators don&#8217;t know the motives for the killings, but that they were not related to Riser&#8217;s police work.</p>
<p>Garcia did not explain why Riser was arrested nearly 20 months after the witness came forward, and police declined to answer subsequent questions about the timing. Riser joined the department in 2008, and Garcia acknowledged that he had been patrolling Dallas while under investigation for the killings.</p>
<p>The chief stressed that his homicide division and the FBI were still investigating the killings and said the department was reviewing Riser&#8217;s arrests.</p>
<p>Saenz’s body was pulled from the Trinity River in southwest Dallas on March 10, 2017, with several bullet wounds, the chief said. Douglas was reported missing that year and his body hasn’t been found.</p>
<p>Three people were previously arrested and charged with capital murder in Saenz’s killing, according to an affidavit for Riser&#8217;s arrest. It does not identify any of them by name.</p>
<p>One of them allegedly told police that he and Riser were involved in burglaries when they were young. They more recently hatched a plan to rob drug stash houses, but they didn&#8217;t follow through with it, according to the affidavit.</p>
<p>Instead, the man told investigators that Riser offered to pay him a total of $9,500 to kidnap and kill Douglas and later Saenz. Both were shot and their bodies were dumped in the river, according to the court record.</p>
<p>The affidavit states that Riser told the hired killer Saenz was an “informant.” The document does not elaborate, and police declined to answer questions about whether Saenz had some connection to the department.</p>
<p>The murder charges are not the officer&#8217;s first alleged crimes. In May 2017, Riser faced a domestic violence charge for allegedly assaulting and injuring an ex-girlfriend. It wasn&#8217;t immediately clear how that case was resolved. Police said Riser “received summary discipline for an incident.”</p>
<p>Riser has been put on administrative leave pending the outcome of an internal affairs investigation. Garcia said “we’re going to expedite our process” toward his firing.</p>
<p>“We will not allow anyone to tarnish this badge,&#8221; the chief said.</p>
<p>Riser had not been booked into the jail as of early Thursday afternoon, a sheriff’s spokesman said.</p>
<p>A spokeswoman for the Dallas County district attorney’s office said her office didn’t have information on the case.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876233</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/bryan-riser.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/bryan-riser.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/bryan-riser.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">bryan riser</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>McDonald&#8217;s employee celebrates 100th birthday, says she has no plans to retire</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/mcdonalds-employee-celebrates-100th-birthday-says-she-has-no-plans-to-retire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 23:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876194</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[IRWIN, Pa. (WSVN) &#8212; A Pennsylvania McDonald&#8217;s worker is celebrating her 100th birthday and said she has no plans to settle down and retire. Wednesday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IRWIN, Pa. (WSVN) &#8212; A Pennsylvania McDonald&#8217;s worker is celebrating her 100th birthday and said she has no plans to settle down and retire.</p>
<p>Wednesday marked Ruth Shuster&#8217;s 100 birthday, and for her, it was just another Wednesday.</p>
<p>&#8220;It doesn&#8217;t feel any different,&#8221; Shuster told <a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/i-feel-im-the-lucky-one-mcdonalds-employee-turns-100-years-old-with-no-plans-to-quit" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FOX Television Stations</a> after her co-workers threw her a party.</p>
<p>Shuster started working for McDonald&#8217;s in 1994, when she was 73 years old. Now, 27 years later, she is still at it.</p>
<p>Before the pandemic, Shuster would greet and help customers. Now, she helps out where she cans and works to boost employees&#8217; morale.</p>
<p>&#8220;They&#8217;re nice to work for, and I&#8217;m lucky they keep me here at my age,&#8221; she said. &#8220;I feel I&#8217;m the lucky one.&#8221;</p>
<p>She said she has no plans to retire. &#8220;No way at all. I don’t even think of that,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>“I became a widow when I was 50, and I’ve been working ever, ever, ever since, and I like working,&#8221; Shuster told <a href="https://wpde.com/news/nation-world/woman-who-works-at-mcdonalds-celebrates-100th-birthday-requests-birthday-cards" target="_blank" rel="noopener">WTAE</a>.</p>
<p>WTAE reports that McDonalds has set up a special mailbox for Shuster to receive birthday cards. If you would like to send her a card, you can address it to 9061 Lincoln Hwy, North Huntingdon, PA 15642.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876194</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ruth-shuster.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ruth-shuster.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/ruth-shuster.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">ruth shuster</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Know that daddy loves you&#8221;: Father records video for children before dying from COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/know-that-daddy-loves-you-father-records-video-for-children-before-dying-from-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 21:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MANVEL, Texas (WSVN) &#8212; A young father left a heartbreaking message behind for his children shortly before he died from complications of COVID-19. Charles &#8220;Charley&#8221;...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MANVEL, Texas (WSVN) &#8212; A young father left a heartbreaking message behind for his children shortly before he died from complications of COVID-19.</p>
<p>Charles &#8220;Charley&#8221; Torres died on Valentine&#8217;s Day 2021, weeks after he was diagnosed with COVID-19.</p>
<p>But before he passed, he recorded a video for his children.</p>
<p>&#8220;I love you with all my heart,&#8221; Torres said while struggling to breathe through a mask. &#8220;I love you so much. Know that daddy loves you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Torres then said the names of his three children and four step-children before telling them again that he loved them and to take care of their mother.</p>
<p>&#8220;One of the things that he did that was most important was that he loved his children and took care of his children,&#8221; Charley’s father, Alex, told <a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/know-that-daddy-loves-you-35-year-old-father-records-video-for-children-before-dying-from-covid-19" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FOX Television Stations</a> on Wednesday. &#8220;He wanted to make sure he left something for the kids just in case that things started going wrong.&#8221;</p>
<p>Torres&#8217; father said his son went to the emergency room in mid-January for what he believed was a bout of pancreatitis, something he had suffered with since 2010. However, he was diagnosed with COVID-19 and was put on a ventilator. He later succumbed to the virus.</p>
<p>&#8220;You never think it&#8217;s going to happen to you,&#8221; Alex said. &#8220;I’ve been praying to God my entire life that I never outlive my children.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876104</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/download-9.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/download-9.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/download-9.jpeg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">download (9)</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Carolina Senate adds firing squad to execution methods</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/south-carolina-senate-adds-firing-squad-to-execution-methods/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 19:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=876009</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — South Carolina senators Tuesday added a firing squad to the electric chair as alternatives if the state can&#8217;t execute condemned inmates...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — South Carolina senators Tuesday added a firing squad to the electric chair as alternatives if the state can&#8217;t execute condemned inmates by way of lethal injection.</p>
<p>The Senate then approved <a href="https://www.scstatehouse.gov/sess124_2021-2022/bills/200.htm">the bill</a> on a key 32-11 vote with several Democrats joining Republicans in the proposal which would allow South Carolina to restart executions after nearly 10 years.</p>
<p>The state can&#8217;t put anyone to death now because its supply of lethal injection drugs expired and it has not been able to buy any more. Currently, inmates can choose between the electric chair and lethal injection and since the drugs are not available, they pick the method that can&#8217;t be done.</p>
<p>The Senate bill keeps lethal injection if the state has the drugs, but requires prison officials to use the electric chair if it does not. An inmate could choose a firing squad if they prefer.</p>
<p>The House is considering <a href="https://www.scstatehouse.gov/sess124_2021-2022/bills/3755.htm">a similar bill </a>without the firing squad option, but it could also consider the Senate version after a procedural vote by senators finalizes the bill later this week.</p>
<p>South Carolina still uses the electric chair first powered up in 1912 after taking over the death penalty from counties, which usually used hanging.</p>
<p>It is just one of nine states that maintains an electric chair. It would become just the fourth state to allow a firing squad with Utah, Oklahoma and Mississippi, according to the Death Penalty Information Center.</p>
<p>South Carolina Gov. Henry McMaster asked for lawmakers to give him any way to restart executions since a few inmates have exhausted their appeals but their death sentences can’t be carried out.</p>
<p>A Republican and a Democrat, both former prosecutors, proposed adding the firing squad.</p>
<p>The Democratic former prosecutor said it is evident in a Republican dominated state like South Carolina where the GOP gained extra seats in November that the death penalty can&#8217;t be abolished <a href="https://apnews.com/article/virginia-death-penalty-repeal-governor-c98c16a996037a4d1e1d497787b7e6f1">like Virginia did</a> last month.</p>
<p>“The death penalty is going to stay the law here for a while. If it is going to remain, it ought to be humane,&#8221; said state Sen. Dick Harpootlian, who said hanging is brutal and often leads to decapitation and in electrocution, the condemned “are burned to death.”</p>
<p>Since the last execution was carried out in May 2011, South Carolina’s death row has dropped from about 60 inmates <a href="http://www.doc.sc.gov/news/death-row-report.pdf">to 37 </a>as of now because of natural deaths and prisoners winning appeals and being resentenced to life without parole. Prosecutors have sent just three new inmates to death row in the past decade.</p>
<p>The Republican former prosecutor, Sen. Greg Hembree, said Tuesday was not the time to debate whether the death penalty was right or wrong.</p>
<p>But several Democrats said the moral aspect of putting someone to death could not be removed from discussions over the method.</p>
<p>They also asked senators how they could justify having a debate over putting people to death this week when last month they passed a bill outlawing most abortions in South Carolina, which is now tied up in court.</p>
<p>Democratic Sen. Kevin Johnson brought up <a href="https://apnews.com/article/64264298f4724defb7bd1f30d4ccf32e">George Stinney</a>, the youngest person executed in the U.S. in the 20th century. He was 14 when he was sent to South Carolina&#8217;s electric chair after a one-day trial in 1944 for killing two white girls. A judge threw out the <a href="https://apnews.com/article/12430910e5e846248029e0e52c78b49a">Black teen’s conviction</a> in 2014 . Newspaper stories reported that witnesses said the straps to keep him in the electric chair didn’t fit around his small frame.</p>
<p>Johnson drives by a memorial to Stinney each time he comes to Columbia from Manning.</p>
<p>“You think it was bad to abort a baby? Think how much worse it is to kill a person who when all is said and done is innocent,&#8221; Johnson said.</p>
<p>Only one senator in the chamber has seen an execution. Hembree, the co-sponsor of the firing squad proposal, tried nearly a dozen death penalty cases as a prosecutor and watched one of the men he condemned to death die by lethal injection.</p>
<p>“There’s nothing pleasant about any of those forms. They are gruesome, they are sad and tragic in a way,&#8221; Hembree said. “Justice is not always a happy place. But it is justice.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">876009</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/jail-cell.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/jail-cell.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/06/jail-cell.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">jail prison cell generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Officials: California serial killer known as the &#8216;I-5 Strangler&#8217; found strangled to death in prison</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/officials-california-serial-killer-known-as-the-i-5-strangler-found-strangled-to-death-in-prison/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[IONE, Calif. (AP) — A California serial killer who authorities say strangled and raped at least seven women was fatally choked himself in a state...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IONE, Calif. (AP) — A California serial killer who authorities say strangled and raped at least seven women was fatally choked himself in a state prison, officials said Wednesday.</p>
<p>Roger Reece Kibbe, 81, known as the “I-5 Strangler” in the 1970s and 1980s, was spotted unresponsive Sunday in his cell at Mule Creek State Prison southeast of Sacramento — his 40-year-old cellmate standing nearby.</p>
<p>An autopsy showed Kibbe had been manually strangled, the Amador County Sheriff’s Office said, calling the death a homicide.</p>
<p>No charges have been filed in the death of Kibbe, a former suburban Sacramento furniture maker whose brother was a law enforcement officer.</p>
<p>He was initially convicted in 1991 of strangling Darcine Frackenpohl, a 17-year-old who had run away from her home in Seattle. Her nearly nude body was found west of South Lake Tahoe below Echo Summit in September 1987.</p>
<p>Investigators said then that they suspected him in other similar slayings.</p>
<p>But it wasn&#8217;t until 2009 that a San Joaquin County District Attorney’s Office investigator used new developments in evidence to connect him to six additional slayings in multiple Northern California counties, with several victims found alongside Interstate 5 or other highways in 1986. Kibbe was serving multiple life terms for the slayings when he was killed.</p>
<p>Authorities said they never stopped trying to prove that he was responsible for even more deaths. Investigators secretly took him on multiple field trips from prison with the hope that he would reveal the whereabouts of more victims.</p>
<p>They would buy him an egg McMuffin and a Coke for breakfast, another Coke and a hamburger and fries for lunch, Vito Bertocchini, a retired San Joaquin County sheriff’s detective and district attorney’s investigator, told <a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article249635438.html?ac_cid=DM397579&amp;ac_bid=-376335684">The Sacramento Bee</a>.</p>
<p>Bertocchini spent nearly two decades pursuing Kibbe and thinks he must have killed others during the 10-year gap between his first and last known slayings. Investigators have said they found other women who had been killed and dumped with Kibbe&#8217;s trademark of cutting his victims’ clothing in odd patterns.</p>
<p>He was finally captured after Sacramento police said a would-be victim escaped and they recovered a garrote made from a pair of dowels and parachute cord along with scissors and other items.</p>
<p>Investigators said they matched the cord to rope found with Frackenpohl’s body and at Kibbe&#8217;s house, all with microscopic dots of red paint. DNA eventually linked him to two other victims, and he agreed to cooperate in exchange for prosecutors taking the death penalty off the table.</p>
<p>Kibbe never admitted to other killings beyond those with which he was charged, but Bertocchini said he never stopped trying to elicit another confession.</p>
<p>Even after he retired in 2012, each year he sent Kibbe birthday and Christmas cards, asking him to speak up if he recalled anything about other victims. He and his old partner last visited Kibbe in prison in 2019, but still he wouldn&#8217;t admit to any more victims.</p>
<p>Now it&#8217;s too late, but Bertocchini called Kibbe&#8217;s death by strangulation “some fitting justice.”</p>
<p>“I don’t wish ill on anyone,” Bertocchini said. “But I hope he remembered every one of his victims while he was being killed.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875892</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/roger-kibbe.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/roger-kibbe.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/roger-kibbe.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">roger kibbe</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meghan accuses palace of &#8216;perpetuating falsehoods&#8217; against her and Harry</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/meghan-accuses-palace-of-perpetuating-falsehoods-against-her-and-harry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 12:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875720</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Meghan, the Duchess of Sussex, has accused Buckingham Palace of &#8220;perpetuating falsehoods&#8221; against her and husband Prince Harry in an explosive clip from an interview with Oprah...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/03/01/entertainment/harry-meghan-oprah-promo-scli-intl-gbr/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meghan, the Duchess of Sussex,</a> has accused Buckingham Palace of &#8220;perpetuating falsehoods&#8221; against her and husband <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2013/02/08/world/europe/prince-harry-fast-facts/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Prince Harry</a> in an explosive clip from an interview with Oprah Winfrey that is due to be aired on Sunday.</p>
<p>In the clip released on Wednesday night, Winfrey asks Meghan: &#8220;How do you feel about the palace hearing you speak your truth today?&#8221;</p>
<p>Meghan then says: &#8220;I don&#8217;t know how they could expect that after all of this time, we would still just be silent if there is an active role that the firm is playing in perpetuating falsehoods about us.</p>
<p>&#8220;And, if that comes with risk of losing things, I mean &#8230; there is a lot that has been lost already.&#8221;</p>
<p>The firm is a term sometimes used to refer to the royal family. Buckingham Palace said it had &#8220;no comment&#8221; when asked about the interview clip.</p>
<p>The full interview conducted by Winfrey with Meghan and Prince Harry will air on CBS on Sunday and on UK channel ITV on Monday. It is their first sit-down appearance since leaving Britain for North America last year.</p>
<p>The couple announced in January 2020 that they were stepping back as working members of the royal family and moved to North America soon afterward. Buckingham Palace confirmed last month that they had agreed with Queen Elizabeth II, Harry&#8217;s grandmother, that they would not be returning as working royals.</p>
<p>The move sparked talk of a rift between the couple &#8212; who are settled in California and expecting their second child &#8212; and the British royal family.</p>
<p>Earlier Wednesday, Buckingham Palace said it would investigate <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/03/uk/meghan-harry-bullying-allegations-smear-gbr-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">allegations that Meghan bullied</a> several staff members after a British media report cited unnamed royal aides saying a complaint had been made against her in 2018.</p>
<p>The Times in the UK published an article on Tuesday citing sources who said that the complaint claimed the Duchess drove out two personal assistants from her <a href="http://www.cnn.com/2021/02/26/media/prince-harry-james-corden-interview-scli-intl-gbr/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kensington Palace household</a> and undermined the confidence of a third staff member. CNN has been unable to corroborate the claims.</p>
<p>The sources also said they approached The Times because they felt the version of the Duchess that had publicly emerged was only partially true and that they were concerned about how matters of bullying had been dealt with. The report said the sources believed the public &#8220;should have insight into their side of the story&#8221; ahead of the couple&#8217;s highly anticipated interview with Winfrey.</p>
<p>Buckingham Palace said it was &#8220;very concerned&#8221; about the allegations outlined in the report.</p>
<p>&#8220;Accordingly our HR team will look into the circumstances outlined in the article. Members of staff involved at the time, including those who have left the Household, will be invited to participate to see if lessons can be learned,&#8221; it said in its statement.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the Sussexes dismissed the Times report as &#8220;a calculated smear campaign&#8221; ahead of the couple&#8217;s interview with Winfrey.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875720</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_7dd502938b34fa335100b34dd070a4c7-h_fc8cbfcf8df263d7b5de8f170e55a383.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3dd541bb-108b-4d69-bc8c-40216f720171/69774cf6-c9ba-4f85-9c88-410763b90e63/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217400~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3dd541bb-108b-4d69-bc8c-40216f720171/69774cf6-c9ba-4f85-9c88-410763b90e63/main.mp4*~hmac=b0b1803f7691a12d312e27630ed0c32752ac8db5513858dfe207a3236b5ae76c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_7dd502938b34fa335100b34dd070a4c7-h_fc8cbfcf8df263d7b5de8f170e55a383.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_7dd502938b34fa335100b34dd070a4c7-h_fc8cbfcf8df263d7b5de8f170e55a383.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_7dd502938b34fa335100b34dd070a4c7-h_fc8cbfcf8df263d7b5de8f170e55a383</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palace: Prince Philip had a successful heart procedure</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/palace-prince-philip-had-a-successful-heart-procedure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 11:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LONDON (AP) — Prince Philip has had a successful heart procedure at a London hospital, Buckingham Palace said Thursday. The palace says the 99-year-old Duke...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LONDON (AP) — Prince Philip has had a successful heart procedure at a London hospital, Buckingham Palace said Thursday.</p>
<p>The palace says the 99-year-old Duke of Edinburgh, the husband of Queen Elizabeth II, “underwent a successful procedure for a pre-existing heart condition at St Bartholomew’s Hospital.”</p>
<p>“His royal highness will remain in hospital for treatment, rest and recuperation for a number of days,&#8221; the palace said in a statement.</p>
<p>Philip, 99, has been hospitalized since being admitted to King Edward VII’s Hospital in London on Feb. 16, where he was treated for an infection. On Monday he was transferred to a specialized cardiac care hospital, St. Bartholomew’s.</p>
<p>His illness is not believed to be related to the coronavirus. Both Philip and the monarch received COVID-19 vaccinations in January and chose to publicize the matter to encourage others to also take the vaccine.</p>
<p>He has had heart issues in the past. In 2011, he was rushed to a hospital by helicopter after suffering chest pains and was treated for a blocked coronary artery.</p>
<p>Philip retired in 2017 and rarely appears in public. Before his hospitalization, Philip had been isolating at Windsor Castle, west of London, with the queen.</p>
<p>The longest-serving royal consort in British history, Philip married the then-Princess Elizabeth in 1947. He and the queen have four children, eight grandchildren and nine great-grandchildren.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875687</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Prince-Philip-e1614604594665.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b8d56d35-3f5a-4024-b49a-223c5be2e58e/429efd4e-6ac7-459b-8811-7dea65b1bed7/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217293~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/b8d56d35-3f5a-4024-b49a-223c5be2e58e/429efd4e-6ac7-459b-8811-7dea65b1bed7/main.mp4*~hmac=1592e3bab5e94bec9ea7119f5a03dee238000d9cd3731293603df9a81503ebb0' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Prince-Philip-e1614604594665.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/Prince-Philip-e1614604594665.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Prince Philip</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SpaceX Starship lands upright, then explodes in latest test</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/spacex-starship-lands-upright-then-explodes-in-latest-test/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 02:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — SpaceX’s futuristic Starship looked like it aced a touchdown Wednesday, but then exploded on the landing pad with so much...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — SpaceX’s futuristic Starship looked like it aced a touchdown Wednesday, but then exploded on the landing pad with so much force that it was hurled into the air.</p>
<p>The failure occurred just minutes after SpaceX declared success. Two previous test flights crash-landed in fireballs.</p>
<p>The full-scale prototype of Elon Musk&#8217;s envisioned Mars ship soared more than 6 miles (10 kilometers) after lifting off from the southern tip of Texas on Wednesday. It descended horizontally over the Gulf of Mexico and then flipped upright just in time to land.</p>
<p>The shiny bullet-shaped rocketship remained intact this time at touchdown, prompting SpaceX commentator John Insprucker to declare, “third time’s a charm as the saying goes” before SpaceX ended its webcast of the test.</p>
<p>But then the Starship exploded and was tossed in the air, before slamming down into the ground in flames.</p>
<p>There was no immediate comment from SpaceX on what went wrong. But Musk looked on the bright side in a tweet: “Starship 10 landed in one piece! RIP SN10, honorable discharge.”</p>
<p>He added: “SpaceX team is doing great work! One day, the true measure of success will be that Starship flights are commonplace.”</p>
<p>Musk plans to use Starships to send people to the moon and Mars.</p>
<p>The last two prototypes reached a similarly high altitude in December and February, but slammed into the ground at Boca Chica, Texas, and exploded.</p>
<p>Each of these last three test flights lasted 6 1/2 minutes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875514</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-SpaceX.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6a26d702-f538-4ce6-ae32-5cbf8ba9fcdd/96d372b0-b02e-4c49-bf4c-7dac6e23fa49/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217324~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/6a26d702-f538-4ce6-ae32-5cbf8ba9fcdd/96d372b0-b02e-4c49-bf4c-7dac6e23fa49/main.mp4*~hmac=9aeb694b76c4fe35ff4410621e57ab071aa95464ad608d6666f0dec39f39a395' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-SpaceX.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-SpaceX.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030321 SpaceX</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joint effort leads to Tennessee law enforcement finding 150 missing children</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/joint-effort-leads-to-tennessee-law-enforcement-finding-150-missing-children/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE (CNN) &#8212; A joint operation between the U.S. Marshals Service, Tennessee Department of Children’s Services and the Tennessee Bureau of Investigation resulted in the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NASHVILLE (<a href="https://www.wsmv.com/news/tennessee/joint-effort-leads-to-agencies-finding-150-missing-children/article_65e8b1d8-7c40-11eb-a693-cfce00fed91b.html?block_id=994460" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CNN</a>) &#8212; A joint operation between the U.S. Marshals Service, Tennessee Department of Children’s Services and the Tennessee Bureau of Investigation resulted in the finding of 150 missing children across the state.</p>
<p>Planning for the effort, named Operation Volunteer Strong, began in fall 2020 with operation efforts launching on Jan. 4.</p>
<p>After identifying 240 missing children statewide, TBI intelligence analysts compiled information and potential leads on each, which designated law enforcement teams carefully pursued during two-week blitzes in each of Tennessee’s three grand regions.</p>
<p>U.S. Marshals said at least two of the missing children were identified as a possible human trafficking victim.</p>
<p>“Whatever we can do to help these children from falling into dangerous situations, we will do,” said David Jolley, U.S. Marshal for the Eastern District of Tennessee.</p>
<p>“I can’t imagine being a parent and not knowing where my child is, or can you imagine being that child, maybe feeling forgotten? I can’t imagine those circumstances,” said Denny King, U.S. Marshal for the Middle District of Tennessee.</p>
<p>King said one of the recovered children in Middle Tennessee was identified as a potential human trafficking victim, resulting in a still-active investigation.</p>
<p>King said one child was found who had been missing for 460 days.</p>
<p>“We can’t give up. Missing kids out there, we will continue to look for you,” said King.</p>
<p>Tyreece Miller, U.S. Marshall for the Western District of Tennessee, said one of the recovered children from there was also identified as a potential human trafficking victim, resulting in a still-active investigation by law enforcement in Mississippi and the FBI.</p>
<p>Miller said another child was recovered during an active kidnapping investigation in Memphis, resulting in the arrest of the suspect on multiple charges.</p>
<p>“We are grateful to be part of this effort, but our work is not done,” said Miller. “Our commitment to finding our missing children will not end.”</p>
<p>Tennessee Department of Children’s Services Commissioner Jennifer Nichols said 93 of the children found are DCS children, most of them girls.</p>
<p>“We are committed to providing the services these children deserve,” said Nichols. “The works is transformational. We cannot stop and there in nothing more worthwhile.</p>
<p>“Our mission ‘That guilt shall not escape, nor innocence suffer’ is more than a motto. It reminds us every day of what really matters,” said TBI Director David Rausch. “In this operation, it was the innocence of children who may need help or love, a new start or just someone safe to talk to. At TBI, we’re committed to playing a part in that kind of work for the long haul and look forward to continuing these types of operations in the future.</p>
<p>“It is critical for families and children to know that even though this operation has ended, we will continue to look for you.”</p>
<p>A look at the blitz in each of Tennessee’s grand divisions:</p>
<p>East Tennessee: Jan. 4-15</p>
<p>Authorities identified 86 missing children of which 56 were recovered, five of them in other states. Of the 56 children recovered, authorities located 27 of them in the weeks leading up to the operation, and three after it concluded. Law enforcement identified three of the recovered juveniles as potential human trafficking victims, resulting in a still-active TBI investigation. “The U.S. Marshals are committed to assisting state and local agencies with locating and recovering endangered missing children to help prevent their falling victim to crimes of violence and exploitation,” said Jolley. “We will use every resource at our disposal to help find these missing children.”</p>
<p>Middle Tennessee: Jan. 25-Feb. 5</p>
<p>Authorities identified 72 missing children, of which 42 were recovered. Of the 42 children recovered, authorities located 29 of them in the weeks leading up to the operation and 13 during the operation. Law enforcement identified one child as a potential human trafficking victim, resulting in a still-active TBI investigation. We can’t give up. We need the public, the media, and all law enforcement to not give up,” said King. “If you see something, or know something, say something. We cannot give up and stop searching for our most vulnerable and those who cannot help themselves.”</p>
<p>West Tennessee: Feb. 8-12 and Feb. 22-26</p>
<p>Authorities identified 82 missing children, of which 52 were recovered, three of them in other states. Of the 52 children recovered, authorities located 33 of them in the weeks leading up to the operation, 18 during the operation and one after it concluded. While searching for missing children, authorities located two adults with outstanding warrants. Law enforcement identified one of the recovered juveniles as a human trafficking victim, resulting in a still-active investigation by a Mississippi local law enforcement agency and FBI. Authorities safely recovered a child during an active kidnapping investigation, resulting in the arrest of the suspect. “I hope this operation changes the course for 150 young lives and leads them to the path of opportunities every child deserves,” said Miller. “Our efforts should also serve notice to those who prey on society’s most vulnerable that these children are not forgotten. Investigations will continue and the next knock at the door could be for you.”</p>
<p>The National Center for Missing and Exploited Children, based in Alexandria, VA, provided research and analytical support during the operation.</p>
<p>“Operation Volunteer Strong is a great example of how working together, we can find missing children and get them the help they need to move forward,” said John Clark, NCMEC’s President and Chief Executive Officer. “We’re thrilled to see so many missing children recovered in Tennessee and we thank all the agencies involved for their dedication to child protection.</p>
<p>The TBI serves as the clearinghouse for missing children in Tennessee. In this role, the agency provides support to local law enforcement agencies, raises awareness of missing children and prevention efforts, and administers high-profile efforts to locate missing children in dangerous situations through its Endangered Child Alert and AMBER Alert programs.</p>
<p>“Many people don’t realize this, but hundreds of children go missing in our state every month,” said TBI Director David Rausch. “From runaway that may leave their home out of desperation or despair, to those entangled in a custody battle, every single one of them deserves a fighting chance, and that’s why they also deserve our best work to help them.”</p>
<p>Most of the children recovered during the operation will receive services through the Tennessee Department of Children’s Services, which may include placements in foster homes, group homes or other specialized care.</p>
<p>“We are grateful that missing children have been recovered and are now receiving the services and treatment they need to stay safe and healthy,” said DCS Commissioner Jennifer Nichols. “This operation was truly a collaboration and it’s strengthened our relationship with our law enforcement partners. Working together, the agents, marshals and DCS case managers put in countless hours to track down leads and locate these missing children.”</p>
<p>Investigators ask, if you know anything about where a missing child might be located, that you give them a call.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875441</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/S167976075-e1614816386293.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/S167976075-e1614816386293.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/S167976075-e1614816386293.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Shelly Smitherman</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man who spent nearly 25 years in prison starts new career in cannabis industry</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/man-who-spent-nearly-25-years-in-prison-starts-new-career-in-cannabis-industry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 22:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FLINT, Mich. (CNN) &#8212; After spending more than two decades behind bars, the very drug that put him there is providing Michael Thompson with a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FLINT, Mich. (<a href="https://www.wnem.com/news/flint-man-who-spent-nearly-25-years-in-prison-starts-new-career-in-cannabis-industry/article_a813fc9e-7b9f-11eb-9226-739f6cf12ef6.html?block_id=994426" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CNN</a>) &#8212; After spending more than two decades behind bars, the very drug that put him there is providing Michael Thompson with a new, life-changing opportunity.</p>
<p>Thompson launched a new career on Tuesday, March 2 in the cannabis industry.</p>
<p>&#8220;Oh, it&#8217;s been like heaven. It&#8217;s been like heaven man, you know,&#8221; Thompson said.</p>
<p>Words are hard for Thompson to find when it comes to describing his freedom. CNN affiliate WNEM was there as Thompson was released from prison after 25 years in January because Gov. Gretchen Whitmer commuted his sentence.</p>
<p>March 2 was Thompson&#8217;s first day on the job for Ubaked Cannabis, a cultivation and processing facility in Burton. The company is offering Thompson a platform to talk about justice system reform.</p>
<p>&#8220;The owner here understands my cry to help them,” Thompson said. “So that&#8217;s what I&#8217;m here for.&#8221;</p>
<p>Thompson had been serving 25 years of a 40 to 60-year sentence for selling three pounds of marijuana and owning guns. His grandson, Michael, who also works for Ubaked, says that&#8217;s an injustice that plays out far too often.</p>
<p>&#8220;Nobody should&#8217;ve did that much time for no marijuana, nobody,&#8221; Thompson said.</p>
<p>Bob Dodge is the CEO for Ubaked Cannabis.</p>
<p>&#8220;Personally, I felt indebted that we are profiting from this industry after he spent 25 years in prison,&#8221; Dodge said.</p>
<p>Flint man serving up to 60 years for selling pot 24 years ago Dodge said Thompson isn&#8217;t allowed near the product, but he said Thompson&#8217;s position is a win-win for both Thompson and the company.</p>
<p>&#8220;We go to dispensaries and we do vendor days and that may be an opportunity for us to incorporate you and you know hire you as a brand ambassador and get your message out there,&#8221; Dodge said.</p>
<p>Thompson was quick to point out there are a lot of people in prison right now who are just like him. He says he&#8217;ll do everything he can to raise awareness that in many cases the punishment doesn&#8217;t fit the crime.</p>
<p>&#8220;The criminal justice system is broken and it needs to be fixed,&#8221; Thompson said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875405</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/S167957940.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/S167957940.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/S167957940.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">WNEM Michael Thompson</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SUV in crash where 13 died came through hole in border fence</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/suv-in-crash-where-13-died-came-through-hole-in-border-fence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 22:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOLTVILLE, Calif. (AP) — Thirteen people killed in one of the deadliest crashes involving migrants sneaking into the U.S. had entered California through a hole...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOLTVILLE, Calif. (AP) — Thirteen people killed in one of the deadliest crashes involving migrants sneaking into the U.S. had entered California through a hole cut into the border fence with Mexico in what was believed to be a larger smuggling operation, officials said Wednesday.</p>
<p>Surveillance video showed a Ford Expedition and Chevrolet Suburban drive through the opening early Tuesday, said Gregory Bovino, the Border Patrol&#8217;s El Centro sector chief.</p>
<p>The Suburban carried 19 people, and it caught fire for unknown reasons on a nearby interstate after entering the U.S. All escaped the vehicle and were taken into custody by Border Patrol agents.</p>
<p>The Expedition crammed with 25 people continued on, and a tractor-trailer struck it a short time later. Ten of the 13 killed in that crash have been identified as Mexican citizens.</p>
<p>The Border Patrol said its agents were not pursuing the vehicle before the wreck. The opening in the fence was about 30 miles (48 kilometers) east of the crash in the heart of California’s Imperial Valley, a major farming region now at the height of a harvest that provides much of the lettuce, onions, broccoli and winter vegetables to U.S. supermarkets.</p>
<p>It was made of steel bollards that were built before former President Donald Trump blanketed much of the border with taller barriers that go deeper into the ground. Photos show a panel of eight steel poles was lifted out and left on the ground in the desert next to an old tire and other debris.</p>
<p>“Human smugglers have proven time and again they have little regard for human life,” Bovino said. “Those who may be contemplating crossing the border illegally should pause to think of the dangers that all too often end in tragedy, tragedies our Border Patrol Agents and first responders are unfortunately very familiar with.”</p>
<p>The breach occurred in a busy area for illegal crossings near the Imperial Sand Dunes where migrants often climb over an aging barrier and wait for drivers to pick them up, hoping to avoid the scrutiny of Border Patrol agents at checkpoints on highways leading to Los Angeles, San Diego and Phoenix.</p>
<p>A pandemic-related measure that allows the Border Patrol to expel people without an opportunity to seek asylum potentially leads some to try to evade authorities instead of surrendering, sometimes with fatal consequences. The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention introduced expulsion powers nearly a year ago under Trump, and the Biden administration has signaled no plans to lift them anytime soon.</p>
<p>The cause of Tuesday&#8217;s collision wasn&#8217;t yet known, authorities said. The Expedition is built to hold eight people safely, but smugglers are known to pack people into vehicles in extremely unsafe conditions to maximize their profits.</p>
<p>Seats in the SUV had been removed except for those for the driver and front passenger, said Omar Watson, chief of the California Highway Patrol’s border division.</p>
<p>The crash happened in an area that became a major route for illegal border crossings in the late 1990s after heightened enforcement in San Diego pushed migrants to more remote areas.</p>
<p>Barely a mile from the crash, there is a cemetery with rows of unmarked bricks that is a burial ground for migrants who died crossing the border.</p>
<p>In 2001, John Hunter founded Water Station, a volunteer group that leaves jugs of water in giant plastic drums for dehydrated migrants.</p>
<p>“I was trying to figure out how to stop the deaths,” said Hunter, whose brother Duncan strongly advocated for border wall construction as a congressman.</p>
<p>Illegal crossings in the area fell sharply in the mid-2000s but the area has remained a draw for migrants and was a priority for wall construction under Trump. His administration&#8217;s first wall project was in Calexico.</p>
<p>When police arrived Tuesday at the crash site about 125 miles (200 kilometers) east of San Diego, some passengers were trying to crawl out of the crumpled SUV. Others were wandering around the nearby fields. The big rig’s front end was pushed into the SUV’s left side and two empty trailers were jackknifed behind it.</p>
<p>The men and women in the SUV ranged in age from 15 to 53, and those who survived had injuries that were minor to severe, including fractures and head trauma, officials said. The driver was from Mexicali, Mexico, just across the border, and was among those killed.</p>
<p>The 68-year-old driver of the big rig, who is from the nearby California community of El Centro, suffered moderate injuries.</p>
<p>The crash occurred around 6:15 a.m. under a clear, sunny sky at an intersection just outside the community of Holtville, about 11 miles (18 kilometers) north of the border. Authorities said the tractor-trailer was heading north on a highway when the SUV pulled in front of it from a road with a stop sign.</p>
<p>It’s not clear if the SUV ran the stop sign or had stopped before entering the highway. How fast both vehicles were going also wasn&#8217;t yet known.</p>
<p>A 1997 Ford Expedition can carry a maximum payload of 2,000 pounds. If it had 25 people inside, that would easily exceed the payload limit, taxing the brakes and making it tougher to steer the vehicle, said Frank Borris, former head of the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration’s Office of Defects Investigation.</p>
<p>“You’re going to have extended stopping distances, delayed reactions to steering inputs and potential overreaction to any type of high-speed lane change,” said Borris, who now runs a safety consulting business.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875387</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-California-SUV-ax.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f46401a0-af3c-4a12-a0db-a6e0e65474d6/39321ee9-b2e9-4415-b885-fea5e0a7d928/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217384~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/f46401a0-af3c-4a12-a0db-a6e0e65474d6/39321ee9-b2e9-4415-b885-fea5e0a7d928/main.mp4*~hmac=4764074948e050542976521755fddfd8660b1cec24d0c815341df9a0b977c204' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-California-SUV-ax.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-California-SUV-ax.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030321 California SUV ax</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Friends find out they&#8217;re biological sisters years after they met working at the same restaurant</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/friends-find-out-theyre-biological-sisters-years-after-they-met-working-at-the-same-restaurant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 21:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; It started as a joke. Cassandra Madison, 32, and Julia Tinetti, 31, began telling people they were sisters not long after they met...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; It started as a joke.</p>
<p>Cassandra Madison, 32, and Julia Tinetti, 31, began telling people they were sisters not long after they met in 2013 while working at The Russian Lady restaurant in New Haven, Connecticut, but a recent DNA test confirmed that they are actually biological sisters.</p>
<p>The two women had a lot in common &#8212; they were both adopted from the Dominican Republic as babies, they looked enough alike that customers and coworkers mixed them up all the time and they each had Dominican flag tattoos.</p>
<p>The tattoos got them talking and they became fast friends.</p>
<p>&#8220;We hit it off right away. There was no trying to force a friendship or anything,&#8221; Madison told CNN. &#8220;Our personalities are very similar, so it was very easy for us to just start hanging out.&#8221;</p>
<p>They really leaned in to the sisterhood gag and would sometimes wear matching clothes to work.</p>
<p>&#8220;We had an event that we went to that we dressed alike &#8212; our socks matched, our sneakers matched, our sunglasses matched our shorts were black &#8212; she made us tank tops that said that she was the big sister and I was the little sister,&#8221; Tinetti said. &#8220;We kind of just went with it like as a joke. It was not serious at all.&#8221;</p>
<p>At one point, they looked through their adoption paperwork to see if they might really be sisters, but the forms said they had different mothers who lived hours away from each other.</p>
<p>&#8220;So we said, &#8216;Okay, never mind, forget it, then we&#8217;re not,&#8217; and we just moved on with our lives,&#8221; Madison said. &#8220;But we still played into us being sisters even though we knew that we weren&#8217;t. Well, we thought we weren&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>Madison moved to Virginia Beach, Virginia, in 2015 and the pair mostly only kept in touch over Facebook.</p>
<p>Madison had grown up knowing that her biological parents had given her up for adoption because they couldn&#8217;t afford to care for her.</p>
<p>She always wanted to meet them and, in 2018, her adoptive mom gave her a DNA test kit for Christmas.</p>
<h3>Seven siblings in the Dominican Republic</h3>
<p>Madison thought she&#8217;d just learn more about where her ancestors came from, but it also turned up a cousin, who also lived in Connecticut and knew her dad.</p>
<p>Her biological mom died in 2015, but Madison has been to the Dominican Republic to meet her dad and family members. They welcomed her at the airport wearing shirts with her picture on them.</p>
<p>There were seven other children in the family.</p>
<p>Madison and Tinetti reconnected last year and realized that something seemed off about their paperwork.</p>
<p>Tinetti&#8217;s best friend, Molly, was adopted from the Dominican Republic on the same day and their moms stayed in touch over the years. Molly&#8217;s adoption papers said that she and Madison had the same mothers, but her DNA results showed that they were distant cousins.</p>
<p>Madison talked to her father about it and he told her that they had given another daughter up for adoption.</p>
<p>&#8220;And I&#8217;m like, &#8216;Why would you not tell me this?&#8217; And he&#8217;s just like &#8216;I&#8217;m sorry. It was just a very difficult time in our lives and your mom and I, we don&#8217;t like to talk about it,'&#8221; Madison said.</p>
<p>Madison drove from Virginia to Connecticut to get Tinetti to take a DNA test.</p>
<p>Tinetti agreed to take the test even though she had never had any interest in learning about her biological family.</p>
<p>&#8220;I had a great family growing up, I got a good education, I didn&#8217;t feel like I was missing anything in my life,&#8221; Tinetti said. &#8220;I was happy with the life that I had. I didn&#8217;t feel the need to do it.&#8221;</p>
<h3>&#8216;This is it&#8217;</h3>
<p>Tinetti got the test results back in late January.</p>
<p>&#8220;I was like, &#8216;This is it,&#8217; and I waited for probably like 10 minutes before I even opened it, because I was trying to prepare myself for what was going to be there,&#8221; Tinetti said.</p>
<p>Both women said they&#8217;d tried not to get their hopes up, but they knew they would have been devastated if they had not turned out to be biological sisters.</p>
<p>Madison said she talks to her dad and siblings every day and that she and Tinetti have picked up right where they left off.</p>
<p>Tinetti said she&#8217;s had video chats with her biological father and her siblings and hopes to go to the Dominican Republic to meet them in person.</p>
<p>She said it was &#8220;quite shocking&#8221; to see them because they look so much alike.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was like seeing myself in these people,&#8221; she said. &#8220;It&#8217;s like, &#8216;Okay, well, now I know where I come from,&#8217; you know what I mean? It has always been a mystery for me.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875328</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c37c972b04736367fceb2c286db3a3b1-h_1289bc616dd18a79ab8869c806339a96.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c37c972b04736367fceb2c286db3a3b1-h_1289bc616dd18a79ab8869c806339a96.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_c37c972b04736367fceb2c286db3a3b1-h_1289bc616dd18a79ab8869c806339a96.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_c37c972b04736367fceb2c286db3a3b1-h_1289bc616dd18a79ab8869c806339a96</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Hurricanes star Kellen Winslow II gets 14 years for rapes</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/former-hurricanes-star-kellen-winslow-ii-gets-14-years-for-rapes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Chalvire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 20:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875292</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO (AP) — Former NFL player Kellen Winslow II was sentenced Wednesday to 14 years in prison for multiple rapes and other sexual offenses...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAN DIEGO (AP) — Former NFL player Kellen Winslow II was sentenced Wednesday to 14 years in prison for multiple rapes and other sexual offenses against five women in Southern California, including one who was homeless when he attacked her in 2018.</p>
<p>The 37-year-old son of San Diego Chargers Hall of Fame receiver Kellen Winslow appeared via videoconference at the hearing in San Diego Superior Court in Vista, a city north of San Diego. He declined to comment before his sentence, saying his lawyers had advised him not to speak.</p>
<p>San Diego County Superior Court Judge Blaine Bowman said Winslow can only be described with “two words and that is sexual predator.&#8221; He said he selected women who were vulnerable because of their age or their living situation with the idea that “hopefully he would get away with it in his mind.&#8221;</p>
<p>Winslow was once the highest-paid tight end in the league, earning more than $40 million over his 10 seasons before he left in 2013.</p>
<p>The 14-year-sentence was the maximum allowed under a plea deal. He was convicted of forcible rape, rape of an unconscious person, assault with intent to commit rape, indecent exposure, and lewd conduct in public.</p>
<p>The forcible rape involved a woman who was homeless in his home town of Encinitas, a beach community north of San Diego.</p>
<p>She was among four of the women who gave statements Wednesday, including one victim who had the prosecutor read hers. All described suffering years after their attacks from fear and emotional trauma.</p>
<p>The woman who was homeless called into the hearing via video conference from the San Diego County District Attorney&#8217;s office, where she was watching the proceedings with another victim.</p>
<p>She said since she was raped she has had trouble raising her head and walking, and she feels afraid constantly, checking under beds and in closets, and cannot be alone.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s affecting my life every day and every night,&#8221; she said. “I don’t ever feel safe inside or outside. You brought so much damage to my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>Winslow&#8217;s attorney Marc Carlos said Winslow suffered from head trauma from the many blows to his head playing football, which can only explain why he “went off the rails&#8221; going from a star athlete to a convicted sexual predator. He said his client has accepted responsibility and intends to get help.</p>
<p>Winslow was convicted of forcible rape and two misdemeanors — indecent exposure and a lewd act in public — after a trial in June 2019.</p>
<p>But that jury failed to agree on other charges, including the alleged 2018 rape of a 54-year-old hitchhiker, and the 2003 rape of an unconscious 17-year-old high school senior who went to a party with him when he was 19.</p>
<p>Before he was retried on those charges, he pleaded guilty to raping the teen and sexual battery of the hitchhiker. Those pleas spared him the possibility of life in prison.</p>
<p>The father of two, whose wife filed for divorce after he was convicted, had faced up to 18 years in prison for all the charges. But both sides agreed to reduce the sexual battery charge to assault with intent to commit rape last month. That reduced the maximum sentence to 14 years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875292</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ap_19165536839664.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ap_19165536839664.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ap_19165536839664.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Kellen Winslow Jr Rape Case</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scientists have taken the first ever picture of a glow-in-the-dark shark</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/scientists-have-taken-the-first-ever-picture-of-a-glow-in-the-dark-shark/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 18:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Scientists have taken the first ever photos of a glow-in-the-dark shark producing its own light. The kitefin shark, Dalatias licha, is the world&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Scientists have taken the first ever photos of a glow-in-the-dark shark producing its own light.</p>
<p>The kitefin shark, Dalatias licha, is the world&#8217;s largest known bioluminescent vertebrate, growing to nearly six feet in length.</p>
<p>It was found in an area of ocean known as Chatham Rise, off the east coast of New Zealand&#8217;s South Island, according to a study published Tuesday by researchers from the Catholic University of Louvain, Belgium and the National Institute of Water and Atmospheric Research (NIWA) in New Zealand.</p>
<p>Bioluminescence refers to the production of visible light by living organisms through a biochemical reaction. Some 57 of the 540 known shark species are thought to be capable of producing light, study co-author Jérôme Mallefet, head of the marine biology laboratory at UCLouvain, told CNN on Wednesday.</p>
<p>While specimens had previously shown that the kitefin shark should be capable of producing light, they are &#8220;really difficult to observe,&#8221; as they live between 200 and 900 meters (656-2,953 feet) below the ocean&#8217;s surface, Mallefet said.</p>
<p>Bioluminescence was also documented in two other species of deepwater shark, Etmopterus lucifer (the blackbelly lanternshark) and Etmopterus granulosus (southern lanternshark), as part of the research.</p>
<p>Mallefet noticed that the sharks had been caught accidentally during NIWA&#8217;s trawling surveys, which are used to measure fish stocks, and contacted the organization.</p>
<p>He was invited to join a survey trip in January 2020 and spent 30 days on board the boat, capturing multiple sharks.</p>
<p>&#8220;I was just like a kid at the bottom of a Christmas tree,&#8221; said Mallefet, describing how he managed to take a picture of a kitefin shark in a bucket in a dark room on the ship.</p>
<p>The deep sea below 200 meters (656 feet) is described as the twilight zone. Many people mistakenly believe there is no light visible there, but there is some light that the sharks find useful, Mallefet said.</p>
<p>&#8220;They use light to disappear,&#8221; he said, explaining how bioluminescence can render the sharks invisible against the faint glow from the ocean&#8217;s surface.</p>
<p>This protects the sharks from predators swimming below them, and also makes it easier for them to hunt prey, Mallefet said.</p>
<p>&#8220;We know that&#8217;s the case for Dalatias licha,&#8221; he said, as the remains of smaller sharks were found inside the bellies of some specimens despite the fact that the species is the slowest swimming shark in the world.</p>
<p>The luminous sharks haven&#8217;t given up all of their secrets, however, including why their dorsal fin glows.</p>
<p>Further research is needed to work out whether this could be used for signaling, Mallefet said, adding: &#8220;There are still question marks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mallefet told CNN he would like to study the dorsal fin in greater detail on future trips to the area, as well as looking into what the sharks eat and whether they are eaten.</p>
<p>The aim is to find out more about the deep sea, which remains mysterious despite the fact that it&#8217;s the most common environment on Earth, in order to make people think more about preserving it, he said.</p>
<p>&#8220;I fear that we have done a lot of mistakes throwing stuff in the sea,&#8221; said Mallefet. &#8220;I fear what will happen for the next generations.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875221</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_aec2b58ef9ca64d028e8b76f44fb68a2-h_6d5af07b2c110e747590b2063fb1a40c.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/245553ea-9d76-43b0-96f0-5df2daff62bd/2007ee39-37c8-4216-91da-dd317b41bcc1/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219199~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/245553ea-9d76-43b0-96f0-5df2daff62bd/2007ee39-37c8-4216-91da-dd317b41bcc1/main.mp4*~hmac=7a7ee7665f28ac26fbebfe3f49067bf7f4bbc63c8b21a4b3f60798217bcd705a' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_aec2b58ef9ca64d028e8b76f44fb68a2-h_6d5af07b2c110e747590b2063fb1a40c.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_aec2b58ef9ca64d028e8b76f44fb68a2-h_6d5af07b2c110e747590b2063fb1a40c.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_aec2b58ef9ca64d028e8b76f44fb68a2-h_6d5af07b2c110e747590b2063fb1a40c</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strong earthquake shakes central Greece, felt in Balkans</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/strong-earthquake-shakes-central-greece-felt-in-balkans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATHENS, Greece (AP) — An earthquake with a preliminary magnitude of at least 6.0 struck central Greece Wednesday and was also felt in neighboring Albania...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATHENS, Greece (AP) — An earthquake with a preliminary magnitude of at least 6.0 struck central Greece Wednesday and was also felt in neighboring Albania and North Macedonia, and as far as Kosovo and Montenegro.</p>
<p>One man was injured by falling debris but there were no other immediate reports of serious injury. Local officials reported structural damage, mainly to old houses and buildings that saw walls collapse or crack.</p>
<p>The midday quake sent thousands of people rushing out of homes and office buildings into the streets in Larissa and Tyrnavos, the closest towns to the epicenter, which was 22 kilometers (14 miles) west-northwest of Larissa. Numerous aftershocks hit the area, the most powerful having a preliminary magnitude of over 5.0.</p>
<p>The quake struck at 12:16 p.m. (1015 GMT), according to the Athens Geodynamic Institute which put the preliminary magnitude at 6.0.</p>
<p>The United States Geological Survey and Global Seismic Monitor Geofon put the preliminary magnitude at 6.3, but it is common for magnitude estimates to vary soon after a quake.</p>
<p>Turkish Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu phoned his Greek counterpart, Nikos Dendias, to convey solidarity and offer assistance if needed, according to officials from the two neighboring countries — which are longtime regional rivals.</p>
<p>In Athens, seismologist Vassilis Karastathis told reporters that the quake originated in a fault line in the area that has historically not produced temblors of much larger magnitude than Wednesday&#8217;s. He said the post-quake activity appeared normal so far but experts were monitoring the situation.</p>
<p>“The earthquake had an estimated depth of just 8 kilometers (5 miles) and that was one of the reasons why it was felt so strongly in the region,” said Karastathis, who is the deputy director of the Athens Geodynamic Institute.</p>
<p>Nikos Gatsas, mayor of the town of Elassona which lies north of the epicenter, told Greece&#8217;s state broadcaster ERT that walls of old houses had collapsed in nearby villages, and that one village school had sustained damage. All pupils had been evacuated from the building and there were no injuries.</p>
<p>The fire department said it had received reports of damage to one home and school, while the fire service and police were patrolling the area. All local fire departments were put on alert.</p>
<p>The head of the National Defense General Staff and other civil defense, fire department and political officials were heading to the area.</p>
<p>Greece lies in a highly seismically active region. The vast majority of earthquakes cause no damage or injuries.</p>
<p>Last October, an earthquake that struck the eastern Greek Aegean island of Samos and the nearby Turkish coast killed two high school students on Samos and at least 75 people in Turkey. In 1999, an earthquake near Athens killed 143 people.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875218</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/earthquake-in-greece.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3bf20fc1-74b6-4d34-b09d-1ce457262502/ccf97b01-e61c-4e11-aee2-df1f16d4e600/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219207~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3bf20fc1-74b6-4d34-b09d-1ce457262502/ccf97b01-e61c-4e11-aee2-df1f16d4e600/main.mp4*~hmac=745e8f500cdad1315a48b233426c906f772a111ec52765a1abfef0200364971f' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/earthquake-in-greece.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/earthquake-in-greece.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">earthquake in greece</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Law enforcement on alert after plot warning at US Capitol</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/politics/law-enforcement-on-alert-after-plot-warning-at-us-capitol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 17:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875213</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Law enforcement was on high alert Thursday around the U.S. Capitol after authorities said intelligence had uncovered a “possible plot” by a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WASHINGTON (AP) — Law enforcement was on high alert Thursday around the U.S. Capitol after authorities said intelligence had uncovered a “possible plot” by a militia group to storm the iconic building again. The alert came two months after Donald Trump supporters smashed through windows and doors to try to stop Congress from certifying now-President Joe Biden&#8217;s victory.</p>
<p>The threat appeared to be connected to a far-right conspiracy theory, mainly promoted by supporters of QAnon, that former President Trump would rise again to power on March 4 and that thousands would come to Washington to try to remove Democrats from office. March 4 was the original presidential inauguration day until 1933, when it was moved to Jan. 20.</p>
<p>There were no signs of disturbance Thursday at the heavily secured building, with Capitol Police and National Guardsmen on duty and a large fence around the perimeter that was put in place after the Jan. 6 riot. The <a href="https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-politics-riots-c1b4973dce1b48c17c3dca7f5fb6e5fb">Pentagon is reviewing a request to extend the Guard deployment 60 days</a> beyond its current expiration date of March 12.</p>
<p>Online chatter identified by authorities included discussions among members of the Three Percenters, an anti-government militia group, concerning possible plots against the Capitol on Thursday, according to two law enforcement officials who were not authorized to speak publicly and spoke on condition of anonymity. Members of the Three Percenters <a href="https://apnews.com/article/white-supremacy-threats-capitol-riots-2d4ba4d1a3d55197489d773b3e0b0f32">were among the extremists who stormed</a> the Capitol on Jan. 6.</p>
<p>The threat came as the Capitol police and other law enforcement agencies were taking criticism from Congress in contentious hearings this week on their <a href="https://apnews.com/hub/capitol-siege">handling of the Jan. 6 riot. </a>Police <a href="https://apnews.com/article/riots-police-michael-pence-capitol-siege-0dfa12d17208295506ca094101e1f838">were ill-prepared</a> for the mass of Trump supporters, some in tactical gear and armed, and it took hours for National Guard reinforcements to come. By then, rioters had broken into the building and they roamed the halls for hours, stalling Congress&#8217; certification effort temporarily and sending lawmakers into hiding.</p>
<p>Lawmakers, congressional staffers and law enforcement officials are still on edge after the attack on Jan. 6, even as security around the Capitol remains at an unprecedented level.</p>
<p>The U.S. House wrapped up its work for the week Wednesday night, but the U.S. Senate still had a busy day scheduled for Thursday with votes into the evening. Police beefed up their presence in and around the Capitol. About 5,200 National Guard members remain in D.C., the remainder of the roughly 26,000 who were brought in for President Biden&#8217;s inauguration in January, which went off with no problems.</p>
<p>Rep. Michael McCaul, R-Texas, the former chairman of the House Homeland Security Committee and among those briefed about the new threat, said lawmakers were braced.</p>
<p>“I think we’ll see some violence here,” he said in an interview.</p>
<p>But unlike on Jan. 6, the Capitol is now fortified against intrusions. “We have the razor wire, we have the National Guard. We didn’t have that January 6. So I feel very confident in the security,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Initially it seemed as though the online chatter did not rise to the level of serious concern; an advisory sent earlier this week to members of Congress by Timothy Blodgett, the acting House sergeant-at-arms, said the Capitol Police had “no indication that groups will travel to Washington, D.C., to protest or commit acts of violence.”</p>
<p>But that advisory was updated in a note to lawmakers Wednesday morning. Blodgett wrote that the Capitol Police had received “new and concerning information and intelligence indicating additional interest in the Capitol for the dates of March 4th – 6th by a militia group.”</p>
<p>Acting Capitol Police Chief Yogananda Pittman said during House testimony Wednesday that her investigators had collected “some concerning intelligence,” but declined to provide any details publicly, saying that it was “law enforcement sensitive” and that she would provide a private briefing for the subcommittee members.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, federal agents found no significant increases in the number of hotel rooms being rented in Washington, or in flights to the area, car rental reservations or buses being chartered, a person familiar with the matter told The Associated Press. The person could not publicly discuss details of the security planning and spoke on the condition of anonymity.</p>
<p>The FBI and Department of Homeland Security also sent a joint intelligence bulletin to local law enforcement officials Tuesday that said a group of militia extremists had discussed trying to take control of the Capitol on March 4 and encouraging thousands of people to come to D.C. to try to remove Democrats from power.</p>
<p>But there has been a noticeable decline in online activity on some social media platforms surrounding efforts on March 4, and there was already considerably less online chatter than during the lead-up to Jan. 6, a day that Trump repeatedly had promoted for a his rally and encouraged thousands to come to the nation&#8217;s capital.</p>
<p>Also, <a href="https://apnews.com/article/9a5539af34b15338bb5c4923907eeb67">thousands of accounts </a>that promoted the Jan. 6 event that led to a violent storming of the U.S. Capitol have since been suspended by major tech companies like Facebook and Twitter, making it far more difficult for groups to organize a repeat of the mass gathering.</p>
<p>So far, about <a href="https://apnews.com/article/capitol-riots-extremist-rhetoric-a5db204fa5b07ffca694a8d96323ae15">300 people have been charged </a>with federal crimes for their roles in the riot. Five people, including a Capitol Police officer, died.</p>
<p>Since his defeat, <a href="https://apnews.com/article/conspiracy-theories-state-elections-misinformation-elections-voting-d1a8f797a03ffcd88972b9634b56a690">Trump has been promoting lies that the election was stolen</a> from him through mass voter fraud, even though such claims have been rejected by judges, Republican state officials and Trump’s own administration. He was impeached by the House after the Jan. 6 riot on a c<a href="https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-riots-acquittals-impeachments-6fb642f97be5f2bd202e8bc002d6a167">harge of incitement of insurrection</a> but was acquitted by the Senate.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875213</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022221-QAnon.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ba36f4a2-a291-47f7-80b3-05e5d49b8c07/b11dc425-d06b-49d5-add4-210f7aa875b4/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219370~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/ba36f4a2-a291-47f7-80b3-05e5d49b8c07/b11dc425-d06b-49d5-add4-210f7aa875b4/main.mp4*~hmac=ed1d8ed51c4845f2a3372cfd761b969c90181ed235a7bc83b5adcecb5befd2b4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022221-QAnon.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/022221-QAnon.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">022221 QAnon</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Volvo to go fully electric by 2030</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/volvo-to-go-fully-electric-by-2030/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 15:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; By the end of the decade, the only Volvo you&#8217;ll be able to purchase will be electric. And you&#8217;ll only be able to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; By the end of the decade, the only Volvo you&#8217;ll be able to purchase will be electric. And you&#8217;ll only be able to buy it online.</p>
<p>The Chinese-owned carmaker announced plans on Tuesday to stop selling cars that run on fossil fuels by 2030, part of an accelerating trend within the industry to respond to pressure to tackle the climate crisis. It also said that its new electric vehicles will only be sold online.</p>
<p>The Swedish brand said that as part of the transition, it wants half of its sales in 2025 to be electric cars, and the other half hybrids. That means it will stop selling vehicles powered solely by gasoline or diesel just four years from now.</p>
<p>The targets are aggressive for a company that has only brought one fully electric vehicle, the XC40 Recharge, to market. But they reflect a growing consensus that carmakers cannot delay the switch to electric vehicles without losing customers and angering regulators.</p>
<p>&#8220;There is no long-term future for cars with an internal combustion engine,&#8221; Volvo chief technology officer Henrik Green said in a statement. The transition to selling only electric cars will allow Volvo &#8220;to meet the expectations of our customers and be a part of the solution when it comes to fighting climate change,&#8221; he added.</p>
<p>Volvo also unveiled a new small electric SUV, the C40 Recharge. The C40 is largely the same as the XC40, but with a more tapered roofline and some changes to the front headlights and &#8220;grille&#8221; area.</p>
<p>Volvo said it will invest heavily in online sales and &#8220;radically reduce&#8221; the complexity of its product offerings. Pricing will be transparent, it said. The strategy is similar to the one used by electric car market leader Tesla, which only sells online. Volvo already sells the XC40 Recharge electric SUV online, and it plans to sell future electric models online only. Dealers will still handle final delivery, accessories and service.</p>
<p>The announcements come less than a week after Volvo&#8217;s owner, Geely, scrapped plans to merge the carmakers. China&#8217;s largest independent automaker said the two companies will keep their independent corporate structures, though they will partner on electric and autonomous driving technology.</p>
<p>Other carmakers have announced plans in recent months to accelerate their transition to electric vehicles. Ford said in February that it plan to sell only electric passenger cars in Europe by 2030. General Motors recently announced it is aiming to sell only emission-free vehicles by 2035.</p>
<p>Much of the action is happening in Volvo&#8217;s home market. Europe has imposed aggressive targets to reduce greenhouse gas emissions from vehicles, and carmakers face huge potential fines if they do not comply. That has helped the continent pace ahead of the United States on adoption of electric vehicles.</p>
<p>German automaker Volkswagen, which announced an alliance with Ford in 2019, is the leader in electric vehicle sales in Europe. Tesla is building its first European factory outside of Berlin, which is due to open later this year.</p>
<p>Electric vehicles are expected eventually to be cheaper to produce than traditional gasoline-powered cars, thanks to fewer moving parts and thus less need for labor to assemble them.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875062</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_3e633aaf748fddb4eadbd2f415e4e26d-h_8ae0f6c17ee9d23bf624de1da21ad2ba.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4fb63297-825c-4636-b843-fd1512cbeeb4/ebe05de3-bfdb-4ace-ae2e-dd001cca6f4b/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217289~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4fb63297-825c-4636-b843-fd1512cbeeb4/ebe05de3-bfdb-4ace-ae2e-dd001cca6f4b/main.mp4*~hmac=8a58135f2e377690707edbf6cfd75ac6262935f65a9ce469dfd1320f0dec04aa' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_3e633aaf748fddb4eadbd2f415e4e26d-h_8ae0f6c17ee9d23bf624de1da21ad2ba.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_3e633aaf748fddb4eadbd2f415e4e26d-h_8ae0f6c17ee9d23bf624de1da21ad2ba.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Volvo Unveils The First Electric XC40 Recharge SUV</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Instacart doubles its valuation for the second time since pandemic began</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/instacart-doubles-its-valuation-for-the-second-time-since-pandemic-began/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 15:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; For the second time since the pandemic began, Instacart has doubled its valuation as a privately-held startup. The on-demand grocery delivery service said...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; For the second time since the pandemic began, Instacart has doubled its valuation as a privately-held startup.</p>
<p>The on-demand grocery delivery service said Tuesday that it is now worth $39 billion after raising $265 million in financing from some of its existing investors.</p>
<p>Instacart was previously valued at $17.7 billion in October after raising another $200 million in financing, up from its nearly $14 billion valuation in June. Prior to the pandemic, Instacart had been valued at just shy of $8 billion.</p>
<p>The company has raised $2.5 billion to date.</p>
<p>&#8220;Today&#8217;s fundraising reflects the strength of Instacart&#8217;s business, the growth our teams have delivered and the incredible opportunity ahead,&#8221; said Nick Giovanni, Instacart&#8217;s chief financial officer, in a statement. &#8220;This past year ushered in a new normal, changing the way people shop for groceries and goods.&#8221;</p>
<p>Giovanni, the former head of the global technology, media and telecom Group at Goldman Sachs, joined Instacart in late January as the company is reportedly making moves to go public. Last week, the company added two new board members, another possible sign it is preparing for a public offering.</p>
<p>After years of working to build momentum, Instacart and other food delivery services have found their moment during the pandemic as households shied away from going to stores. Since March, Instacart has added hundreds of thousands of new contract workers &#8212; who shop and deliver groceries &#8212; and raised hundreds of millions in new financing.</p>
<p>But as the company has grown, it has also had tensions with some of its workers over safety and pay. As CNN Business previously reported, Instacart is cutting more than 1,800 in-store shoppers, who are part-time employees of the company, as a result of changes in how it works with partners. Among those impacted is a small group of workers at an Illinois-based Kroger-owned Mariano&#8217;s store who had voted to unionize last year.</p>
<p>The company largely relies on contract workers who shop and deliver for the company. Along with DoorDash, Uber, and Lyft, Instacart has had to defend its business model of treating these workers as independent contractors, rather than employees who would be entitled to traditional labor protections and benefits under the law.</p>
<p>Instacart said it plans to use the new funding to further fuel growth, including increasing its corporate headcount of 2,000 people by 50% and supporting certain areas of its business, including its marketplace, and its enterprise offering, as well as its advertising function, which allows brands to reach customers.</p>
<p>Instacart partners with more than 600 retailers in North America, including Aldi, Costco, Kroger and Wegmans. More recently, the company has struck deals with Big Lots, Staples, and Walgreens on same-day delivery, giving consumers alternatives to Amazon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875059</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_d73d230fe02bdcd86781d18ebd7afb3f-h_646f67aee21516f6220adfbd01988efa.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4d63706e-09a1-4776-9923-88f2c92d88b8/0b541ed5-e9f7-45a4-a3a3-0abe11199287/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219196~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4d63706e-09a1-4776-9923-88f2c92d88b8/0b541ed5-e9f7-45a4-a3a3-0abe11199287/main.mp4*~hmac=e810a529ae78e492961fca92bda338b0dbc7e00e461d8b3b2cafca32c891f052' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_d73d230fe02bdcd86781d18ebd7afb3f-h_646f67aee21516f6220adfbd01988efa.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_d73d230fe02bdcd86781d18ebd7afb3f-h_646f67aee21516f6220adfbd01988efa.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Instacart Workers Deliver Goods To Homes During Pandemic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon alters app logo after comparisons to Hitler mustache</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/amazon-alters-app-logo-after-comparisons-to-hitler-mustache/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 15:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Amazon has quietly changed the design of its new app icon, replacing the blue ribbon on top that drew some unfavorable comparisons. Users of the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/01/business/amazon-discrimination-lawsuit/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a> has quietly changed the design of its new app icon, replacing the blue ribbon on top that drew some unfavorable comparisons.</p>
<p>Users of the Amazon Shopping app will now see a <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/10/13/tech/amazon-box-ar-app/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">brown box that resembles a parcel</a> with a blue strip that looks like packaging tape above the company&#8217;s signature arrow in the shape of a smile.</p>
<p>Amazon introduced the initial new icon in a handful of international markets in late January, but has now changed the design of the blue tape after some said it resembled a toothbrush-style mustache, similar to the one worn by Adolf Hitler.</p>
<p>&#8220;I completely missed that amazon quietly tweaked its new icon to make it look&#8230; less like hitler,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/alexhern/status/1366396140116131842" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote Alex Hern,</a> a technology editor for the Guardian, on Twitter.</p>
<p>The new icon, the first design change in more than five years, <a href="https://twitter.com/avstorm/status/1353959772584816642" target="_blank" rel="noopener">replaces the shopping cart</a> and ditches the word &#8220;Amazon,&#8221; but displays the company&#8217;s smiling arrow logo more prominently. The blue tape looks like it&#8217;s being torn off, as if opening the package.</p>
<p>&#8220;We designed the new icon to spark anticipation, excitement, and joy when customers start their shopping journey on their phone, just as they do when they see our boxes on their door step,&#8221; an Amazon spokesperson said. The app icon was tweaked based on user feedback.</p>
<p>Only iOS users in the United Kingdom, Spain, Italy and Netherlands saw the Hitler-esque logo over the past few weeks. The updated logo rolled out worldwide for iOS users last week. Android users will see the new logo beginning this week.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875039</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_be839da16a440f7aceb9b033e6c3aef1-h_ef4444aa08363da2f0faf7716c4b3356.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0538bc8e-6136-4c98-8803-0daf8377bd7b/415ebe1d-f234-4792-9692-3f2b5c6e232f/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217292~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0538bc8e-6136-4c98-8803-0daf8377bd7b/415ebe1d-f234-4792-9692-3f2b5c6e232f/main.mp4*~hmac=44cfbfd986933deaf7bb95e60e2e57ee4210c4365f5a0e34ef522db1b6b01f5b' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_be839da16a440f7aceb9b033e6c3aef1-h_ef4444aa08363da2f0faf7716c4b3356.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_be839da16a440f7aceb9b033e6c3aef1-h_ef4444aa08363da2f0faf7716c4b3356.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">hypatia-h_be839da16a440f7aceb9b033e6c3aef1-h_ef4444aa08363da2f0faf7716c4b3356</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Virginia Commonwealth University fraternity has been suspended after the death of a 19-year-old student</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/a-virginia-commonwealth-university-fraternity-has-been-suspended-after-the-death-of-a-19-year-old-student/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 13:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN) &#8212; Virginia Commonwealth University has suspended a fraternity and announced a review of all Greek life after a student was found dead at an...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN) &#8212; Virginia Commonwealth University has suspended a fraternity and announced a review of all Greek life after a student was found dead at an off-campus house on Saturday.</p>
<p>The VCU chapter of the Delta Chi fraternity was also suspended by the national Delta Chi organization.</p>
<p>The suspensions follow the death of VCU student Adam Oakes. Statements from the <a href="https://twitter.com/VCU/status/1366089628072239109" target="_blank" rel="noopener">university</a>, the national fraternity and the Richmond police did not mention any cause of death, although police are investigating.</p>
<p>Oakes&#8217; family told <a href="https://www.nbc12.com/2021/03/01/adam-had-huge-huge-heart-family-believes-hazing-led-vcu-students-death/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CNN affiliate WWBT</a> that the student &#8212; who was an only child &#8212; had been offered a bid to join the Delta Chi fraternity and had gone to a party Friday night to begin the initiation process.</p>
<p>&#8220;He had already tried to get into other fraternities and had been turned down, but he saw the camaraderie. He&#8217;d see the brotherhood and just loved the actual acceptance,&#8221; his father, Eric Oakes, told WWBT.</p>
<p>&#8220;At 9 p.m., he texts his dad and just said, &#8216;I&#8217;m going in. Love you.&#8217; and he went in,&#8221; Oakes&#8217; cousin Courtney White told the affiliate. &#8220;He wasn&#8217;t just a good kid or good person to us, he was to everybody,&#8221; White said.</p>
<p>CNN has reached out to Oakes&#8217; family for comment but has not yet heard back.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, VCU officials said the school was launching an &#8220;independent, comprehensive review&#8221; of all Greek life at the university at the direction of university president Michael Rao.</p>
<p>&#8220;In light of Adam&#8217;s death and our commitment to a safe and healthy campus, this review will make recommendations about how Greek organizations meet the high expectations we have for them,&#8221; Charles Klink, VCU senior vice provost, said in a statement. &#8220;Simply put, this cannot happen again.&#8221;</p>
<p>Oakes&#8217; cause of death has not yet been determined by the Medical Examiner, said Tammie Smith, spokesperson for Virginia Department of Health.</p>
<p>According to a statement from the <a href="http://www.richmondgov.com/Police/index.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Richmond Police Department (RPD), </a>officers responded &#8220;for the report of a person down&#8221; around 9:16 a.m. Saturday. &#8220;Officers arrived and found Oakes down and unresponsive. He was pronounced dead at the scene,&#8221; it said.</p>
<p>Detectives from RPD and the VCU Police Department are investigating, the department said.</p>
<p>The VCU Delta Chi house is about a mile from where Oakes was found unresponsive. Neither the university nor the police gave any information about whether the house where Oakes was found was linked to the fraternity.</p>
<p>&#8220;The health and safety of our chapter communities is always a top priority for The Delta Chi Fraternity, which suspended the VCU chapter after learning of the incident late Saturday afternoon,&#8221; the national <a href="https://twitter.com/DeltaChiHQ/status/1366124066588004354" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fraternity statement</a> said.</p>
<p>By Monday, social media accounts, websites and university pages associated with VCU chapter of Delta Chi had been taken down.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874983</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_aa1f7c30624a6e1410652802d200c48f-h_060fb908471e9a22d27b8a300e84a482.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_aa1f7c30624a6e1410652802d200c48f-h_060fb908471e9a22d27b8a300e84a482.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/hypatia-h_aa1f7c30624a6e1410652802d200c48f-h_060fb908471e9a22d27b8a300e84a482.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Virginia,Commonwealth,University,Richmond,Virginia</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deadly California crash was on route for illegal crossings</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/deadly-california-crash-was-on-route-for-illegal-crossings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 13:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874938</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOLTVILLE, Calif. (AP) — Barely a mile from where an SUV packed with 25 people struck a tractor-trailer — killing 13 inside — there is...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOLTVILLE, Calif. (AP) — Barely a mile from where an SUV packed with 25 people struck a tractor-trailer — killing 13 inside — there is a cemetery with unmarked bricks that is a burial ground for migrants who died crossing the border from Mexico to remote California desert.</p>
<p>Authorities are investigating whether human smuggling was involved in the early Tuesday morning collision that killed the 22-year-old male driver of the SUV and 12 passengers. The Mexican government said 10 of the dead were Mexican citizens and that nationalities of the three others who died was undetermined.</p>
<p>Seats of the 1997 Ford Expedition had been removed except for the driver and right front passenger seats, said Omar Watson, chief of the California Highway Patrol&#8217;s border division.</p>
<p>The cause of the collision was undetermined, authorities said. It also was unknown why so many people were crammed into a vehicle built to hold eight people safely. But smugglers have been known to pack people into vehicles in extremely unsafe conditions to maximize their profits.</p>
<p>The crash happened during the height of the harvest in California&#8217;s Imperial Valley agricultural region, which provides much of the lettuce, onions, broccoli and winter vegetables to U.S. supermarkets. The community of Holtville where the crash happened is a no-stoplight town with a gazebo in its large central square and calls itself the world&#8217;s carrot capital.</p>
<p>The area became a major route for illegal border crossings in the late 1990s after heightened enforcement in San Diego pushed migrants to more remote areas. Many crossed the All-American Canal, an aqueduct that runs along the border and unleashes Colorado River water to farms through a vast network of canals.</p>
<p>At the back of Terrace Park Cemetery in Holtville, single bricks — rows of them — mark the unidentified remains of people who died, including many migrants.</p>
<p>In 2001, John Hunter founded Water Station, a volunteer group that leaves jugs of water in giant plastic drums for dehydrated migrants.</p>
<p>“I was trying to figure out how to stop the deaths,” said Hunter, whose brother Duncan strongly advocated for border wall construction as a congressman.</p>
<p>Illegal crossings in the area fell sharply in the mid-2000s but the area has remained a draw for migrants and was a priority for wall construction under former President Donald Trump. His administration&#8217;s first wall project was in Calexico.</p>
<p>U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement said late Tuesday that agents in its Homeland Security Investigations unit &#8220;have initiated a human smuggling investigation (into Tuesday&#8217;s crash). The investigation is ongoing and no further details are available at this time.”</p>
<p>When police arrived at the crash site about 125 miles (200 kilometers) east of San Diego, some passengers were trying to crawl out of the crumpled SUV. Others were wandering around the fields. The rig’s front end was pushed into the SUV’s left side and two empty trailers were jackknifed behind it.</p>
<p>“It was a pretty chaotic scene,” said Watson.</p>
<p>The Border Patrol said its agents were not pursuing the vehicle before the crash.</p>
<p>Passengers in the SUV ranged in age from 15 to 53 and were a mix of men and women, officials said. The driver was from Mexicali, Mexico, just across the border, and was among those killed. The 68-year-old driver of the big rig, who is from the nearby California community of El Centro, was hospitalized with moderate injuries.</p>
<p>The passengers’ injuries ranged from minor to severe and included fractures and head trauma. They were being cared for at several hospitals. One person was treated at a hospital and released.</p>
<p>The crash occurred around 6:15 a.m. under clear, sunny skies at an intersection just outside Holtville, about 11 miles (18 kilometers) north of the border. Authorities said the tractor-trailer and its two empty containers were northbound on State Highway 115 when the SUV pulled in front of it from a road with a stop sign.</p>
<p>A California Highway Patrol report said the SUV entered an intersection directly in front of the big-rig, which hit the left side of the SUV. Both vehicles came to a halt on a dirt shoulder.</p>
<p>It’s not clear if the SUV ran a stop sign or had stopped before entering the highway. Speeds were also unknown.</p>
<p>The speed limit for tractor-trailers on the highway is 55 mph (89 kph), according to California Highway Patrol Officer Jake Sanchez. The other road also has a 55 mph speed limit.</p>
<p>A 1997 Ford Expedition can carry a maximum payload of 2,000 pounds. If it had 25 people inside, that would easily exceed the payload limit, taxing the brakes and making it tougher to steer the vehicle, said Frank Borris, former head of the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration’s Office of Defects Investigation.</p>
<p>“You’re going to have extended stopping distances, delayed reactions to steering inputs and potential over-reaction to any type of high-speed lane change,” said Borris, who now runs a safety consulting business.</p>
<p>SUVs of that age tended to be top-heavy even when not carrying a lot of weight, Borris said.</p>
<p>“With all of that payload above the vehicle’s center of gravity, it’s going to make it even more unstable,” he said.</p>
<p>The crash happened amid verdant farms that grow a wide variety of vegetables and alfalfa used for cattle feed.</p>
<p>Many workers commute cross the border from Mexico to California during the winter harvest, taking buses and SUVs to the fields from the small California city of Calexico just before dawn.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874938</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/california-crash-e1614778146909.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/038b6cd1-a15f-4d75-b344-e0d252206579/f5eea311-f136-4132-a654-2c9314bcb949/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217380~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/038b6cd1-a15f-4d75-b344-e0d252206579/f5eea311-f136-4132-a654-2c9314bcb949/main.mp4*~hmac=ed4132154cbc68ee6bff5f4965ce1b87957a974cee31a72e1013f2cd7e109e8c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/california-crash-e1614778146909.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/california-crash-e1614778146909.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">california crash</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>3-year-old survives 12-story fall from apartment balcony in Vietnam</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/us-world/3-year-old-survives-12-story-fall-from-apartment-balcony-in-vietnam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brittany McIntosh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 12:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874907</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A heart-pounding moment was caught on camera when a toddler survived a 12-story fall from an apartment building in Vietnam. The 3-year-old was seen clinging...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A heart-pounding moment was caught on camera when a toddler survived a 12-story fall from an apartment building in Vietnam.</p>
<p>The 3-year-old was seen clinging onto the balcony before falling to the street below.</p>
<p>Local reports said a delivery driver who was passing by managed to grab the toddler before she hit the ground.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s unclear how the child got off the balcony.</p>
<p>The toddler was taken to a hospital with a hip fracture and other injuries but is expected to be OK.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874907</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-vietnam-child-falls.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e53f443a-0d53-4c88-86dc-1875281c2fd1/6fc80904-390e-4c18-b7a3-2dfba9b103ec/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217307~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e53f443a-0d53-4c88-86dc-1875281c2fd1/6fc80904-390e-4c18-b7a3-2dfba9b103ec/main.mp4*~hmac=7b9cd14c93b6e456de6d4e514ae6e13d75029fbaa3c8deb28c595de2ff5c0254' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-vietnam-child-falls.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/03/030321-vietnam-child-falls.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">030321 vietnam child falls</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
