<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Miami Marlins &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-marlins/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 04:38:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Miami Marlins &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>Waiting game for Marlins as heralded young hitters struggle</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/waiting-game-for-marlins-as-heralded-young-hitters-struggle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Marlins outfield prospect Monte Harrison says he surprised himself when he made his major league debut last year. It wasn&#8217;t just...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Marlins outfield prospect Monte Harrison says he surprised himself when he made his major league debut last year.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t just that he didn&#8217;t hit; it was how he reacted when he didn&#8217;t hit.</p>
<p>“I said I was not going to be that guy who gets called up to the big leagues and struggles mentally,” Harrison said. “And then when I got to the big leagues, I struggled mentally. That’s very humbling.”</p>
<p>Harrison&#8217;s experience wasn&#8217;t isolated in Miami last season; several other Marlins prospects also scuffled in their first crack at the majors. In fact, while the farm system rebuilt under CEO Derek Jeter brims with young talent, it has yet to produce a hitter who busts out in the majors.</p>
<p>With pitching it&#8217;s different. The Marlins have stockpiled young arms so successfully their rotation is expected to be the strength of this year&#8217;s team, with no starter older than 26.</p>
<p>Development of hitters lags. That&#8217;s baseball.</p>
<p>“There are a few young guys who don’t struggle; the majority do,” Marlins manager Don Mattingly said Wednesday. “There are very few Sotos, Griffey Jrs. and Acunas of the world who are instantly stars. It doesn’t happen that often.”</p>
<p>For the Jeter regime, instant success hasn&#8217;t happened at all. Four of the Marlins&#8217; top 12 prospects made their MLB debuts last year, and none batted above .170.</p>
<p>Harrison went 8 for 47 with 26 strikeouts. Outfielder Jesús Sánchez went 1 for 25 with 11 strikeouts. First baseman Lewin Díaz went 6 for 39 with 12 strikeouts. Infielder Jazz Chisholm went 9 for 56 with 19 strikeouts.</p>
<p>Other heralded youngsters, including second baseman Isan Díaz and outfielder Magneuris Sierra, also have been unable to win a starting job.</p>
<p>Outfielder Lewis Brinson feels their pain. A prospect acquired in the Christian Yelich trade with Milwaukee, Brinson has a .189 career average in 761 at-bats, although he did show progress in 2020 and might have a role on this year&#8217;s team.</p>
<p>His advice for scuffling young hitters?</p>
<p>“Embrace that struggle,” Brinson said. &#8220;Embrace getting slapped, getting humbled a little bit.</p>
<p>“We’ve killed it in the minors; when you get to the big leagues it’s a different ballgame. You can&#8217;t succeed without failing sometimes. You’ve got to take your lumps.”</p>
<p>Mattingly said he doesn&#8217;t believed the Marlins have been calling up youngsters too soon. Instead, he thinks the game has changed since 1984, when he won the American League batting title at age 23 by hitting .343.</p>
<p>“There is a bigger separation now between Triple-A and the big leagues,” Mattingly said. &#8220;It almost always takes that getting slapped, as Lew would say, and then going back and working on your game, and the next time it’s usually a little better.</p>
<p>“We’re seeing it with Lew. He&#8217;s making strides, and it has taken a little bit. Hopefully it’s not going to take two or three years with guys, but sometimes that’s what it takes.”</p>
<p>Or, as Mattingly noted, success may never come. But that&#8217;s where the Marlins&#8217; depth of young talent helps their chances of building on last year&#8217;s surprising run to their first playoff berth since 2003.</p>
<p>The Marlins remain high on their 2020 rookie class, and even if the entire group flops, there are more young prospects on the way. That includes outfielders JJ Bleday, Kameron Misner, Peyton Burdick and Connor Scott, and shortstop Jose Devers.</p>
<p>The improved depth of the farm system has been evident during the first week of spring training games, Mattingly said.</p>
<p>“You see it clear as day,” he said. “There is just no doubt our quality has been up, and you see that depth coming.”</p>
<p>In the meantime, last year&#8217;s rookies battle to win roster spots.</p>
<p>Harrison, for one, embraces getting slapped last year. A dynamic player and personality, he failed to make the roster out of camp last summer, and saw only spot duty after later joining the Marlins.</p>
<p>“I think the best thing that ever happened to me was in that time period where I got sent down and called back up and I had to sit on the bench,” Harrison said. &#8220;The best of Monte will come out. I can&#8217;t wait for the fans of Miami to see that, and the world.”</p>
<p>The Marlins remain confident, too, that they won&#8217;t continue to strike out with their young hitters.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875581</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Marlins logo on flag</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lefty Gio González agrees to minor league deal with Marlins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/lefty-gio-gonzalez-agrees-to-minor-league-deal-with-marlins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 04:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875580</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Veteran left-hander Gio González has agreed to terms on a minor league contract with the Miami Marlins and will take part in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Veteran left-hander Gio González has agreed to terms on a minor league contract with the Miami Marlins and will take part in their major league camp.</p>
<p>González, a South Florida native, pitched in 12 games last year for Chicago White Sox with four starts and had an ERA of 4.83. He has a career record of 131-101 with a 3.70 ERA in 13 seasons for four teams.</p>
<p>At 35, González provides experienced depth for the Marlins&#8217; talented young rotation. He is a two-time All-Star, with Oakland in 2011 and Washington in 2012.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875580</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alcantara leads young staff that should be Marlins&#8217; strength</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/alcantara-leads-young-staff-that-should-be-marlins-strength/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=874784</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — At 25, Sandy Alcantara says he&#8217;s old enough to be the Miami Marlins&#8217; ace. The Marlins agree. Alcantara has pitched less than...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — At 25, Sandy Alcantara says he&#8217;s old enough to be the Miami Marlins&#8217; ace.</p>
<p>The Marlins agree.</p>
<p>Alcantara has pitched less than 300 innings and has a career record of 11-19, but Miami is counting on him to lead a parade of talented young starting pitchers who are considered the team&#8217;s strength.</p>
<p>“That’s what the Marlins are looking for from me, and that&#8217;s what I want,” said the Dominican right-hander, who pitched two scoreless innings against the Mets in his first spring training start Monday. “There are a lot of young guys behind me. I have to show them they can be like me.</p>
<p>“It doesn’t matter how young I am. I have experience. I&#8217;ve been in the big leagues for four years now.”</p>
<p>On Miami&#8217;s staff, that&#8217;s a lot. The other right-handers expected to help make up the rotation include Pablo López, Elieser Hernández and Sixto Sánchez. Four pitchers are contending for the last spot — left-hander Trevor Rogers and Daniel Castano, and right-handers Nick Neidert and Braxton Garrett.</p>
<p>Among the eight pitchers, Castano is the oldest at 26, and their combined career record is 36-54.</p>
<p>Even so, the Marlins believe starting pitching can lead them back to the playoffs after they made a surprising run last year to their first postseason berth since 2003.</p>
<p>“We hang our hat on pitching,” manager Don Mattingly said. “We feel like that is going to be our thing. Every time we put a starter out there, you feel like you’ve got a guy who can keep you in the game.”</p>
<p>Relying on young pitching is nothing new for the Marlins, due to their perennially small payrolls. But the depth of 25-and-under talent might be the franchise&#8217;s best since 2002, when the rotation included Josh Beckett, Brad Penny, A.J. Burnett and Ryan Dempster.</p>
<p>A year later, the Marlins won the World Series.</p>
<p>“We have arms that are able to shut any lineup down,” López said. “Electric arms. It’s a very exciting rotation.”</p>
<p>The Marlins have stockpiled the young pitchers as a foundation for CEO Derek Jeter&#8217;s rebuilding project, now entering Season 4. One of Jeter&#8217;s first moves was to acquire Alcantara in the 2017 trade that sent outfielder Marcell Ozuna to the Cardinals.</p>
<p>The 6-foot-5 Alcantara made his first major league start the following year. In 2019 he became an All-Star and pitched two shutouts, most in the majors.</p>
<p>Alcantara was sidelined early last season by the Marlins&#8217; COVID-19 outbreak, but returned and finish with a 3.00 ERA in seven starts, and then beat the Cubs in his playoff debut.</p>
<p>“You see the wannabe, which is huge,” Mattingly said. “His stuff can be as good as anybody&#8217;s, and he wants to be great.”</p>
<p>Even so, the starter who created the most buzz last year was Sánchez, acquired in the trade two years ago that sent catcher J.T. Realmuto to the Philadelphia Phillies. The highly touted 22-year-old performed so well he was able to trade in uniform number 73 for 45, the number worn by his hero and fellow Dominican, Pedro Martínez.</p>
<p>“It means a lot,” Sánchez said in Spanish. “I used to watch Pedro pitch. I want to accomplish many things he did.”</p>
<p>He&#8217;s off to a good start. Called up in August, Sánchez went 3-2 with a 3.46 ERA in seven starts, and he pitched five shutout innings against the Cubs in the playoffs.</p>
<p>“Sixto came as advertised,” Mattingly said. “There really wasn’t anything not to like.”</p>
<p>Perhaps Miami&#8217;s most promising pitching prospect is another 22-year-old, right-hander Edward Cabrera. He was expected to contend for a rotation spot but is sidelined indefinitely with an inflamed nerve in his right biceps.</p>
<p>That still leaves plenty of pitching depth in camp.</p>
<p>&#8220;We have a lot of young guys,” Alcantara said. “And when they get opportunity, they’re going to be good.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">874784</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-488-Sandy-Alcantara-1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-488-Sandy-Alcantara-1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-488-Sandy-Alcantara-1.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">210218 Pitchers &#38; Catchers 488 - Sandy Alcantara 1</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins unveil COVID-19 protocols for fans wanting to attend games</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-unveil-covid-19-protocols-for-fans-wanting-to-attend-games/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins have revealed their COVID-19 protocols that will be enforced for fans who attend home games at Marlins Park during the 2021 MLB...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins have revealed their COVID-19 protocols that will be enforced for fans who attend home games at Marlins Park during the 2021 MLB season.</p>
<p>In a release sent out on Wednesday, the Marlins announced face coverings will be mandatory for all guests above 2 years old. However, they may be temporarily removed to consume a beverage or eat a meal.</p>
<p>Also, Marlins officials said tickets will be digital for 2021, and guests can access them through the MLB Ballpark App. Ticketed fans will receive a time and gate location to enter the ballpark on their ticket, and officials encourage them to adhere to the staggered entry.</p>
<p>Miami plans to have around <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-will-allow-fans-with-capacity-at-about-25-percent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">25% capacity</a> at the ballpark to begin the season and may increase capacity as the season progresses.</p>
<p>The team became the second MLB team to <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-enroll-in-covid-19-safety-rating-plan-to-have-fans-for-opening-day/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enroll in the WELL Health-Safety Rating</a> prior to the season. The rating was created in response to the coronavirus pandemic, and it incorporates guidance from the World Health Organization, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and other health agencies.</p>
<p>They also partnered with RB, the makers of Lysol, to have ample disinfecting products around the ballpark. According to the Marlins, they will have frequently touched surfaces and objects regularly disinfected, and they will have hand sanitizing stations throughout the stadium.</p>
<p>Officials encourage all fans to pay for items using a credit or debit card at all concession and retail spots.</p>
<p>Bags will not be allowed inside of Marlins Park unless it is for medical or infant purposes, Marlins officials said.</p>
<p>Miami will play the Tampa Bay Rays on Opening Day at Marlins Park on April 1 to begin their 2021 season.</p>
<p>For a full list of changes to attend a game in the 2021 season, click <a href="https://www.mlb.com/marlins/ballpark/health-and-safety" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870734</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021821-marlins-park-interior.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021821-marlins-park-interior.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021821-marlins-park-interior.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021821 marlins park interior</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins killer Adam Duvall is now on their side and in RF</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-killer-adam-duvall-is-now-on-their-side-and-in-rf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=870732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Adam Duvall gave the Miami Marlins fits last year, and they solved the problem by bringing him over to their side. Duvall...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Adam Duvall gave the Miami Marlins fits last year, and they solved the problem by bringing him over to their side.</p>
<p>Duvall hit five homers for Atlanta in nine games against Miami and had an OPS of 1.201. The Marlins were especially mindful of his three-homer, nine-RBI game in the midst of the playoff race when they signed him to a $5 million, one-year deal two weeks ago.</p>
<p>“They talked about how I had had some success against them,” Duvall said with a laugh Wednesday.</p>
<p>His signing changes the Marlins&#8217; outlook as full-squad spring training workouts begin in Jupiter, Florida. They&#8217;re planning to plug him into right field and the middle of lineup, where he provides a significant power upgrade for an offense that ranked fifth-worst in MLB in homers in 2020.</p>
<p>Duvall hit 16 for the Braves, five more than Marlins leader Brian Anderson.</p>
<p>“Adam has solidified right field for us,” manager Don Mattingly said. “He&#8217;s a guy who is big and strong and capable of hitting the ball out of the ballpark, and it doesn’t really matter what ballpark. He&#8217;s one of those true power guys, and you do want danger in there.”</p>
<p>Duvall, 32, has been much more dangerous since the Braves demoted him to Triple-A for much of the 2019 season. He returned to post a career-high .882 OPS with 10 homers for Atlanta in 41 games that year.</p>
<p>Last season, only two National League players hit more homers.</p>
<p>“He definitely has closed some holes up,” Mattingly said.</p>
<p>Duvall said he bonded in the minors with batting coach Bobby Magallanes, who became a mentor.</p>
<p>“It was a blessing in disguise,” Duvall said. “I like the growth I&#8217;ve had in the past two years.</p>
<p>“I really enjoy learning the game. I enjoy trying to get every edge I can, and that’s one thing that has helped me progress as I get older. Every little piece of the game, I enjoy learning about and talking about.”</p>
<p>Duvall believes that makes him a good fit with the Marlins, who made the playoffs last year for the first time since 2003 with a young team that appears to be trending upward.</p>
<p>“We have a group of guys that are hungry and want to learn,” Duvall said. “That’s going to be fun.”</p>
<p>Duvall said he&#8217;s still learning, too. He&#8217;s solid defensively and was an offensive force last year, but he batted only .237 with an on-base percentage of .301. His career batting average is .233, with a strikeout rate of one per game.</p>
<p>“I want to be the best hitter I can be,&#8221; he said. &#8220;That’s going to be driving the ball, but I want to be better in other aspects as far as walking and just getting base hits when they&#8217;re needed.”</p>
<p>Duvall&#8217;s deal includes a $2 million salary this year and a $7 million mutual option for 2022 with a $3 million buyout.</p>
<p>Mattingly said Duvall has looked good in the cage in camp. But the manager said he doesn&#8217;t need any convincing that Duvall can hit.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;ve seen enough of him the last couple of years,” Mattingly said with a smile.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">870732</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/210218-Pitchers-Catchers-230.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Marlins logo on flag</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins overachiever Rojas still improving as he turns 32</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-overachiever-rojas-still-improving-as-he-turns-32/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 19:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=869882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins were about to take the field Tuesday for the initial full-squad workout of spring training, and manager Don Mattingly...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins were about to take the field Tuesday for the initial full-squad workout of spring training, and manager Don Mattingly was eager to get his first look at a team trending upward and filled with players still growing into the job.</p>
<p>That included shortstop Miguel Rojas, who turns 32 Wednesday.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m going to quit setting the bar on Miggy,” Mattingly said. “Every time you say that’s as good as he can get, he gets better.”</p>
<p>Rojas has been with the Marlins since 2015, longer than any other player. He&#8217;s a perfect fit for the small-budget franchise because he&#8217;s an overachiever, and thus a sound investment.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s also the undisputed clubhouse leader who knows there&#8217;s still work to be done for a team that last year made a surprising run to its first postseason berth since 2003.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re getting picked again to be last in the division,” Rojas said with a smile. “That chip on the shoulder is still going to be there.”</p>
<p>That chip has long helped to drive Rojas, who broke into the majors with the Dodgers in 2014 but didn&#8217;t become a full-time player until 2018 in Miami.</p>
<p>In the past three seasons, Rojas&#8217; OPS has gone from .643 to .710 to .888. He totaled four homers in his first four seasons and has hit 21 in the past three years.</p>
<p>Rojas&#8217; glovework has always been excellent, and now he has a bat to match.</p>
<p>“I’m not surprised at all,” he said following Tuesday&#8217;s workout in Jupiter, Florida. “I&#8217;ve been working so hard on becoming a complete player. That has always been my goal since I was little — I wanted to be an everyday shortstop. I needed to get better and stronger and learn from my mistakes.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mattingly, long a Rojas fan, said the veteran&#8217;s steady improvement at the plate shows why analytics don&#8217;t bat 1.000 in player projections.</p>
<p>“You can&#8217;t measure a guy’s will to be better,” Mattingly said. “Most guys don’t really reach their full potential. They settle short.”</p>
<p>Not Rojas. In 2020 he missed 16 games because of COVID-19 during the Marlins’ early-season outbreak, but he returned to bat .304 with a .496 slugging percentage, both career highs.</p>
<p>His work ethic make him a natural leader on a young team, and the Venezuelan is an eager mentor to prospects. During the offseason he took under his wing Victor Mesa Jr., a Cuban defector and 19-year-old outfield prospect.</p>
<p>“Miggy has done a great job of growing into that role and trying to be vocal and connect with all the guys, whether they&#8217;re American or Latin,” third baseman Brian Anderson said. “He’s great at breaking down those boundaries.”</p>
<p>New general manager Kim Ng was quick to notice.</p>
<p>“Miguel is a really interesting guy, an interesting player,” Ng said. “He takes great pride in being a leader.”</p>
<p>Rojas&#8217; voice stood out after CEO Derek Jeter ’s group bought the team in late 2017. While other veteran players looked for the exit as the Marlins embarked on yet another rebuilding effort, Rojas became a vocal supporter of the plan.</p>
<p>The first payoff came last year with an unexpected playoff berth. And now that Jeter&#8217;s group has transformed a bereft farm system into one of the baseball&#8217;s best, Rojas sees more winning ahead.</p>
<p>“The depth in this organization is unbelievable,” he said. “All this young talent pushes me harder.&#8221;</p>
<p>Even though Rojas has a newborn daughter, he was so excited about spring training he showed up a week early. Once again, it was time to get better.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">869882</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Miguel-Rojas.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Miguel-Rojas.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/Miguel-Rojas.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Miguel Rojas</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Marlins owner Jeffrey Loria to reimburse government $5.5 million</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/former-marlins-owner-jeffrey-loria-to-reimburse-government-5-5-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Chalvire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 17:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=867122</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Former Miami Marlins owner Jeffrey Loria reached a final lawsuit settlement to reimburse local government $5.5 million for the cost of building...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Former Miami Marlins owner Jeffrey Loria reached a final lawsuit settlement to reimburse local government $5.5 million for the cost of building Marlins Park, which opened in 2012.</p>
<p>The Miami-Dade County commission approved the deal after Loria agreed to a last-minute increase in the amount. A tentative settlement of $4.2 million was reached last month.</p>
<p>The payment stems from the $1.2 billion sale of team by Loria in 2017 to Derek Jeter and his ownership group. Loria bought the Marlins for $158.5 million in 2002.</p>
<p>In 2009, local government agreed to help pay to build Marlins Park in exchange for Loria’s pledge to share profits if he later sold the team. That agreement called for Loria to pay 5% of net proceeds from the sale of the team.</p>
<p>Public money covered more than three-fourths of the $634 million cost for Marlins Park.</p>
<p>The settlement follows months of negotiations. The county will receive $4.8 million, and the city of Miami will receive $700,000 under terms approved Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">867122</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/171010-loria.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4d6094ba-af3c-4269-9c44-96cc84e3f167/abf4c23e-c651-4341-b581-bea50b115de4/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218986~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4d6094ba-af3c-4269-9c44-96cc84e3f167/abf4c23e-c651-4341-b581-bea50b115de4/main.mp4*~hmac=a766914bd60184f37a5c91c504e5c46e8e2d20a977fb3190c8d42b2e31ec5322' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/171010-loria.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/10/171010-loria.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">171010 loria</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reliever Curtiss acquired by Marlins from Rays for prospect</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/reliever-curtiss-acquired-by-marlins-from-rays-for-prospect/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Right-handed reliever John Curtiss was traded Wednesday by the Tampa Bay Rays to the Miami Marlins for minor league first baseman Evan...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MIAMI (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Right-handed reliever John Curtiss was traded Wednesday by the Tampa Bay Rays to the Miami Marlins for minor league first baseman Evan Edwards.<p>The Rays also dealt minor league catcher Ronaldo Hern&#xC3;&#xA1;ndez and minor league infielder Nick Sogard to the Boston Red Sox for right-handed pitcher Chris Mazza, left-handed pitcher Jeffrey Springs and cash.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/Marlins/status/1362099847201972226?s=20</embed></div><p>Boston placed catcher Kevin Plawecki on the COVID-19-related injured list.</p><p>Curtiss went 3-0 with a 1.80 ERA in 17 games last year. He had a 6.30 ERA in 10 innings in the postseason for the American League champions.</p><p>Curtiss also has pitched for the Angels and Twins, and he has a 3,83 career ERA. He further strengthens the bullpen for the Marlins, who earlier added left-hander Ross Detwiler and right-handers Dylan Floro, Anthony Bass and Adam Cimber.</p><p>Mazza pitched nine games as a starter and reliever for Boston last year and went 1-2 with a 4.80 ERA. Springs went 0-2 with a 7.08 ERA in 16 games out of the bullpen.</p><p>Edwards was a fourth-round pick out of North Carolina State in 2019. He hit .281 with nine homers in 73 games in the low minors that year. Hern&#xC3;&#xA1;ndez is a career .293 hitter over five minor league seasons. Sogard batted .290 with 20 stolen bases in 63 games in Class A in 2019.</p><p>Notes: The Marlins finalized outfielder Adam Duvall&#x2019;s one-year contract, which guarantees $5 million. He has a $2 million salary, and the agreement includes a $7 million mutual option with a $3 million buyout.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866740</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Marlins GM Ng eager to finally see her team in action</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/new-marlins-gm-ng-eager-to-finally-see-her-team-in-action/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Three months into the job, Kim Ng will finally get to see her team. Miami Marlins pitchers and catchers hold their first...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Three months into the job, Kim Ng will finally get to see her team.</p>
<p>Miami Marlins pitchers and catchers hold their first workout Thursday at the team&#8217;s spring training complex in Jupiter, Florida. The first full-squad drills will be Tuesday.</p>
<p>And Ng, hired in November as the first female general manager in Major League Baseball, will be watching.</p>
<p>“I feel like a kid on Christmas,” Ng said Wednesday. “We&#8217;ve talked about these guys quite a bit every day for the last three months, and finally I get to see them live — how they react to situations, how they compete, their demeanor. You get to see them in their element. I&#8217;m incredibly excited to meet them all in person and see what they bring to the table live.”</p>
<p>Ng joined a long-suffering franchise on the upswing under CEO Derek Jeter after the Marlins made the playoffs last year for the first time since 2003. The achievement came with an asterisk because the season was shortened by the COVID-19 pandemic, and Jeter has since stressed there&#8217;s much work yet to do to transform the Marlins into a consistent winner for the first time in franchise history.</p>
<p>Ng was hired to help after nine years as an executive with MLB. She made offseason moves to improve the team as she was still learning about it.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m sure it has been a whirlwind for her, getting to know the organization and the personnel,” Jeter said. “It&#8217;s almost like an orientation for her.”</p>
<p>The Marlins, still hamstrung by a small budget, made no big offseason splashes — aside from hiring Ng after president of baseball operations Michael Hill wasn&#8217;t retained.</p>
<p>Ng did address the bullpen, which Jeter had identified as the No. 1 offseason priority. She acquired Anthony Bass, Dylan Floro, Ross Detwiler, Adam Cimber and — in a trade Wednesday with the Rays — John Curtiss.</p>
<p>“This pen — we quietly just keep putting quality guys into it, kind of sneakily almost,” manager Don Mattingly said.</p>
<p>Ng also signed outfielder Adam Duvall to a $5 million, one-year deal. Last year for the Braves he hit 16 homers, five more than anyone with Miami.</p>
<p>“We went about the offseason in a very systematic way,” Ng said. “You have a plan going in, and it didn’t seem that hard to stick to. In terms of targets, we were able to acquire a decent number of them. I thought it was a great offseason for us.”</p>
<p>Jeter&#8217;s group bought the team in late 2017, and he has since built a moribund farm system into one of the best in baseball. Ng said it&#8217;s even deeper than she thought when she took the job.</p>
<p>Young pitching is the Marlins&#8217; strength, both at the major league level and in the minors. They also have a long list of outfield prospects.</p>
<p>Now, Ng can start to assess it all in the flesh.</p>
<p>“What you see on paper, a lot of times it’s just not what it looks like in real life,” Ng said. “I definitely need to see these guys and lay eyes on them. All these guys I&#8217;ve been hearing about all offseason, I just can&#8217;t wait to get out there.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866741</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/kim-ng-2.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/kim-ng-2.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/kim-ng-2.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">kim ng</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Players return to COVID protocols as spring training opens</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/players-return-to-covid-protocols-as-spring-training-opens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866739</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One year later, players and managers say they have a better understanding of what it takes to play baseball through a pandemic. Pitchers and catchers...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One year later, players and managers say they have a better understanding of what it takes to play baseball through a pandemic.</p>
<p>Pitchers and catchers around the game reported to spring training Wednesday saying they appreciate what’s at stake as they try to make sure the season starts on time. The protocols have been tightened even further from what they experienced during the abbreviated 2020 season.</p>
<p>“We’ve all gone through a year of this, of living through this,” New York Yankees manager Aaron Boone said. “And so I think we’re a little, much better equipped of how to handle ourselves, how to conduct ourselves, how to make good use of our time.”</p>
<p>New standards agreed to by Major League Baseball and the players’ association require players, staffers and other team personnel to wear electronic tracing wristbands for ballpark access. Players underwent a five-day at-home quarantine before reporting, with exceptions for essential activities and approved outdoor workouts and exercise.</p>
<p>They’ll need to stay in their living quarters throughout spring training except for baseball activities, medical care, grocery shopping, takeout food pickups and outdoor physical activity. Outdoor dining will only be allowed if they get permission beforehand.</p>
<p>“Between the players&#8217; union and MLB, the agreement I think is pretty rock-solid when it comes to player safety, staff safety,” Chicago White Sox pitcher Lucas Giolito said Tuesday. “There’s going to be a few things that are a little more, what’s the word for it, given more importance. I think some of the workouts are going to be in smaller groups, a lot more on point with mask wearing and things like that. I don’t think it will affect our work too much. We’ll certainly be able to get done what we need to get done.”</p>
<p>But the restrictions will make it more challenging to get ready for the season.</p>
<p>Catcher James McCann faces hurdles this spring trying to bond with an entirely new pitching staff after signing a $40 million, four-year deal with New York Mets. Normally, the veteran backstop would invite pitchers to dinner, set up play dates for their kids, go out and grab a drink — anything to help develop those relationships.</p>
<p>Forget the off-field meetups. Under MLB’s protocols, even getting together at the team’s Florida complex is more difficult. Gathering in places like the video room — usually a convenient spot for 3-4 players to meet — is a no-no.</p>
<p>“Nobody likes to wear a mask and sit and talk 6 feet away from each other,” McCann said. “A lot of different things I guess we took for granted.”</p>
<p>MLB is hoping to have a full season after playing a 60-game schedule last year that included no fans in the stands until the postseason. The Miami Marlins and St. Louis Cardinals both dealt with COVID-19 outbreaks that resulted in multiple postponements.</p>
<p>“We’re the lucky sport to have 162 games, but with that obviously comes a lot of thoughtfulness and dedication and commitment,” new Marlins general manager Kim Ng said. “To play this game, you have to be absolutely committed, especially this team with them going through what they went through last year. People understand how it can decimate.”</p>
<p>Cardinals pitcher Carlos Martinez battled COVID-19 last summer and says he wasn’t the same the rest of the season.</p>
<p>“After that, I was not comfortable with my body,” said Martinez, who added that he feels great now.</p>
<p>Oakland right-hander Frankie Montas was quarantining at home in Scottsdale, Arizona, on Wednesday with COVID-19. Manager Bob Melvin said Montas is “several days into it” after testing positive prior to reporting day.</p>
<p>Two other players were added to the COVID-19-related injured list Wednesday, which doesn&#8217;t necessarily mean they&#8217;ve tested positive: Boston Red Sox catcher Kevin Plawecki and Chicago Cubs left-hander Kyle Ryan.</p>
<p>One of the first things Cardinals president John Mozeliak did upon arriving in Jupiter, Florida, was to request a list from the medical staff of players and coaches who tested positive for COVID-19 antibodies.</p>
<p>Mozeliak believes knowing which players already have at least some measure of protection from the coronavirus can help in preventing an outbreak during spring training.</p>
<p>“I believe we had about 15 or 18 people with antibodies in this camp,” Mozeliak said, “so that was encouraging.”</p>
<p>Mozeliak also expressed hope that some staff and players could begin receiving the COVID-19 vaccine by opening day.</p>
<p>“But I certainly understand, collectively, you’re dealing with a pretty healthy group of young people,” he said, “and when you’re looking across our country, there are people more deserving of that opportunity than this group. But clearly if you were vaccinated, it would ease up a lot of the protocols we have in a sense of where you can go and where you can’t.”</p>
<p>For now, players say they are ready to follow the protocols while looking forward to the day they’re playing in full stadiums again.</p>
<p>“Thankful it’s going to be, not quite normal, but closer to it,” Arizona Diamondbacks pitcher Madison Bumgarner said. “I think we’re on the path back to that, so hopefully it all happens sooner rather than later.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866739</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/07/mlb-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MLB logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black MLB players, executives strive to diversify baseball</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/black-mlb-players-executives-strive-to-diversify-baseball/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 23:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=866117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Michele Meyer-Shipp doesn&#8217;t have to travel far to realize the challenge of growing the sport of baseball in the Black community. She just sits down...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michele Meyer-Shipp doesn&#8217;t have to travel far to realize the challenge of growing the sport of baseball in the Black community.</p>
<p>She just sits down at the dinner table.</p>
<p>Meyer-Shipp, who is Major League Baseball&#8217;s chief people and culture officer, has three sons who love sports. They know all about some of baseball&#8217;s Black legends like Hank Aaron, the sport&#8217;s one-time home run king who recently died at age 86.</p>
<p>But today&#8217;s Black baseball stars? Not so much.</p>
<p>“When I listen to my boys talk about sports, they&#8217;re always talking about the Black football player. Always,” Meyer-Shipp said. &#8220;And I&#8217;m like, ‘You know, there are Black baseball players.’ They talk about Black basketball players as well. But those are the guys you always see on commercials, on TV.</p>
<p>“We need our guys from baseball out there building a brand for Black talent in the game. I think that would really make a difference.&#8221;</p>
<p>Marketing the game&#8217;s best Black players was one of many topics discussed by a five-person panel of current MLB players, executives and coaches. The conversation, which was streamed Tuesday on MLB.com, is part of MLB&#8217;s Diversity, Equity &amp; Inclusion program.</p>
<p>Dodgers manager Dave Roberts, Marlins outfielder Lewis Brinson, former Astros manager Bo Porter and Red Sox coach Bianca Smith were also on the panel. The 26-year-old Brinson said he started playing baseball in south Florida when he was 4 years old and immediately grew to love it, but as he got older, he eventually realized not many Black kids were playing baseball.</p>
<p>He said he only had two Black teammates from tee ball through high school.</p>
<p>“I got made fun of for playing baseball — ‘Oh you’re playing that white sport. What are you doing playing that, man?” Brinson said. “But obviously I didn&#8217;t really care because I loved it.”</p>
<p>The number of Black players in MLB has been dwindling for years, hovering around 8% of the league in recent seasons.</p>
<p>Brinson said that&#8217;s one reason he&#8217;s proud to be in the The Players Alliance, which is a group of more than 100 Black current and former professional baseball players. The goal is for their platform to lead to “increased opportunities for the Black community in every aspect of our game and beyond.”</p>
<p>Brinson said going into poor areas of cities, providing baseball equipment and giving back was important. He added that it&#8217;s also good for the sport when children see players who look like them.</p>
<p>“Having those Black kids see us, touch us and talk to us, knowing that ‘Man, they look like me. I could be in their shoes,'&#8221; Brinson said. “I think more than anything, us actually going ourselves into the community and showing these kids, ‘Listen, you could be where I’m at.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The panel also discussed how to diversify the upper levels of the game, especially among managers and front office staff. Porter was the manager of the Astros in 2013 and &#8217;14 and is now a consultant for MLB.</p>
<p>Porter said he remains optimistic about baseball&#8217;s progress in diversity, but said it&#8217;s important that executives work to find ways to broaden their hiring pool so they have a more diverse group of candidates.</p>
<p>“We have to open up the access gate because they don&#8217;t know what they don&#8217;t know,” Porter said. “A lot of these general managers, presidents of baseball operations, if they were to open the access gate and have conversations when these jobs come available, I guarantee you the hiring process will get better and it will change.</p>
<p>“As Black people, we&#8217;re not looking for a handout. What we want is an opportunity.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">866117</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180325_lewis_brinson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180325_lewis_brinson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/03/180325_lewis_brinson.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">180325_Lewis_Brinson</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins will allow fans, with capacity at about 25 percent</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-will-allow-fans-with-capacity-at-about-25-percent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=865431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Small crowds at Marlins Park will be back this season. The attendance-challenged Marlins plan to allow fans at home games, although crowds...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Small crowds at Marlins Park will be back this season.</p>
<p>The attendance-challenged Marlins plan to allow fans at home games, although crowds will initially be limited to about 25% of capacity. That would mean a maximum of about 9,300 spectators in the 37,446-seat ballpark.</p>
<p>“We look forward to having the opportunity to have fans come back to our ballpark,” CEO Derek Jeter said Monday. “There will be a limited number of fans that are allowed at the onset. We hope those numbers increase throughout course of the season, but the most important thing for us is to make sure everyone is healthy and safe.”</p>
<p>The Marlins, like the rest of MLB, didn&#8217;t allow fans during the 2020 regular season because of the coronavirus pandemic. Limited crowds were permitted for the postseason, and that will be the case for spring training games in Florida and Arizona starting late this month.</p>
<p>The Marlins averaged about 10,000 fans in 2018 and 2019, the first two seasons that Jeter&#8217;s group owned the team. They finished last in the majors in attendance both years, and ranked last in the National League 14 out of 15 seasons through 2019.</p>
<p>The 2020 season might have brought an increase as the Marlins made surprising run to their first playoff berth in 17 years. But because of COVID-19, the size of the bandwagon was impossible to gauge.</p>
<p>“One thing that was a little bit disappointing last year — going through the pandemic, you hear about the excitement of our fan base, but they weren’t able to come to games,” Jeter said. &#8220;I would have loved to have seen what that looked like.</p>
<p>“There is a level of excitement, and we need to continue to build on that, not only on the baseball side but on the business side as well.”</p>
<p>The Marlins anticipate increased revenue this year not only at the box office, but thanks to a pending rights agreement that is expected to more than double income from local game telecasts.</p>
<p>“We will no longer have the worst deal in major league baseball,” majority owner Bruce Sherman said.</p>
<p>Pitchers and catchers report Wednesday to spring training in Jupiter, Florida, and like every team at this time of year, the Marlins are optimistic. Their young, promising rotation provides a strong foundation, and the minor league system is much improved since Jeter&#8217;s group bought the franchise in late 2017.</p>
<p>The Marlins are low on star power, but Jeter — a former Yankees captain who will be inducted into the Hall of Fame this summer — knows how quickly that can change.</p>
<p>“Every star wasn’t always a star,” he said. “I can go off experience. When our group was younger, nobody knew who we were. After a couple of years and a little bit of success, you become a household name.</p>
<p>“Last year was a good first step for us, getting to the postseason. That’s how you become a star &#8212; having personal success, but even more so having team success.”</p>
<p>Still in doubt is how well Miami will support baseball even if the team consistently wins. The pandemic interrupted the Jeter group&#8217;s efforts to build a bigger following.</p>
<p>“We wouldn’t have put together an ownership group and purchased the organization if we didn’t feel as though Miami was a baseball town, and that fans ultimately would come out and support the team,” Jeter said. “I wish we would average 37,000 fans this year, but we understand it&#8217;s going to take some time.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">865431</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021121-marlins-park-interior.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021121-marlins-park-interior.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021121-marlins-park-interior.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021121 marlins park interior</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins acquire reliever Floro from Dodgers for 2 pitchers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-acquire-reliever-floro-from-dodgers-for-2-pitchers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=864209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Well-traveled right-handed reliever Dylan Floro was traded Friday by the Los Angeles Dodgers to the Miami Marlins for left-handed reliever Alex Vesia...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Well-traveled right-handed reliever Dylan Floro was traded Friday by the Los Angeles Dodgers to the Miami Marlins for left-handed reliever Alex Vesia and pitching prospect Kyle Hurt.</p>
<p>Floro, 30, went 3-0 with a 2.59 ERA in 25 games last year for the World Series champions. He has also pitched for the Rays, Cubs and Reds, and has a career ERA of 3.33 over 159 2/3 innings in five seasons.</p>
<p>Floro has a 4.38 ERA in 14 postseason games, getting a key strikeout of Tampa Bay&#8217;s Randy Arozarena to strand two runners in the second inning of World Series Game 6. The Dodgers trailed 1-0 at the time and rallied for 3-1 win and their first title since 1988.</p>
<p>He agreed last month to $975,000, one-year contract and is eligible for free agency after 2023 season.</p>
<p>Vesia, 24, got rocked as a rookie for the Marlins last year, when he allowed nine earned runs in 4 1/3 innings. He has a 1.62 ERA in 52 career minor league games.</p>
<p>Hurt, a right-handed starter, was a fifth-round pick in the 2020 amateur draft who pitched for Southern Cal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">864209</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NL East teams at the start of spring training</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/nl-east-teams-at-the-start-of-spring-training/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=863532</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A team-by-team look at the National League East entering spring training, including key players each club acquired and lost, and dates of the first workout...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A team-by-team look at the National League East entering spring training, including key players each club acquired and lost, and dates of the first workout for pitchers and catchers, and the full squad:</p>
<p>___</p>
<p>Atlanta Braves</p>
<p>Manager: Brian Snitker (sixth season).</p>
<p>2020: 35-25, first place, lost to Dodgers in NL Championship Series.</p>
<p>Training Town: North Port, Florida.</p>
<p>Park: CoolToday Park.</p>
<p>First Workout: Feb. 18/23.</p>
<p>He’s Here: RHP Charlie Morton, LHP Drew Smyly, RHP Carl Edwards, SS Ehire Adrianza, RHP Victor Arano.</p>
<p>He’s Outta Here: OF Nick Markakis, OF Adam Duvall, INF Charlie Culberson, RHP Mike Foltynewicz, RHP Mark Melancon, C Tyler Flowers, RHP Shane Greene, RHP Darren O’Day, RHP Jhoulys Chacin, INF Adeiny Hechavarria, LHP Cole Hamels.</p>
<p>Going campin’: The key offseason move was re-signing left fielder Marcell Ozuna to a four-year, $65 million deal. Morton and Smyly add experience to the rotation. The team can take a cautious approach with 2020 opening day starter Mike Soroka’s return from surgery to repair his torn right Achilles tendon. Touted rookie Cristian Pache will try to solidify a starting job in center field. Pache showed strong defense as a postseason starter after only four regular-season at-bats. Ronald Acuña Jr. would start in right field. Alex Jackson and William Contreras are the top candidates in the competition to be the second catcher behind Travis d’Arnaud. If Melancon is not re-signed, Will Smith, A.J. Minter, Chris Martin and others could compete for the closer’s role. The team has not announced how many fans, if any, will be allowed to attend home spring training games.</p>
<p>___</p>
<p>Miami Marlins</p>
<p>Manager: Don Mattingly (sixth season).</p>
<p>2020: 31-29, second place, lost to Braves in Division Series.</p>
<p>Park: Roger Dean Stadium.</p>
<p>First Workout: Feb. 18/23.</p>
<p>They’re Here: GM Kim Ng, OF Adam Duvall, LHP Ross Detwiler, C Sandy Leon, RHP Anthony Bass, RHP Adam Cimber.</p>
<p>He’s Outta Here: RHP Jose Urena, RHP Brandon Kintzler, LF Matt Joyce, RHP Drew Steckenrider, C Francisco Cervelli, RHP Brad Boxberger, LHP Stephen Tarpley, RHP Robert Dugger, RHP Ryne Stanek, RHP Nick Vincent, RHP Jordan Yamamoto, RHP Johan Quezada.</p>
<p>Going campin’: Ng hasn’t swung many deals since CEO Derek Jeter hired her in November as baseball’s first female general manager. Instead, she and Jeter hope a wealth of young talent will allow the Marlins to build on last year’s progress, when they reached the playoffs for the first time since 2003 and had their first winning season since 2009. Depth in young starting pitchers is Miami’s strength, and prospects Edward Cabrera, Max Meyer and Braxton Garrett — all contenders to join the rotation at some point in 2021 — will get long looks in spring training. They’ll compete to join starters Sandy Alcantara, Pablo López and Sixto Sánchez, none of whom is older than 25. CF Starling Marte anchors the lineup, and Duvall adds pop to an offense that ranked 23rd in OPS. But to contend in a full season, the Marlins need prospects such as OF Jesus Sanchez, 1B Lewin Diaz, OF Monte Harrison and INF Jazz Chisholm to blossom.</p>
<p>___</p>
<p>Philadelphia Phillies</p>
<p>Manager: Joe Girardi (second season).</p>
<p>2020: 28-32, third place.</p>
<p>Training Town: Clearwater, Florida.</p>
<p>Park: Spectrum Field.</p>
<p>First Workout: Feb. 17/22.</p>
<p>He’s Here: RHP Archie Bradley, RHP Chase Anderson, LHP Matt Moore, LHP Jose Alvarado, RHP Sam Coonrod, INF C.J. Chatham, RHP Neftali Feliz, RHP Ivan Nova, RHP Hector Rondon, RHP David Paulino, RHP Michael Ynoa, C Christian Bethancourt, RHP Brandon Kintzler, OF Matt Joyce.</p>
<p>He’s Outta Here: OF Jay Bruce, RHP Jake Arrieta, RHP Brandon Workman, INF Phil Gosselin, RHP Heath Hembree, RHP David Phelps, RHP Blake Parker, LHP Adam Morgan, LHP Cole Irvin, OF Kyle Garlick, RHP Victor Arano.</p>
<p>Going campin’: Even with the expanded postseason format last year, the Phillies fell one win short of their first playoff berth since 2011 following a third straight September collapse. The team’s failure cost general manager Matt Klentak his job. David Dombrowski was hired to run baseball operations and Sam Fuld was promoted to GM. The Phillies re-signed two-time All-Star catcher J.T. Realmuto and agreed on a two-year deal to bring back shortstop Didi Gregorius, two key parts of an offense that tied for fifth in the majors in runs. Scoring shouldn’t be a problem for a group led by Realmuto, Gregorius, Bryce Harper, Andrew McCutchen, Rhys Hoskins and Alec Bohm, coming off an excellent rookie season. RHPs Aaron Nola, Zack Wheeler and Zach Eflin are a solid trio atop the rotation. New arms Anderson and Moore will compete with veteran Vince Velasquez and prospect Spencer Howard for the final two spots. Nova, a non-roster player, averaged 31 starts between 2017-19 so he’s another option. A dismal bullpen cost Philadelphia a postseason berth last season. Phillies relievers had a 7.06 ERA and the team blew eight separate three-run leads. Bradley has closer experience and will be a late-inning option along with righty Hector Neris. The Phillies are counting on Alvarado returning to his 2018 form with the Rays, and they’re hoping non-roster pitchers like Feliz and Rondon can do the same. Fans will not be allowed to watch spring workouts due to COVID-19, and tickets for games have yet to go on sale.</p>
<p>___</p>
<p>New York Mets</p>
<p>Manager: Luis Rojas (second season).</p>
<p>2020: 26-34, tied for fourth place.</p>
<p>Training Town: Port St. Lucie, Florida.</p>
<p>Park: Clover Park.</p>
<p>First Workout: Feb. 19/22.</p>
<p>He’s Here: SS Francisco Lindor, RHP Carlos Carrasco, C James McCann, RHP Trevor May, RHP Marcus Stroman, LHP Aaron Loup, OF/1B José Martínez, LHP Joey Lucchesi, RHP Jacob Barnes, INF Jonathan Villar (deal pending), CF Albert Almora Jr., RHP Jordan Yamamoto, LHP Stephen Tarpley, RHP Sean Reid-Foley, RHP Yennsy Díaz, RHP Sam McWilliams, OF Khalil Lee, RHP Arodys Vizcaíno, LHP Jerry Blevins, INF/OF José Peraza, OF Mallex Smith, RHP Jerad Eickhoff, INF/OF Brandon Drury, SS Wilfredo Tovar, president Sandy Alderson, acting GM Zack Scott.</p>
<p>He’s Outta Here: GM Brodie Van Wagenen, 2B Robinson Canó, C Wilson Ramos, SS Amed Rosario, INF Andrés Giménez, RHP Rick Porcello, RHP Michael Wacha, LHP Justin Wilson, LHP Steven Matz, LHP Chasen Shreve, OF Jake Marisnick, 3B Todd Frazier, OF Yoenis Céspedes, C Robinson Chirinos, RHP Jared Hughes, INF Eduardo Núñez, C René Rivera, RHP Erasmo Ramírez, RHP Paul Sewald, RHP Hunter Strickland, RHP Ariel Jurado, RHP Corey Oswalt, C Ali Sánchez, OF Ryan Cordell, INF Jed Lowrie.</p>
<p>Going campin’: The whirlwind offseason has been a rollercoaster ride since new owner Steve Cohen bought the franchise from the Wilpon and Katz families for $2.42 billion in early November. Cohen brought back Alderson, the Mets’ general manager from 2010-18, as team president and he immediately fired Van Wagenen and several top aides. Canó was then suspended for 162 games by Major League Baseball after testing positive for a performance-enhancing drug for the second time in his decorated career. He’ll sit out the entire season. New York abandoned its initial search for a president of baseball operations and hired Jared Porter as GM — only to fire him just more than a month later when ESPN reported he sent sexually explicit, uninvited text messages and images to a female reporter in 2016 when he was working for the Cubs in their front office. Scott, hired as assistant GM on Dec. 23 after 17 seasons with Boston, was promoted to acting general manager. With deep pockets, Cohen had the busy Mets shopping at the top of the market all winter and they still seem eager to add. They landed a big star in Lindor, along with Carrasco, in a blockbuster trade with Cleveland, but missed out on premium free agents Trevor Bauer, George Springer, J.T. Realmuto, DJ LeMahieu and Brad Hand. That was a disappointment. Stroman accepted an $18.9 million qualifying offer to return for one year after missing the start of last season with a calf injury and then opting out because of coronavirus concerns. Significant upgrades at catcher (McCann) and shortstop (Lindor) make a dangerous lineup even longer, but the Mets need to come through in the clutch. They ranked second in the majors in on-base percentage last year and third in OPS, yet finished only 13th in runs. New York focused on building much-needed depth this offseason and filled out a pitching staff that struggled behind two-time Cy Young Award winner Jacob deGrom. The team hopes to get starter Noah Syndergaard back from Tommy John surgery in June. With no DH in the National League this season, breakout slugger Dominic Smith, a converted first baseman, makes for a liability in left field. Defense remains an issue at several spots, though a couple are improved. Worth watching in spring training will be whether Lucchesi and second-year lefty David Peterson — or perhaps another candidate — can lock down jobs at the back of the rotation. That could send Seth Lugo back to the bullpen, where he’s been most effective. New York might also try to sign Lindor long-term. He’s eligible for free agency after the season and said he’s open to a multiyear contract, but doesn’t want to negotiate once spring training ramps up. The Mets look talented enough to end a four-year playoff drought, but it won’t be easy in a difficult division. No announcement yet on whether any fans will be permitted at Grapefruit League home games.</p>
<p>___</p>
<p>Washington Nationals</p>
<p>Manager: Dave Martinez (fourth season).</p>
<p>2020: 26-34, tied for fourth place.</p>
<p>Training Town: West Palm Beach, Florida.</p>
<p>Park: Ballpark of the Palm Beaches.</p>
<p>First Workout: Feb. 18/23.</p>
<p>He’s Here: 1B Josh Bell, LF Kyle Schwarber, LHP Brad Hand, LHP Jon Lester, C Alex Avila, C Welington Castillo, 1B Ryan Zimmerman, RHP Joe Ross.</p>
<p>He’s Outta Here: INF Wilmer Difo, LHP Sean Doolittle, C Kurt Suzuki, INF Howie Kendrick, RHP Wil Crowe, RHP James Bourque, RF Adam Eaton, CF Michael A. Taylor, 1B Eric Thames, LHP Roenis Elias.</p>
<p>Going campin’: After Washington went from World Series champion in 2019 to tied for last in the NL East in 2020, GM Mike Rizzo set out to fill some obvious holes while turning over a chunk of the roster — and he seems to have gone through his check list of biggest needs. One key caveat: He didn’t spend particularly lavishly in cash or prospects, perhaps with an eye to making a strong effort to eventually sign his two best position players to long-term deals, outfielder Juan Soto and shortstop Trea Turner. Soto, expected to switch from LF to RF with Schwarber’s arrival and Eaton’s departure, is coming off a batting title, Turner remains a sparkplug on offense and reliable on defense; both finished in the top seven in NL MVP voting last season. Sticking with his “pitching wins” philosophy, Rizzo added to an already terrific rotation by bringing aboard postseason stalwart Lester to follow three-time Cy Young Award winner Max Scherzer, World Series MVP Stephen Strasburg (who is coming off a nerve issue in his right wrist) and Patrick Corbin. The hope for the lineup is that Bell and Schwarber can be the best past versions of themselves, while Hand strengthens the back end of the bullpen. Zimmerman and potential fifth starter Ross are back after sitting out in 2020 because of COVID-19 concerns. The Nationals intend to allow spectators at spring training games, selling tickets in “pods” of up to six seats.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">863532</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins enroll in COVID-19 safety rating, plan to have fans for Opening Day</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-enroll-in-covid-19-safety-rating-plan-to-have-fans-for-opening-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=863515</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins have become the second team in Major League Baseball to enroll their ballpark in the WELL Health-Safety Rating. The rating was created...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins have become the second team in Major League Baseball to enroll their ballpark in the WELL Health-Safety Rating.</p>
<p>The rating was created in response to the coronavirus pandemic. It incorporates guidance developed by the World Health Organization, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and other health agencies.</p>
<p>Marlins officials <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-will-allow-fans-with-capacity-at-about-25-percent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plan to have fans in the stands</a> for Opening Day on April 1, when the team plays the Tampa Bay Rays.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">863515</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021121-marlins-park-interior.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/efa50afc-7b89-4d2f-acb1-522a9bb58d3b/65c9b6eb-76ad-48d8-add0-9f243ae6764a/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218286~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/efa50afc-7b89-4d2f-acb1-522a9bb58d3b/65c9b6eb-76ad-48d8-add0-9f243ae6764a/main.mp4*~hmac=71f73c020717b9d5e7165b5c44987ad1d627d3c773224c80e513a76b6c6162c9' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021121-marlins-park-interior.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2021/02/021121-marlins-park-interior.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021121 marlins park interior</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>OF Adam Duvall agrees to 1-year contract with Marlins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/of-adam-duvall-agrees-to-1-year-contract-with-marlins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 22:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=862219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Outfielder Adam Duvall agreed to terms Tuesday on a one-year contract with the Miami Marlins. At 32, Duvall will provide power and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Outfielder Adam Duvall agreed to terms Tuesday on a one-year contract with the Miami Marlins.</p>
<p>At 32, Duvall will provide power and a veteran bat to a team that is expected to rely heavily on developing youngsters. Duvall hit 16 home runs last year for Atlanta, which would have led the Marlins.</p>
<p>Miami finished ahead of only four other teams in homers in 2020, and Brian Anderson led them with 11.</p>
<p>Duvall had an OPS of .833 in 57 games last year. He has hit 105 homers since 2016.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">862219</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mets get RHP Jordan Yamamoto from Marlins for minor leaguer</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mets-get-rhp-jordan-yamamoto-from-marlins-for-minor-leaguer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 04:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=853764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — Right-hander Jordan Yamamoto was acquired by the New York Mets from the Miami Marlins on Monday for minor league infielder Federico...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK (AP) — Right-hander Jordan Yamamoto was acquired by the New York Mets from the Miami Marlins on Monday for minor league infielder Federico Polanco.</p>
<p>The 24-year-old Yamamoto was 4-5 with a 4.46 ERA in 15 starts in 2019, striking out 82 and walking 36 in 78 2/3 innings. He was 0-1 with an 18.26 ERA in 11 1/3 innings over three starts and one relief appearance during the pandemic-shortened 2020 season.</p>
<p>Yamaamoto had a $565,000 salary in the majors last year and $173,368 in the minors, and he earned $98,849 in prorated pay.</p>
<p>The 19-year-old Polanco has hit .244 in 450 at-bats in two minor league seasons with 20 doubles and 50 RBIs. He split 2019 between the Dominican Summer League and the Gulf Coast League.</p>
<p>New York opened a roster by for Yamamoto by designating infielder Robel García for assignment. The 27-year-old was claimed off waivers from Cincinnati last Oct. 26. He hit 208 with five homers and 11 RBIs 72 at-bats over 31 games for the Chicago Cubs in 2019.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">853764</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/190618_marlins_yamamoto-e1612241545150.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/190618_marlins_yamamoto-e1612241545150.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/06/190618_marlins_yamamoto-e1612241545150.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">190618_Marlins_Yamamoto</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins reach deals with Anderson, Alfaro and 3 relievers</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-reach-deals-with-anderson-alfaro-and-3-relievers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 03:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=832840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins agreed to contract terms with all of their arbitration-eligible players, including third baseman Brian Anderson. Miami also announced deals...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins agreed to contract terms with all of their arbitration-eligible players, including third baseman Brian Anderson.</p>
<p>Miami also announced deals Friday with catcher Jorge Alfaro and three relievers — Yimi Garcia, Richard Bleier and Adam Cimber.</p>
<p>In addition, Miami signed 11 players from four countries, including 18-year-old Cuban infielder Yiddi Cappe, during Major League Baseball&#8217;s international signing period. Cappe is widely regarded as one of baseball&#8217;s top 10 international prospects.</p>
<p>Anderson led the Marlins last year with 11 homers and 38 RBIs and is considered part of their long-terms plan. He has been remarkably consistent, with an average of .255 to .273 in each of his four major league seasons.</p>
<p>Alfaro batted .226 with three home runs last year and lost his starting job in the postseason to Chad Wallach, who is better defensively.</p>
<p>Garcia allowed only one run in 15 innings with 19 strikeouts last year, and he’s considered a potential closer in 2021. Bleier had a 2.16 ERA in 21 games last year for the Marlins and Orioles. Cimber had a 3.97 ERA in 14 games for the Indians, and Miami acquired him in a trade in November for $100,000.</p>
<p>Cappe is a 6-foot-3 and 175 pounds and has played shortstop in national competition in Cuba since he was 16. The Marlins also signed players from the Dominican Republic, Venezuela and Mexico.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">832840</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Detwiler signs with Marlins; Leon gets minor league deal</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/detwiler-signs-with-marlins-leon-gets-minor-league-deal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=820980</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Veteran left-hander Ross Detwiler has signed an $850,000, one-year contract with the Miami Marlins, whose primary offseason goal is to upgrade their...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Veteran left-hander Ross Detwiler has signed an $850,000, one-year contract with the Miami Marlins, whose primary offseason goal is to upgrade their bullpen.</p>
<p>The Marlins also announced on Sunday the signing of veteran catcher Sandy Leon to a minor league contract with an invitation to major league spring training. Left-hander Stephen Tarpley was designated for assignment.</p>
<p>Detwiler, 34, pitched in 16 games out of the bullpen for the Chicago White Sox in 2020, going 1-1 with a 3.20 ERA in 44 innings. He broke into the majors in 2007 and has a 4.56 ERA in 224 games for seven teams.</p>
<p>Detwiler can earn $100,000 in performance bonuses for games as a pitcher: $50,000 each for 60 and 70 games.</p>
<p>Leon, 31, batted .136 in 25 games last year for Cleveland. He has a .216 career average in nine seasons with three teams.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">820980</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Marlins offering weekly COVID-19 saliva tests to community partners</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-marlins-offering-weekly-covid-19-saliva-tests-to-community-partners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=801238</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins are pitching in to help stop the spread of COVID-19 within the community. Throughout the pandemic, the Miami Marlins have stepped up...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins are pitching in to help stop the spread of COVID-19 within the community.</p>
<p>Throughout the pandemic, the Miami Marlins have stepped up to distribute food to members of the community, but now the team is helping out by donating COVID-19 saliva tests to several local centers.</p>
<p>7News cameras were at the Boys and Girls Club of Miami-Dade on Thursday when the first testing event was held.</p>
<p>&#8220;Each week we&#8217;re providing 50 COVID-19 saliva tests to each of our community partners, so it totals about 300 a week, 1,200 a month,&#8221; said Miami Marlins Assistant Director of Communications Jon Erik Alvarez.</p>
<p>The Marlins are working with Major League Baseball to provide the needed free tests. Their goal is to help provide a safe environment for the children, as well as their families, once they are tested.</p>
<p>&#8220;They reached out and said, &#8216;Listen, we want to help. We want to help with what you guys do. We want to help the community. We want to help your staff, the kids,'&#8221; said Alex Rodriguez-Roig with the Boys and Girls Club of Miami-Dade, &#8220;so the idea of having weekly testing has been phenomenal.&#8221;</p>
<p>The saliva tests are easy to take. They are the same tests that Marlins players took during the season.</p>
<p>Results come back in 24 to 48 hours.</p>
<p>Ronny Vera, who took the test on Thursday, spoke to 7News about his experience.</p>
<p>&#8220;As you come in, it&#8217;s really simple. It takes less than 5 minutes,&#8221; he said. &#8220;They don&#8217;t put nothing up your nose, so it doesn&#8217;t hurt. It&#8217;s not uncomfortable.&#8221;</p>
<p>The free testing is available to anyone in the community.</p>
<p>&#8220;The biggest thing we get is, &#8216;Wow, this is fantastic that it&#8217;s right here in our backyard,&#8221; said Rodriguez-Roig.</p>
<p>&#8220;It helps them continue to function and provide a safe space for the kids to come out and play,&#8221; said Alvarez.</p>
<p>The Marlins&#8217; community partners also include Alpha Charter of Excellence, Big Brothers Big Sisters of Miami, CNC, Knowledge is Power Program Miami and the Overtown Youth Center.</p>
<p>&#8220;It allows for their staff, for the families and for the kids of the community to get tested, to know that they have a safe space for them to come,&#8221; said Alvarez.</p>
<p>The tests will be conducted weekly through the spring of 2021.</p>
<p>Free COVID-19 tests are also being conducted outside of Marlins Park. For more information about COVID-19 testing in Miami-Dade, click <a href="https://www.miamidade.gov/global/initiatives/coronavirus/schedule-test.page" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">801238</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/covid-saliva-tests.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2bfb68b8-eb73-4157-80d1-85aed7741deb/24719442-5f5a-470d-b430-01344a9456d0/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217231~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/2bfb68b8-eb73-4157-80d1-85aed7741deb/24719442-5f5a-470d-b430-01344a9456d0/main.mp4*~hmac=a1ee394c060f0c0bba4e7c66a5eb863424e288d27264932dc2e03ac9d2abdfd5' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/covid-saliva-tests.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/covid-saliva-tests.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">covid saliva tests</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Group of preschoolers treated to fun-filled day, presents at Marlins Park</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/group-of-preschoolers-treated-to-fun-filled-day-presents-at-marlins-park/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 19:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=796539</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Christmas came early at Marlins Park for nearly 30 preschoolers. Three and 4-year-olds from Nurturing Hispanic Communities Group, a local service organization, were treated to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Christmas came early at Marlins Park for nearly 30 preschoolers.</p>
<p>Three and 4-year-olds from Nurturing Hispanic Communities Group, a local service organization, were treated to a fun-filled day at Marlins Park on Friday morning.</p>
<p>They got silly, with Santa Billy the Marlin, opened gifts and even got to play games on the field with former Marlins catcher Charles Johnson.</p>
<p>&#8220;Oh my goodness! This is cool!&#8221; said one child.</p>
<p>&#8220;They&#8217;re so excited,&#8221; said Miami Marlins Foundation Executive Director Rocky Egusquiza.</p>
<p>They also had the opportunity to take pictures with Marlins&#8217; second baseman Isan Diaz.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s great to just spread some cheer, put some laughs, put some smiles on the kids&#8217; faces, and just have this opportunity to come out on such a tough time and just spread some love,&#8221; said Diaz.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s awesome,&#8221; said Johnson. &#8220;It&#8217;s been such a challenging year for all of us and I think a lot of us have been waiting for this time of the year, for Christmas to come around a little bit and have some kind of joy.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Miami Marlins Foundation had some help in making the memorable experience happen.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s nice to be able to get out, especially to the stadium,&#8221; said HairClub President and CEO Mike Nassar. &#8220;I think this is going to make great memories for everybody, including us.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a day the kids will most likely be talking about for a while, and it&#8217;s just part of an entire week of holiday giving.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re just so excited that our team, the Miami Marlins, and us as an organization, are able to bring smiles to kids in a year that we know they&#8217;ve missed out on so much,&#8221; said Egusquiza.</p>
<p>The week of giving for the Miami Marlins Foundation includes gift giveaways and food distributions as well.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">796539</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/marlins-park-fun-day.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a9368d2f-372a-4e4f-911e-11555f202e55/28d7c2a1-3281-4428-8573-45c78078d78e/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218386~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/a9368d2f-372a-4e4f-911e-11555f202e55/28d7c2a1-3281-4428-8573-45c78078d78e/main.mp4*~hmac=23235aa0b3de9f82a9afb5165a91d759845a6e409fd72d49f329d855ac5db8d4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/marlins-park-fun-day.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/marlins-park-fun-day.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">marlins park fun day</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins players hand out gifts to Liberty City families during drive-thru giveaway</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-players-hand-out-gifts-to-liberty-city-families-during-drive-thru-giveaway/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 01:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=795898</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins spread some holiday cheer to more than 100 families in need during a drive-thru giveaway. 7News cameras captured Marlins outfielders Lewis Brinson...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins spread some holiday cheer to more than 100 families in need during a drive-thru giveaway.</p>
<p>7News cameras captured Marlins outfielders Lewis Brinson and Monte Harrison, as well as at least one other participant dressed as Santa Claus, handing out gift bags as cars lined up Thursday for the event hosted by the Marlins Foundation.</p>
<p>In the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic there hasn&#8217;t been an offseason off the field for the baseball team.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s a tough time for everybody. A lot of people are hurting right now,&#8221; said Brinson. &#8220;To bring some gifts, some cheer, some things that they can hold on to and hug tight for a long time during this rough time, it means a lot for me to come out here and to give some stuff away.&#8221;</p>
<p>Brinson, who grew up in South Florida, and Harrison spent more than an hour handing out bags filled with gifts for 120 families.</p>
<p>The families from Liberty City were pre-selected based on need. Brinson and Harrison played the role of Santa by giving the children some of their game-worn equipment.</p>
<p>&#8220;A couple of bats, a couple of cleats, some batting gloves, lizard skins, you know, stuff little kids like,&#8221; said Harrison, &#8220;so we&#8217;re going to see who takes what.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;In the season of what I call uncertainty, it&#8217;s great to see you have organizations like the Marlins that still care for the kids,&#8221; said recipient Jerry Sawyer.</p>
<p>Several Marlins players have worked hand in hand with the Marlins Foundation since the pandemic started.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our players are so committed. They&#8217;re always reaching out to us at the foundation to figure out, &#8216;How can I be more involved?&#8217; What else can I do?'&#8221; said Rocky Egusquiza, executive director of the Marlins Foundation. &#8220;To have Lewis here, who&#8217;s from this community, giving back to this community is extremely inspirational.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I love seeing, not only kids, but just their parents, all the hard work that they&#8217;re putting in, to maybe take a load off their back, give them something for Christmas, so maybe they can use this as a Christmas gift,&#8221; said Brinson. &#8220;A lot of people are struggling right now, and I just want to be out here and help.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Marlins continue to show they&#8217;re embracing the community during this difficult time. They will be handing more than 100 holiday fruit gift bags across from Marlins Park next Wednesday, beginning at 1 p.m.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">795898</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201210_Marlins_toy_giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4bfcb6b0-7861-4bae-ac74-540576b29c6a/e7da47f6-d227-4553-acf5-4322ff229cf8/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219452~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/4bfcb6b0-7861-4bae-ac74-540576b29c6a/e7da47f6-d227-4553-acf5-4322ff229cf8/main.mp4*~hmac=4732970c920d23f49f6643f13a731cfc4ca82e54ed2421770321c5bd155cb7ca' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201210_Marlins_toy_giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/201210_Marlins_toy_giveaway.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">201210_Marlins_toy_giveaway</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins distribute meals in Miami to South Floridians in need</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-distribute-meals-in-miami-to-south-floridians-in-need/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 01:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=795016</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins have pitched in to help South Floridians who are struggling to put food on the table ahead of the holidays. Volunteers with...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins have pitched in to help South Floridians who are struggling to put food on the table ahead of the holidays.</p>
<p>Volunteers with the Miami Marlins Foundation distributed food to hundreds of waiting food recipients during a drive-thru giveaway in Miami, Wednesday.</p>
<p>&#8220;I haven&#8217;t worked in seven and a half months,&#8221; recipient Manny Sosa said. &#8220;The entertainment industry has suffered so much. I dress up so I can look nice and do normal things, and this food and this help that you guys are giving us is making such a difference. Thank you, so, so much.&#8221;</p>
<p>More than 500 meal boxes were on hand to help those who lined up in their vehicles for more than two hours.</p>
<p>Wednesday was not the first time the Marlins have helped others during the pandemic.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ve been able to distribute more than 800,000 meals this year,&#8221; said Jon Erik Alvarez, the Marlins&#8217; Assistant Director of Communications. &#8220;On top of that, we mixed in hand cleaner, hand sanitizers that we made with Tito&#8217;s Handmade Vodka. We&#8217;ve been able to distribute 24,000 bottles as well as masks. As you can see, this Miami Marlins Foundation mask, we&#8217;ve distributed 20,000 masks, as well.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Marlins worked together with volunteers who continue to help distribute the necessities people need.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve done about five or six,&#8221; volunteer Petra Vanhelvourt said. &#8220;I&#8217;m European, and in Europe, we have a very social nature, I think. We do care about each other, and I think here, especially now, it definitely is. We have to care about each other, and we have to take care about each other, so that&#8217;s why I&#8217;m here.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;There&#8217;s definitely folks in our community that are really feeling the strain of the pandemic, and any thing we can do to help them and get food on the table for them is something that we&#8217;re happy to do and will continue to do,&#8221; Miami Marlins Foundation spokesperson Angela Smith said.</p>
<p>The Marlins will hold another drive-thru distribution across the street from Marlins Park next Wednesday, when they will distribute 1,000 holiday gift baskets to help feed people in need.</p>
<p>Marlins infielder Miguel Rojas will be on hand for the next distribution, which will begin at 1 p.m.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">795016</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/120920-marlins-food-distribution.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0861fe66-bc52-4bba-8205-f4099440e6d3/a51d089a-1f59-4411-9f39-c779e14dee47/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219088~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0861fe66-bc52-4bba-8205-f4099440e6d3/a51d089a-1f59-4411-9f39-c779e14dee47/main.mp4*~hmac=4b9d2f35aff33e089d28a1f3dbfb476deca17ee6dfafd94a0705e79bece9674c' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/120920-marlins-food-distribution.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/12/120920-marlins-food-distribution.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">120920 marlins food distribution</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kim Ng&#8217;s crash course: She&#8217;s bullish on Marlins&#8217; future</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kim-ngs-crash-course-shes-bullish-on-marlins-future/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 19:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=790578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — For Kim Ng, the first three weeks as general manager of the Miami Marlins has meant less rest and more coffee. She...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — For Kim Ng, the first three weeks as general manager of the Miami Marlins has meant less rest and more coffee.</p>
<p>She has been getting to know colleagues at work, contacting agents and other teams, and learning as much as she can about the 150 or so players in the Marlins organization.</p>
<p>“Let&#8217;s call it a crash course,” Ng said with a smile. “I got to sleep in until 5:30 this morning, so I&#8217;m doing pretty good. Not a big coffee drinker, but I&#8217;ve had to dip in there a bit these past couple of weeks. My husband has been really great making sure I&#8217;m eating three times a day.”</p>
<p>Having a husband in a supporting role is a reminder Ng is the first female general manager in major league history. That milestone wasn&#8217;t mentioned once during her 30-minute news conference Thursday, a sign of how quickly a breakthrough can become part of the norm.</p>
<p>Instead, Ng&#8217;s comments focused on efforts to build on the Marlins&#8217; recent progress as CEO Derek Jeter&#8217;s ownership group begins Year 4 of a franchise revival.</p>
<p>This year the Marlins reached the playoffs for the first time since 2003. A rebuilt farm system ranked among baseball&#8217;s best began to bear fruit, and an abundance of prospects has the organization enthusiastic about 2021.</p>
<p>After three weeks studying video and talking with Marlins scouts, Ng shares in the optimism about the foundation built by Jeter and his group.</p>
<p>“They are ahead of the game,” Ng said. “It takes a really, really long time to build a farm system of this quality and caliber. That’s the most exciting thing about all of this, and making sure we as a front office are doing everything we can to help in their development.”</p>
<p>Heading into next week&#8217;s winter meetings, which will be held virtually, the Marlins&#8217; priorities include upgrading the bullpen and adding a veteran bat, Ng said. But improvement can also come from within, she said, because so many prospects are on the cusp of major league success.</p>
<p>“If just one of those guys lives up to their potential that we haven&#8217;t seen yet, that would be a huge impact on our club,” Ng said.</p>
<p>The Marlins likely won&#8217;t be too busy in the free agent market, because they don&#8217;t want veterans clogging competition.</p>
<p>“Whenever we can give a prospect a chance to play, we really would like to do that,” Ng said. “The quicker they come along and develop, the better off we&#8217;re going to be as a club for a long time.”</p>
<p>One veteran who could be part of the long-term plans is third baseman Brian Anderson, who is heading into his fifth season with the Marlins. He&#8217;s unlikely to receive a long-term contract offer this winter, however, in part because the team has a new GM.</p>
<p>“I personally would like to see how this year goes before we venture down that road,” Ng said, “so I have a better understanding of who he is as a player, and I get a better sense of the situation.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">790578</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Kim-Ng.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Kim-Ng.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Kim-Ng.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Kim Ng</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Heat, Marlins, Dolphins collaborate for Thanksgiving food drive</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-heat-marlins-dolphins-collaborate-for-thanksgiving-food-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 01:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Heat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=784286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Three South Florida sports teams came together to feed a need in the community by organizing their respective Thanksgiving food drives. The pandemic couldn&#8217;t slow...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three South Florida sports teams came together to feed a need in the community by organizing their respective Thanksgiving food drives.</p>
<p>The pandemic couldn&#8217;t slow down South Florida&#8217;s top three sports teams from doing their part to help the community, as the Miami Dolphins made sure to score touchdowns with families in Miami Gardens by providing 850 boxed meals filled with delicious sides and a nice turkey.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s an opportunity for you to really sit down with your family and to give thanks and to be happy and to just relax for a moment,&#8221; Dolphins Senior Director of Community Affairs Leslie Nixon said. &#8220;Having the burden of trying to figure out where your next meal is gonna come from, how you&#8217;re gonna pay the bills is really tough. Again, if we can take that burden off a family member&#8217;s plate and just allow them to enjoy each other&#8217;s company, that&#8217;s really what Thanksgiving means.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Miami Marlins joined forces with Feeding South Florida to dish out 1,000 Thanksgiving dinners. Sponsored by Tito&#8217;s Handmade Vodka, the Marlins&#8217; 12th Annual Home Plate Meals Thanksgiving distribution is something Derek Jeter and the team feels is a big hit for the community during the holidays.</p>
<p>&#8220;This has always been one of our favorite times of the year to give back, and considering everything that&#8217;s gone on this year, it&#8217;s a little extra meaningful,&#8221; Jeter said. &#8220;We said early on right when we took over this organization that we wanted to be this community&#8217;s team, and part of that is being here to support the community.&#8221;</p>
<p>For two decades, Miami Heat Hall of Famer Alonzo Mourning provided hundreds of hearty meals with all the trimmings where no virus was going to stop the tradition for the Awesome 33 Thanksgiving Giveaway.</p>
<p>&#8220;Being able to provide that during a very, very difficult time, during a very devastating pandemic, to be able to provide the relief and support to all the 300 families is truly a blessing,&#8221; said Mourning.</p>
<p>The Dolphins said they&#8217;ll give out almost 22,000 meals by Thanksgiving Day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">784286</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/97c3685c-6e8f-462d-97e8-7968a5c2e76e/da314c77-7945-46f8-a02c-8687589d8cc9/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217602~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/97c3685c-6e8f-462d-97e8-7968a5c2e76e/da314c77-7945-46f8-a02c-8687589d8cc9/main.mp4*~hmac=12d74011688a465fbc67e0bc148e6a43ff382a7c1a338982a6382ad29b7daad6' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/112320-Marlins_Thanksgiving-food-drive.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">112320 Marlins_Thanksgiving food drive</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kim Ng ready to bear the torch as baseball&#8217;s 1st female GM</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kim-ng-ready-to-bear-the-torch-as-baseballs-1st-female-gm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 18:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=779960</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins&#8217; new general manager sat at home plate in the team&#8217;s ballpark Monday, reflecting on all the times she struck...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins&#8217; new general manager sat at home plate in the team&#8217;s ballpark Monday, reflecting on all the times she struck out.</p>
<p>As baseball&#8217;s first female GM, Kim Ng can bask in a breakthrough achievement that&#8217;s all the more admirable because she was turned down for a similar job by at least five other teams over the past 15 years.</p>
<p>During an hour-long introductory virtual news conference, Ng confessed she had doubted whether the moment would ever come for her.</p>
<p>“Look, it’s a tribute to the idea that you just have to keep plowing through,” she said. “That’s what this is. It&#8217;s like what we tell the players — you can mope and sulk for a few days, but that’s it. You’ve got to come back, and that’s what I&#8217;ve been able to do. I&#8217;ve been defeated and deflated numerous times, but you keep hoping.”</p>
<p>And now, Ng (pronounced Ang) has earned a win for women everywhere. She is believed to be the first female general manager in the four major North American professional sports leagues, and she&#8217;s also being saluted as a pioneering Asian American, even overseas.</p>
<p>“Apparently I have a small little fan club in China,” she said.</p>
<p>Ng celebrated her achievement with her four sisters and her mother, who was born in China and came to the United States at age 5. Other ceiling-busting women offered congratulations, from Michelle Obama to Billie Jean King.</p>
<p>Ng said at least 500 people have told her they&#8217;re now Marlins fans. She&#8217;s especially heartened to set an example for young girls who might aspire to a career in sports management.</p>
<p>“There&#8217;s an adage: You can&#8217;t be it if you can&#8217;t see it. Now you can see it,” she said.</p>
<p>Ng, who turns 52 on Tuesday, started her baseball career as a Chicago White Sox intern in 1990, and for the past nine years was a senior vice president for Major League Baseball.</p>
<p>She spent four years with the New York Yankees when their star shortstop was Derek Jeter, now the Marlins&#8217; CEO. By reaching out to her regarding the Miami job, she said, Jeter showed fearlessness.</p>
<p>“Derek embodies that word,” Ng said. “I was privileged to watch Derek for four years every day on the field, and that was his approach to the game. He left it all out there every single day. Fearlessness on the field, and now with this, we see it off the field.”</p>
<p>Ng joins a long-suffering franchise on the upswing. The Marlins reached the playoffs this year for the first time since 2003 and have built one of baseball&#8217;s best farm systems since Jeter&#8217;s group bought the team three years ago.</p>
<p>Ng replaces president of baseball operations Michael Hill, who had been with the Marlins since 2002 but wasn&#8217;t retained after the season.</p>
<p>“When I first reached out to Kim, I think through our first couple of conversations it became evident to both of us that this was a perfect fit,” Jeter said. “We couldn’t be more excited to have her experience and leadership to help lead us down our path to sustained success.”</p>
<p>Ng&#8217;s father introduced her to baseball, and she learned the game by playing stickball while in elementary school in Queens.</p>
<p>“First base would be the red car on the right,” she said. “Second base was the manhole. Third base was the green car on the left, and another manhole for home. Those are great memories.”</p>
<p>She attended her first game at Yankee Stadium in the late 1970s, and her favorite player was catcher Thurman Munson. She played shortstop for the University of Chicago&#8217;s softball team, and then began to climb the major league ranks.</p>
<p>There was occasional resistance. In 2003, a New York Mets scout was fired for making racially insensitive remarks to Ng at baseball&#8217;s GM meetings, when she was with the Los Angeles Dodgers. Some teams that gave her job interviews didn&#8217;t really seem interested in hiring her, she said.</p>
<p>Even now, as she reaches the pinnacle in her profession, Ng said she feels as though a 10,000-pound weight has been transferred from one shoulder to the other.</p>
<p>“You&#8217;re bearing the torch for so many,” Ng said. “That’s a big responsibility, but I take it on.”</p>
<p>As baseball&#8217;s first female general manager, she embraces the chance to be judged on wins and losses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">779960</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/kim-ng-2.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e90fb190-2d9a-4a1f-acb4-08bd30b9f75a/75b1ed31-b244-4e96-a743-1b71ad62bb65/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615218319~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/e90fb190-2d9a-4a1f-acb4-08bd30b9f75a/75b1ed31-b244-4e96-a743-1b71ad62bb65/main.mp4*~hmac=aaccbdc8921121725f296171848772090ee503752039c8f2d0dea1dc244848b4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/kim-ng-2.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/kim-ng-2.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">kim ng</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breakthrough for women: Miami Marlins hire Kim Ng as GM</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/breakthrough-for-women-miami-marlins-hire-kim-ng-as-gm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Johari Canty]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 16:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=778458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Kim Ng started her Major League Baseball career as an intern, and three decades later she&#8217;s still on the rise while shattering...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MIAMI (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Kim Ng started her Major League Baseball career as an intern, and three decades later she&#x2019;s still on the rise while shattering ceilings.<p>Ng became the majors&#x2019; highest-ranking woman in baseball operations when she was hired Friday as general manager of the Miami Marlins. She is believed to be the first female GM in the four major North American professional sports leagues, the Marlins said.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/Marlins/status/1327276960595243009</embed></div><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I think this is the most noteworthy day for baseball since Jackie Robinson broke the color barrier in 1947,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; said Richard Lapchick, an expert on race and gender in sports at the University of Central Florida.</p><p>Ng (pronounced Ang) won three World Series rings while spending 21 years in the front offices of the Chicago White Sox (1990-96), New York Yankees (1998-2001) and Los Angeles Dodgers (2002-11). She spent the past nine years with MLB as a senior vice president.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;After decades of determination, it is the honor of my career to lead the Miami Marlins,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Ng said in a statement. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;When I got into this business, it seemed unlikely a woman would lead a major league team, but I am dogged in the pursuit of my goals. My goal is now to bring championship baseball to Miami.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Marlins CEO Derek Jeter played for the Yankees when Ng worked for them.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We look forward to Kim bringing a wealth of knowledge and championship-level experience to the Miami Marlins,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Jeter said in a statement. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Her leadership of our baseball operations team will play a major role on our path toward sustained success. Additionally, her extensive work in expanding youth baseball and softball initiatives will enhance our efforts to grow the game among our local youth as we continue to make a positive impact on the South Florida community.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Jeter became baseball&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s first Black CEO after his group bought the Marlins in 2017. He then hired Caroline O&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;Connor, who as senior vice president is one of the highest ranking women in professional sports.</p><p>Ng, 51, is also a groundbreaking Asian American. She joins at the top ranks of her profession the San Francisco Giants&#x2019; president of baseball operations, Farhan Zaidi. She becomes the fifth person to hold the Marlins&#x2019; top position in baseball operations and succeeds Michael Hill, who was not retained after the 2020 season.</p><p>A virtual news conference for Ng is planned for Monday.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;All of us at Major League Baseball are thrilled for Kim and the opportunity she has earned with the Marlins,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; baseball Commissioner Rob Manfred said in a statement. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Kim&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s appointment makes history in all of professional sports and sets a significant example for the millions of women and girls who love baseball and softball. The hard work, leadership, and record of achievement throughout her long career in the national pastime led to this outcome.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>The Miami Dolphins&#x2019; Brian Flores, one of four head coaches of color in the NFL, was among those to applaud Ng&#x2019;s hiring.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;It&#x2019;s phenomenal,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Flores said. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Anyone who thinks a woman can&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t manage or coach or lead, I think, is silly. Kudos to the Marlins.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Marlins shortstop Miguel Rojas offered Ng a virtual fist bump on Twitter.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I am proud of the Marlins for this hiring,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Rojas said in a statement. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;It is a special day.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>Ng joins a long-suffering franchise that achieved surprising progress in Year 3 of Jeter&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s rebuilding effort, reaching the playoffs for the first time since 2003 and sweeping the Chicago Cubs in the wild-card round. The Marlins were swept by the Atlanta Braves in the National League Division Series.</p><p>Ng started her baseball career as a White Sox intern and rose to become assistant director of baseball operations. She worked for the American League for one year and then joined the Yankees, becoming the youngest assistant general manager in MLB at 29, and only the second woman to attain that position with a major league club. She was the Dodgers&#x2019; vice president and assistant general manager.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;It is wonderful seeing people accomplish their stated goals, and this has been a dream of hers for as long as I&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;ve known her,&#x201D; Yankees general manager Brian Cashman said in a statement. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;She will provide the Marlins with vast experience and institutional knowledge, along with a calm demeanor and an amazing ability to connect with others.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p><p>In Ng&#x2019;s most recent job with Major League Baseball, she directed international baseball operations, working with the front offices of the major league clubs and many other baseball leagues and entities around the world. She led a team that set policy for and enforced international signing rules, established MLB&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s first system for registering international players for signing, managed protocols for signing international players, and negotiated agreements with international winter leagues.</p><p>Ng graduated from the University of Chicago, where she played softball and earned a degree in public policy. Jean Afterman, who has been the Yankees&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99; assistant GM since succeeding Ng nearly 20 years ago, said her predecessor possesses talents that are gender-blind.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;It is a tremendous achievement to be the first female GM in Major League Baseball, and I hope young girls (and boys) take notice of this and further understand that there are no limits to their dreams,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Afterman said in a written statement. &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;I congratulate the Marlins &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; that after a remarkable season, during extraordinary times &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; they have broken a barrier that needed shattering.&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D;</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">778458</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Kim-Ng.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/485489e8-6a16-4764-8590-5e3ba249516f/4d3b7650-dcef-45d4-96d5-b211079f9810/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615217733~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/485489e8-6a16-4764-8590-5e3ba249516f/4d3b7650-dcef-45d4-96d5-b211079f9810/main.mp4*~hmac=730c0d8ebac50b6842b38af71c83ea71446a5c8354a66f5b3724c661555bb5a4' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Kim-Ng.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/Kim-Ng.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Kim Ng</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kevin Cash, Don Mattingly win Manager of the Year awards</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kevin-cash-don-mattingly-win-manager-of-the-year-awards/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 23:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=776865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[By the time Kevin Cash pulled Tampa Bay ace Blake Snell from the last game of the World Series, he had already been voted Manager...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the time Kevin Cash pulled Tampa Bay ace Blake Snell from the last game of the World Series, he had already been voted Manager of the Year in the American League.</p>
<p>Even if he ended up losing the biggest prize.</p>
<p>It was a Sunshine State sweep for skippers Tuesday night, with Miami’s Don Mattingly winning NL Manager of the Year and Cash receiving the AL award.</p>
<p>Long regarded as one of baseball’s brightest young minds, Cash guided the thrifty Rays to an AL-best 40-20 record during the pandemic-shortened season. But he was roundly criticized for pulling a dominant Snell in the sixth inning of the decisive Game 6 of the Fall Classic against the champion Los Angeles Dodgers.</p>
<p>“Have I reflected on it? There’s not a day that goes by that I don’t reflect on it,” Cash said. “Being in this position we owe it to ourselves and more importantly our players to continue to reflect on those decisions.”</p>
<p>After Snell exited, the Dodgers rallied against Nick Anderson and went on to a 3-1 victory. Cash said he has had multiple conversations with many people within the game since the loss and has received a lot of positive support.</p>
<p>“Yes, I would do it the same way all over again. I would plead for a different outcome, that’s for sure,” Cash said with a chuckle.</p>
<p>“That decision was not reflective of my confidence in Blake. It was very reflective of my confidence in Nick, and that’s (what) I felt was, at the moment, the best chance for us to win the game.”</p>
<p>Voting by the Baseball Writers’ Association of America concluded before the beginning of the playoffs. Rick Renteria, let go by the Chicago White Sox after the team made the postseason for the first time since 2008, finished second in the AL, followed by Toronto’s Charlie Montoyo.</p>
<p>Mattingly led the Marlins to their first playoff appearance since 2003 despite dealing with a COVID-19 outbreak that paused their season and ravaged the roster.</p>
<p>The Marlins’ 31-29 record was Mattingly’s first winning season in his fifth year with the club. The former New York Yankees first baseman and captain had a winning record in each of his five seasons as manager of the Dodgers.</p>
<p>Mattingly, the first Manager of the Year for the Marlins since Joe Girardi in 2006, was the AL MVP in 1985. He became the fifth person to win both MVP and Manager of the Year.</p>
<p>“They’re just different. The first one feels personal and this one feels more like a team thing,” Mattingly said, “and that’s why I’m proud of it because we’ve struggled for a couple years and for us to move forward is important, and I think this is a sign that we’re heading in that direction.”</p>
<p>San Diego’s Jayce Tingler finished second behind Mattingly in balloting by the BBWAA, followed by David Ross of the Chicago Cubs.</p>
<p>The Cy Young Awards will be announced by the BBWAA on Wednesday night, followed by the MVPs on Thursday.</p>
<p>After losing 105 games a year ago, Miami had its 2020 season nearly derailed by a coronavirus outbreak during the first weekend of play. The team had to make 174 roster moves but still managed the franchise’s first winning record since 2009.</p>
<p>The steady hand of the 59-year-old Mattingly played a big role in the turnaround, which continued in the playoffs. Miami eliminated the NL Central champion Cubs in the first round before getting swept by the Atlanta Braves in the Division Series.</p>
<p>“Over 100 losses, that’s the tough part,” Mattingly said. “It just feels good that we’re moving in the right direction.”</p>
<p>Cash, who turns 43 on Dec. 6, hit .183 with 12 homers and 58 RBIs in 246 major league games as a catcher for five teams, including Tampa Bay. After his playing career ended, he worked as an advance scout for Texas and Toronto before joining manager Terry Francona’s staff in Cleveland as the bullpen coach.</p>
<p>The Tampa, Florida, native and Florida State alum was hired as Tampa Bay manager the day before his 37th birthday. He finished third in balloting for AL Manager of the Year in each of the past two seasons. He is the franchise’s first winner of the award since Joe Maddon in 2011.</p>
<p>“There is a sense of pride being a Tampa guy,” said Cash, who is 454-416 in six years as manager of the Rays.</p>
<p>Tampa Bay had a $29 million prorated payroll as of Aug. 1, which ranked 28th out of 30 teams. Still, the Rays won the AL East for the first time since 2010.</p>
<p>The Rays leaned heavily on their bullpen throughout the truncated season, with 12 pitchers recording at least one save — matching the major league record. So the move to get Snell was in line with what made the Rays so successful all year.</p>
<p>“Yes, we did that multiple times throughout the year. Does that mean that it has to be done in Game 6? No, it doesn’t,” Cash said. “I think there’s many things that go into those decisions.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">776865</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/02/021319-mattingly-e1568980874806.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/02/021319-mattingly-e1568980874806.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/02/021319-mattingly-e1568980874806.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">021319 Mattingly</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins, Feed the Polls partner to feed voters on Election Day</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-feed-the-polls-partner-to-feed-voters-on-election-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 23:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=772541</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Marlins teamed up with several local organizations to help feed voters who were in line to cast their ballot on Election Day. The...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Marlins teamed up with several local organizations to help feed voters who were in line to cast their ballot on Election Day.</p>
<p>The Marlins partnered with Feed the Polls to promote voting where voter suppression and voting intimidation has been an issue.</p>
<p>&#8220;We don&#8217;t want food and security to be a road block to getting out to the polls,&#8221; Marlins Vice President of Experience and Innovation Mike Shaw said, &#8220;so as a group, we joined together with Zagat and with the infatuation in the micro kitchen to make sure that meals or food and security would not be a reason to come out and vote.&#8221;</p>
<p>Expecting long lines on Election Day, the two organizations plan to distribute 4,000 meals in both Little Havana and Liberty City.</p>
<p>&#8220;Absolutely, man, obviously, this election is important, can&#8217;t stress that enough, and to see people out here voting and putting in their vote and giving them meals for families that may need it,&#8221; outfielder Lewis Brinson said.</p>
<p>&#8220;If there&#8217;s a line, if you think you might not make it home for dinner, you might not make it home for lunch, we&#8217;re here,&#8221; Rocky Egusquiza, the executive director of the Miami Marlins Foundation, said. &#8220;We&#8217;re serving food. We&#8217;ll be here until 7 p.m., that the polls close today.&#8221;</p>
<p>All voters have to do is cast their ballot to receive the free food.</p>
<p>&#8220;There&#8217;s no reason &#8212; know it&#8217;s good sharing with the community, voting,&#8221; Lamar Williams, a voter, said. &#8220;Everybody is getting it done.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">772541</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110320-miami-marlins-feeding.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8655a9ba-1914-4767-b1fe-db01345a8152/ebf3470e-41a7-49f4-867a-ca9d2dd68add/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219050~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/8655a9ba-1914-4767-b1fe-db01345a8152/ebf3470e-41a7-49f4-867a-ca9d2dd68add/main.mp4*~hmac=b48ce323c409672691963193b16b3376705642814fac3c5d2d0a335b4d016052' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110320-miami-marlins-feeding.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/110320-miami-marlins-feeding.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">110320 miami marlins feeding</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins, Jeter part with exec Michael Hill after 19 seasons</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-jeter-part-with-exec-michael-hill-after-19-seasons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 16:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=762676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Marlins executive Michael Hill&#8217;s 19-season tenure with the franchise has ended. Hill was president of baseball operations for the past six...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Marlins executive Michael Hill&#8217;s 19-season tenure with the franchise has ended.</p>
<p>Hill was president of baseball operations for the past six years and provided continuity after a 2017 change in ownership, but his contract expired and he will not be back next season, CEO Derek Jeter said Sunday.</p>
<p>“I had to approach this as a new negotiation,” Jeter said. “We had conversations over the last week or so, and I just felt it would be best for the organization at this particular time to move on without Mike.”</p>
<p>The Marlins will cast a wide search for a replacement, but potential candidates are unlikely to include vice president of player development and scouting Gary Denbo, who has been instrumental in the franchise turnaround and is expected to remain in his current role.</p>
<p>“We have a lot of smart baseball minds in our organization, and there are smart baseball minds around the game,” Jeter said. “We’re going to sit down and see what type of person we need in this role.”</p>
<p>Hill joined the Marlins&#8217; front office in 2002, and the next year they won the World Series. But this year&#8217;s 31-29 finish was their first above .500 since 2009, and they made the playoffs for the first time in 17 years.</p>
<p>Hill helped steer the Marlins through a coronavirus outbreak that nearly derailed their season. The Marlins beat the Chicago Cubs in the wild-card round of the playoffs before being eliminated by Atlanta and exceeded all outside expectations with a young, patchwork roster one year after losing 105 games.</p>
<p>“It was a great step for us as an organization to see some of the progress we have made over the last three years,” Jeter said.</p>
<p>Hill was general manager for six seasons before becoming president of baseball operations, and he retained that title even as Jeter overhauled the organizational structure.</p>
<p>“The roles and the responsibilities have changed since we’ve gotten here,” Jeter said. “I think we’ve done a pretty good job of building each department of baseball operations.”</p>
<p>Hill had a hand in the record $325 million, 13-year contract Giancarlo Stanton signed with the Marlins in 2014. He later was involved in trading Stanton and All-Stars Christian Yelich, Marcell Ozuna, Dee Gordon and J.T. Realmuto as the Marlins rebuilt from the farm system up under Jeter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">762676</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wright, d&#8217;Arnaud lead Braves to sweep Marlins, reach NLCS</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/wright-darnaud-lead-braves-to-sweep-marlins-reach-nlcs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 22:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AP_FL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com?p=757232&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=757232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOUSTON (AP) — Rookie Kyle Wright dazzled for six innings in his postseason debut, and the Atlanta Braves rode their superb pitching to beat the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOUSTON (AP) — Rookie Kyle Wright dazzled for six innings in his postseason debut, and the Atlanta Braves rode their superb pitching to beat the Miami Marlins 7-0 Thursday for a three-game sweep and their first trip to the NL Championship Series since 2001.</p>
<p>Atlanta had lost eight straight Division Series, including in each of the previous two seasons, before outscoríng the Marlins 18-5, including 11-0 in the final two games. The Braves are 5-0 with a 0.92 ERA in the postseason, allowing five runs in 49 innings.</p>
<p>There were only a few scattered cheers as the Braves wrapped up the series in an almost empty Minute Maid Park, where the only fans allowed were players’ friends and families.</p>
<p>They will play the Los Angeles Dodgers or San Diego in the NLCS starting Monday in Arlington, Texas. They had not advanced to the NLCS since they were led by Chipper Jones, Greg Maddux, Tom Glavine and John Smoltz, a team managed by Bobby Cox.</p>
<p>Wright (1-0) was sharp despite not pitching since Sept. 25, allowing three hits and walking two with a career-high seven strikeouts. A.J. Minter, Jacob Webb and Shane Greene finished the five-hitter to give the Braves four shutouts in five playoff games.</p>
<p>They’re the second team in history to throw four shutouts in the first five playoff games, joining the 1905 New York Giants.</p>
<p>Travis d’Arnaud doubled twice, with the first one driving in two runs in Atlanta’s big third inning. The veteran catcher, who bounced around three teams in a tough 2019, helped steady Atlanta’s young starters, was 6 for 10 with three doubles, two home runs and seven RBIs in the sweep.</p>
<p>The Marlins, who lost 105 games last season, were the feel-good story of this postseason after overcoming a coronavirus outbreak to reach the postseason for the first time since 2003. With a front office led by Derek Jeter and and a dugout headed by manager Don Mattingly, they entered confident after sweeping the Chicago Cubs in the wild-card round. But the young team was overwhelmed and lost a playoff series for the first time after entering 7-0 with titles in 1997 and 2003.</p>
<p>Rookie Sixto Sánchez (0-1) walked Ronald Acuña Jr. to start the third, and Acuña stole second before advancing to third on a single by Freddie Freeman. Marcell Ozuna laced a single that scored Acuña.</p>
<p>D’Arnaud knocked a double off the bullpen in right-center to send two home and extend the lead to 3-0. The Braves tacked on another run on a sacrifice fly by Dansby Swanson.</p>
<p>Sánchez, who threw five scoreless frames in Game 2 of the wild card, was done after that inning, allowing four hits and runs with three walks as he tied his shortest outing of the season.</p>
<p>The Marlins had a chance to cut into the lead in the bottom of the inning when they loaded the bases with two outs. But Jazz Chisholm grounded out to end the threat.</p>
<p>It was a theme throughout the day for Miami, which went 0 for 9 with runners in scoring position.</p>
<p>Atlanta added a run in the fourth when Acuña scored from first after centerfielder Magneuris Sierra committed an error on a single by Freeman.</p>
<p>The Braves continued to pour it on in the fifth when Swanson had an RBI single and Adam Duvall sent him home with a double to make it 7-0.</p>
<p>Atlanta’s win overshadowed a terrific catch by Corey Dickerson in the second that helped Sánchez escape a bases-loaded with no outs jam. Sánchez struck out Adam Duvall for the first out before Dickerson dived to catch a ball hit by Nick Markakis just before it hit the grass that likely saved multiple runs from scoring.</p>
<p>Dickerson’s catch came a day after Markakis made a perfect throw to pick Dickerson off at second in the eighth inning of Game 2.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">757232</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anderson sharp, Markakis alert, Braves blank Miami, lead 2-0</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/anderson-sharp-markakis-alert-braves-blank-miami-lead-2-0/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 23:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AP_FL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com?p=756483&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=756483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOUSTON (AP) — Rookie Ian Anderson pitched like a poised veteran, right fielder Nick Markakis made a nifty defensive play late and the Atlanta Braves...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOUSTON (AP) — Rookie Ian Anderson pitched like a poised veteran, right fielder Nick Markakis made a nifty defensive play late and the Atlanta Braves threw another playoff shutout, beating the Miami Marlins 2-0 Wednesday for a 2-0 lead in the NL Division Series.</p>
<p>The Braves have pitched three shutouts in four games this postseason. Travis d&#8217;Arnaud and Dansby Swanson each homered for the second straight day, putting Atlanta one win away from a sweep in the best-of-five matchup.</p>
<p>The 22-year-old Anderson scattered three hits and struck out eight over 5 2/3 innings. The lanky right-hander who made his major league debut in late August added to his impressive outing last week in the wild-card series when he fanned nine in six scoreless frames against Cincinnati.</p>
<p>The 36-year-old Markakis helped preserve the shutout and the lead in the eighth.</p>
<p>Corey Dickerson reached on an error by Swanson at shortstop to start the inning, setting up Markakis&#8217; heads-up play. Jon Berti sliced a high fly down the line that Markakis alertly plucked on one hop and, with Dickerson holding up to see if the ball would be caught, threw to Swanson for a forceout at second base in a close play.</p>
<p>Will Smith retired the next two batters and Mark Melancon, Atlanta&#8217;s fifth pitcher of the game, closed the combined three-hitter for a save.</p>
<p>Swanson and d’Arnaud provided the offense in this one, with both players hitting solo shots a day after the two hit multi-run homers in a huge seventh inning for the Braves in their Game 1 win.</p>
<p>Game 3 is Thursday in Houston.</p>
<p>Players from both teams behaved themselves a day after tempers flared in the opener when Braves star Ronald Acuña Jr. was nailed by a 98 mph fastball. Acuña had a quiet afternoon, going 0 for 4 and striking out all four times.</p>
<p>Swanson’s homer off Pablo Lopez put the Braves up 1-0 with two outs in the second inning.</p>
<p>There was one out in the fourth when d’Arnaud launched his soaring home run to left field, where it bounced off a metal sign high on the wall making a loud bang. Cameras panned to Anderson in the dugout, and the pitcher smiled broadly as he watched the ball sail away.</p>
<p>D’Arnaud’s homer made him the first catcher for the Braves to hit multiple home runs in one postseason since Brian McCann also had two in 2005. He’s made quite a comeback this season after bouncing around between three teams in a tough 2019.</p>
<p>Now he’s helped put the Braves one win away from reaching the NL Championship Series for the first time since 2001 when Bobby Cox was manager and Chipper Jones the team’s star.</p>
<p>They’ve lost in the division series eight times since then, including in the last two seasons — a fact Freddie Freeman said put a chip on their shoulders entering this round.</p>
<p>The Marlins, who made the playoffs for the first time since 2003, bounded their way into this round with high energy and plenty of smiles. They had little reason to grin on Wednesday when they couldn’t scratch a single run across, going 0-4 with runners in scoring position.</p>
<p>It’s put them cusp of losing the first playoff series in franchise history after entering this round 7-0 all-time in the postseason.</p>
<p>They had a chance to cut into the lead in the sixth inning when Berti singled with one out before Darren O’Day took over for Anderson with two outs and plunked Brian Anderson. The veteran reliever than walked Garrett Cooper to load the bases, but the Marlins came away empty when Matt Joyce grounded out to end the inning.</p>
<p>Lopez didn’t pitch badly, allowing just three hits in and striking out seven in five innings. But he was done in by the home runs in his postseason debut after not pitching since Sept. 24.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Atlanta’s Kyle Wright will make his postseason debut when he starts in Game 3 against rookie Sixto Sanchez. Wright hasn’t pitched since Sept. 25 when he allowed two runs in a career-high 6 2/3 innings against the Red Sox. Sanchez started Game 2 of the wild-card round, striking out six in five scoreless innings.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">756483</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>D&#8217;Arnaud, Braves rally in 7th, beat Marlins 9-5 to open NLDS</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/darnaud-braves-rally-in-7th-beat-marlins-9-5-to-open-nlds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 22:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AP_FL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com?p=755844&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=755844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOUSTON (AP) — Ronald Acuña Jr. made history with his leadoff homer, Travis d’Arnaud hit a tiebreaking shot in Atlanta’s huge seventh inning and the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOUSTON (AP) — Ronald Acuña Jr. made history with his leadoff homer, Travis d’Arnaud hit a tiebreaking shot in Atlanta’s huge seventh inning and the Braves beat the Miami Marlins 9-5 Tuesday in Game 1 of the NL Division Series.</p>
<p>D&#8217;Arnaud also doubled and singled in driving in four runs and Dansby Swanson homered during a six-run seventh to help power Atlanta.</p>
<p>After shutting out Cincinnati for 22 innings during a two-game sweep in the wild-card round, the Braves relied on their bats in this opener.</p>
<p>Game 2 of the best-of-five series is on Wednesday in Houston.</p>
<p>The Braves trailed 4-3 in the seventh before Austin Riley and Acuña hit consecutive singles with no outs to chase Miami starter Sandy Alcantara.</p>
<p>Yimi Garcia took over and Freddie Freeman grounded into a forceout that left runners at the corners. Marcell Ozuna lined a single to left that made it 4-all.</p>
<p>Then d’Arnaud, in his first season with Atlanta, belted a slider over the fence in center field for a three-run drive that made it 7-4. The shot caused the Braves dugout to erupt with Acuña jumping over the railing to celebrate.</p>
<p>D&#8217;Arnaud, who played for the Mets, Dodgers and Rays last year, began the day as a .169 career hitter in the postseason, striking out 27 times in 83 at-bats.</p>
<p>But the Braves weren’t done yet.</p>
<p>James Hoyt replaced Garcia with one out and Swanson sent his first pitch off the wall in center field for a two-run homer.</p>
<p>Acuña got things going for the Braves in the bottom of the first when he sent Alcantara’s second pitch into right-center for a homer. He watched it for a second before flipping his bat and rounding the bases as he became the youngest player (22 years, 293 days old) in postseason history with a leadoff home run.</p>
<p>The Braves, who have long dominated the Marlins in the NL East, improved to 3-0 this postseason after sweeping the Reds in the wild-card round for their first playoff series win since 2001.</p>
<p>The Marlins overcame a coronavirus outbreak that sidelined more than half the team in July to make the playoffs for the first time since 2003 before sweeping their wild-card series against the Cubs.</p>
<p>And the scrappy Marlins, who lost 105 games in 2019, looked good early in this one, using a three-run third inning to take a 4-1 lead. But their offense stalled after that and the Braves scored two in the third to get within one before putting Miami away with their home run barrage in the seventh.</p>
<p>The Braves got the win despite a tough start from Max Fried, who allowed six hits and a season-high four runs in just four innings. He was picked up by a bevy of relievers who allowed just one run over the last five innings. Will Smith pitched a perfect seventh for the win.</p>
<p>Alcantara yielded eight hits and five runs with eight strikeouts in six-plus inning.</p>
<p>Atlanta’s scoreless streak in the playoffs ended early in this one when Miguel Rojas homered to the seats in left field to make it 1-all in the second.</p>
<p>Garrett Cooper hit a two-run double to put the Marlins up 3-1 in the third. Brian Anderson followed with an RBI single.</p>
<p>Things got a little testy in the bottom of the inning when Alcantara plunked Acuña on the hip with a fastball. Acuña held onto his bat and walked a few steps toward the mound before umpires and Braves coaches surrounded him and directed him away from Alcantara, who had started to walk toward him.</p>
<p>After a short delay, featuring plenty of chirping from both dugouts, Acuña calmed down and took his base. Umpires warned the teams against further trouble — past history between the teams includes Acuña being hit, leading to a lot of acrimony.</p>
<p>Ozuna doubled with two outs in the inning to score Acuña, and d’Arnaud followed with an RBI double to cut the lead to 4-3.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Right-hander Pablo Lopez will make his postseason debut when he starts for the Marlins in Game 2 against Ian Anderson. Lopez was 6-4 with a 3.61 ERA in 11 starts this season.</p>
<p>Anderson allowed two hits and struck out nine in six scoreless innings to get the win in Atlanta’s win over Reds in Game 2 of the wild card series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">755844</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami OF Marté left off NLDS roster against Braves</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-of-marte-left-off-nlds-roster-against-braves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 18:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=755693</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HOUSTON (AP) — The Miami Marlins left outfielder Starling Marté off their NL Division Series roster against the Atlanta Braves because of a hand injury....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOUSTON (AP) — The Miami Marlins left outfielder Starling Marté off their NL Division Series roster against the Atlanta Braves because of a hand injury.</p>
<p>Marté fractured his left hand in Miami&#8217;s first wild-card game against the Chicago Cubs on Sept. 30, though the Marlins had hoped he would be able to play in this series. Manager Don Mattingly said Marté worked out on Monday and they didn&#8217;t feel comfortable that he would be able to play effectively in this series because of the injury.</p>
<p>Miami will carry 14 pitchers and 14 position players, adding right-hander Nick Vincent and left-hander Dan Castano to the roster. The Marlins selected the contract of infielder Sean Rodriguez from the alternate training site and also added him to the NLDS roster. Along with Marté, first basman Lewin Diaz and and left-handed reliever Stephen Tarpley were left off the roster.</p>
<p>The Braves went with 15 pitchers and 13 position players after their wild-card roster had 13 pitchers and 15 position players. Atlanta added right-handers Bryce Wilson and Huascar Ynoa. Catcher William Contreras and utility infielder Johan Camargo were left off.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">755693</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;Bottom-feeding&#8217; Marlins are making a splash in playoffs</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/bottom-feeding-marlins-are-making-a-splash-in-playoffs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 16:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=753736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Their T-shirts say Bottom Feeders, even though the Miami Marlins are showing they’re a different kind of fish in 2020 — the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Their T-shirts say Bottom Feeders, even though the Miami Marlins are showing they’re a different kind of fish in 2020 — the sort that rises to make a splash.</p>
<p>Surprising Miami has advanced to MLB&#8217;s final eight, disproving disparaging adjectives so often applied to the long-suffering franchise by detractors. That includes the opposing-team broadcaster who described the Marlins early in the season as “bottom feeders.”</p>
<p>Instead, they made the playoffs for the first time since 2003, swept the Chicago Cubs <a href="https://apnews.com/article/mlb-luis-castillo-steve-bartman-don-mattingly-philadelphia-phillies-04d550e3ea30bf4ed8d961f158d0f51d">in this week&#8217;s wild-card </a>round, and advanced to the best-of-five NL Division Series to face the Atlanta Braves beginning Tuesday in Houston.</p>
<p>“I don’t think we’re going to be satisfied,” manager <a href="https://apnews.com/article/mlb-miami-archive-don-mattingly-miami-marlins-6990a51a889bdf21249e60862472bf33">Don Mattingly </a>said. “We’re going to be looking to win.”</p>
<p>Don&#8217;t count them out: This is a franchise that tends to be an also-ran in the summer but dominant in October, with a 7-0 record in postseason series. That includes World Series titles in 1997 and 2003.</p>
<p>After holding the Cubs to one run and nine hits in two games, the Marlins posed for a team photo in the Wrigley Field infield. A few players wore masks, the rest wore grins, and all wore Bottom Feeders T-shirts.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s a mindset,” said first baseman Garrett Cooper, who hit a pivotal homer in Thursday&#8217;s 2-0 win. “You take that to heart and you try to stick it to everybody, because we don’t get the respect we think we deserve. It’s a great mantra, because it shows everybody is riding on the same train.”</p>
<p>By bouncing back from a 105-loss year in 2019, and then from a coronavirus outbreak in July that sidelined more than half the team, Derek Jeter&#8217;s Marlins have earned some respect. Nonetheless, they&#8217;re the biggest underdogs in next week&#8217;s round, partly because Miami has been Atlanta&#8217;s perennial punching bag in the NL East.</p>
<p>The Braves went 29-9 against the Marlins in 2018-19. Coincidentally, on Sept. 9 they beat the Marlins by that same eye-popping margin: 29-9.</p>
<p>Miami won four of 10 games against the high-scoring Braves this year.</p>
<p>“They’ve run this division for a few years now,” Cooper said. “They have that offense, and some good pitching. But anything can happen. They know us; we know them.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Marlins&#8217; young pitching gives them a chance, as 22-year-old Sixto Sanchez showed Friday. The precocious right-hander, making his eighth major league start, struck out six in five shutout innings.</p>
<p>“He has incredible stuff, and that gives him the confidence to go out there and compete,” teammate Matt Joyce said. “He&#8217;s not scared. He&#8217;s really poised for his age. He really went at those guys.”</p>
<p>Sandy Alcantara was just as good in Game 1 against the Cubs, allowing one run in 6 2/3 innings. Pablo Lopez and Trevor Rogers give Mattingly two other well-rested, hard-throwing options to start against Atlanta.</p>
<p>“We like the power,” Mattingly said. &#8220;I&#8217;ve been watching the playoff games, and it seems like <a href="https://apnews.com/article/mlb-new-york-new-york-yankees-cincinnati-atlanta-braves-2927801ed8841bd6b0675a5e26dd4042">a lot of games </a>are just bullpen games. We’re a little different. We trust our starters, every guy that goes out there usually has better stuff than anybody we’ve got in the pen.</p>
<p>“So you trust those guys to go a little ways. They are young and inexperienced, but it&#8217;s just baseball.”</p>
<p>And the Marlins are getting good at it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">753736</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cooper homers, Sanchez dominates, Marlins knock out Cubs 2-0</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/cooper-homers-sanchez-dominates-marlins-knock-out-cubs-2-0/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=753301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHICAGO (AP) — Garrett Cooper homered against Yu Darvish in a two-run seventh, hard-throwing rookie Sixto Sánchez dominated for five innings and the Miami Marlins...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CHICAGO (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Garrett Cooper homered against Yu Darvish in a two-run seventh, hard-throwing rookie Sixto S&#xC3;&#xA1;nchez dominated for five innings and the Miami Marlins won their first playoff series in 17 years, beating the Chicago Cubs 2-0 Friday to complete a two-game wild card series sweep.<p>Miami will face Atlanta in the NL Division Series in Houston starting Tuesday.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/Marlins/status/1312143367040532486?s=20</embed></div><p>Led by manager Don Mattingly and CEO Derek Jeter, the Marlins remained unbeaten in all seven postseason series they have played following triumphs in the 1997 and 2003 NL Championship and World Series.</p><p>And this time, in empty Wrigley Field, they didn&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;t need a hand from a fan. In Game 6 of the 2003 NLCS, fan Steve Bartman deflected Luis Castillo&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s foul ball as Cubs left fielder Moises Alou tried to make a leaping catch, which led to an eight-run, eighth-inning rally.</p><p>Miami lost 105 games in 2019 and became the first team to reach the playoffs after a 100-loss season. The Marlins finished second in the NL East at 31-29 being beset by a virus outbreak early this season that forced 18 players from the field following the opening series and prevented them from playing for more than a week.</p><p>Miami had T-shirts with &#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;Bottom Feeders&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; in its dugout Friday, a reference to a remark by Ricky Bottalico, a former Phillies pitcher and current NBC Sports Philadelphia analyst, after the Marlins&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99; opening-day win in Philadelphia.</p><p>&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9C;We&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;re here and the Phillies are at home, so I think the `bottom feeders&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99; is a good mantra to live on,&#xE2;&#x80;&#x9D; Cooper said.</p><p>Chicago, the NL Central champion, went 3 for 27 (.111) with runners on base in the series. Javier B&#xC3;&#xA1;ez, Kris Bryant and Anthony Rizzo combined to go 0 for 12 Friday and finished the series 1 for 24. The trio is 19 for 142 (.134) with 52 strikeouts and six walks in the postseason since the 2016 World Series title as Chicago has lost nine of 13.</p><p>Cooper gave the Marlins a 1-0 lead with two out in the seventh with a drive into the seats beyond the left-field wall. Matt Joyce doubled off the glove of diving center fielder Ian Happ, and Miguel Rojas chased Darvish with an RBI single.</p><p>Sanchez overpowered the Cubs, striking out six and giving up four hits. The 22-year-old right-hander walked two and hit two batters.</p><p>Winner Brad Boxberger threw 1 1/3 innings. Richard Bleier got two outs in the seventh and Yimi Garc&#xC3;&#xAD;a worked the eighth.</p><p>Former Cub Brandon Kintzler gave up a leadoff double to Jason Heyward in the ninth. But he struck out the next three batters, pumping his right arm after he got pinch hitter Jason Kipnis swinging on a 2-2 pitch to end the game.</p><p>Darvish, who took the loss, gave up two runs and five hits in 6 2/3 innings. The four-time All-Star struck out six and walked two in his first playoff appearance since Game 7 of the 2017 World Series, when he got knocked out early pitching for the Dodgers in a loss to the Houston Astros.</p><p>But the Cubs &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; who ranked among the worst in the majors with a .220 average &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; got just five hits after managing four in a 5-1 on Wednesday.</p><p>TRAINER&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;S ROOM</p><p>Marlins: The Marlins held OF Starling Marte out of the lineup because of a small nondisplaced fracture of the bone running between his left pinky and wrist. He was hit by a fastball in the ninth inning Wednesday.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">753301</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Game 2 of Marlins-Cubs wild-card series postponed</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/game-2-of-marlins-cubs-wild-card-series-postponed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=752419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHICAGO (AP) — Game 2 of the National League wild-card series between the Chicago Cubs and Miami Marlins was postponed because of a forecast for...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHICAGO (AP) — Game 2 of the National League wild-card series between the Chicago Cubs and Miami Marlins was postponed because of a forecast for rain on Thursday.</p>
<p>Miami leads 1-0 after winning the opener 5-1, and the teams will meet Friday.</p>
<p>If a Game 3 is needed, it would be played Saturday.</p>
<p>Yu Darvish was scheduled to start Game 2 for Chicago, and rookie Sixto Sánchez for the Marlins.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">752419</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dickerson homers as Marlins beat Cubs 5-1 in playoff opener</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/dickerson-homers-as-marlins-beat-cubs-5-1-in-playoff-opener/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 21:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=751737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CHICAGO (AP) — Corey Dickerson hit a three-run homer off a fading Kyle Hendricks in the seventh inning, and the Miami Marlins beat the Chicago...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHICAGO (AP) — Corey Dickerson hit a three-run homer off a fading Kyle Hendricks in the seventh inning, and the Miami Marlins beat the Chicago Cubs 5-1 on Wednesday in Game 1 of their NL wild-card series.</p>
<p>Jesús Aguilar also homered and Sandy Alcantara pitched three-hit ball into the seventh as Miami conjured up memories of past playoff magic in the franchise&#8217;s first postseason game since it won the World Series in 2003. The Marlins, who rallied past the Cubs in a memorable NLCS that year, have never lost a playoff series.</p>
<p>Game 2 of the best-of-three series is Thursday. Yu Darvish starts for the Central champion Cubs, while rookie right-hander Sixto Sánchez pitches for upstart Miami, looking to make an unexpected division series trip in the same season that roughly half the roster was sidelined by COVID-19.</p>
<p>The Marlins may be without center fielder Starling Marte after he was hit on the left hand by a fastball in the ninth inning. Marte was in obvious pain and quickly retreated down the clubhouse tunnel. He was replaced by Monte Harrison. No immediate update was given on his status.</p>
<p>Miami was 0 for 9 with runners in scoring position before Dickerson drove Hendricks&#8217; 106th pitch just over the wall in left-center for his first career playoff homer, erasing the Cubs&#8217; 1-0 lead on a cool, blustery afternoon.</p>
<p>After Hendricks was pulled by first-year manager David Ross, Marte singled and Aguilar hit a drive to right off Jeremy Jeffress for his third career playoff homer.</p>
<p>The last time the Marlins scored five or more runs in an inning during a playoff game was Oct. 14, 2003, at Wrigley Field, when the club scored eight times in the eighth during Game 6 of the NLCS. That outburst included fan Steve Bartman deflecting Luis Castillo’s foul ball as Cubs left fielder Moises Alou tried to make a leaping catch.</p>
<p>There was only a smattering of onlookers — primarily fans and team employees — Wednesday because of baseball&#8217;s COVID-19 protocols, and the lower bowl that surrounds the field was almost completely empty.</p>
<p>Hendricks (0-1) matched a season high with 106 pitches in his first start in a week. Known for his pinpoint control, the right-hander issued three walks and hit a batter. He had permitted just two hits before the Marlins chased him with three in a row in the seventh, culminating in Dickerson&#8217;s one-out homer.</p>
<p>Hendricks had walked two or fewer batters in 41 consecutive starts dating to April of 2019.</p>
<p>Alcantara (1-0) struck out four and walked three in 6 2/3 innings in his first career playoff start.</p>
<p>Chicago got its only run on Ian Happ&#8217;s two-out drive in the fifth for his first postseason homer. Happ had two of the Cubs&#8217; four hits.</p>
<p>TRAINER&#8217;S ROOM</p>
<p>Marlins: Marte got the start after he was hit on the front of his helmet by Clarke Schmidt’s 94-mph fastball during Sunday’s regular-season finale against the Yankees. Manager Don Mattingly said Marte was “100%,&#8221; but that was before he was hit by another pitch Wednesday. &#8230; RHP José Ureña was placed on the team&#8217;s taxi squad. Ureña broke his right forearm when he was hit by a line drive Sunday at New York.</p>
<p>Cubs: INF Ildemaro Vargas was activated from the 10-day injured list after missing the last part of the season with a right hamstring strain.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Sánchez, one of baseball&#8217;s top prospects, made his big league debt on Aug. 22. Game 2 will be his first start at Wrigley.</p>
<p>“To be honest, I don’t know much about the history of the ballpark, but I know I will be pitching against the Cubs,” he said through a translator. “It’s going to be great.”</p>
<p>Darvish is making his first playoff appearance since signing with Chicago before the 2018 season. He is 2-4 with a 5.81 ERA in six career postseason starts.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">751737</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>For Marlins, playoff berth could be start of a new era</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/for-marlins-playoff-berth-could-be-start-of-a-new-era/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 02:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=750511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins&#8217; first playoff appearance since 2003 is not supposed to last long. They&#8217;re regarded as young, inexperienced overachievers who benefited...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Miami Marlins&#8217; first playoff appearance since 2003 is not supposed to last long.</p>
<p>They&#8217;re regarded as young, inexperienced overachievers who benefited from <a href="https://apnews.com/article/virus-outbreak-mlb-sports-baseball-atlanta-braves-ee2f0c26d25aeeb00ee3829405bacd8a">the short season </a> and expanded playoff format. They were outscored by 41 runs this year, and no team has longer odds of winning the World Series at 33-1.</p>
<p>But even if their postseason ends this week in the wild-card round at Wrigley Field, the Marlins believe it&#8217;s just the beginning of a new era for the long-suffering franchise.</p>
<p>“For us, this is a stepping stone,” CEO Derek Jeter said Monday. “We didn’t come here to chase ‘a’ championship or ‘a’ playoff appearance. We want to be sustainable.”</p>
<p>Three years into Jeter&#8217;s organizational overhaul, the Marlins appear to be built to last as they&#8217;re just starting to win. They have an abundance of young pitching, a strong farm system and a modest, manageable payroll.</p>
<p>One year removed from a 105-loss season, the NL East runner-up Marlins will face the NL Central champion Cubs in the best-of-three wild-card round beginning Wednesday.</p>
<p>“To go through what we did last year, you feel like you&#8217;re in a boat in the middle of the ocean and you have no idea where land is, but you know it&#8217;s out there,” manager <a href="https://apnews.com/article/mlb-miami-archive-don-mattingly-miami-marlins-6990a51a889bdf21249e60862472bf33">Don Mattingly </a> said. “You have to have faith. That’s why it feels so good to get to this point, and this is the beginning of that, not the end.”</p>
<p>Attendance remains at zero because of the coronavirus, but the bandwagon is growing. Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores wore a Marlins cap at work Monday.</p>
<p>Few foresaw the Marlins as a playoff team, especially after a virus outbreak nearly ended their season after just three games. But a patchwork roster thanks to 174 roster moves produced the Marlins&#8217; first winning season since 2009.</p>
<p>“There has been a lot of adversity for this group,” Jeter said. “I’m a little biased, but I don’t think there’s a team in baseball that deserves it more, because our guys have been through quite a bit.”</p>
<p>The Marlins navigated a marathon closing stretch — Monday was their first day off after 28 games in 24 days.</p>
<p>Now they can catch their breath. And in the playoffs, they&#8217;ll go about their business with little pressure, especially compared to, say, the Cubs.</p>
<p>“We’re playing loose; we’ve got nothing to lose,” closer Brandon Kintzler said. “We&#8217;re playing with house money. We’re a dangerous team — we’ve got starting pitching that contends with anybody in baseball.”</p>
<p>The rotation is indeed the Marlins&#8217; strength, and with Sandy Alcantara, Pablo Lopez and Sixto Sanchez, they have three young right-handers capable of taking over a short series.</p>
<p>“We know our dudes have got some stuff,” Mattingly said. “If they get on a roll, you don’t really want to be on the other side of that.”</p>
<p>Miami will be without right-hander Jose Urena, who broke his right forearm when he was hit by a line drive Sunday against the New York Yankees.</p>
<p>The Marlins&#8217; last trip to the playoffs also included games at Wrigley Field. In 2003, they won the National League Championship Series there one night after a fan literally lent a hand to the Marlins&#8217; comeback win in Game 6 by trying to catch a foul ball at a pivotal moment.</p>
<p>This time, because of the pandemic, there will be no fans in the stands. Mattingly figures that&#8217;s good news for his young team.</p>
<p>“It’s really different playing with nobody at Wrigley than with the streets going crazy and people packed into the building,” Mattingly said. &#8220;The younger guys get a little bit of a break not to have to walk in with the place packed and a hostile environment.”</p>
<p>Even minus spectators, however, the Marlins hear taunts from skeptics. One disparaging description — bottom feeders — stuck and raised their hackles even before the season began.</p>
<p>“That has been the term that has pushed us. Every time we won a game, we said, ‘Good job, bottom feeders,’” outfielder Lewis Brinson said. &#8220;We knew going into spring training nobody believed in us. We appreciate it. We love it. We want to eat it for breakfast, lunch and dinner, because that’s what has gotten us to this moment.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">750511</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins clinch 1st playoff berth since 2003, beat Yanks 4-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-clinch-1st-playoff-berth-since-2003-beat-yanks-4-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 02:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=747486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — The Marlins clinched an improbable playoff berth in their coronavirus-decimated season, beating the New York Yankees 4-3 in 10 innings Friday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>NEW YORK (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; The Marlins clinched an improbable playoff berth in their coronavirus-decimated season, beating the New York Yankees 4-3 in 10 innings Friday night to seal a postseason trip on the field of the team that Miami CEO Derek Jeter and manager Don Mattingly once captained.<p>Miami earned its first postseason trip since 2003 when it won the World Series as the Florida Marlins, capped by a Game 6 victory in the Bronx over Jeter and his New York teammates at the previous version of Yankee Stadium.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/Marlins/status/1309681081457799168?s=20</embed></div><p>The Marlins had the worst record in the NL last year at 57-105, then was beset by a virus outbreak early this season that prevented it from playing for more than a week.</p><p>After Jes&#xC3;&#xBA;s Aguilar hit a sacrifice fly in the top of the 10th, Marlins reliever Brandon Kintzler got major league batting leader DJ LeMahieu to ground into a game-ending double play with the bases loaded.</p><p>Miami players ran onto the field, formed a line and exchanged non socially-distant hugs.</p><p>The Marlins became the first team to make the playoffs in the year following a 100-loss season. Miami was one of baseball&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s great doubts at the start of the shortened season, forced off the field when 18 players tested positive for COVID-19 following the opening series in Philadelphia.</p><p>Mattingly captained the Yankees from 1991-95 and is in his fifth season managing the Marlins, Jeter captained the Yankees from 2003-14 as part of a career that included five World Series titles in 20 seasons and is part of the group headed by Bruce Sherman that bought the Marlins in October 2017.</p><p>Miami is second in the NL East at 30-28 and improved to 19-13 on the road, The Marlins will play 34 road games due to the schedule disruption caused by the coronavirus; they arrived at their hotel at 5:30 a.m. following a rain-delayed win in Atlanta.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">747486</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Braves beat Marlins again 9-4, but Fried hurt in 1st inning</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/braves-beat-marlins-again-9-4-but-fried-hurt-in-1st-inning/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 03:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=744943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — Dansby Swanson hit a three-run homer and the Atlanta Braves cruised to their third straight win over the Miami Marlins, 9-4 Wednesday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — Dansby Swanson hit a three-run homer and the Atlanta Braves cruised to their third straight win over the Miami Marlins, 9-4 Wednesday night in a game overshadowed by Max Fried&#8217;s early departure with an ankle injury.</p>
<p>The Braves ace was making his final regular-season start, hoping to boost his NL Cy Young Award credentials ahead of starting Game 1 in the NL playoffs next week.</p>
<p>But Fried lasted only one inning, <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308917805098700800">tweaking an ankle</a> while fielding a bunt down the third-base line by Starling Marte. While the left-hander didn&#8217;t appear to be hurt, he wasn&#8217;t the same pitcher after the play.</p>
<p>Having gone the entire season without allowing a homer, covering 55 2/3 innings, Fried suddenly gave up two in a row. Jesus Aquilar hit one off the facade of the second deck, Brian Anderson drove one into the empty center-field seats, and Garrett Cooper nearly made it three in a row with a double off the wall.</p>
<p>The left-hander got the third out, then sat solemnly in the dugout while <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308915449883750400">talking to manager Brian Snitker</a> and getting an apparent pep talk from teammate Freddie Freeman. While the decision to remove Fried was described as precautionary, it created more uncertainty for the NL East champions, who have struggled all season to put together a consistent rotation behind Fried.</p>
<p>Atlanta bounced back with three runs in the bottom half of the first to ensure Fried wouldn&#8217;t take his first loss. He finished the regular season 7-0 with a 2.25 ERA.</p>
<p>Luke Jackson (2-0) earned the win with four innings in relief of Fried.</p>
<p>There are no concerns about the Atlanta offense. One night after clinching their third straight division title, the Braves dealt another blow to Miami&#8217;s precarious playoff hopes by knocking around budding young star Sixto Sanchez.</p>
<p>Ozzie Albies and Adeiney Hechavarria, making a rare start, drove in two runs apiece. <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308932579324841984">Swanson blew the game open</a> with his ninth homer of the season, a 401-foot, opposite-field drive into the Braves bullpen off Josh Smith (1-1) to cap a five-run fourth.</p>
<p>The second-place Marlins lost their fourth in a row, dropping to 28-28 with four games left in the shortened regular season. They are a half-game ahead of the Philadelphia Phillies, trying desperately to hang on for their first playoff appearance since winning the World Series in 2003.</p>
<p>TRAINER&#8217;S ROOM</p>
<p>All eyes will be on Fried over the next several days. He&#8217;s got a full week to recover before the Braves open the best-of-three wild card series, which will be held entirely at Truist Park.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>The Braves go for a four-game sweep of the Marlins when rookie RHP Ian Anderson (3-1, 2.36) makes his final start of the regular season against Miami&#8217;s RHP Pablo López (5-4. 3.96). Anderson is expected to start Game 2 of the wild card series.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">744943</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ozuna, Braves beat Miami, clinch 3rd straight NL East title</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ozuna-braves-beat-miami-clinch-3rd-straight-nl-east-title/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 03:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=743767</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — After clinching their third straight NL East title, the Atlanta Braves set their sights on ended a much longer streak. After losses...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — After clinching their third straight NL East title, the Atlanta Braves set their sights on ended a much longer streak.</p>
<p>After losses in 10 straight postseason appearances, the Braves are desperate to end the drought.</p>
<p>“If you ask me, it’s World Series or nothing,” said Ronald Acuña Jr. said through a translator after Atlanta clinched the division title by beating the Miami Marlins 11-1 on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Bryse Wilson pitched five scoreless innings, and Marcell Ozuna drove in five runs with four hits that included two home runs.</p>
<p>Atlanta hit five homers, including drives by Dansby Swanson and Freddie Freeman off Nick Vincent in a five-run seventh. Freeman drove in two runs with three hits.</p>
<p>“I think when it’s all said and done, this is the most satisfying with all we had to go through this season to get to this point,” said Freeman, who missed the start of the delayed season with a high fever and other symptoms after testing positive for the novel coronavirus.</p>
<p>Freeman rebounded to become an MVP candidate. He pushed his batting average to .347.</p>
<p>After Jorge Alfaro&#8217;s game-ending lineout to Freeman, Braves players hugged on the field and exchanged high-fives in the dugout. Players wore “Respect Atlanta” T-shirts and posed for photos on the field with the 2020 banner.</p>
<p>From the visitor&#8217;s dugout, Marlins manager Don Mattingly watched the low-key celebration with respect.</p>
<p>“They’ve been probably the class of the division over the last few years,” Mattingly said. &#8220;They’re the gold standard. They’re the guys you have to go after.”</p>
<p>Wilson (1-0) allowed three hits and one walk, striking out a career-high seven.</p>
<p>Atlanta clinched its record 20th division title, one more than the New York Yankees. The Braves won 14 straight in completed seasons from 1991-2005 but have not won a postseason series since 2001 and have not won a championship since 1995.</p>
<p>“Everyone has got the taste the last couple of years and we’ve had a lot of heartbreak, especially last year,” Freeman said. “We’ve been grinding this year and we’re going to grind again.”</p>
<p>Miami remained in position to earn its first playoff berth since winning the 2003 World Series.</p>
<p>“We’ve got to keep focused and keep our heads up all the time,” said José Ureña, (0-3), who allowed four runs in six innings.</p>
<p>Ozuna hit a first-inning homer, Ozzie Albies homered in the second, and Ozuna added a two-run double in the fifth and drove in Freeman with a 450-foot homer to center field in the eighth.</p>
<p>Starling Marte led off the sixth with a homer off Josh Tomlin.</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM</p>
<p>Marlins: INF Sean Rodriguez, who was designated for assignment on Sunday, has cleared waivers and reported to the alternate training site in Jupiter.</p>
<p>Braves: Wilson is the 13th starting pitcher for Atlanta this season. He was recalled on Monday when LHP Cole Hamels was shut down with left shoulder fatigue after making only one start.</p>
<p>LOW-KEY CELEBRATION</p>
<p>Manager Brian Snitker said the Braves were prepared for a low-key celebration, due to social distancing rules in the pandemic. He said Major League Baseball “pretty much restricted all that” due to space constraints in the clubhouse.</p>
<p>“I think we go in and air high-five to everybody,” Snitker said.</p>
<p>WILSON&#8217;S SURPRISE</p>
<p>It was an unexpected showing by Wilson, the 22-year-old right-hander. He had a 7.04 ERA in four relief outings and had been at the team’s alternate training site until Monday. He had not started since July 16 last year at Milwaukee.</p>
<p>“Bryse was awesome,” Snitker said. &#8220;That was a big start for Bryse. He hadn’t pitched in a while.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Marlins: RHP Sixto Sánchez will look for his second win over the Braves in about two weeks on Wednesday night. He allowed only three hits in six innings in an 8-0 win at Atlanta on Sept. 8.</p>
<p>Braves: LHP Max Fried (7-0, 1.96) will try to strengthen his Cy Young Award candidacy. Fried has allowed 12 runs in his 10 starts.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">743767</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bullpen, defense preserves Braves 5-4 win over Marlins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/bullpen-defense-preserves-braves-5-4-win-over-marlins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 04:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=742802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — At the start, it looked like a slugfest. By the end, it came down to defense. The Braves ad-libbed a brilliant double play to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — At the start, it looked like a slugfest.</p>
<p>By the end, it came down to defense.</p>
<p>The Braves <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308234995190976513">ad-libbed a brilliant double play</a> to snuff out a potential Miami comeback in the ninth, moving Atlanta a step closer to a third straight NL East title with a 5-4 victory over the second-place Marlins on Monday night.</p>
<p>With speedy pinch-runner Monte Harrison at first, Matt Joyce hit a high chopper behind the mound that was fielded by Braves closer Mark Melancon. While he made the throw to retire Joyce, Harrison noticed third base wasn&#8217;t covered and kept right on running around second.</p>
<p>Third baseman Austin Riley had gone after the ball and wasn’t in position, but shortstop Dansby Swanson alertly took off running for the bag. First baseman Freddie Freeman hit the moving target with a perfect throw, and Swanson was able to leap at Harrison and <a href="https://www.mlb.com/gameday/marlins-vs-braves/2020/09/21/630440#game_state=final,lock_state=final,game_tab=videos,game=630440">swipe him on the left hip</a> a split-second before he got a hand to the bag on a headfirst slide.</p>
<p>“I saw the ball coming right back at me really quickly. Freddie turned and launched it right over my head,” said Melancon, who dropped to one knee to avoid getting struck. “It was definitely a heads-up play there by Dansby. Just an athletic play all around. That was fun.”</p>
<p>Swanson celebrated by pounding his glove into the dirt. Brian Anderson flied out to deep right to end the game, giving Melancon his 11th save and putting the Braves in position to clinch the East title as soon as Tuesday.</p>
<p>“That was amazing,” manager Brian Snitker said. “Just amazing.”</p>
<p>Even with the loss that dropped them four games behind Atlanta with six to play, the Marlins are still positioned to earn their first playoff berth since 2003. But they&#8217;ve got a tough final week, with three more games in Atlanta and a weekend series against the New York Yankees.</p>
<p>“This was a playoff atmosphere,” said Miami starter Trevor Rogers, who bounced back from a rough start to keep the Marlins in the game. “There’s obviously no fans, but this was a very, very good ballgame. It’s coming down to the wire.”</p>
<p>Riley&#8217;s two-run double capped a wild first inning in which the Marlins scored three in the top half with a barrage of singles — and the Braves responded with four runs in the bottom half. In all, the opening frame took 45 minutes and 74 pitches to get through.</p>
<p>There were only two more runs the rest of the way as both teams got stellar performances from their bullpens. Three Miami relievers combined for four hitless innings after Rogers (1-2) left, while the Braves surrendered only one run over the final six innings.</p>
<p>Tyler Matzek (4-3) pitched two hitless innings for the win, and Darren O&#8217;Day and Chris Martin each worked a scoreless frame. Will Smith escaped a bases-loaded jam in the eighth after Shane Green surrendered a two-out run. With a big assist from the defense, Melancon finished it off.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308190990134640640">The Marlins got things rolling</a> against Huascar Ynoa with RBI singles from Jesus Aquilar, Anderson and Garrett Cooper.</p>
<p>The Braves bounced right back against Rogers, who created a mess for himself by walking Ronald Acuña Jr. and Freeman to start the inning. Travis d&#8217;Arnaud brought home a run with <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308193428765913090">an infield dribbler</a>, Ozzie Albies ripped a run-scoring single to center and <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1308193293843529728">Riley doubled</a> into the right-field corner to put the Braves ahead 4-3.</p>
<p>Both pitchers settled down after that. Ynoa faced the minimum over the next two innings before giving way to the bullpen. Rogers surrendered another run on back-to-back doubles to start the second, but the rookie avoided further trouble by getting d&#8217;Arnaud to hit into a double play.</p>
<p>HANGING TOUGH</p>
<p>Rogers, Miami&#8217;s first-round pick in the 2017 draft, came back from his rough start to strike out the last six hitters he faced in his four-inning stint.</p>
<p>“It’s huge,” Rogers said. “The stat line might say different, but for me personally might be my best outing as far as growing as a big leaguer.”</p>
<p>TRAINER&#8217;S ROOM</p>
<p>Atlanta left-hander Cole Hamels is done for the season, dealing a big blow to the Braves&#8217; beleaguered rotation.</p>
<p>The 36-year-old Hamels has spent all year struggling to bounce back from shoulder and triceps issues. He finally made his first start of the season last week at Baltimore, giving up three runs in 3 1/3 innings, and was scheduled to go Tuesday against the Marlins.</p>
<p>But Hamels told general manager Alex Anthopoulos shortly before Monday&#8217;s game that he didn’t feel like he could get anything on the ball. The Braves placed Hamels on the 10-day injured list and are seeking permission from Major League Baseball to replace him in postseason player pool.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Marlins: RHP José Ureña (0-2, 6.00 ERA) gets his fourth start of the season against a team he has annoyed in the past with his tendency to hit batters.</p>
<p>Braves: After being called up to replace Hamels, RHP Bryse Wilson is set to make his first start of 2020.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">742802</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rojas, Cooper homer to lead Marlins over Nationals 7-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/rojas-cooper-homer-to-lead-marlins-over-nationals-7-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 04:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=741084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miguel Rojas and Garrett Cooper each had a double and a homer and the Miami Marlins beat the Washington Nationals 7-3 on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miguel Rojas and Garrett Cooper each had a double and a homer and the Miami Marlins beat the Washington Nationals 7-3 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>With the win, Miami maintained its hold on second place in the NL East.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re close to the finish line, we&#8217;re close to something this organization hasn&#8217;t done in a long time,” Cooper said of Miami&#8217;s 17-year post-season drought. “Everyone knows that and we&#8217;re trying to keep it on an even keel.”</p>
<p>Starling Marte and Brian Anderson each singled twice for the Marlins, who had 14 hits against Washington starter Patrick Corbin. Miami also got two hits from Lewis Brinson and Chad Wallach.</p>
<p>Pablo Lopez (5-4) matched his win total from last season with his 5 1/3 inning outing. Lopez allowed two runs and three hits, struck out seven and walked three.</p>
<p>Miami struck early, with Rojas hitting a leadoff homer off Corbin (2-6) in the first. Rojas drove Corbin’s fastball over the wall in left-center for his fourth homer of the season.</p>
<p>Cooper’s opposite field two-run blast to right-center increased the Marlins’ lead 3-0.</p>
<p>“Singles are great but as a big man, that’s your job, to hit some doubles and home runs,&#8221; said the 6-foot-5, 230-pound Cooper.</p>
<p>Andrew Stevenson’s two-run single in the fourth got Washington within 3-2 before Miami responded with RBI singles from Corey Dickerson and Wallach in the bottom of the inning.</p>
<p>The Marlins padded their lead with an RBI single from Jesus Aguilar in the fifth and Cooper’s run-scoring double in the sixth.</p>
<p>Richard Bleier retired the four batters he faced to set up Brandon Kintzler, who pitched a scoreless ninth.</p>
<p>Corbin was lifted after six innings. The left-hander allowed seven runs and struck out seven.</p>
<p>“One of those days, it wasn’t very good,” Corbin said. “They came out swinging, they didn’t miss any of my mistakes, they came to hit it.”</p>
<p>The loss dropped the Nationals to 19-31 — the same record before their 74-38 finish and eventual run to a World Series championship last season.</p>
<p>“I’d rather be 31-19, but hey, we just gotta keep battling, we gotta keep it going for the next 10 games or whatever it is and just try to go 1-0 (Sunday),” Washington manager Dave Martinez said . “That’s where we’re at right now.”</p>
<p>LOPEZ OVERCOMES DIFFICULT FOURTH:</p>
<p>After enduring a 22-pitch fourth inning, Lopez rebounded in the fifth, when he retired Victor Robles on a flyout to center and struck out Trea Turner and Juan Soto. Lopez limited the Nationals to the two-run fourth after Carter Kieboom was thrown out at home on an attempted double steal for the third out.</p>
<p>“That was huge and that gave me an extra boost through the fifth and into the sixth,” Lopez said.</p>
<p>ALFARO SITS FOR LOPEZ’S START:</p>
<p>Although he’s driven in nine runs and hit .318 in the current homestand, Marlins starting catcher Jorge Alfaro didn’t start Saturday. Manager Don Mattingly opted to go with Wallach because of his work with Lopez in the right-hander’s previous start. Lopez allowed a combined 12 runs over 5 2/3 innings in starts against Tampa Bay and Atlanta before Wallach caught him in a seven-inning, one-run outing against Philadelphia on Sept. 14.</p>
<p>“I thought Chad was really good with Pablo the last time,” Mattingly said. &#8220;(Lopez) kind of got back on track and I wanted to leave that combination.”</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM:</p>
<p>Nationals: RHP Aaron Barrett (right tricep tightness) received treatment Saturday. The reliever walked and hit the two batters he faced before leaving with his injury in the second game of Friday’s doubleheader.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Nationals: RHP Max Scherzer (4-3, 4.04) will start the first game of a seven-inning doubleheader against Miami on Sunday. The second starter has not been announced.</p>
<p>Marlins: RHP Sandy Alcantara (2-2, 3.45) will face the Nationals in the first game. Miami has not announced the second starter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">741084</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alfaro homers twice, Marlins beat Red Sox 8-4</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/alfaro-homers-twice-marlins-beat-red-sox-8-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AP_FL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com?p=737692&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=737692</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Jorge Alfaro homered twice before he took a foul ball to his helmet and the Miami Marlins beat the Boston Red Sox...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Jorge Alfaro homered twice before he took a foul ball to his helmet and the Miami Marlins beat the Boston Red Sox 8-4 on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Garrett Cooper also homered and scored twice for Miami, which moved within 2 1/2 games of first-place Atlanta in the NL East.</p>
<p>Alfaro, the Marlins’ catcher, was removed in the seventh inning as a precaution after Christian Vázquez’s foul ball beaned him.</p>
<p>Miami chased Boston starter Michael Kickham with a four-run third. Alfaro hit his first of two two-run blasts. Brian Anderson had a run-scoring single and scored from first on Lewis Brinson’s RBI double to make it 6-1.</p>
<p>Alfaro also went deep in the fifth, a 412-foot shot to left-center off Robinson Leyer.</p>
<p>Yimi Garcia (2-0) pitched a perfect eighth and was credited with the win even though he entered with an 8-4 lead. Brandon Kintzler was the sixth Miami reliever and worked a scoreless ninth.</p>
<p>Miami starter Trevor Rogers was lifted after three innings and 76 pitches. Rogers allowed one run on three hits, walked two, hit a batter and struck out three.</p>
<p>J.D. Martinez snapped a 1-for-30 funk with a two-run homer off Miami reliever Ryne Stanek in the seventh. Martinez drove in another run with a sacrifice fly in the third.</p>
<p>Cooper hit a two-run homer to center in the first that snapped a 14-inning scoreless string by Boston pitchers.</p>
<p>Kickham (1-1) allowed six runs on seven hits in 2 2/3 innings.</p>
<p>Alex Verdugo had three hits, a walk and scored twice for Boston.</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM</p>
<p>Marlins: OF Starling Marte was given the night off after playing 16 consecutive games since joining the club in a trade with the Arizona Diamondbacks Aug. 31.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Red Sox: RHP Nate Eovaldi (2-2, 4.82) will pitch the series finale on Thursday. Before joining the New York Yankees in 2015, Eovaldi spent three seasons in Miami, where he went 13-27.</p>
<p>Marlins: RHP Jose Urena (0-1, 7.71) allowed five earned runs in 4 1/3 innings against Philadelphia in his previous start.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">737692</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Houck wins MLB debut, goes 5 innings, Red Sox blank Marlins</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/houck-wins-mlb-debut-goes-5-innings-red-sox-blank-marlins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 03:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AP_FL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com?p=736431&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=736431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Tanner Houck gave up just two singles over five innings to win his major league debut, pitching the Boston Red Sox past...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Tanner Houck gave up just two singles over five innings to win his major league debut, pitching the Boston Red Sox past the Miami Marlins 2-0 Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Houck, the first-round draft pick of the Red Sox in 2017, struck out seven and walked three on 86 pitches. The 24-year-old righty became Boston’s 15th starting pitcher this season.</p>
<p>Jackie Bradley Jr. broke up a scoreless game with an opposite-field double off Miami starter Sandy Alcantara in the sixth. Alcantara (2-2) allowed a leadoff single to Xander Bogaerts and walked Christian Vazquez before Bradley delivered against the playoff-contending Marlins.</p>
<p>The Red Sox increased their lead on Vazquez’s run-scoring single in the eighth. Rafael Devers hit a leadoff double, advanced to third on reliever James Hoyt’s errant pickoff throw and scored on the hit by Vazquez.</p>
<p>Dylan Covey pitched two perfect innings in relief of Houck. Ryan Brasier followed with a scoreless eighth.</p>
<p>Matt Barnes allowed Brian Anderson’s two-out double before striking out Garrett Cooper for his seventh save.</p>
<p>Alcantara scattered five hits, walked two and struck out five in six innings.</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM:</p>
<p>Red Sox: RHP Darwinson Hernandez (shoulder) showed no ill effects from his bullpen session Tuesday.</p>
<p>Marlins: INF Isan Diaz (groin strain) was placed on the 60-day injured list. Diaz played the first series of the season at Philadelphia but opted out after the team’s coronavirus outbreak. Diaz successfully petitioned for reinstatement late last month and rejoined the club Sept. 10. Sean Rodriguez was reinstated from the injured list.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Red Sox: LHP Mike Kickham (1-0, 5.00) will start the middle game of the series against Miami on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Marlins: Rookie LHP Trevor Rogers (1-1, 6.50) looks to bounce back from the worst outing of his young major league career. Rogers allowed eight earned runs and nine hits in three innings against Philadelphia on Sept. 11.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">736431</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lopez, Marlins win finale in 7-game set against Phils, 6-2</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/lopez-marlins-win-finale-in-7-game-set-against-phils-6-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 03:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=735679</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The Marlins still have never lost a Game 7. Pablo Lopez allowed one run in seven innings with the help of flashy defense by right...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The Marlins still have never lost a Game 7.</p>
<p>Pablo Lopez <a href="https://www.mlb.com/gameday/phillies-vs-marlins/2020/09/14/631321#game_state=final,lock_state=final,game_tab=videos,game=631321">allowed one run in seven innings </a>with the help of <a href="https://www.mlb.com/gameday/phillies-vs-marlins/2020/09/14/631321#game_state=final,lock_state=final,game_tab=videos,game=631321">flashy defense by right fielder Matt </a>Joyce, and the upstart Marlins won the finale of their marathon seven-game series against Philadelphia on Monday, 6-2.</p>
<p>The series, the majors’ longest in the regular season in 53 years, included three makeup games and two doubleheaders. The Marlins&#8217; only other Game 7s were in the 1997 and 2003 postseasons, and they won the World Series both years.</p>
<p>“For Game 7 you have in your mind a lot more fans and more energy, but these were huge games for us,&#8221; Joyce said. &#8220;We played really well, and we’re excited to be in the position we’re in.”</p>
<p>Marlins Park was mostly empty because of the coronavirus, but the home team still created some buzz by winning five of seven from Philadelphia, including the final three in the series.</p>
<p>The Marlins (24-21) moved into second place in the NL East, 1 1/2 games ahead of the Phils, and have a shot at their first playoff berth in 17 years after overcoming an early season COVID-19 outbreak that sidelined more than half the team.</p>
<p>“We&#8217;re just kind of doing what we believed we could do,” manager Don Mattingly said. &#8220;Before the season, nationally nobody was thinking about the Marlins at all, but we felt pretty good about ourselves.”</p>
<p>Lopez (4-4) bounced back from his worst outing of the year by allowing only three hits and retiring his final 13 batters. He was helped by not one but two over-the-shoulder basket catches on the warning track by a retreating Joyce, who robbed Scott Kingery and Jean Segura.</p>
<p>“Way more fun if you catch those, right?” Joyce said. “Definitely that football feel. The Phillies&#8217; bullpen was giving me a hard time — I said it was a touchdown, and they said I didn’t keep my feet in. Got to go to the replay.”</p>
<p>The only run Lopez allowed came on <a href="https://www.mlb.com/gameday/phillies-vs-marlins/2020/09/14/631321#game_state=final,lock_state=final,game_tab=videos,game=631321">Andrew McCutchen’s seventh homer </a>to start the game. Philadelphia totaled four hits without J.T. Realmuto and Rhys Hoskins, both nursing injuries.</p>
<p>“It’s always frustrating when you’re not scoring runs,&#8221; manager Joe Girardi said. &#8220;We hit the ball hard; just didn’t have any runs to show for it.”</p>
<p>Jesus Aguilar put the Marlins ahead with <a href="https://www.mlb.com/gameday/phillies-vs-marlins/2020/09/14/631321#game_state=final,lock_state=final,game_tab=videos,game=631321">a two-run double </a>in the third. Miguel Rojas hit his third home run and Starling Marte added his fifth, both off David Phelps.</p>
<p>Kingery, reinstated from the injured list before the game, hit his second homer. Phils catcher Rafael Marchan made his major league debut and went 1 for 3.</p>
<p>Vince Velasquez (0-1) allowed four runs in 3 2/3 innings, and his ERA rose to 6.46.</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM</p>
<p>Phillies: 1B Hoskins (left wrist) will go on the 10-day injured list but might play again this season. Realmuto has a mild strain of the left hip flexor, and he&#8217;ll likely miss a couple more days. “As long as I keep progressing like I did today, it shouldn’t be too long,&#8221; Realmuto said. &#8230; RHP Zack Wheeler (finger) threw a bullpen session before the game. Barring a setback, he&#8217;ll start in the upcoming series against the New York Mets.</p>
<p>Marlins: 2B Isan Diaz left the game in the fourth inning with a tight left groin. Mattingly said the move was precautionary, and Diaz&#8217;s status is day to day.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Phillies: RHP Jake Arrieta (3-4, 5.54 ERA) is scheduled to start when the Phillies return home Tuesday to face the Mets.</p>
<p>Marlins: Continue their 15-game homestand with a three-game series against Boston. RHP Sandy Alcantara (2-1, 3.97 ERA) is scheduled to start Tuesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">735679</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alfaro&#8217;s 2 RBIs help Marlins earn split against Phils, 5-3</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/alfaros-2-rbis-help-marlins-earn-split-against-phils-5-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 03:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=732430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Jorge Alfaro had his fourth consecutive two-RBI game, and the Miami Marlins salvaged a split of their doubleheader against the Philadelphia Phillies...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Jorge Alfaro had his fourth consecutive two-RBI game, and the Miami Marlins salvaged a split of their doubleheader against the Philadelphia Phillies by winning 5-3 Friday night.</p>
<p>Alfaro&#8217;s two-run single capped a three-run fourth for the Marlins. Yimi Garcia gave up a run for the first time this season but earned his first save since 2015.</p>
<p>In the opener, Aaron Nola struck out 10 and went the distance for the first time in his career as the Phillies handed the Marlins their worst drubbing in two days, winning 11-0. Officially, the performance went in the books as a complete game.</p>
<p>“I don’t feel like it counts,” Nola said. “Nine innings is a complete game. But I felt good today. I&#8217;m glad I finished it out.”</p>
<p>While Nola cruised, Game 1 was another rough outing for Marlins pitchers, who gave up a National League record 29 runs against Atlanta on Wednesday.</p>
<p>With the split, third-place Miami remained half a game behind the second-place Phillies in the NL East.</p>
<p>GAME 1</p>
<p>Nola (5-3) didn&#8217;t allow a hit until Brian Anderson singled to cap a 10-pitch at-bat leading off the fifth. By then the Phillies had their 11-run lead.</p>
<p>Andrew McCutchen drove in three runs with three hits, including his sixth homer. Rhys Hoskins hit a three-run homer, his 10th. Adam Haseley doubled twice, singled and drove in two runs.</p>
<p>Nola allowed three singles, hit two batters, walked none, threw 106 pitches and reached double digits in strikeouts for the fourth time this year. The complete game was his first in 136 career starts, and he conceded he kept the game ball as a souvenir.</p>
<p>“I might throw with it tomorrow,” he said.</p>
<p>Nola lowered his ERA to 2.40 and pitched at least seven innings for the fifth time this year.</p>
<p>“I definitely want to go as long as I can, especially in a doubleheader,” he said. “That’s kind of our job as starters. We want to take as much stress off the bullpen as possible.”</p>
<p>Trevor Rogers (1-1) gave up nine runs, eight earned, in three-plus innings.</p>
<p>GAME 2</p>
<p>Lewis Brinson hit his third homer for the Marlins.</p>
<p>James Hoyt (2-0) struck out the only batter he faced. Ranger Suarez (0-1) allowed three runs while getting just one out.</p>
<p>MOVES</p>
<p>Phillies: Before the doubleheader, they selected INF Ronald Torreyes from Lehigh Valley, optioned RHP Connor Brogdon to Lehigh Valley, reinstated LHP Adam Morgan from the IL, and designated INF Neil Walker for assignment.</p>
<p>Marlins: They selected the contract of RHP Johan Quezada. RHP Justin Shafer cleared waivers and was granted his unconditional release.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Phillies: RHP Spencer Howard (1-2, 5.66) is scheduled to start Saturday in place of Zack Wheeler, whose start was pushed back at least until Monday after he ripped a nail putting on his pants.</p>
<p>Marlins: RHP José Ureña (0-0, 5.40) is scheduled to start in the fourth game of the series. He allowed three runs in five innings in his first start of the year against Atlanta after being sidelined by the coronavirus.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">732430</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marlins rally past Phillies 7-6, open 1st 7-game series since &#8217;67</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/marlins-rally-past-phillies-7-6-open-1st-7-game-series-since-67/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 04:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MLB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=731454</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Starling Marte hit a tying, three-run double off Brandon Workman in the eighth inning, Jorge Alfaro singled home the winning run in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Starling Marte hit a tying, three-run double off Brandon Workman in the eighth inning, Jorge Alfaro singled home the winning run in the ninth and the Miami Marlins beat the Philadelphia Phillies 7-6 Thursday night in the opener of a seven-game series, the longest in a major league regular season in 53 years.</p>
<p>The series includes three makeup games and two doubleheaders, replacing a series postponed from July 31 to Aug. 2 due to a novel coronavirus outbreak among the Marlins.</p>
<p>The previous seven-game, regular-season series was between the New York Mets and Chicago Cubs at Wrigley Field from Aug. 31 to Sept. 3, 1967, according to the Elias Sports Bureau. The Phillies have not played a seven-game, regular-season series since Aug. 16-20, 1930, at the Cubs, a set that included two ties that ended because of darkness in the era before night games.</p>
<p>Miami began a season-high, 15-game homestand and improved the worst home record in the major leagues to 3-9. The Marlins were coming off 29-9 loss to Atlanta.</p>
<p>“It’s happened too many times and we’ve been through a lot,” Marlins manager Don Mattingly said. “Every time it looks like these guys will fade, they show up and put up a W and keep it going.&#8221;</p>
<p>Brian Anderson singled off Workman (1-2) leading off the ninth, and pinch-runner Monte Harrison advanced on Garret Cooper’s groundout and stole third on catcher J.T. Realmuto with a headfirst slide, a call by third base umpire David Arrieta play upheld in a video review.</p>
<p>Miguel Rojas was intentionally walked to set up a potential double play, Workman advanced Rojas with a wild pitch and Jazz Chisholm struck out. Alfaro grounded a single up the middle just past the glove of diving shortstop Didi Gregorius for his first big league walk-off hit, giving the Marlins their first walkoff win this season.</p>
<p>Alfaro, who was the first of the Marlins’ 18 players to test positive for COVID-19 and was placed on the IL before opening day, has hit .220 with 19 strikeouts in 50 at-bats since returning to action. But he is hitting .292 (7 for 24) over his past seven games.</p>
<p>“Honestly I was looking for something up in the zone that I can drive through the middle,” Alfaro said. “I saw the first fastball was up and I took it, so I just waited for something in the spot I was looking for.”</p>
<p>Miami (20-19) pulled within a half-game of the Phillies (21-19) for second place in the NL East.</p>
<p>Tommy Hunter allowed three runs in two-thirds of an inning, and Workman one run in one inning. Philadelphia’s bullpen has allowed 101 earned runs in 127 1/3 innings, a 7.14 ERA that is the worst in the major leagues.</p>
<p>“I think we’ve just got to do a better job of attacking guys,” Realmuto said. “I think the stuff is there. We’re just getting in bad counts, walking leadoff guys with a three-run lead. You can’t do stuff like that and be successful late in the game.”</p>
<p>Realmuto hit his 11th homer and had an RBI grounder as Philadelphia built a 6-3 lead in the fifth.</p>
<p>Alfaro had his third straight game with multiple RBIs for the Marlins.</p>
<p>Phillies starter Jake Arrieta allowed three runs, five hits and four walks in 5 2/3 innings. Marlins starter Sandy Alcantara gave up six runs — three earned — and seven hits in six innings, hurt by Alfaro’s passed ball and errors by Jesús Aguilar at first and Marte in center.</p>
<p>“It’s frustrating for all of us, but the one thing this team’s always done is it’s bounced back,” Phillies manager Joe Girardi said. “We went through this a couple of times this year, and they’ve got to do it again. It’s what they have to do. We don’t have a choice.”</p>
<p>MOVES</p>
<p>Miami optioned RHP Jordan Yamamoto and LHP Alex Vesia to the alternate training site, and the Marlins recalled INF Isan Díaz and selected the contract of RHP Brett Eibner.</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM</p>
<p>Phillies LHP José Álvarez (groin) is starting to take part in light activity, but Girardi doesn’t expect him to pitch again in the regular season. Álvarez took a 105.3 mph line drive off the bat of Toronto’s Lourdes Gurriel Jr. on Aug. 20.</p>
<p>Marlins: INF Jon Berti (index finger) was placed on the 10-day IL. Berti, batting .250 with 10 RBIs and eight steaks, was hurt while attempting a bunt in the 10th inning of Monday’s game against the Braves. &#8230; C Francisco Cervelli (concussion) was transferred to the 60-day IL, ending his season.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Phillies: RHP Aaron Nola (4-3, 2.74 ERA) is scheduled to pitch the first game of the doubleheader. Nola allowed six runs — three earned — and struck out 10 in 5 1/3 innings against the Mets last Sunday. No starter was announced for the second game.</p>
<p>Marlins: LHP Trevor Rogers (1-0, 3.00) is scheduled to start the second game. He allowed three runs and struck out 10 in six innings last Sunday against the Rays. No starter was announced for the opener.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">731454</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sánchez, 4 relievers throw 4-hitter as Marlins blank Braves</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/news/sanchez-4-relievers-throw-4-hitter-as-marlins-blank-braves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 03:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AP_FL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Marlins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com?p=729405&#038;preview=true&#038;preview_id=729405</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — Sixto Sánchez combined with four relievers on a four-hitter, Jorge Alfaro hit one of three homers for Miami and the Marlins beat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — Sixto Sánchez combined with four relievers on a four-hitter, Jorge Alfaro hit one of three homers for Miami and the Marlins beat the Atlanta Braves 8-0 on Tuesday night.</p>
<p>Garrett Cooper had two hits, including a two-run homer, and drove in three runs. Alfaro drove in two runs with two hits, including his first homer. Matt Joyce also homered.</p>
<p>The first-place Braves&#8217; hopes a fourth straight NL East title suffered a setback when left-hander Max Fried, the team&#8217;s top starter, was placed on the 10-day injured list Tuesday with a left-side muscle spasm in his lumbar spine.</p>
<p>Miami trails Atlanta by 2 1/2 games in the division after winning the first two games of the three-game series.</p>
<p>Sánchez (2-1) allowed three hits in six-plus innings. The right-hander opened the game by striking out Ronald Acuña Jr. with a 100-mph fastball, the first of six strikeouts with one walk.</p>
<p>The 22-year-old Sánchez didn’t allow a runner to reach second base until the seventh. Marcell Ozuna had an infield single and Sánchez hit Austin Riley with a pitch.</p>
<p>James Hoyt walked Adeiny Hechavarria with two outs to load the bases. Richard Bleier ended the inning on pinch-hitter Travis d’Arnaud’s groundout.</p>
<p>Kyle Wright (0-4) allowed five runs on seven hits, including three homers, in four innings as his ERA climbed to 8.05.</p>
<p>Freddie Freeman doubled off Nick Vincent with two outs in the eighth for Atlanta&#8217;s only extra-base hit.</p>
<p>Fried had been the only current healthy member of Atlanta&#8217;s projected starting rotation. Atlanta lost ace Mike Soroka for the remainder of the season to a torn right Achilles tendon, and the Braves&#8217; starters began the day with a 5.49 ERA. Miami&#8217;s young starters rank fifth in the NL with a 3.94 mark.</p>
<p>TRAINER’S ROOM</p>
<p>Marlins: INF Jon Berti did not start after cutting his hand while bunting and leaving Monday&#8217;s game in the 10th inning. “We’re going to try to give him one day, maybe two,” manager Don Mattingly said. “We feel like we dodged a bullet there.”</p>
<p>Braves: General manager Alex Anthopoulos said LHP Cole Hamels (triceps tendinitis) could make his first start of 2020 next week at Baltimore after throwing on Thursday at the alternate training site. Hamels impressed pitching coach Rick Kranitz when he threw batting practice for the first time on Sunday. It would be unusual to activate Hamels after so little preparation, but losing Fried to the IL adds urgency to the team&#8217;s need for rotation help.</p>
<p>TRANSACTIONS</p>
<p>The Marlins optioned infielder Lewin Diaz to their alternate training site and recalled right-hander Jordan Yamamoto. Left-hander Adam Conley was outrighted to Triple-A Memphis after Monday’s game.</p>
<p>Braves right-hander Jacob Webb was reinstated from the 45-day IL and gave up two unearned runs in two innings. Utility infielder Charlie Culberson was designated for assignment.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Marlins: RHP Pablo López (3-3, 3.05) will try to end a streak of two straight losses, each to Tampa Bay, in Wednesday night&#8217;s final game of the series. He allowed two runs in six innings of an 8-2 win over the Braves on Aug. 14.</p>
<p>Braves: LHP Tommy Milone has a 5.91 ERA in six career games against Miami, including three starts. Milone has an 11.37 ERA in his first two starts with the Braves.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">729405</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/11/marlins-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami marlins logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
