<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
		>

<channel>
	<title>Miami Hurricanes &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wsvn.com/sports/college/miami-hurricanes/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:59:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/cropped-cropped-7News_logo_FBbghex-1-1.png?w=32</url>
	<title>Miami Hurricanes &#8211; WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale</title>
	<link>https://wsvn.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">174089892</site>	<item>
		<title>McGusty scores 27, rallies Miami over Boston College 80-76</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mcgusty-scores-27-rallies-miami-over-boston-college-80-76/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 04:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=877116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Kameron McGusty scored a season-high 27 points and led a late rally as Miami defeated Boston College 80-76 on Friday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Kameron McGusty scored a season-high 27 points and led a late rally as Miami defeated Boston College 80-76 on Friday in a regular-season finale.</p>
<p>Boston College (4-15, 2-11 Atlantic Coast Conference) erased Miami&#8217;s largest lead of the game of nine points with a 11-0 run while the Hurricanes (8-16, 4-15) went scoreless for over 4 1/2 minutes to trail 68-66 with 3:40 left. McGusty ended the drought with a bucket, scoring the first seven points of a 9-0 run that gave Miami a 75-68 lead with 1:49 remaining. Boston College got within three on a 3-pointer by Frederick Scott with 6.4 seconds to go but an Isaiah Wong free throw ensured the win.</p>
<p>McGusty was 9-of-12 shooting with four 3-pointers and five assists. Nysier Brooks scored a career-high 21 points on 8-of-11 shooting and Anthony Walker added 17 points, seven rebounds and four assists. Miami, injury-plagued all season, had just six scholarship athletes available but were able to snap a six-game losing streak.</p>
<p>James Karnik scored 15 points, hitting all nine of his free throws, to lead the Eagles. Makai Ashton-Langford added 13 points, Frederick Scott and Kamari Williams scored 11 points each and JC Felder had 10 points and a career-high six blocks. Jay Heath, the Eagles&#8217; leading scorer who had 25 points in BC&#8217;s 84-62 win over Miami on Jan. 13, finished with 10 points on 4-of-16 shooting. The Eagles, who made a season-high 18 3-pointers in that January win, had nine on Friday.</p>
<p>The teams started the day with the same winning percentage (.167) so they were playing to avoid becoming the lowest seed for the conference tournament that runs March 9-13 in Greensboro, North Carolina.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">877116</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Hurricanes star Kellen Winslow II gets 14 years for rapes</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/former-hurricanes-star-kellen-winslow-ii-gets-14-years-for-rapes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Chalvire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 20:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US & World]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=875292</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO (AP) — Former NFL player Kellen Winslow II was sentenced Wednesday to 14 years in prison for multiple rapes and other sexual offenses...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAN DIEGO (AP) — Former NFL player Kellen Winslow II was sentenced Wednesday to 14 years in prison for multiple rapes and other sexual offenses against five women in Southern California, including one who was homeless when he attacked her in 2018.</p>
<p>The 37-year-old son of San Diego Chargers Hall of Fame receiver Kellen Winslow appeared via videoconference at the hearing in San Diego Superior Court in Vista, a city north of San Diego. He declined to comment before his sentence, saying his lawyers had advised him not to speak.</p>
<p>San Diego County Superior Court Judge Blaine Bowman said Winslow can only be described with “two words and that is sexual predator.&#8221; He said he selected women who were vulnerable because of their age or their living situation with the idea that “hopefully he would get away with it in his mind.&#8221;</p>
<p>Winslow was once the highest-paid tight end in the league, earning more than $40 million over his 10 seasons before he left in 2013.</p>
<p>The 14-year-sentence was the maximum allowed under a plea deal. He was convicted of forcible rape, rape of an unconscious person, assault with intent to commit rape, indecent exposure, and lewd conduct in public.</p>
<p>The forcible rape involved a woman who was homeless in his home town of Encinitas, a beach community north of San Diego.</p>
<p>She was among four of the women who gave statements Wednesday, including one victim who had the prosecutor read hers. All described suffering years after their attacks from fear and emotional trauma.</p>
<p>The woman who was homeless called into the hearing via video conference from the San Diego County District Attorney&#8217;s office, where she was watching the proceedings with another victim.</p>
<p>She said since she was raped she has had trouble raising her head and walking, and she feels afraid constantly, checking under beds and in closets, and cannot be alone.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s affecting my life every day and every night,&#8221; she said. “I don’t ever feel safe inside or outside. You brought so much damage to my life.&#8221;</p>
<p>Winslow&#8217;s attorney Marc Carlos said Winslow suffered from head trauma from the many blows to his head playing football, which can only explain why he “went off the rails&#8221; going from a star athlete to a convicted sexual predator. He said his client has accepted responsibility and intends to get help.</p>
<p>Winslow was convicted of forcible rape and two misdemeanors — indecent exposure and a lewd act in public — after a trial in June 2019.</p>
<p>But that jury failed to agree on other charges, including the alleged 2018 rape of a 54-year-old hitchhiker, and the 2003 rape of an unconscious 17-year-old high school senior who went to a party with him when he was 19.</p>
<p>Before he was retried on those charges, he pleaded guilty to raping the teen and sexual battery of the hitchhiker. Those pleas spared him the possibility of life in prison.</p>
<p>The father of two, whose wife filed for divorce after he was convicted, had faced up to 18 years in prison for all the charges. But both sides agreed to reduce the sexual battery charge to assault with intent to commit rape last month. That reduced the maximum sentence to 14 years.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">875292</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ap_19165536839664.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ap_19165536839664.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/ap_19165536839664.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">Kellen Winslow Jr Rape Case</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Devoe, Georgia Tech, dominate 1st half, swamp Miami 89-60</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/devoe-georgia-tech-dominate-1st-half-swamp-miami-89-60/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 23:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=868442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Michael Devoe scored 29 points, Moses Wright had a double-double and Georgia Tech used a dominant first half to defeat...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Michael Devoe scored 29 points, Moses Wright had a double-double and Georgia Tech used a dominant first half to defeat short-handed Miami 89-60 on Saturday.</p>
<p>With Devoe making all six of his shots, including four 3-pointers, the Yellow Jackets took a 48-18 lead at halftime. Georgia Tech went 6 of 12 behind the arc and shot 63% (19 of 30) while holding the Hurricanes to 28.6% shooting (6 of 21) and forcing 12 turnovers.</p>
<p>Jose Alvarado scored 16 points for Georgia Tech (11-8, 7-6 Atlantic Coast Conference) and <a href="https://twitter.com/theACCDN/status/1363198753130369027">Wright added 14</a>, making him the fourth active Yellow Jacket to surpass 1,000 for his career and had 12 rebounds.</p>
<p>Devoe finished with a career-high 7 3s on 11 attempts as the team went 11 of 26 and finished at 57% (36 of 63) from the field.</p>
<p>Elijah Olaniyi led Miami (7-13, 3-12), which used just seven players until the closing minutes, with 18 points. Anthony Walker added 16 points and Nysier Brooks 12.</p>
<p>Harlond Beverly, who had started 15 games, missed the game with a back injury and is out indefinitely and leading scorer Isaiah Wong (17.4 ppg) sprained his ankle in the first half and didn&#8217;t play in the second half, finishing with four points in 18 minutes.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes shot 47% (14 of 30) after the miserable first half to stay even with the Yellow Jackets in the second half but trailed by as many as 36 points and never got closer than 25.</p>
<p>It was a Georgia Tech record for largest road win in an ACC game.</p>
<p>Devoe opened the game with back-to-back 3s and Georgia Tech scored the first 12 points. His third 3 made it 15-3 and his fourth, less than eight minutes in, made it 26-7. Alvarado had a 3-pointer and Jordan Usher the last six points, four on dunks, as the Yellowjackets closed on a 9-0 run for that 30-point lead.</p>
<p>Miami scored 14 points in the first half against Purdue early in the season, shooting 22.7% but only trailed by 18.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech plays at No. 18 Virginia Tech on Tuesday; Miami is home against No. 16 Florida State on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">868442</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Surging Notre Dame takes down feisty but depleted Hurricanes 71-61</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/surging-notre-dame-takes-down-feisty-but-depleted-hurricanes-71-61/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 02:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=865087</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Nikola Djogo scored 18 points on 7-for-10 shooting and Nate Laszewski scored 14 and Notre Dame beat Miami 71-61 on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Nikola Djogo scored 18 points on 7-for-10 shooting and Nate Laszewski scored 14 and Notre Dame beat Miami 71-61 on Sunday.</p>
<p>Laszewski finished shooting 6 for 8, Juwan Durham scored 12 and Dane Goodwin scored 11 with 11 rebounds for the Irish.</p>
<p>Notre Dame (9-10, 6-7 Atlantic Coast Conference) now has won back-to-back games for the third time this season, and six of its last eight as it tries to make a push coming down the season&#8217;s home stretch.</p>
<p>Laszewski&#8217;s three-point play gave the Irish a 50-43 lead with 10:46 remaining in the game. Miami (7-12, 3-11) countered with an 11-2 run over the next four minutes, and Elijah Olaniyi&#8217;s 3-pointer put the Hurricanes ahead 54-52.</p>
<p>Laszewski responded with consecutive layups, the second resulting in a three-point play, and the Irish proceeded to distance itself.</p>
<p>Isaiah Wong scored 17 points for the Hurricanes, Anthony Walker 14 with 10 rebounds, Kameron McGusty 12, Olaniyi 11 and Nysier Brooks secured 10 rebounds.</p>
<p>The injury-ravaged Hurricanes again played with just seven scholarship athletes. Point guard Chris Lykes suffered a setback in practice late last week to his injured ankle, which has kept him out for all but two games this year.</p>
<p>Compounding Miami’s injury woes, the club announced freshman Earl Timberlake will miss the rest of the season because of a shoulder ailment. He averaged 9.3 points and five rebounds in seven games this season.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes next host Georgia Tech on Saturday. The Irish host Clemson on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">865087</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 16 Virginia Tech escapes with overtime win over Hurricanes</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-16-virginia-tech-escapes-with-overtime-win-over-hurricanes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=859623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Virginia Tech had to go to overtime to avoid a losing streak. Justyn Mutts scored 22 points and Keve Aluma...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Virginia Tech had to go to overtime to avoid a losing streak.</p>
<p>Justyn Mutts scored 22 points and Keve Aluma added 16 as the No. 16 Hokies defeated Miami 80-76 Saturday.</p>
<p>Nahiem Alleyne hit a go-ahead jumper with 25 seconds remaining in the extra period and Hunter Cattoor’s two free throws with four seconds left as the Hokies (14-4, 8-3 Atlantic Coast Conference) needed a late 3-pointer to avoid consecutive losses.</p>
<p>“Good teams don’t lose two games in a row,” Virginia Tech coach Mike Young said. “Good teams find ways to hang in there and continue to keep your shoulders back and hit the practice floor to improve. You’ve heard me say it many times. I’ve got great dudes.”</p>
<p>Cattoor finished with 14 points and forced the overtime with a 3-pointer at the buzzer to tie the game at 74-all. The basket erased Isaiah Wong’s go-ahead 3-pointer seconds earlier for Miami.</p>
<p>There was question as to whether Cattoor stepped out of bounds before his game-tying conversion.</p>
<p>“I don’t know if that’s true or not; I know there were several very close calls at the end,” Miami coach Jim Larranaga said. “It’s a strange ending to a game if in fact the guy who made the game tying shot was out of bounds. I’ll be very disappointed if I find out that was a violation.”</p>
<p>Young had not heard anything about Cattoor stepping out of bounds.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don’t really care. The kid made a great shot. We got it to overtime,” Young said.</p>
<p>Wong and Elija Olaniyi scored 19 points each for the Hurricanes (7-11, 3-10). Kameron McGusty added 18 points.</p>
<p>“With Hunter we’ve seen him hit that shot so many times,” Mutts said of Cattoor’s 3-pointer. “For him to make it at that big of a time in the game it’s really not a surprise to anybody. But my mindset at that point was now let’s go win the game.”</p>
<p>Miami erased a double-digit deficit with a 20-7 spurt late in the second half. Wong hit two 3-pointers to key the surge and Nysier Brooks’ dunk with 3:34 to go gave the Hurricanes a 68-66 lead.</p>
<p>The Hokies opened their first double-digit lead with a 12-2 run midway through the second half. Mutts’ layup with 8:03 remaining capped the surge and gave Virginia Tech a 59-48 lead.</p>
<p>Mutts’ two free throws gave Virginia Tech a 31-28 lead at halftime.</p>
<p>MUTTS CONTINUES WITH SOLID EFFORTS:</p>
<p>Mutts shot 9-of-14 from the field and finished with a career high seven assists. The performance followed his 17-point outing on 7-of-12 shooting in the loss at Pitt Wednesday.</p>
<p>“Coaches and my teammates told me to be a lot more aggressive,” Mutts said. “I’m just trying to do whatever it takes to get the wins. At the end of the day, that’s all that really matters.”</p>
<p>FRESHMAN BAMISILE STEPS IN FOR CONE:</p>
<p>Hokies starting forward Jalen Cone left with an undisclosed lower leg injury early in the game and didn’t return. Freshman Joseph Bamisile picked up most of the playing time following Cone’s injury and finished with 11 points and three assists.</p>
<p>“You never know when you’re opportunity is going to come,” Young said. “You can’t get ready when the opportunity presents itself. You get ready with preparation leading for days like today.”</p>
<p>ANOTHER HEARTBREAKER AGAINST VIRGINIA TECH:</p>
<p>The close loss followed Miami&#8217;s 80-78 setback at Blacksburg Dec. 29. The Hurricanes also trailed by double figures before a late comeback.</p>
<p>“I’m glad with the way we played and fought,” McGusty said. “I’m proud of our fight. We just came up short. Of course we’re upset but you cant drop your head.”</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE:</p>
<p>Virginia Tech: Guard Tyrece Radford missed his fourth consecutive game and his return remains uncertain. Radford, who averages a Hokies’ second-best 11.1 points, has been suspended since his arrest for driving under the influence Jan. 24.</p>
<p>Miami: Senior guard Chris Lykes, the team’s leading scorer last season, resumed practice Thursday after a lengthy absence but didn’t play. Sidelined for two months because of a left ankle injury, Lykes also topped the Hurricanes in assists, steals, field goals and free throws made as a junior.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Virginia Tech: The Hokies will have a week off before their home game against Louisville next Saturday. The gap occurred after a home date with No. 20 Florida State on Tuesday was postponed because of a recent COVID-19 outbreak involving the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Miami: the Hurricanes begin a two-game road set Monday at North Carolina. The Tar Heels defeated Miami 67-65 in Coral Gables Jan. 5.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">859623</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hurricanes end skid, hang on to defeat Duke 77-75</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hurricanes-end-skid-hang-on-to-defeat-duke-77-75/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 04:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=853771</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Elijah Olaniyi scored 21 points, Anthony Walker and Isaiah Wong added 16 points apiece and short-handed Miami overcame shaky foul...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) &#xE2;&#x80;&#x94; Elijah Olaniyi scored 21 points, Anthony Walker and Isaiah Wong added 16 points apiece and short-handed Miami overcame shaky foul shooting down the stretch to defeat Duke 77-75 on Monday, ending a four-game losing streak.<p>The Hurricanes, whose previous three games with the Blue Devils were losses by at least 30 points, made this one difficult by missing 4 of 8 free throws, including the front end of two 1-and-1 opportunities, in the final 75 seconds.</p><p>But Walker made a pair with 12.8 seconds to go that proved to be the difference. He made it 77-73 before a tipin by Duke forward Wendell Moore Jr. at 4.9 seconds.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/7SportsXtra/status/1356456400784916481?s=20</embed></div><p>Wong missed his front end with 4.3 seconds remaining but Duke capped its frustrating night by not being able to get up a final shot.</p><p>With just six scholarship players available, Miami (7-10, 3-9 Atlantic Coast Conference) had lost four-straight games without reaching 60 points in any of them. Wong was questionable after spraining an ankle on Saturday.</p><p>But Wong appeared fine and the Hurricanes didn&#x2019;t have any problem getting the ball inside, shooting 52.5%, including 17 of 28 (60.7%) in the second half. When Duke went to a 3-2 zone, one of the worst Division I 3-point shooting teams (28.4%) made 7 of 15 behind the arc, led by Olaniyi&#x2019;s 3-for-5 shooting.</p><p>Matthew Hurt led the Blue Devils (7-6, 5-4) with 21 points. Moore added 18 points, DJ Steward scored 14 and Jalen Johnson 13. Duke was just 5 of 18 (27.8%) from distance and shot 46% overall, 44% in the second half.</p><p>There were 20 lead changes and the big lead for both teams was six points. Duke led 35-33 at the half.</p><p>The next game for both teams is on Saturday. Duke faces North Carolina when both are unranked for the first time since the 1959-60 season. Miami plays No. 16 Virginia Tech.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">853771</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Williams with 16, Wake Forest tops short-handed Hurricanes 66-54</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/williams-with-16-wake-forest-tops-short-handed-hurricanes-66-54/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=851303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[WINSTON-SALEM, N.C. (AP) — Daivien Williamson scored 16 points, leading four players into double figures, as Wake Forest ended its January slate with a 66-54...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINSTON-SALEM, N.C. (AP) — Daivien Williamson scored 16 points, leading four players into double figures, as Wake Forest ended its January slate with a 66-54 defeat of a depleted Miami on Saturday.</p>
<p>Jalen Johnson added 15 points and Isaiah Mucius 13 with nine rebounds for the Demon Deacons (5-7, 2-7 Atlantic Coast Conference). Carter Whitt adding 11 on 4-for-4 shooting. Ody Oguama pulled down a career-best 12 rebounds, nine off the defensive glass.</p>
<p>Whitt, Williamson and Johnson each made three 3-pointers for Wake Forest, which kicked off Saturday&#8217;s game with a season-high nine treys in the first half.</p>
<p>Thirteen of the Deacons&#8217; 23 field goals came from behind the arc.</p>
<p>Kameron McGusty and Isaiah Wong led the short-handed Hurricanes (6-10, 2-9) with 17 and 14 points, respectively. Anthony Walker scored 12.</p>
<p>Miami was down to seven players, each of whom saw at least 11 minutes of court time, and Wong departed in the closing minutes with an ankle injury.</p>
<p>Elijah Olaniyi and Earl Timberlake were out with shoulder injuries, Chris Lykes with an ankle injury. Rodney Miller Jr. and Sam Waardenburg are out for the season with knee and foot issues, respectively.</p>
<p>Coach Jim Larranaga said he didn&#8217;t yet know the severity of Wong&#8217;s injury, and still doesn&#8217;t know when Lykes — Miami&#8217;s leading scorer a year ago — might return after being sidelined for two months.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes are depleted by a departure as well. Freshman Matt Cross, who appeared in Miami’s first 14 games and started nine, left the program Thursday.</p>
<p>“I probably just was not the right coach for him,” Larranaga said. &#8220;I have my own way of doing things. You&#8217;ve got to buy into that approach. If you don&#8217;t, it probably makes you unhappy; you don&#8217;t feel like it&#8217;s an ideal fit. I just came to the conclusion the best thing would be for him to find someplace where he would be happier.”</p>
<p>Wake Forest lost seven of its first eight games in January, eking past Pitt 76-75 for its lone win before Saturday. Miami ends the month on a four-game slide.</p>
<p>Short roster or no, Miami jumped out to a 7-0 lead to start the game as Wake Forest whiffed on its first nine shots. The Deacons caught up midway through the first half when Johnson, Whitt and Mucius drained 3-pointers for a 20-13 lead Miami could never surmount.</p>
<p>McGusty got the Hurricanes as close as 23-21 but Wake Forest led by 10 at the break and had an answer to every Miami challenge in the second half.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Wake Forest is at Notre Dame, Miami returns to Coral Gables to host Duke.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">851303</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hubb&#8217;s 19 points lift Notre Dame past Miami in 73-59 win</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hubbs-19-points-lift-notre-dame-past-miami-in-73-59-win/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 03:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=843218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Prentiss Hubb scored 19 points with five 3-pointers and Notre Dame beat Miami 73-59 on Sunday night. Miami scored the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Prentiss Hubb scored 19 points with five 3-pointers and Notre Dame beat Miami 73-59 on Sunday night.</p>
<p>Miami scored the game’s first six points before a 9-3 Notre Dame run evened the count. Dane Goodwin&#8217;s 3-pointer with 4:33 left before halftime gave Notre Dame a 19-16 lead and the Fighting Irish never trailed again.</p>
<p>Notre Dame led 30-22 at intermission and extended the lead to 58-39 with 9:24 left on a pair of free throws by Juwan Durham.</p>
<p>Durham and Nate Laszewski each scored 16 for Notre Dame (5-8, 2-5 Atlantic Coast Conference). The Fighting Irish were 28-for-52 shooting (53.8%); including 10 for 18 from (55.6%) from 3-point range.</p>
<p>Kameron McGusty scored 20 points for Miami (6-8, 2-7), Isaiah Wong added 16 and Elijah Olaniyi 10. Miami finished shooting 3 for 22 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>The Irish won their second straight game and leads the series 13-12.</p>
<p>Notre Dame hosts No. 16-ranked Virginia Tech on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Miami now has dropped back-to-back games and three of its last four. The Hurricanes head to Florida State on Wednesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">843218</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wong scores 30, leads Hurricanes over No. 16 Louisville 78-72</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/wong-scores-30-leads-hurricanes-over-no-16-louisville-78-72/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 05:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=833622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Isaiah Wong had 30 points, seven rebounds and six assists, and Miami beat No. 16 Louisville 78-72 on Saturday night...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Isaiah Wong had 30 points, seven rebounds and six assists, and Miami beat No. 16 Louisville 78-72 on Saturday night to end an 18-game skid against ranked opponents.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes lost their first four Atlantic Coast Conference games by single digits before an 84-62 blowout at Boston College on Tuesday.</p>
<p>“He is a terrific scorer,” Miami coach Jim Larranaga said of Wong. “When he has the ball in his hands, he has a nose for the basket.”</p>
<p>Larranaga said Wong sprained his ankle and received treatment immediately after the game.</p>
<p>Matt Cross scored 16 points and Elijah Olaniyi had 15 points and 10 rebounds for Miami. The previous time the Hurricanes (6-6, 2-5 Atlantic Coast Conference) topped a ranked foe was at No. 9 North Carolina in February of 2018.</p>
<p>“This is a great confidence booster for us, especially coming off our last game,” Olaniyi said. “We didn’t feel we played to the best of our abilities in that game.”</p>
<p>Louisville (9-2, 4-1) rallied from a 12-point halftime deficit and got within 68-64 on Matt Slazinski’s three free throws with 2:21 remaining. Cross’ 3-pointer with 1:29 left gave Miami another seven-point margin.</p>
<p>Carlik Jones scored 25 points and Jae’Lyn Withers finished with 18 points for the Cardinals.</p>
<p>“In basketball you can’t turn it on and turn it off,” Louisville coach Chris Mack said. “I thought (Friday) in Louisville, our practice left a lot to be desired. It was really, really frustrating. I got on the plane with a not-so-good feeling and it manifested itself tonight.”</p>
<p>After allowing 18 3-pointers in a 84-62 loss Tuesday at Boston College, Miami limited Louisville to 3-of-20 from behind the arc. The Cardinals missed their first 11 3-pointers until Withers’ conversion 6:32 into the second half.</p>
<p>&#8220;They had some very good open looks from 3 but they missed them,” Larranaga said. “Our defense has been pretty good against teams that don’t shoot 3s.”</p>
<p>Wong’s jumper with 5:29 remaining capped an 18-4 run and gave the Hurricanes their largest lead of the first half at 25-12. Miami led 33-21 at halftime after Cross’ 3-pointer with 12 seconds left.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Louisville: Because of two home postponements, the Cardinals completed a stretch of four-of-five conference road games Saturday. The Cardinals last encountered a similar stretch in 1994-95, when they played in the Metro Conference.</p>
<p>Miami: Senior point guard Chris Lykes missed his 10th consecutive game because of a left ankle injury. Lykes, the Hurricanes leading scorer as a junior and a pre-season second team All-ACC, has been sidelined since Dec. 4. Miami also played without starting guard Kameron McGusty, who is out with a right hamstring injury.</p>
<p>DON’T I KNOW YOU?</p>
<p>Miami graduate center Nysier Brooks, who finished with eight points and 11 rebounds, became familiar with Mack during the intense inter-city rivalry between Cincinnati and Xavier. Brooks&#8217; freshman and sophomore seasons at Cincinnati coincided with Mack’s final two years guiding the Musketeers.</p>
<p>CLUTCH MOMENT FROM CROSS:</p>
<p>In addition to his late 3-pointer, Cross converted two free throws with nine seconds left after Jones’ field goal put the Cardinals again within a four-point deficit.</p>
<p>TIP-INS: Miami shot 49% from the field against a Louisville defense which allowed 38% prior to Saturday. &#8230; Four airballs early in the first half forewarned the Cardinals’ struggles. “We started off the game as if we didn’t know how to run our offense and our defense was just as bad,” Mack said.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Louisville: The Cardinals open a three-game homestand against Florida State on Monday night.</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes will visit Syracuse Tuesday night.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">833622</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wong, Timberlake lead Miami past North Carolina State 65-59</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/wong-timberlake-lead-miami-past-north-carolina-state-65-59/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=827091</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Isaiah Wong scored 24 points and Earl Timberlake had six of his career-high 13 in the last 68 seconds as Miami...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Isaiah Wong scored 24 points and Earl Timberlake had six of his career-high 13 in the last 68 seconds as Miami finally won a close game, defeating North Carolina State 64-59 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Wong had a layup in an 8-0 run inside the last four minutes that put the Hurricanes, who lost their previous three games by a total of five points, ahead 58-54. Timberlake capped the run from the foul line with 1:08 to play.</p>
<p>The Wolfpack got a quick 3-pointer from Thomas Allen in the right corner, his fourth, to make it a one-point game. Miami ran the clock down before Wong missed a layup but Timberlake grabbed the rebound and slammed it home. Seconds later he grabbed a Wolfpack miss and was fouled, the freshman calmly making two at the line for a 62-57 lead.</p>
<p>Wong added free throws after N.C. State missed for a 14-3 closing run before DJ Funderburk scored at the buzzer.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes (5-5, 1-4 Atlantic Coast Conference) were coming off losses of 80-78 to Virginia Tech, 66-65 to Clemson and 67-65 to North Carolina.</p>
<p>Allen scored 14 points to lead the Wolfpack (6-3, 2-2), who played their fourth tight game. Funderburk scored 12 and matched his career-high with 11 rebounds and Devon Daniels added 11. N.C. State&#8217;s last three games were decided by a total of 10 points, including two wins.</p>
<p>Miami led 32-31 after a tight first half. Until the closing seconds, Miami&#8217;s biggest lead in the second half came after Wong and Timberlake combined for a 7-0 run for a 40-36 lead. In the middle of the half, Daniels and Funderburk combined for 10 points in an 11-0 that gave N.C. State it&#8217;s biggest second-half lead at 51-45.</p>
<p>In the second half, Miami shot 52% and made 9 of 12 free throws while the Wolfpack shot 35.5% and was 2 of 6 from the line.</p>
<p>Miami goes to Boston College on Tuesday. N.C. State is scheduled to play at Florida State on Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">827091</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami hires Travaris Robinson as defensive backs coach</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-hires-travaris-robinson-as-defensive-backs-coach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 18:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=826891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Miami native Travaris Robinson is coming home. Robinson was hired Saturday as the new defensive backs coach at Miami, the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Miami native Travaris Robinson is coming home.</p>
<p>Robinson was hired Saturday as the new defensive backs coach at Miami, the first move in what is expected to be a flurry of hires on that side of the ball by the Hurricanes in the coming days. Robinson played at Auburn and spent the last decade in the SEC — coaching at Florida, Auburn and most recently South Carolina as defensive coordinator for five seasons.</p>
<p>He wasn’t retained by the Gamecocks when they hired Shane Beamer as their new head coach last month.</p>
<p>“We are excited to welcome Travaris and his family back to Miami,” Hurricanes coach Manny Diaz said. “He is a proven defensive coach and an excellent recruiter who will be an outstanding addition to our coaching staff.”</p>
<p>Robinson’s hire is contingent on the completion of a background check, which is standard at most schools including the University of Miami.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes were 67th in total defense and 51st in scoring defense out of 127 teams at the FBS level nationally this season, and the way the season finished certainly suggested changes would be coming. Miami allowed school records of 554 rushing yards and 778 total yards in a <a href="https://apnews.com/article/college-football-syracuse-orange-football-miami-football-michael-carter-9fc4601ba93659b1c896157548c74464">62-26 loss to North Carolina</a> last month in the regular-season finale — a loss that kept the Hurricanes from making the Orange Bowl — and yielded 37 more points in a <a href="https://apnews.com/article/college-football-brennan-presley-oklahoma-football-spencer-sanders-bfbf35f57e945cebda88146777f705ef">Cheez-It Bowl loss to Oklahoma State</a>.</p>
<p>Miami already has seen the departure of co-defensive coordinator and safeties coach Ephraim Banda this offseason; he took a job at Utah State. Safety Bubba Bolden has announced that he is not entering the NFL draft and will remain at Miami in 2021, and there are other defensive draft-eligible players who are also weighing returns to the Hurricanes.</p>
<p>Robinson, 39, was born in Miami and played four years of high school football at Miami Coral Park High, where he was All-State as a defensive back and wide receiver. He has also coached at Western Kentucky, Southern Mississippi and Texas Tech.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">826891</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami QB D&#8217;Eriq King tore knee ligament, plans 2021 return</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-qb-deriq-king-tore-knee-ligament-plans-2021-return/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 18:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=818209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Miami quarterback D’Eriq King tore the anterior cruciate ligament in his right knee during the Hurricanes’ loss this week in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Miami quarterback D’Eriq King tore the anterior cruciate ligament in his right knee during the Hurricanes’ loss this week in the Cheez-It Bowl.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes said Thursday an MRI a day earlier confirmed the tear. King will have surgery in the coming days and the Hurricanes expect him to be ready for training camp — which will begin about seven months after the ligament is repaired.</p>
<p>Miami’s opener next season is scheduled for Sept. 4 in Atlanta against Alabama.</p>
<p>“I’ll be fine,” King wrote on Twitter in a message to well-wishers.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes went 8-3 this season, the best record among the seven FBS schools in the state of Florida. King, in first season at Miami following his transfer from Houston, was a big reason for that. He started every game for the Hurricanes, passing for 2,686 yards and 23 touchdowns while also rushing for 538 yards and four more scores.</p>
<p>King completed 64.1 percent of his passes, the second-best single-season completion percentage for any Miami quarterback and one that qualifies him as, for now anyway, the most accurate passer in Hurricanes history.</p>
<p>“We are obviously disappointed for D’Eriq but we know he is in great hands with our medical staff,” Miami coach Manny Diaz said in a message posted to social media. “D’Eriq is the leader of this football team and we know that he will approach his rehabilitation with the same tenacity that he has approached every facet of his game since he arrived on our campus.”</p>
<p>King announced last week he will not enter the upcoming NFL draft and would return to Miami for a sixth season of college football. He spent parts of four seasons at Houston before electing to end his 2019 season after four games, preserving his final year of eligibility and ultimately deciding to use it at Miami.</p>
<p>The NCAA is allowing players to extend their eligibility for another year in response to the coronavirus pandemic and how it shortened some seasons or kept some athletes from their sports entirely. That’s why King can return in 2021.</p>
<p>“We can’t wait to see him back on the field leading our team in August,” Diaz said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">818209</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091020-deriq-king.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091020-deriq-king.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091020-deriq-king.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">091020 d&#039;eriq king</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sanders, Oklahoma State beat Miami 37-34 in Cheez-It Bowl</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/sanders-oklahoma-state-beat-miami-37-34-in-cheez-it-bowl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 03:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=816673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Spencer Sanders threw for 305 yards and four touchdowns, and Oklahoma State held off No. 18 Miami for a 37-34 victory...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Spencer Sanders threw for 305 yards and four touchdowns, and Oklahoma State held off No. 18 Miami for a 37-34 victory in the Cheez-It Bowl on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Brennan Presley caught three of Sanders&#8217; TD passes, finishing with six receptions for 118 yards. Sanders also led the Cowboys with 45 yards rushing.</p>
<p>Oklahoma State (8-3) scored on its first three possessions while jumping out to a 21-0 lead. Sanders threw TD passes of 30 and 32 yards to Presley, and LD Brown had a 2-yard touchdown run.</p>
<p>Miami (8-3) got on the board in the second quarter when D’Eriq King threw a 10-yard touchdown pass to Brevin Jordan. But King left the game with a right knee injury with 4:06 remaining in the first half.</p>
<p>Backup quarterback N’Kosi Perry threw for 228 yards and two touchdowns for Miami. Perry&#8217;s 5-yard TD pass to Michael Harley helped the Hurricanes close to 37-34 with 5:39 left.</p>
<p>Perry misfired on six of his final nine passes and his 6-yard pass to Michael Redding III was not enough to convert a fourth-and-9 with under two minutes remaining.</p>
<p>Miami outgained Oklahoma State 512-418.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Oklahoma State used a near perfect performance from Sanders to earn its fourth bowl victory in the past five years. Sanders was 27-of-40 passing and did not commit a turnover.</p>
<p>Miami will finish the season with back-to-back losses. It has lost five consecutive bowl games and 11 of its past 12.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Oklahoma State was unranked coming into the game, but likely will make the final Top 25 of the season.</p>
<p>Miami, ranked No. 18, could be out of the final rankings after consecutive losses.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Oklahoma State should have a dynamic offense with Spencer returning at quarterback when it opens next season against Missouri State.</p>
<p>Miami has to hope King’s injury isn’t serious enough to keep him out of spring practice because the Hurricanes open next season against Alabama in Atlanta.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">816673</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>QB D&#8217;Eriq King says he&#8217;s returning to Hurricanes in 2021</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/qb-deriq-king-says-hes-returning-to-hurricanes-in-2021/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=812593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — D’Eriq King transferred to Miami with the hope of competing for championships. He’s staying with the same hope for 2021....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — D’Eriq King transferred to Miami with the hope of competing for championships.</p>
<p>He’s staying with the same hope for 2021.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes’ quarterback — who came to Miami with the intention of spending just one year at the school — announced Saturday he is returning for another senior season, taking advantage of the NCAA rule that essentially gave all college athletes another year of eligibility in response to the hardships caused by the coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s always been a dream of mine to play in the NFL,” said King, who studied his 2021 draft options and where he would likely be selected. “But it&#8217;s going to be there.”</p>
<p>His decision likely means Miami will enter next season as a top contender in the Atlantic Coast Conference, the league that sent Clemson and Notre Dame into this season’s College Football Playoff.</p>
<p>“I think the sky&#8217;s the limit,” King said. “I think we can be really, really good next year.”</p>
<p>King helped Miami engineer a major turnaround this season. The Hurricanes never reached the AP Top 25 last season and sputtered their way to a 6-7 finish; they appeared in all 15 of the AP regular-season rankings this year, reaching as high as No. 7 nationally in early October.</p>
<p>King has completed 201 of 316 passes this season for 2,573 yards, 22 touchdowns and has only thrown five interceptions. King is also Miami’s second-leading rusher so far this season, with 520 yards and four more touchdowns on the ground.</p>
<p>There have been only two instances in the last three seasons where a quarterback threw for 400 yards and ran for 100 yards in the same game — and King is responsible for both. He had a 419-yard passing, 132-yard rushing game for Houston in 2018 and a 430-yard passing, 105-yard rushing game for Miami this season against North Carolina State.</p>
<p>Yet his assessment of his play in 2020? “It wasn&#8217;t to my standard,” King said.</p>
<p>At his current pace, King’s 63.6% completion percentage would rank as Miami’s all-time best, exceeding the record of 62.3% that Bernie Kosar has held since 1984. King’s percentage rate this season, for now, is the second-best single-year mark in Miami history; Jacory Harris completed 65% of his throws in 2011.</p>
<p>“Hearing that we&#8217;re getting our guy back, our leader, that&#8217;s huge for us,” tight end Will Mallory said. “A guy like that, it really elevates this team to a different level.”</p>
<p>No. 18 Miami (8-2) closes this season Tuesday in the Cheez-It Bowl against Oklahoma State (7-3). A win would ensure that the Hurricanes finish the season ranked for just the third time in the last eight years — and King coming back gives Miami a real shot of entering next year as a Top 10 team for what would be just the second time since 2005.</p>
<p>Miami coach Manny Diaz said this month he thought King would benefit from a return, and being in the same offensive system in two consecutive years for the first time.</p>
<p>“D&#8217;Eriq King has now chosen us twice,” Diaz said. “He certainly had a lot of options last year and I&#8217;m certain any school that he would have chosen at this time last year would have had a really good season.”</p>
<p>Next season will be King’s sixth in college — a very unusual quirk. He appeared in nine games for Houston in 2016, 10 more there in 2017, 11 for the Cougars in 2018 and four in 2019 before announcing that he was forgoing the rest of that season’s eligibility and would seek a transfer. Playing in only four games last season made it possible for him to remain eligible for a fifth year, and the NCAA rule regarding the pandemic gave him the option of extending his career once again.</p>
<p>King suggested this month that staying was a real possibility. And now it&#8217;s official, the last major decision in a year that started with him choosing Miami, then found him coming to grips with the sudden death of his father, finding a home with the Hurricanes and even battling COVID-19 this season.</p>
<p>“There&#8217;s a lot of pressure being the quarterback at the University of Miami,” King said. “But I like that.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">812593</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/012020-deriq-king-transfer.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/012020-deriq-king-transfer.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/012020-deriq-king-transfer.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">012020 deriq king transfer</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wong, Walker lead Miami over Jacksonville 73-64</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/wong-walker-lead-miami-over-jacksonville-73-64/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 01:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=804077</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Isaiah Wong scored a season-high 25 points, Anthony Walker added career highs with 18 points and 10 rebounds, and Miami...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Isaiah Wong scored a season-high 25 points, Anthony Walker added career highs with 18 points and 10 rebounds, and Miami beat Jacksonville 73-64 on Saturday.</p>
<p>Jacksonville (6-3) cut a 14-point deficit early in the second half and pulled to 68-64 with 1:23 remaining, but then missed its last two shots and committed a turnover.</p>
<p>Wong hit three 3-pointers and scored 15 points in the first half, and finished 9-of-18 shooting with nine rebounds. Walker made 5 of 10 field goals and all eight of his free throws, and matched a career best with three blocks. Walker also had a double-double (12 points, 10 rebounds) in Wednesday&#8217;s loss to Pittsburgh.</p>
<p>Highly touted freshman Earl Timberlake returned from an ankle injury to make his season debut and scored 10 of his 12 points in the second half for Miami (4-2).</p>
<p>Dontarius James, a junior transfer from Xavier, made five 3-pointers and scored 19 points to lead Jacksonville, but fouled out with 7:55 remaining. Bryce Workman added 14 points. The Dolphins were outrebounded 49-26 and made just 4 of 10 free throws.</p>
<p>Miami coach Jim Larranaga is now tied with John Wooden with 664 career victories, 36th on the all-time wins list. The Hurricanes are 112-37 (.752) at the Watsco Center in Larranaga’s nine seasons.</p>
<p>Larranaga said he expects injured starters Chris Lykes and Kameron McGusty to return for the Hurricanes&#8217; next game Dec. 29 at Virginia Tech.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">804077</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lykes scores 20, Hurricanes beat Stetson 82-60</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/lykes-scores-20-hurricanes-beat-stetson-82-60/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 23:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=791992</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Chris Lykes made 3 of 5 shots from 3-point range and scored 20 points to help Miami beat Stetson 82-60...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Chris Lykes made 3 of 5 shots from 3-point range and scored 20 points to help Miami beat Stetson 82-60 on Friday night.</p>
<p>Lykes went to the locker room midway through the second half with a sprained ankle and did not return. Matt Cross, who added 11 points, also left the game late with a sprained ankle.</p>
<p>Isaiah Wong added 17 points and 12 rebounds for his second career double-double and Kameron McGusty scored 11 points for the Hurricanes (2-0).</p>
<p>Chase Johnston had 19 points, including five 3-pointers, and Mahamadou Diawara added 14 points for the Hatters (0-2). Johnston made four of his 3s in the final 3:35, after Miami had its largest lead at 76-45.</p>
<p>Stetson had a 15-4 run to cut a 12-point deficit to 28-27 late in the first half. The Hurricanes responded by scoring the final 12 points of the period and opened the second half with nine straight to lead 49-27 at the 18-minute mark.</p>
<p>The game was originally scheduled to be both teams’ season opener on Nov. 25 and was postponed due to positive COVID-19 tests in the Stetson program.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">791992</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 9 Miami returns to field in newly scheduled trip to Duke</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-9-miami-returns-to-field-in-newly-scheduled-trip-to-duke/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 19:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=790574</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ninth-ranked Miami is finally set to play again. The Hurricanes travel to Duke on Saturday night for their first game since beating Virginia Tech on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ninth-ranked Miami is finally set to play again.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes travel to Duke on Saturday night for their first game since beating Virginia Tech on Nov. 14. It’s the latest among multiple changes to the Atlantic Coast Conference schedule for the Hurricanes, who had spent recent weeks dealing with positive COVID-19 tests and quarantines.</p>
<p>“These kids want to play. They want to finish the season,” Miami coach Manny Diaz said. “You don’t ever know &#8230; with what we went through (with the virus) and what you see going on around the country.”</p>
<p>Miami (7-1, 6-1 ACC) was set to visit Wake Forest on Saturday, but the Demon Deacons recently paused football activities due to their own coronavirus concerns. The ACC revised the schedule Sunday for Duke to host Miami instead of Florida State this weekend.</p>
<p>Miami is trying to keep alive its slim hopes of reaching the ACC title game. The Hurricanes must win out and see Clemson lose at Virginia Tech this weekend for Miami to meet No. 2 Notre Dame.</p>
<p>It’s easy to see how Miami might not be razor-sharp Saturday night, too, considering it&#8217;s had essentially two weeks away from football amid coronavirus issues along with players having exams this week.</p>
<p>“The players have to understand that there’s adversity, more of a difference in preparation for this game than any other game that they’ll ever play or that I’ve ever been a part of,” Diaz said.</p>
<p>Like Miami, the Blue Devils (2-7, 1-7) played just twice in November. Their Nov. 21 game against Wake Forest was canceled amid the Demon Deacons’ combination of positive tests, quarantines and injuries. Duke lost 56-33 at Georgia Tech last weekend.</p>
<p>“We’ve been healthy all year, we’ve been available,” Duke coach David Cutcliffe said. “And I think that’s part of what’s happened: a lot of people have had a lot of issues with COVID-19. So we’re up and ready, and our team enjoys the challenges and the opportunities to play.”</p>
<p>Some other things to know about Saturday’s Miami-Duke game:</p>
<p>TURNOVER TROUBLES</p>
<p>Miami could get several chances to break out its turnover chain considering Duke has been the nation’s worst team at protecting the football. The Blue Devils have lost 30 turnovers, at least six more than any other Bowl Subdivision team.</p>
<p>BACK AGAIN</p>
<p>The elimination of divisions for this season created some ACC schedule quirks, and adding this game is just another example.</p>
<p>By sending Miami to Duke this year, it raises the chance that the Hurricanes will go to Durham in three consecutive seasons &#8212; they lost there last year in their regular-season finale and the current grid for the 2021 schedule has Miami visiting again.</p>
<p>Still, it’s not unheard of; Virginia played at Miami in 2019, went back this season and is slotted to again next fall.</p>
<p>TOUTING KING</p>
<p>In a rare step for Miami, the Hurricanes are openly campaigning for quarterback D’Eriq King in the Heisman Trophy race. The school has even added a section devoted to King’s Heisman hopes on its website, the first time a player has gotten such a push by Miami officials.</p>
<p>Miami hasn’t had a top-three Heisman finisher since Ken Dorsey was third in 2001.</p>
<p>DECEMBER DATES</p>
<p>This is the second regular-season game for Duke in December in the last 59 seasons; the other in that span was a 59-31 loss at Clemson on Dec. 1, 2001. That game was to have been played in September and was rescheduled after the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks that year.</p>
<p>The last December home game for Duke was Dec. 2, 1961, a 37-13 win over Notre Dame.</p>
<p>Miami’s last December regular-season contest was Dec. 4, 2004, a 16-10 home loss to Virginia Tech in a game that decided that season’s ACC championship.</p>
<p>SCHEDULE SHUFFLE</p>
<p>Miami hosts North Carolina on Dec. 12 followed by Georgia Tech on Dec. 19, though that game won&#8217;t be played if the Hurricanes qualify for the ACC championship game.</p>
<p>Duke now visits Florida State on Dec. 12.</p>
<p>“Just due to all this COVID going on, you really don&#8217;t know who you&#8217;re going to play, especially towards the end with all the cancellations that&#8217;s going on,&#8221; Duke receiver Jarett Garner said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">790574</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cooper City goalie stays local committing to UMs soccer team</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/cooper-city-goalie-stays-local-to-commit-to-ums-soccer-team/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 20:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Broward]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=788356</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When it comes to South Florida signing days, it&#8217;s usually all about the boys that play under the Friday night lights, but girls play too,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to South Florida signing days, it&#8217;s usually all about the boys that play under the Friday night lights, but girls play too, just on a different field.</p>
<p>For Skylah Klein, choosing where she wanted to go to college was an easy decision.</p>
<p>She made her school choice the first week of her freshman year of high school, making her official signing for the University of Miami just a formality.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a really easy decision because Miami was just everything I pictured for my future,&#8221; said Klein. &#8220;To be able to do that and go there and verbally committing that early on was really exciting.&#8221;</p>
<p>Her father, Jeffery Klein, is also happy with her choice.</p>
<p>&#8220;Being 30 miles from her mother&#8217;s chicken soup, that&#8217;s an absolute recipe for success,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>She is listed as one of the top 150 players in the country.</p>
<p>When she&#8217;s not on the field or in the gym training for her club teams, the goalkeeper enjoys spending quality time with her family and friends.</p>
<p>7News was there when she signed for the team while at her home in Cooper City.</p>
<p>&#8220;To be able to have my family and close friends by my side as I signed those papers is a really exciting moment and it&#8217;s something that I know I&#8217;ll remember and cherish forever,&#8221; said Klein.</p>
<p>Boasting an above 4.0 GPA, Klein is goal-oriented in every way.</p>
<p>The Canes are getting a true warrior to mind the net in Coral Gables.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s something nobody else is going to get this year in 2020, that&#8217;s for sure,&#8221; said goalkeeper coach Giuseppe Weller. &#8220;I just know with her caliber of training, UM is going to get something big.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m really excited and looking forward to going with the rest of commits in my class and to help change that program,&#8221; said Klein. &#8220;We&#8217;re very excited.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">788356</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/skylah-klein-e1606766449609.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/44972569-05a7-4004-83ba-29cf7d1e983e/751b425c-62fc-4ef6-9dc4-5b674aa22b29/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615220006~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/44972569-05a7-4004-83ba-29cf7d1e983e/751b425c-62fc-4ef6-9dc4-5b674aa22b29/main.mp4*~hmac=4ccb0e5bc787d6353d14f88ee9b18b79ef48fb20467000d1fd915774a5382c09' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/skylah-klein-e1606766449609.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/skylah-klein-e1606766449609.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">skylah klein</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UM head coach Manny Diaz tests positive for COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/um-head-coach-manny-diaz-tests-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 13:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=782772</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Miami coach Manny Diaz said Friday he is in isolation after testing positive for the coronavirus, and he will work...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) &#x2014; Miami coach Manny Diaz said Friday he is in isolation after testing positive for the coronavirus, and he will work virtually with the No. 12 Hurricanes until he can return to the field.<p>Miami is not scheduled to play again until Dec. 5 at Wake Forest. The Hurricanes had games scheduled for this coming Saturday and Nov. 28, postponing both earlier this week because of coronavirus issues.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/Coach_MannyDiaz/status/1329774836877553666</embed></div><p>&#x201C;I have tested positive for COVID-19. I am currently in isolation and feeling good overall,&#x201D; Diaz tweeted. &#x201C;I will continue to work with our team virtually as we prepare for our next game at Wake Forest.&#x201D;</p><p>The Hurricanes are third in the Atlantic Coast Conference, 7-1 overall and 6-1 in league play. They&#x2019;ve won each of their last four games, including a comeback 25-24 win at Virginia Tech last weekend. Miami was &#x201C;on the brink,&#x201D; Diaz said, of choosing to not play that game because its roster was dealing with so many coronavirus cases.</p><p>&#x201C;We were just really down on the numbers at offensive line,&#x201D; Diaz said after that game, in which his five starting offensive linemen played all 86 snaps without a substitution. &#x201C;And you know, just makes it hard to practice, makes it hard to do anything.&#x201D;</p><p>He becomes the latest major-college football coach to have a positive COVID-19 test released, a list that includes Florida&#x2019;s Dan Mullen, Florida State&#x2019;s Mike Norvell, Purdue&#x2019;s Jeff Brohm, Arizona&#x2019;s Kevin Sumlin and Kansas&#x2019; Les Miles. Alabama coach Nick Saban also tested positive, but did not miss a game after that result was later deemed false.</p><p>Earlier this week, Diaz said he believes the coronavirus numbers nationally &#x201C;are really, really getting to a bad place.&#x201D; The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said more than 1 million coronavirus cases have been diagnosed in the U.S. in the past week alone, numbers that &#x2014; when combined with soaring hospitalization rates &#x2014; prompted the CDC to urge Americans to curtail Thanksgiving travel and not partake in large gatherings with people from outside their household.</p><p>&#x201C;What we know is we don&#x2019;t have a coronavirus-in-college-football problem,&#x201D; Diaz said Monday. &#x201C;We have a coronavirus-in-America problem.&#x201D;</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">782772</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/manny-diaz-e1605879415397.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/21b2a099-fa6d-4f05-bcbd-a59c36621e24/72b1d510-95f5-4a74-ac2b-592fcadd807d/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219930~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/21b2a099-fa6d-4f05-bcbd-a59c36621e24/72b1d510-95f5-4a74-ac2b-592fcadd807d/main.mp4*~hmac=9fc5d3233c7da9323665b6f3f2df7be3aedbd710de36981acf6028875be41251' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/manny-diaz-e1605879415397.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/11/manny-diaz-e1605879415397.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">manny diaz</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 University of Miami football games rescheduled due to COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/3-university-of-miami-football-games-rescheduled-due-to-covid-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 22:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=780112</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Three University of Miami football games have been rescheduled after the program reported positive COVID-19 tests. The Atlantic Coast Conference announced Monday that Miami&#8217;s home...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three University of Miami football games have been rescheduled after the program reported positive COVID-19 tests.</p>
<p>The Atlantic Coast Conference announced Monday that Miami&#8217;s home game against Georgia Tech on Nov. 21 and its game at Wake Forest on Nov. 28 will be rescheduled for December.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are disappointed that we will not be able to play the next two weeks as scheduled, but this decision was made in the best interests of the health and safety of all teams,&#8221; Director of Athletics Blake James said. &#8220;The health and safety of our student-athletes is always our top priority, and we will continue to follow the conference&#8217;s protocols in order to safely and responsibly return to play.&#8221;</p>
<p>The first of the Hurricanes&#8217; last three regular season games will be played on Dec. 5, when the team travels to Wake Forest.</p>
<p>From there, the team will host the University of North Carolina at Hard Rock Stadium on Dec. 12.</p>
<p>According to the ACC, the Hurricanes&#8217; game against Georgia Tech will be played on Dec. 19 &#8220;if Miami is not in the ACC Football Championship Game, and if the result of the Georgia Tech at Miami game would not directly impact the determination of which two teams play in the league championship game.&#8221;</p>
<p>The members of the Hurricanes&#8217; football program who tested positive for COVID-19 have entered into quarantine, officials said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">780112</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/02/170209_university_of_miami_um_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/02/170209_university_of_miami_um_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/02/170209_university_of_miami_um_sign.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170209_university_of_miami_um_sign</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hurricanes rally behind King, D to be beat VTech 25-24</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/hurricanes-rally-behind-king-d-to-be-beat-vtech-25-24/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 22:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=779148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BLACKSBURG, Va. (AP) — After coming precariously close to not being able to play Virginia Tech because of COVID-19 issues, No. 9 Miami came away...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BLACKSBURG, Va. (AP) — After coming precariously close to not being able to play Virginia Tech because of COVID-19 issues, No. 9 Miami came away with one of its gutsiest victories of the season.</p>
<p>D’Eriq King threw for 255 yards and a touchdown and ran for a score, rallying the Hurricanes to a 25-24 victory over Virginia Tech on Saturday.</p>
<p>Miami announced it had 13 players unavailable before the game, including three starters and several offensive linemen. There were 15 games called off this week across major college football because of COVID-19, the most of any week both by number and percentage of the schedule.</p>
<p>Miami-Virginia Tech was nearly No. 16.</p>
<p>&#8220;We were on the brink,” Miami coach Manny Diaz said. “The players’ attitude was the most telling. They wanted to play. We were right on the brink at some position groups as to whether we could function as a team.</p>
<p>“We brought the team, and the players came here to win the game. I told them I thought they won the game on Friday with their mentality and their attitude, with all the things we had to go through this week.”</p>
<p>The Hurricanes (7-1, 6-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) rallied from an 11-point, third-quarter deficit to win their fourth consecutive game and stay very much alive for a spot in the ACC championship game.</p>
<p>“I just think part of the way you do it is to not panic,” Diaz said. “You don&#8217;t believe you have to play perfectly. You just got to find a way to get the job done.”</p>
<p>Miami scored the game’s final 12 points and held the Hokies (4-4, 4-3 ACC) scoreless on their final five possessions.</p>
<p>“It’s definitely a lot of positive energy and a lot of belief in the locker room right now,” Miami defensive end Jaelan Phillips said. “Obviously, you don’t want to have tight games like that every week, but a win is a win, and I think every week we’re becoming stronger as a team.”</p>
<p>King guided the ’Canes on two long second-half scoring marches. A 13-play, 75-yard drive ended with Cam’Ron Harris’ 6-yard touchdown run, and cut the lead to 24-19 with 1:27 left in the third quarter. Miami failed to convert a 2-point conversion.</p>
<p>Miami put together a 10-play, 82-yard drive that ended with King throwing a dart to Mark Pope for a 36-yard touchdown to take a 25-24 lead with 5:59 left in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>King, who rushed for a 10-yard touchdown in the second quarter, completed 24 of 38.</p>
<p>Hendon Hooker paced Virginia Tech, throwing for 201 yards and rushing for 53 yards and a touchdown.</p>
<p>“I hurt for them,” Virginia Tech coach Justin Fuente said of his players. “They came up short today, but it wasn’t for a lack of preparation. It wasn’t for a lack of effort. It wasn’t for a lack of guys caring about each other and guys being selfless. I’m hurting for them because they were so close to getting what they desperately wanted.”</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAYS</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes played well on defense, despite missing a couple of starters. Miami held the Hokies to a season-low 160 yards rushing and sacked Hooker six times, with Phillips (4.5 tackles for loss, including 2.5 sacks) providing a lot of the pressure.</p>
<p>“Shoutout to the defense,” King said. “They played great all day, and I think the offense made plays when we had to, and that’s always good.”</p>
<p>Virginia Tech: The Hokies have lost two straight and three of their past four as they struggle to sustain drives in the second half. Their final five drives ended with three punts, an interception, and on downs. The Hokies need to win two of their final three games to become bowl eligible for the 28th consecutive season.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Miami will remain in the top 10 of the Associated Press poll and may jump a couple of spots pending the outcomes of other games.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami: The ’Canes host Georgia Tech next Saturday.</p>
<p>Virginia Tech: The Hokies travel to Pittsburgh — if the Panthers are ready to play. Pitt&#8217;s game Saturday against Georgia Tech was postponed because both teams were having issues with COVID-19.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">779148</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>D’Eriq King leads Hurricanes to comeback win over NC State</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/deriq-king-leads-hurricanes-to-comeback-win-over-nc-state/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=774676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — D’Eriq King threw five touchdown passes, the last a go-ahead 54-yard catch-and-run play with Michael Harley with 2:43 left, and No....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — D’Eriq King threw five touchdown passes, the last a go-ahead 54-yard catch-and-run play with Michael Harley with 2:43 left, and No. 11 Miami rallied to beat North Carolina State 44-41 on Friday night.</p>
<p>Miami (6-1, 5-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) scored the final 13 points to win its third game in a row and match last season&#8217;s victory total under second-year coach Manny Diaz.</p>
<p>King was 31 for 41 for 430 yards and ran for a game-high 105 yards on 15 carries. Harley also had a 20-yard TD catch in the second quarter. He finished with 153 yards on eight receptions.</p>
<p>Zonovan Knight had a 100-yard kickoff return to put NC State (4-3, 4-3) on top in the third quarter. Bailey Hockman was 19 for 28 for 248 yards and two touchdowns for the Wolfpack. He had a pass intercepted by DJ Ivey after Miami’s final touchdown.</p>
<p>Knight also had a 1-yard TD run in the third quarter.</p>
<p>NC State padded its lead to 41-31 on Christopher Dunn’s 53-yard field goal on the first play of the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Josh Borregales kicked three field goals, connecting from 38 and 22 yards in the fourth quarter. The latter came with 6:12 remaining after the Hurricanes were within a half-yard of the end zone before a fourth-down penalty.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes, coming off a 19-14 home victory over Virginia, had a 21-14 lead less than 16 1/2 minutes into the game. NC State led at halftime on the strength of Hockman’s 9-yard touchdown pass to Cary Angeline with 2:49 left.</p>
<p>Miami was missing 11 players, including starting left tackle John Campbell Jr. and starting tight end Brevin Jordan.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes outscored their first six opponents by a combined margin of 57-23 in the second quarter. But NC State’s 10-7 edge produced a 24-21 lead, marking only the second halftime deficit of the season for the Hurricanes.</p>
<p>NC State: Angeline, a redshirt senior, has caught at least one touchdown pass in five of the Wolfpack’s games. NC State won the other four games.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Miami could move back into the Top 10 after four weeks outside of that territory.</p>
<p>With a victory, NC State would have been a candidate to climb back into the rankings. The Wolfpack spent one week in the Top 25 following a three-game winning streak before dropping out with a loss to then-No. 14 North Carolina.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami: At Virginia Tech next Saturday.</p>
<p>NC State: Host Florida State next Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">774676</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami forward Waardenburg to miss season with foot injury</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-forward-waardenburg-to-miss-season-with-foot-injury/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 17:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=770210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Forward Sam Waardenburg, the Miami Hurricanes&#8217; leading rebounder a year ago, will miss the entire season after injuring his left...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Forward Sam Waardenburg, the Miami Hurricanes&#8217; leading rebounder a year ago, will miss the entire season after injuring his left foot during practice.</p>
<p>He is expected to be sidelined about six months, the Hurricanes said Friday.</p>
<p>The 6-foot-10 Waardenburg has made 35 starts over the past three seasons. Last season he played in 30 games with 24 starts, and averaged 5.9 points and 6.0 rebounds.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">770210</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Hurricanes bench 6 players due to COVID-19 concerns</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-hurricanes-bench-6-players-due-to-covid-19-concerns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 18:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=767438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Several Miami Hurricanes players have been benched after coronavirus concerns spread through the team&#8217;s locker room. Before Saturday&#8217;s game against Virginia, the UM Football program...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several Miami Hurricanes players have been benched after coronavirus concerns spread through the team&#8217;s locker room.</p>
<p>Before Saturday&#8217;s game against Virginia, the UM Football program abruptly benched six Canes players, placing them on the unavailable list.</p>
<p>Although the reason for the late scratches were not disclosed, reports suspected positive COVID-19 tests may have been the cause.</p>
<p>&#8220;2020 has been a year unlike any other, I mean not just with the coronavirus but with everything else that&#8217;s going on,&#8221; said Miami Hurricanes head coach Manny Diaz.</p>
<p>On Monday morning on WQAM, Diaz addressed how the pandemic has affected his team.</p>
<p>&#8220;I mean, this is just the reality of 2020, and I know we&#8217;re all fatigued of it. We&#8217;re fatigued of talking about it, and we&#8217;re no different, and I&#8217;m not different, but we can feel it, you know?&#8221; said Diaz. &#8220;The coronavirus is not going away, it is here. You can see the numbers where they&#8217;re at all over the country. I think our players can feel it that it&#8217;s around again, and it&#8217;s more prominent, and we really, really have to be smart and safe here to be able to play this football this last month.&#8221;</p>
<p>Diaz mentioned that if any of his players did test positive, the team&#8217;s coronavirus protocol would align with the university&#8217;s.</p>
<p>&#8220;Those players are quarantined away from the rest of the team, the rest of the student body, and it&#8217;s no different than it would be if it was someone that was here to major in business or any other UM student. We&#8217;re just right along with Dr. Frank&#8217;s policy on any positive tests we have,&#8221; Diaz said.</p>
<p>The six last-minute scratched players were all reportedly freshmen.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">767438</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/manny-diaz.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0f70702c-c702-48e3-8344-e36827a2c3d0/a7dacbc2-67e8-4c16-9036-d34201637c2c/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219987~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/0f70702c-c702-48e3-8344-e36827a2c3d0/a7dacbc2-67e8-4c16-9036-d34201637c2c/main.mp4*~hmac=952f67597b515412767444005ee3d7a99d117d674a77136eb5491511f73d0b49' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/manny-diaz.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/10/manny-diaz.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">manny diaz</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 11 Miami holds off Virginia 19-14, moves to 5-1</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-11-miami-holds-off-virginia-19-14-moves-to-5-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 04:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=766727</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Miami&#8217;s coaching staff sent a clear message to its receivers this week by opening up what was a nine-player competition...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Miami&#8217;s coaching staff sent a clear message to its receivers this week by opening up what was a nine-player competition for three starting spots.</p>
<p>Mike Harley heard them — and came up with the best game of his career.</p>
<p>D’Eriq King threw for 322 yards and a touchdown, Harley had career bests of 10 catches for 170 yards and No. 11 Miami outlasted Virginia 19-14 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>“I think Mike absolutely accepted the challenge,&#8221; Miami coach Manny Diaz said.</p>
<p>Harley&#8217;s big night for Miami (5-1, 4-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) started with a 43-yard touchdown grab on the Hurricanes’ second play from scrimmage. King completed his first nine passes and finished 21 for 30.</p>
<p>Harley said the receivers got a group text early in the week saying nobody was assured of a starting job.</p>
<p>“Me being a senior, being the oldest guy, I just had to step up,&#8221; Harley said.</p>
<p>Don Chaney had a 1-yard rushing touchdown in the fourth for Miami.</p>
<p>Brennan Armstrong, back in the lineup after missing a game with a concussion, completed 16 of 30 passes for 181 yards and two touchdowns for Virginia (1-4, 1-4). It was the fourth straight loss for the Cavaliers, and this marks the first time since 2013 that they’ve played four consecutive games without ever holding a lead.</p>
<p>Armstrong also ran for 91 yards for Virginia.</p>
<p>“It was a really tough game,&#8221; Virginia coach Bronco Mendenhall said. “Those were two teams battling really hard today. &#8230; Miami&#8217;s good. They played well. I thought we played well.&#8221;</p>
<p>The King-to-Harley touchdown came just 28 seconds into the game, the fastest TD to open a game by Miami since Tracy Howard ran back an interception 19 yards for a score just six seconds into the Hurricanes’ game against Virginia on Nov. 23, 2013.</p>
<p>That was the first of eight touchdowns that day, Miami eventually winning 45-26.</p>
<p>This one was much different.</p>
<p>Points had been a rare commodity the past two Miami vs. Virginia games — the Cavaliers winning one 16-13, the Hurricanes winning the other 17-9 — and this one followed suit. Virginia tied the game at 7-7 on its first drive, with Tony Poljan hauling in a 2-yard scoring pass from Armstrong.</p>
<p>From there, the slog began. The teams combined for six points on their next 13 possessions, the Hurricanes leading 10-7 at the half after a 32-yard field goal by Jose Borregales with 1:02 left until intermission and stretching the lead to 13-7 when he connected again from 20 yards out with 3:47 left in the third.</p>
<p>“They were having a hard time stopping us at times &#8230; but the score was always tight,” Diaz said. “At halftime we had to kind of readjust our mentality and say, ‘Did you not expect it to be this way?’ We want to be OK with it being difficult to win.”</p>
<p>Chaney’s 1-yard run with 12:04 left made it 19-7, that touchdown coming 64 plays after Miami’s first of the night.</p>
<p>Armstrong took off on a 32-yard fourth-down run in the fourth quarter to extend a drive, and one play later found Ra’Shaun Henry with a 35-yard pass that got the Cavaliers to 19-14 with 5:27 left.</p>
<p>Virginia, however, was out of time-outs at that point and Miami punted the ball away with only 23 seconds left. The Cavaliers took all of them in the second half with their defense on the field, the last of them when Miami tried a two-point conversion after Chaney&#8217;s score.</p>
<p>“Had to use it, and glad I did because we stopped the two-point play which did give us a chance,&#8221; Mendenhall said. “But that was not by design nor was it good time management, nor was it good communication by my staff.&#8221;</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Virginia: The Cavaliers had a chance to take the lead in the second quarter, but what would have been a 24-yard TD pass by Armstrong was washed out by an ineligible-receiver-downfield penalty and the Cavaliers wound up missing a field goal. “That changes the game,&#8221; Mendenhall said of the touchdown coming off the board.</p>
<p>Miami: Harley’s previous career-bests were seven catches (done twice, most recently the rout of Florida State earlier this season) and 116 yards against Louisville last year. Among his highlights: catches of 20, 28, 28 again and the 43-yarder for a score.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>The Hurricanes will remain in the AP Top 25 for a seventh consecutive week, the school’s longest such run since 2017. With No. 8 Penn State losing to Indiana, it would seem possible for Miami to return to the Top 10.</p>
<p>CARTER TARGETING</p>
<p>Miami safety Amari Carter was ejected for targeting on the Hurricanes’ first defensive snap of the game, marking the second time this season and fourth in his career that he’s been sent off early for that infraction.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Virginia: Hosts North Carolina on Oct. 31.</p>
<p>Miami: At North Carolina State on Friday, Nov. 6.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">766727</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>King&#8217;s 4 TD passes lead No. 13 Miami past Pittsburgh, 31-19</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/kings-4-td-passes-lead-no-13-miami-past-pittsburgh-31-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=762426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Miami avoided the post-Clemson letdown and now can set its sight on remaining in the conference championship picture. A week...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Miami avoided the post-Clemson letdown and now can set its sight on remaining in the conference championship picture.</p>
<p>A week after a 42-17 road loss to the top-ranked Tigers, the No. 13 Hurricanes beat Pittsburgh 31-19 on Saturday.</p>
<p>D’Eriq King threw four touchdowns, including two to Will Mallory, to lead the Hurricanes (4-1, 3-1 Atlantic Coast Conference), who never trailed in this one.</p>
<p>“We were disappointed and a little bit angry coming off last week,” Miami coach Manny Diaz said. “That’s a difficult situation — you have a noon kickoff, not a super juicy environment because of the restrictions that we have and against a team with a sense of desperation. For those guys to go out there and know that it was not going to be an easy game regardless of your mental mindset says a lot about the leadership of our football team.”</p>
<p>The Panthers (3-3, 2-3) lost their third consecutive game and were without senior quarterback Kenny Pickett, who suffered an ankle injury against Boston College last week. Entering Saturday&#8217;s game, Pickett led the nation with 1,389 passing yards but didn’t travel with the team to South Florida.</p>
<p>Redshirt freshman Joey Yellen replaced Pickett, completing 22 of 46 passes for 277 yards and a touchdown.</p>
<p>“You didn’t know what to expect; I thought he played solid,” Pitt coach Pat Narduzzi said of Yellen. “I thought he put the ball in people’s hands to make plays. We’ve got to help him out.”</p>
<p>Alex Kessman kicked four field goals for the Panthers and became Pitt&#8217;s all-time leader with 57. Kessman surpassed Chris Blewitt, who had 55 field goals from 2013-16.</p>
<p>Pitt rallied from a 21-6 deficit with 10 unanswered points on Kessman’s record-setting third field goal and Yellen’s 1-yard touchdown pass to Daniel Moraga early in the third quarter. Marcus Williams’ 38-yard interception return to the Miami 1 set up Moraga’s score.</p>
<p>But Miami regained its double-digit advantage on King’s 45-yard touchdown pass to Mallory.</p>
<p>“As far as today, I’m super proud of those guys,” King said. “We put Clemson behind us and tried to put a W anyway we could. We knew we had a tough challenge in back-to-back weeks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Kessman’s fourth conversion with 31 seconds remaining in the third quarter made it 28-19 before Jose Borregales gave Miami another double-digit cushion with his 37-yard field goal late in the fourth quarter. The drive drained 7:11 off the clock and prevented the Panthers from making a late comeback.</p>
<p>“Pitt&#8217;s defense is good every single year,” King said. “They make you earn every single thing.”</p>
<p>The Hurricanes struck first on King’s 35-yard touchdown pass to Cam’Ron Harris midway through the first quarter. King retreated from an attempted draw and found an open Harris down the middle.</p>
<p>King connected with Mallory on a 6-yard score with 6:44 left in the second quarter for a 14-0 lead.</p>
<p>Kessman kicked two field goals late in the second quarter and got the Panthers to within 14-6. Pitt settled for the second field goal after being unable to capitalize on a drive starting at the Miami 12 that was set by Harris Ford’s 25-yard interception return.</p>
<p>King found an open Mike Harley down the right sideline for a 38-yard touchdown pass in Miami’s opening drive of the second half. Harley eluded a Panthers defender before reaching the end zone for his first TD reception of the season.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>The Hurricanes erased the frustrations of the loss at Clemson with quick-strike scores and a defense that allowed 22 yards rushing and forced Pitt to settle for field goals on three possessions inside the red zone.</p>
<p>“Red-zone defense is a mentality, to me that’s where it gets into the culture of your defensive room,” Diaz said. “Really proud of them the way they went down there and never panicked and made them kick field goals.”</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Miami will probably hold steady in the rankings.</p>
<p>MALLORY STEPS UP</p>
<p>With pre-season All-American tight end Brevin Jordan missing the game because of a shoulder injury, Mallory accepted additional responsibilities as his replacement.</p>
<p>“When you got a player like Brevin out for the week, someone’s got to fill those big shoes because he’s a heck of a player,” Mallory said. “Coming in, I hadn’t gotten as many passes this year. I just had to step up.&#8221;</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Pittsburgh: Hosts No. 4 Notre Dame next Saturday.</p>
<p>Miami: Plays its third night home game of the season next Saturday against Virginia.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">762426</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diaz says Hurricanes must shed arrogance, rebound vs Pitt</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/diaz-says-hurricanes-must-shed-arrogance-rebound-vs-pitt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 18:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=761206</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — The competition isn’t as formidable this week for the Miami Hurricanes, and that has their coach concerned. After losing last week at...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — The competition isn’t as formidable this week for the Miami Hurricanes, and that has their coach concerned.</p>
<p>After losing last week at No. 1 Clemson, Miami will try to rebound Saturday against Pittsburgh. The No. 13-ranked Hurricanes are 9 1/2-point favorites, which makes it a game that will test the attitude second-year coach Manny Diaz is trying to instill in Coral Gables.</p>
<p>Diaz said that for too long, the Hurricanes have played with an arrogance they don&#8217;t deserve, a hangover from the era when Miami was a perennial national championship contender.</p>
<p>“We can&#8217;t just think we&#8217;re Miami, and we are more talented than, say, Pitt,” Diaz said. “Our players have been hearing that for many years, regardless of who the head coach has been, and it has not been serving them well. We have to have respect for who we’re playing. That’s the arrogance I’m speaking of.”</p>
<p>REGROUPING</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a bounce-back game for both teams. The Hurricanes (3-1, 2-1 Atlantic Coast Conference) went to Clemson ranked No. 7 and harbored hopes of making a prime-time splash reminiscent of their glory days. Instead, they endured a 42-17 drubbing.</p>
<p>The Panthers (3-2, 2-2) are two points from being undefeated. They lost 30-29 to North Carolina State, and were beaten 31-30 in overtime last week at Boston College.</p>
<p>“We’ve got to win it in the fourth quarter,” coach Pat Narduzzi said. “We’ve got to find a way to finish the darned game.”</p>
<p>Quarterback D’Eriq King, who is in his first season at Miami, said any arrogance that might go along with being favored won&#8217;t be a problem for the Hurricanes.</p>
<p>“I don’t have any doubt in my mind the team will go out there and play super, super hard,” King said. “You’ve got to respect everybody you play. I know how it has been in the past, but I don&#8217;t think this team is even thinking about that.”</p>
<p>THE LINE ON PICKETT</p>
<p>Pitt senior quarterback Kenny Pickett’s coming-out party happened three years ago against the second-ranked Hurricanes when he ran for two scores and threw for another in a 24-14 upset win.</p>
<p>The game remains the highlight of the enigmatic Pickett’s career, but the senior has won teammates over with his toughness. Pickett has carried the ball 45 times this year, many of them coming on scrambles after protection broke down. He briefly went to the sideline each of the past two weeks after taking particularly hard hits.</p>
<p>Narduzzi wants to keep Pickett healthy but has no plans to tell him to stop using his legs.</p>
<p>“He’s going to compete, that’s for sure,” Narduzzi said. “You saw how he came back. He’s tough, and I could tell Kenny to run out of bounds or take a knee. He ain’t taking a knee. That’s not Kenny Pickett.”</p>
<p>ON THE RISE</p>
<p>Junior safety Bubba Bolden has emerged as one of the Hurricanes’ top playmakers, as well as a marathon man. Against Clemson he blocked two field goals, made 10 tackles and forced a fumble.</p>
<p>“He played about 90 snaps Saturday, which is probably a game and half,” Diaz said. “He’s sprinting down the field covering punts. He&#8217;s completely committed to the team.”</p>
<p>Said Bolden: “You’ve just got to go out there and lead. I didn’t let fatigue get to me at all.”</p>
<p>STAYING FRESH</p>
<p>Narduzzi admitted he left the more experienced members of his secondary on the field too long in both losses. The result? A pass defense that began the season looking dominant was instead dominated.</p>
<p>The Panthers have allowed 694 yards passing and seven touchdowns with no interceptions over their last eight-plus quarters.</p>
<p>“We’re going to have to rotate our corners, we’re going to have to keep them fresh, and I did a poor job of making sure that we were doing that,” Narduzzi said.</p>
<p>WEATHER REPORT</p>
<p>The 2020 Hurricanes will play their first day game, and the forecast of humid 85-degree weather — just the sort they practice in — could work to the home team&#8217;s advantage.</p>
<p>“Happy to have a noon kickoff and get to play under the sun,” Diaz said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">761206</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/12/181230_Manny_Diaz.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/12/181230_Manny_Diaz.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2018/12/181230_Manny_Diaz.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">181230_Manny_Diaz</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who&#8217;s Boss? No. 1 Clemson powers past No. 7 Miami 42-17</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/whos-boss-no-1-clemson-powers-past-no-7-miami-42-17/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 03:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=758480</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CLEMSON, S.C. (AP) — Trevor Lawrence threw for three touchdowns and rushed for another as No. 1 Clemson proved once more who&#8217;s boss in the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CLEMSON, S.C. (AP) — Trevor Lawrence threw for three touchdowns and rushed for another as No. 1 Clemson proved once more who&#8217;s boss in the Atlantic Coast Conference with a 42-17 beatdown of seventh-ranked Miami on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Travis Etienne rushed for 149 yards and two scores, including a 72-yard burst down the left sidelines as the Tigers opened 4-0 for a sixth straight season.</p>
<p>This is was billed as an ACC showdown where the Hurricanes (3-1, 2-1 ACC) could prove the swagger had truly returned to “The U.”</p>
<p>Instead, Miami&#8217;s offense was suffocated by the Tigers (3-0 ACC) and held without an offensive touchdown until the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Hurricanes quarterback D&#8217;Eriq King came in alongside Lawrence as the ACC&#8217;s dominant, dynamic playmakers. The Houston transfer, though, was swarmed by Clemson all game and completed just 12 of 28 passes for 121 yards and his first two interceptions of the season.</p>
<p>Miami entered as the ACC leader in offense at 499 yards a game. It was held to 210 and never truly came close to challenging the Tigers.</p>
<p>Clemson got out fast with touchdowns on its first two drives, on tight end Braden Galloway&#8217;s 24-yard catch and a 2-yard run by Etienne.</p>
<p>Etienne, the two-time ACC player of the year who returned for his senior season, became college football&#8217;s all-time leader with a score in his 39th career game. He broke a three-way tie he was in with Florida&#8217;s Tim Tebow and Louisiana Tech&#8217;s Kenneth Dixon.</p>
<p>Another Galloway TD catch, this one from 11 yards, put Clemson ahead 21-3 with 1:14 remaining in the half.</p>
<p>But perhaps Clemson coach Dabo Swinney&#8217;s desire to smother the &#8216;Canes led to a horrendous mistake as the half ended.</p>
<p>Swinney sent kicker B.T. Potter out for a 61-yard field field with 3 seconds remaining. But Potter&#8217;s kick was blocked and bounced into the arms of DJ Ivey, who took it 48 yards for a touchdown.</p>
<p>Miami rushed off the field in celebration while the reduced crowd at Death Valley — less than quarter of its 81,500 capacity — sat stunned.</p>
<p>Swinney, the two-time national championship coach, called it “as bad a decision (as) I&#8217;ve made.”</p>
<p>Any Miami “mo” quickly disappeared in the third quarter with three straight three-and-outs, including tailback Jaylan Knighton getting stuffed for no gain on fourth-and-short on the Hurricanes&#8217; 34.</p>
<p>Etienne ended most of the drama with his 72-yard burst down the left sideline to put Clemson up 28-10.</p>
<p>About the only other troubling moment for Clemson came when Lawrence was on the ground grabbing his leg after getting hit in the third quarter. The nervous crowd sat silent as the training staff surrounded the likely No. 1 pick in next year&#8217;s NFL draft.</p>
<p>Lawrence, though, popped up and ran off to the sidelines on his own. Moments later, Lawrence rushed for a 4-yard TD, spiking the ball was staring down a Miami defender — and got called for unsportsmanlike conduct.</p>
<p>Lawrence ended with 292 yards, completing 29 of 41 and went without an interception for a 12th straight game.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes have some work to do when it comes to facing the nation&#8217;s best. They seemed to lose their poise at times with 15 penalties, including two for targeting on safety Amari Carter and linebacker Keontra Smith.</p>
<p>Clemson: The Tigers have been in four of the last five matchups of Top-10 ACC teams — and won them all. There are still some huge moments left for Clemson (at Notre Dame on Nov. 7, maybe?) as it tries for a sixth ACC title and College Football Playoff appearance.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami starts a two-game homestand against Pitt next Saturday.</p>
<p>Clemson hits the road for the first time in more than a month at Georgia Tech on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">758480</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>King has Canes on the rise as they prepare for No. 1 Clemson</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/king-has-canes-on-the-rise-as-they-prepare-for-no-1-clemson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=757068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI (AP) — Miami Hurricanes senior D’Eriq King has been chosen Atlantic Coast Conference quarterback of the week after each of his past two games....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI (AP) — Miami Hurricanes senior D’Eriq King has been chosen Atlantic Coast Conference quarterback of the week after each of his past two games.</p>
<p>Against top-ranked Clemson, he would happily settle for quarterback of the night.</p>
<p>The No. 7-ranked Hurricanes (3-0, 2-0 ACC) are two-touchdown underdogs Saturday at Clemson (3-0, 2-0), but they believe they can win in part because of King. He has thrown for 736 yards and run for 157 while directing an offense that is reminding Miami fans of the school&#8217;s glory days.</p>
<p>King now faces his toughest challenge since transferring from Houston in January: to outscore the high-powered Tigers and Trevor Lawrence.</p>
<p>“I&#8217;m not playing Trevor; our defense is playing him,” King said Wednesday. “But I&#8217;m excited to play in this game.”</p>
<p>This isn&#8217;t the first time King has gone against a marquee QB. He threw for two touchdowns and ran for one last season in Houston&#8217;s 49-31 loss to Oklahoma and Jalen Hurts.</p>
<p>“Playing Jalen last year was kind of similar to this,” King said. “It was a big game, a lot of headlines. But you’ve got to play like it&#8217;s any other game.”</p>
<p>King made 22 starts in Houston, and his maturity has been a stabilizing influence for the Hurricanes, whose unsettled quarterback situation contributed to a disappointing 6-7 record last year. He has helped Miami climb to its highest ranking since November 26, 2017.</p>
<p>King threw for 325 yards in a victory at No. 18 Louisville, and passed for 267 to help the Hurricanes beat Florida State 52-10 in their most recent game Sept. 26.</p>
<p>Like Lawrence, King has yet to throw an interception.</p>
<p>“The great things about D&#8217;Eric is that being a guy who has played a lot of college football, he&#8217;s a mature kid,” offensive coordinator Rhett Lashlee said. &#8220;He&#8217;s got that experience, and that was a big advantage for us.</p>
<p>“He&#8217;s just a very consistent young man, the same kid every day. He&#8217;s a very loose, confident person, but he&#8217;s focused and locked in on what we’re doing. That is slowly but surely hopefully becoming the personality of our offense.&#8221;</p>
<p>Miami’s blocking has been much improved so far this year, but the line hasn’t face a front as formidable as Clemson’s, which could force King to throw more quickly and run more.</p>
<p>Like Lawrence, King poses a threat both as a passer and a runner. Tigers coach Dabo Swinney notes he&#8217;s averaging 5.4 yards after contact as a rusher.</p>
<p>“There’s nothing he can’t do,” Swinney said. “He can make all the throws, and when he runs it, he’s a running back — he’s got that mindset.”</p>
<p>In a big game, King said, it&#8217;s important not to try to do too much — even with Trevor Lawrence on the other side. Still, he acknowledged the opportunity the match-up presents.</p>
<p>“Trevor is a great talent,” he said. “He&#8217;s going to be the No. 1 pick in the draft.”</p>
<p>King would happily settle for being No. 1 on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">757068</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>King throws 2 TD passes, No. 12 Miami routs Florida State</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/king-throws-2-td-passes-no-12-miami-routs-florida-state/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 03:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=748562</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) &#8212; D&#8217;Eriq King threw for 267 yards and two touchdowns in three quarters and No. 12 Miami beat Florida State 52-10...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) &#8212; D&#8217;Eriq King threw for 267 yards and two touchdowns in three quarters and No. 12 Miami beat Florida State 52-10 on Saturday night.</p>
<p>Cam&#8217;Ron Harris and Don Chaney scored twice and Brevin Jordan and Dee Wiggins each caught touchdown passes for Miami (3-0, 2-0 Atlantic Coast Conference).</p>
<p>Miami scored touchdowns on its five possessions and built a 35-point lead at halftime. The margin of victory was the largest for Miami in the series since a 47-0 rout in 1976, the first season of Bobby Bowden&#8217;s 34-year coaching career at Florida State.</p>
<p>The Seminoles (0-2, 0-2) were without head coach Mike Norvell, who tested positive for coronavirus and remained in Tallahassee under quarantine. Assistant Chris Thomsen served as head coach.</p>
<p>King capped the Hurricanes&#8217; game-opening drive with a 24-yard touchdown pass to Jordan.</p>
<p>After Ryan Fitzgerald&#8217;s 26-yard field goal ended Florida State&#8217;s first drive, Miami responded with Harris&#8217; 3-yard-run late in the first quarter. Harris&#8217; second touchdown from 12 yards put the Hurricanes ahead 21-3.</p>
<p>Asante Samuel recovered Mark Pope&#8217;s fumble inside the Miami 40 but the Seminoles turned it over on the next play after Jaelan Phillips intercepted Jordan Travis&#8217; pass. Three plays later, King connected with Wiggins from 40 yards to make it 28-3.</p>
<p>King, a graduate transfer from Houston, has completed six touchdown passes without an interception through his first three games with the Hurricanes. He also ran for 65 on eight carries against Florida State.</p>
<p>Chaney scored his first college touchdown on a 2-yard run with 3:37 late in the second quarter. Jose Borregales closed the first half with a 30-yard field goal as time expired.</p>
<p>Camren McDonald caught a 12-yard touchdown pass from James Blackman on the Seminoles&#8217; first drive of the second half before Chaney&#8217;s 5-yard run early in the fourth quarter gave Miami another 35-point lead.</p>
<p>STREAK REVERSAL:</p>
<p>Miami won its fourth straight over Florida State and leads the series 35-30. The Seminoles enjoyed a seven-game winning streak before the Hurricanes&#8217; current string.</p>
<p>SELLOUT BUT FAR FROM CAPACITY:</p>
<p>Saturday&#8217;s attendance of 12,806 was listed as a sellout. The crowd total fell within the 20 percent capacity allowed at 65,000-seat Hard Rock Stadium to comply with coronavirus social distancing guidelines.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Florida State: the Seminoles will return home and face Jacksonville State next Saturday.</p>
<p>Miami: after a bye week, the Hurricanes will play at No. 1 Clemson on Oct. 10.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">748562</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>No. 17 Miami runs past No. 18 Louisville 47-34 in ACC opener</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/no-17-miami-runs-past-no-18-louisville-47-34-in-acc-opener/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=741511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — D&#8217;Eriq King threw three touchdown passes and No. 17 Miami used big plays to beat No. 18 Louisville 47-34 on Saturday...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — D&#8217;Eriq King threw three touchdown passes and No. 17 Miami used big plays to beat No. 18 Louisville 47-34 on Saturday night in the Atlantic Coast Conference opener for both teams.</p>
<p>King threw a 75-yarder touchdown pass to Jaylon Knighton in the third quarter, a series after Cam’Ron Harris ran 75 yards for a score on the way to finishing with 134 yards on nine carries.</p>
<p>Miami (2-0) led 20-6 at halftime before Louisville (1-1) scored twice in a wild third to get within seven. The Hurricanes answered both TDs on their next snap with an unbalanced look against an out-of-place defense, with Knighton wide open for his catch that made it 34-20. Knighton also had a 3-yard TD run in the first half after King threw a 17-yard scoring pass to Will Mallory.</p>
<p>The &#8216;Canes had 10 chunk plays of at least 18 yards, including seven passing.</p>
<p>“We talked about creating more explosive plays through the passing game, which we were able to do,&#8221; Miami coach Manny Diaz said, “but we obviously had some through the running game, as well. We can still be so much better. The explosive plays, it was who we wanted to be.”</p>
<p>Said Louisville coach Scott Satterfield, &#8220;Just too many big plays. Two two-play drives that went for six. You gotta at least make the offenses drive the ball.”</p>
<p>King also hit Brevin Jordan (seven catches, 120 yards) with a 47-yard TD pass in the fourth to finish with 325 yards on 18-of-30 passing. That spoke volumes about his protection, which allowed the dual-threat QB time to scout the defense and find receivers who were often open.</p>
<p>So much so that King&#8217;s nine yards rushing on eight carries were just a footnote on a night his arm helped lead an 86-yard TD drive and three others of 75.</p>
<p>“The offensive line played a great game,” he said. “They allowed me to sit in the pocket and throw the ball, and we did pretty good.”</p>
<p>Jose Borregales added four field goals, including first-half kicks of 48 and 57 yards, with the latter breaking the Cardinal Stadium record for an opponent by 6 yards and the overall mark by 5.</p>
<p>Louisville&#8217;s Micale Cunningham passed for 307 yards and three TDs, two to Tutu Atwell, and Javian Hawkins had a 19-yard TD run and finished with 164 yards on 27 carries. But the Cardinals couldn&#8217;t stop Miami for much of the game and lost their second in a row to the &#8216;Canes despite outgaining them 516-485.</p>
<p>“It was extremely frustrating,” Louisville linebacker C.J. Avery said of allowing explosive plays. “We just didn&#8217;t have an edge, and they did like a pop pass and guys didn&#8217;t do their job, didn&#8217;t take their man. It was really on us not doing our job.&#8221;</p>
<p>The game was played before a sellout crowd of 12,120.</p>
<p>THIRD-DOWN EFFICIENCY</p>
<p>Miami converted 6 of 13 third-down chances, including several in the first half that helped provide a lead it never lost. Louisville on other hand was just 4 of 14, though it was 3 of 4 on fourth down.</p>
<p>PREGAME PROTEST</p>
<p>About 40 protesters seeking the arrest of Louisville police in the death of Breonna Taylor during a March narcotics raid demonstrated briefly outside Cardinal Stadium before the game. A Louisville athletic spokesman said they left after kickoff and there were no arrests.</p>
<p>OPTING OUT</p>
<p>Miami confirmed that quarterback Tate Martell has opted out of playing this season. He transferred from Ohio State last season and played in five games.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Already ranked sooner than some expected, Miami figures to move up after an impressive road win. The loss could drop Louisville or out of the poll completely.</p>
<p>THE TAKEAWAY</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes scored on four consecutive drives in both halves, demonstrating their offensive dominance. King showed the passing skills expected of him after transferring from Houston, even with a 74-yard completion wiped out by a holding penalty. The defense struggled at times against the Cardinals&#8217; speedy playmakers but forced two turnovers that forced them to play catchup.</p>
<p>Louisville: Aiming to atone for last year’s 52-27 drubbing in south Florida, the Cardinals instead let another early lead slip away fast. The defense reverted to last season&#8217;s tendency to allow big plays and appeared completely flummoxed yielding those TDs that sapped momentum after getting within a touchdown.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami hosts in-state rival Florida State on Saturday, seeking its fourth consecutive win over the Seminoles.</p>
<p>Louisville visits Pittsburgh on Saturday. The Cardinals lost the previous meeting 45-34 in 2015 to fall to 8-9 against the Panthers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">741511</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FSU coach Norvell tests positive for virus before Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/college/fsu-coach-norvell-tests-positive-for-virus-before-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=740821</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(AP) &#8212; Florida State coach Mike Norvell has tested positive for COVID-19 and will not coach the Seminoles in-person this week as they prepare for...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(AP) &#8212; Florida State coach Mike Norvell has tested positive for COVID-19 and will not coach the Seminoles in-person this week as they prepare for Miami.</p>
<p>Norvell released a statement Saturday saying he tested positive a day earlier but is feeling fine. He said his wife and daughter tested negative Saturday.</p>
<p>Florida State athletic director David Coburn said Norvell is isolating, which lasts a minimum of 10 days.</p>
<p>“We will continue to test staff and student-athletes as we have been,” Coburn said in a statement. “We have communicated with Commissioner John Swofford and Miami athletic director Blake James. At this point, based on our testing this week, we have no reason to believe that the Miami game is in jeopardy.&#8221;</p>
<p>While that game is still on, COVID-19 complications caused more schedule rearrangement Saturday.</p>
<p>Memphis announced that it needed another week off to get through its issues and canceled its nonconference game against Texas-San Antonio that was scheduled for Friday. The Tigers were supposed to play Houston this weekend but that game was postponed after a COVID-19 outbreak among Memphis&#8217; players.</p>
<p>Memphis announced it added FCS Stephen F. Austin on Nov. 21 and UTSA said instead of the Tigers it will play Middle Tennessee on Friday.</p>
<p>In Tallahassee, Florida, deputy head coach Chris Thomsen is taking over Norvell&#8217;s duties, but the first-year Florida State head coach said he still intends to contribute.</p>
<p>“I will remain involved remotely as much as possible to help our team continue to prepare,&#8221; Norvell said. “I’m grateful to the administration, players and staff for their commitment to the protocols we have in place, which have helped us limit contact with others and allowed us to continue moving forward.”</p>
<p>Thomsen has 24 years of college coaching experience and was head coach at Division II Abilene Christian from 2005-11, where he went 51-21.</p>
<p>Florida State lost its season opener at home to Georgia Tech last week and was off Saturday. The Seminoles play at the rival Hurricanes next Saturday.</p>
<p>Norvell, who came to Florida State from Memphis after last regular season, is the first major college football coach known to have tested positive for the coronavirus in season.</p>
<p>Toledo coach Jason Candle and UCLA coach Chip Kelly tested positive earlier this year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">740821</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UM fans adjust to social distancing guidelines set for first game at Hard Rock Stadium</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/um-fans-adjust-to-social-distancing-guidelines-set-for-first-game-at-hard-rock-stadium/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 13:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=731631</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Miami Hurricanes kicked off the start of the season with fans in the stands. On Thursday, only 13,000 fans were able to watch the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Miami Hurricanes kicked off the start of the season with fans in the stands.</p>
<p>On Thursday, only 13,000 fans were able to watch the game while sitting in the stands at Hard Rock Stadium in Miami Gardens.</p>
<p>No more than six people per group were allowed to sit together.</p>
<p>There were no benches on the Canes sidelines and there were separate chairs for the players.</p>
<p>&#8220;The thing is, if you think about three, four, five, six months ago, we probably thought we were having no football,&#8221; said Canes fan Rico Pradel. &#8220;The fact that we actually have an opportunity to be able to be on the field and watch football in general, we just kind of gotta adapt.&#8221;</p>
<p>Safety protocols were in place in the midst of the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</p>
<p>Signs were posted throughout the stadium encouraging fans to social distance, masks were mandatory and no tailgating was allowed.</p>
<p>7News spoke to fans who said they didn&#8217;t mind the new normal if it means they can see their team play.</p>
<p>&#8220;Nothing is going to bother me as soon as I see D&#8217;Eriq King on that football field and I see a brand-new Miami Hurricane football team,&#8221; Canes fan Brad Tejeda said. &#8220;I drove five and a half hours from Gainesville for tonight.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve never seen anything like it but it is what it is,&#8221; said Canes fan Keith McCullough. &#8220;We didn&#8217;t sign up for it but we gotta deal with it.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Go Hurricanes!&#8221; said another eager fan.</p>
<p>&#8220;I know we have these precautions, we don&#8217;t take it lightly, I don&#8217;t think anybody does,&#8221; said Canes fan Matt Griffin. &#8220;At the same time, I think it&#8217;s a great game that needs to be played.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;This is what I do,&#8221; said Canes fan Derek Cole. &#8220;I mean, it&#8217;s in my blood &#8212; it&#8217;s orange and green. This is the University of Miami, like there is nothing else. There&#8217;s no question: the game is played, I&#8217;m here.&#8221;</p>
<p>After a slow first half, the Canes beat UAB 31 to 14.</p>
<p>UM&#8217;s next game is at home again on Sept. 26.</p>
<p>They will play against FSU.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">731631</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/um-game-e1599830723579.png' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/um-game-e1599830723579.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/um-game-e1599830723579.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">um game</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>QB D&#8217;Eriq King set for Miami Hurricanes debut against UAB</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/qb-deriq-king-set-for-miami-hurricanes-debut-against-uab/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 21:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=731136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Miami is hoping quarterback D&#8217;Eriq King can lead a Hurricanes&#8217; offensive revival. The graduate transfer from Houston will make his...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MIAMI GARDENS, Fla. (AP) — Miami is hoping quarterback D&#8217;Eriq King can lead a Hurricanes&#8217; offensive revival.</p>
<p>The graduate transfer from Houston will make his Hurricanes debut against UAB (1-0) in Miami&#8217;s opener Thursday night after an offseason of doubt due to COVID-19.</p>
<p>“It’s a great feeling,” King said. &#8220;A couple of months ago, nobody really thought we’d be playing right now. And now to get the opportunity to go play a game on Thursday night — the only game on — it’s a great feeling.</p>
<p>“Playing for the University of Miami &#8230; it’s just an honor for me to go out there and play my first game.”</p>
<p>The Hurricanes are banking on King to help spark a rebound from a 6-7 season when the offense ranked 98th out of 130 teams nationally in yards per game. They were also the only team shut out in a bowl game.</p>
<p>The dual-threat King is reason enough for excitement in a program employing new offensive coordinator Rhett Lashlee&#8217;s spread offense.</p>
<p>King left Houston after four games last fall so he could take a redshirt year. He&#8217;s the only FBS quarterback to throw for at least one touchdown and run for at least one touchdown in 15 consecutive games.</p>
<p>UAB coach Bill Clark calls the 5-foot-11, 195-pound King “a running back-quarterback.”</p>
<p>“He is a guy who can really throw it, but also has running back speed and legs,” Clark said.</p>
<p>CONFERENCE USA AGAIN UAB has never beaten an ACC opponent and doesn&#8217;t have a victory over a Power Five opponent since topping Baylor in 2004. However, the Hurricanes did lose to Conference USA&#8217;s FIU 30-24 last season.</p>
<p>SPREADING IT OUT</p>
<p>Lashlee, a former Auburn offensive coordinator, came to Miami from SMU. Miami wide receiver Michael Harley said fans will be pleased with what they see from the offense.</p>
<p>“The only thing I can say is just watch the game and the offense will come alive,” Harley said.</p>
<p>UAB GROUND GAME</p>
<p>One challenge for the Hurricanes&#8217; defense will be stopping UAB career rushing leader Spencer Brown. Brown enters the game with 3,122 career yards despite missing four games with an ankle injury in 2019.</p>
<p>Jermaine Brown Jr. joins him in the backfield.</p>
<p>“Both really talented guys,” Miami linebacker Zach McCloud said. &#8220;I know they play hard, especially if you just take the time to really watch them play.</p>
<p>“Those are two guys that will give you as much trouble as anybody else, if not more.”</p>
<p>MORE TRANSFERS</p>
<p>Miami will rely heavily on other transfers besides King. That includes right tackle Jarrid Williams, placekicker Jose Borregales and defensive end Quincy Roche. Roche, a grad transfer from Temple, helps fill the void left by Gregory Rousseau, who opted out of the season to prepare for the 2021 draft.</p>
<p>Borregales was a huge pickup out of FIU considering the Hurricanes&#8217; kicking woes of last season. That included eight missed field goals from 40 yards or closer.</p>
<p>NO STUDENTS</p>
<p>The Hurricanes won&#8217;t allow students to attend their first two games at Hard Rock Stadium. Plans call for the crowds to be limited to 13,000 fans.</p>
<p>“That’s not a problem,” McCloud said. “I played high school football, too. That’s the least of my concerns.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">731136</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091020-deriq-king.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091020-deriq-king.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/09/091020-deriq-king.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">091020 d&#039;eriq king</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jacory Harris, former football pro from Liberty City, finds fulfillment as MDFR firefighter</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/jacory-harris-former-football-pro-from-liberty-city-finds-fulfillment-as-mdfr-firefighter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 22:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MDFR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wsvn.com/?p=721785</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A former professional football player from South Florida has traded one helmet for another as he begins a second chapter in his life. Jacory Harris,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A former professional football player from South Florida has traded one helmet for another as he begins a second chapter in his life.</p>
<p>Jacory Harris, who grew up in Liberty City, first suited up as a Miami Northwestern Bull, then as a Miami Hurricane, a Philadelphia Eagle and a Montreal Alouette for the Canadian Football League.</p>
<p>Despite his athletic accomplishments, Harris said, nothing is more fulfilling than suiting up as a Miami-Dade firefighter.</p>
<p>&#8220;It absolutely means everything. I&#8217;ve never wanted people to see me as just a football player,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It made me feel more human, just being able to help somebody and knowing that I made a difference in their lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>Harris was literally thrown into the fire shortly after graduating from the Fire Academy in July.</p>
<p>&#8220;You never know when you&#8217;re going to get that career fire that&#8217;s going to be grueling &#8212; all night, 12 hours &#8212; and I actually got that on my second shift,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Now 30, Harris said, he feels honored to help those in the same neighborhood who helped mold him into the man he is today.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s an amazing experience, man. They can even tell through the mask, &#8216;Hey, Jacory. That&#8217;s you?'&#8221; he said. &#8220;It&#8217;s a good feeling, and it&#8217;s a good experience, just basically knowing I&#8217;m doing something for my community.&#8221;</p>
<p>The former quarterback said the second act of his career has countless parallels with his gridiron past.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s kind of what gets you up in the morning, knowing that you&#8217;re going to come to work and be around a bunch of guys that you call your brothers,&#8221; he said, &#8220;and that you know that if something is on the line, they&#8217;re going to be right there to save you. They&#8217;re going to be right there to help you, and I&#8217;ve been blessed to have it in both careers that I&#8217;ve chosen.&#8221;</p>
<p>Harris said he has his mother to thank for persuading him to choose his latest career path.</p>
<p>&#8220;She said, &#8216;Hey, you know, after football, you should consider being a firefighter,'&#8221; he said. &#8220;I was always interested in the medical side of things, and then being a firefighter still has that athletic, team bonding thing.&#8221;</p>
<p>But like everyone, Harris, still thinks about his first love.</p>
<p>&#8220;I do miss it. I can&#8217;t lie to you. It is special to me, something that I&#8217;ll always remember,&#8221; he said, &#8220;but at the end of the day, I&#8217;m beyond football right now. I&#8217;m on a different path in life.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">721785</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200831_Jacory_Harris.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7327e1cf-d977-45e2-87ab-082e4a7df191/9ce8b229-851d-4345-ae08-c5c8b10d61c0/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615220028~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/7327e1cf-d977-45e2-87ab-082e4a7df191/9ce8b229-851d-4345-ae08-c5c8b10d61c0/main.mp4*~hmac=1987dc753db0104daf8b2b5939ca5fcfa3d14b1cff0b498e8e41ab421578979e' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200831_Jacory_Harris.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/08/200831_Jacory_Harris.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200831_Jacory_Harris</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Hurricanes&#8217; 2020 game schedule released</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/miami-hurricanes-2020-game-schedule-released/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=704754</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The 2020 season schedule for the University of Miami&#8217;s Hurricanes Football Team has been released. The announcement on Thursday morning comes one day before the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The 2020 season schedule for the University of Miami&#x2019;s Hurricanes Football Team has been released.<p>The announcement on Thursday morning comes one day before the Canes&#x2019; first fall practice.</p><p>The full 2020 season schedule is as follows:</p><ul>
<li>9/10 vs UAB at Hard Rock Stadium</li>
<li>9/19 away at Louisville, K.Y</li>
<li>9/26 vs FSU at Hard Rock Stadium</li>
<li>10/10 away at Clemson, S.C.</li>
<li>10/17 vs Pittsburgh at Hard Rock Stadium</li>
<li>10/24 vs Virginia at Hard Rock Stadium</li>
<li>11/6 away at NC State, Raleigh, N.C.</li>
<li>11/14 away at Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.</li>
<li>11/21 vs Georgia Tech at Hard Rock Stadium</li>
<li>11/28 away at Wake Forest, Winston-Salem, N.C.</li>
<li>12/5 vs UNC at Hard Rock Stadium</li>
</ul><p>The first game scheduled for Sept. 10 will be the only non-conference game the team will play.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/CanesFootball/status/1291360711835373569</embed></div><p>It remains unclear how many fans will be able to attend the games.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">704754</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UM athletics kneels, tennis stars share video in protest of racial injustice</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/um-athletics-kneels-tennis-stars-share-video-in-protest-of-racial-injustice/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 21:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=658648</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The University of Miami&#8217;s athletic department has taken a knee to join demonstrators to demand justice and racial equality. Players, coaches and staff across the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The University of Miami&#8217;s athletic department has taken a knee to join demonstrators to demand justice and racial equality.</p>
<p>Players, coaches and staff across the department kneeled for eight minutes and 46 seconds inside the university&#8217;s indoor practice facility on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Men&#8217;s Basketball head coach Jim Larranaga showed his support in a social media post.</p>
<p>&#8220;Eight minutes &amp; 46 seconds of silence today speaks volumes about the concern UM coaches, athletes and administrators have for the circumstances that created the need for protests &amp; demonstrations. Let us pray,&#8221; he said in a tweet.</p>
<p>The time spent kneeling represents the exact time former Minneapolis Police Officer Derek Chauvin spent pressing his knee on George Floyd&#8217;s neck.</p>
<p>However, the university was not the only program showing solidarity towards the demonstrations.</p>
<p>Professional tennis player Frances Tiafoe, along with Serena Williams, Coco Gauff, Sloane Stephens and other tennis players, shared a video online with the initiative &#8220;Racquets Down, Hands Up&#8221; to spread awareness on racial discrimination around the world.</p>
<p>&#8220;We wanted to do a small gesture to spread awareness about the unjust deaths of many African Americans here in this country,&#8221; 2019 NCAA National Champion Ayan Bloomfield said.</p>
<p>&#8220;Today, we put our racquets down and our hands up,&#8221; Tiafoe said.</p>
<p>The video ends with #SayTheirName and features the names of people who fell victim to race-related violence.</p>
<p>As their names fill the screen, the video ends in a call to continue educating people, speaking out and for people to love one another.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">658648</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/060320-um-kneels.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/060320-um-kneels.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/060320-um-kneels.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">060320 um kneels</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UM coaches join student-athletes for kneeling protest</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/um-coaches-join-student-athletes-for-kneeling-protest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Samantha Branca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 14:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=658357</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The University of Miami community joined together for a protest against the death of George Floyd in police custody. The University of Miami&#8217;s head football...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The University of Miami community joined together for a protest against the death of George Floyd in police custody.<p>The University of Miami&#x2019;s head football coach Manny Diaz, head men&#x2019;s basketball coach Jim Larranaga and women&#x2019;s head basketball coach Katie Meier joined together with student-athletes for the demonstration on Tuesday.</p><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/Coach_MannyDiaz/status/1268004470341996544</embed></div><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/CanesCoachL/status/1267995038207873025</embed></div><div><embed type="oembed">https://twitter.com/CoachKatieMeier/status/1267985048520687617</embed></div><p>The protesters knelt down on one knee for 8 minutes and 46 seconds, the same amount of time a Minneapolis police officer had his knee on Floyd&#xE2;&#x80;&#x99;s neck, pinning him to the ground.</p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">658357</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/um-kneeling-protest.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3ff1b8e6-be2c-402b-90f3-cf38a49665c4/8ccd87c3-4cff-4b03-9c77-794f123f395b/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615219898~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/3ff1b8e6-be2c-402b-90f3-cf38a49665c4/8ccd87c3-4cff-4b03-9c77-794f123f395b/main.mp4*~hmac=35465dbb1fced5530f82399a500be1edd796370f24166dd9991791a885576439' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/um-kneeling-protest.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/06/um-kneeling-protest.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">um kneeling protest</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UM President: On-campus classes expected to return for fall, football probably played in empty stadiums</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/um-president-on-campus-classes-expected-to-return-for-fall-football-probably-played-in-empty-stadiums/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Reinaldo Llerena]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 21:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=649949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The University of Miami is getting ready for students to return in the fall. Julio Frenk, the school&#8217;s president, said Wednesday he expects to have...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The University of Miami is getting ready for students to return in the fall.</p>
<p>Julio Frenk, the school&#8217;s president, said Wednesday he expects to have on-campus classes that will incorporate proper social distancing.</p>
<p>Also, the university will conduct extensive cleaning, require all students to wear masks and require that every student be vaccinated for the flu.</p>
<p>When asked if the school&#8217;s football season would go on as scheduled, Frenk said, &#8220;We certainly hope so. Obviously, everything that we do will have safety of our students as the top priority. If we don&#8217;t feel it&#8217;s safe, we won&#8217;t do it, but with the measures we&#8217;re taking, we will. We will probably play in empty stadiums like so many other sports, but we hope to have a season, and we hope to have a winning season.&#8221;</p>
<p>As for Florida&#8217;s public universities, the state&#8217;s education leaders said they also expect to reopen in the fall, but specifics won&#8217;t be released until late June.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">649949</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/052020-um-president.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/052020-um-president.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/052020-um-president.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">052020 um president</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UM president optimistic about Canes playing 2020 season despite coronavirus pandemic</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/um-president-optimistic-about-canes-playing-2020-season-despite-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=649721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A lot has happened since Miami Hurricanes players ended their spring practice amidst the coronavirus outbreak in March, and University of Miami president Julio Frenk...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lot has happened since Miami Hurricanes players ended their spring practice amidst the coronavirus outbreak in March, and University of Miami president Julio Frenk is weighing in with optimism that there will be a 2020 college football season.</p>
<p>However, you shouldn&#8217;t make any tailgating plans or supply runs just yet because there&#8217;s a major catch: Frenk was asked early Wednesday whether the Canes will be playing on the field.</p>
<p>&#8220;We certainly hope so. I mean, everything we do will have the safety of our students as the top priority,&#8221; he said. &#8220;We don&#8217;t feel it&#8217;s safe, we won&#8217;t do it, but with the measures that we&#8217;re taking, we will and we hope that&#8230; they will probably play in an empty stadium like so many other sports and we hope to have a season. We hope to have a winning season.&#8221;</p>
<p>Frenk said he also plans to have students take in-person classes at the Coral Gables campus of UM in the fall.</p>
<p>The school plans to conduct plenty of testing and keeping appropriate social distancing measures in place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">649721</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/052020-um-football.png' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/052020-um-football.png" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/05/052020-um-football.png" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">052020 UM football</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>University of Miami places gold turnover chain up for auction</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/university-of-miami-places-gold-turnover-chain-up-for-auction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 20:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Local]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami-Dade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=630065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The fight against the coronavirus pandemic is causing a chain reaction, and this one involves gold — and lots of jewels. University of Miami&#8217;s famous...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fight against the coronavirus pandemic is causing a chain reaction, and this one involves gold — and lots of jewels.</p>
<p>University of Miami&#8217;s famous turnover chain is hitting the auction block.</p>
<p>Ray Lewis put out a video calling out all University of Miami fans around the world to bid on a dream package.</p>
<p>The package will help raise money to feed those in need during the COVID-19 crisis.</p>
<p>The winner will go home with one of the two original turnover chains used by the Canes back in 2017.</p>
<p>The original chain is 5-and-a-half pounds of solid gold with 900 orange and green sapphire stones.</p>
<p>It is reportedly worth around $100,000.</p>
<p>The winning bid also includes a VIP game experience for the Canes-Florida State game scheduled for Nov. 7 at Hard Rock Stadium.</p>
<p>The winner and 14 other fans will be in the suite to watch the game.</p>
<p>Plus, there will be a two-person weekend stay at the Fontainebleau Hotel.</p>
<p>The current bid for the Canes package stands at $16,500. There are nine days left to bid.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;d like to place your bid on the Canes package, go to <a href="http://fanatics.com/">fanatics.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">630065</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/041620-um-chain.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/041620-um-chain.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/04/041620-um-chain.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">041620 UM chain</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senior Vasiljevic seals Miami&#8217;s 69-65 OT win over Syracuse</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/senior-vasiljevic-seals-miamis-69-65-ot-win-over-syracuse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 01:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=604642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Miami Hurricanes senior guard DJ Vasiljevic launched the final shot of his home career and triumphantly raised his fist even...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Miami Hurricanes senior guard DJ Vasiljevic launched the final shot of his home career and triumphantly raised his fist even before the ball swished through the net.</p>
<p>Vasiljevic&#8217;s two free throws with two seconds left in overtime Saturday sealed Miami&#8217;s 69-65 victory over Syracuse.</p>
<p>&#8220;I wanted everyone to know the game was over,&#8221; Vasiljevic said. &#8220;I was a little emotional, I&#8217;m not going to lie. To get on that free throw line and score the last point, it means a lot.&#8221;</p>
<p>Syracuse forward Elijah Hughes, the leading scorer in the Atlantic Coast Conference, took a blow to the head and sat out after halftime. He played all 20 minutes in the first half and scored eight points.</p>
<p>&#8220;He was a little dizzy, a little blurry,&#8221; coach Jim Boeheim said.</p>
<p>Miami (15-15, 7-13 ACC) broke a three-game losing streak heading into the league tournament. Syracuse (17-14, 10-10) finished at .500 or worse in the conference for the fourth time in the past six years.</p>
<p>The Orange&#8217;s 14 losses are the most in the regular season Boeheim has had in his 44 years at Syracuse. And again, a big problem was shooting &#8212; the Orange made only 37 percent, and went 5 for 25 from 3-point range.</p>
<p>&#8220;We haven&#8217;t shot the ball well for a long time, so I don&#8217;t think it&#8217;s a surprise,&#8221; Boeheim said. &#8220;We&#8217;re just not making enough shots to win.&#8221;</p>
<p>Isaiah Wong had 18 points, nine rebounds, four assists and three steals for Miami. The 6-3 freshman helped run the offense in place of an injured Chris Lykes, the Hurricanes&#8217; leading scorer this season.</p>
<p>&#8220;I would like for Lykes to play,&#8221; Boeheim said. &#8220;Wong is bigger and more difficult for us. Lykes is a really good player, but Wong is more of a concern because he&#8217;s bigger and gets to the basket.&#8221;</p>
<p>Vasiljevic made five 3-pointers to climb into second place on the school&#8217;s all-time list, and he scored 17 points. His sister and two best friends from his native Australia were part of the crowd.</p>
<p>Miami missed 12 consecutive shots against Syracuse&#8217;s zone early in the second half and went nearly eight minutes without a field goal before Vasiljevic sank three consecutive 3-pointers for a 39-all tie.</p>
<p>Afterward, Hurricanes coach Jim Larranaga grinned as he recalled Vasiljevic jump-starting the offense.</p>
<p>&#8220;My coaches were saying to me, `We just need to get the ball to DJ and let him shoot every shot,&#8221;&#8216; Larranaga said.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes saved their best shooting for overtime, when they went 3 for 6. They shot 37 percent for the game.</p>
<p>Syracuse&#8217;s Joe Girard sank a 15-footer with 1 second left to make the score 56-all and force overtime, but the Orange&#8217;s first basket in the extra period came with 23 seconds left. They went 0 for 4 from 3-point range in overtime.</p>
<p>Marek Dolezaj led Syracuse with 17 points.</p>
<p>DEALING</p>
<p>Hurricanes forward Keith Stone, operating in the middle of the Syracuse zone, dished out a season-high six assists.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t look at people when I pass,&#8221; Stone said. &#8220;I tell them beforehand, &#8216;Just expect it. I&#8217;m not looking at you.&#8221;&#8216;</p>
<p>The Hurricanes had a season-high 18 assists.</p>
<p>SIDELINED</p>
<p>Lykes took an elbow to the nose in Wednesday&#8217;s loss to Virginia, suffered facial injuries and likely will miss the league tournament.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>The Orange fell to 56-54 in the ACC in the past six seasons.</p>
<p>With the Hurricanes unlikely to make the postseason, they probably need to win one game in the league tournament to avoid a second consecutive losing season, which hasn&#8217;t happened to Larranaga since 1991-93 at Bowling Green.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Both teams will play in the ACC Tournament next week in Greensboro, North Carolina.</p>
<p>The Orange have a first-round bye. Hughes&#8217; status for their first game is uncertain.</p>
<p>&#8220;He&#8217;s gotten hit in the head 20 times this year,&#8221; Boeheim said.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">604642</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alvarado helps Georgia Tech hold off Miami 63-57</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/alvarado-helps-georgia-tech-hold-off-miami-63-57/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 05:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=598142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ATLANTA (AP) — Georgia Tech really wants to earn a first-round bye in the Atlantic Coast Conference tournament for the first time in seven years,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ATLANTA (AP) — Georgia Tech really wants to earn a first-round bye in the Atlantic Coast Conference tournament for the first time in seven years, and for a long time Saturday night the Yellow Jackets looked like they would lock up that privilege against Miami as they cruised to a 20-point lead in the second half.</p>
<p>And just like that the dream faded but then returned as Jose Alvarado scored nine of his 16 points after intermission and Tech rallied after Miami&#8217;s 24-2 run for a 63-57 win, clinching a first-round bye in the ACC tournament for the first time since 2013.</p>
<p>Fellow guard Michael Devoe added 14 points for Tech (15-14, 9-9) and center James Banks III pitched in 13 points and 14 rebounds. Alvarado was 7-of-15 shooting and had seven steals.</p>
<p>Point guard Chris Lykes paced the Hurricanes (14-14, 6-12) with 14 points, but the Tech defense tightened and Miami failed to score over the final 4:08.</p>
<p>The Jackets won their fifth consecutive ACC home game, and also held a conference opponent under 60 points for the fifth straight time in McCamish Pavilion.</p>
<p>“One thing I think we got out of this is we never stopped fighting regardless of what happens. A lot of teams probably would have went down,” Alvarado said. “We don’t want to play on Tuesday (March 10, the first day of the ACC tournament), we keep on saying that.”</p>
<p>Tech’s biggest lead came when Devoe hit a 3-pointer with 15:33 left for a 49-29 edge, but the Hurricanes went on a 24-2 run during a stretch when the Yellow Jackets were plagued by turnovers (six in that time) and a missed alley-oop by Jordan Usher. Tech missed 10 of 11 shots.</p>
<p>Lykes gave Miami leads of 53-51 on a 3-pointer with 7:36 remaining, and 57-55 on a pair of free throws with 4:08 to go.</p>
<p>Banks pushed Tech ahead for good, 58-57, on two free throws with 3:04 left as the Hurricanes missed their last seven shots.</p>
<p>“We still got outrebounded by 15 (48-33), but at least in the second half we were trying to rebound the basketball,” said Miami coach Jim Larranaga. “We were able to take the lead, but they executed much better in the last four minutes than we did.”</p>
<p>The Hurricanes scarcely challenged Tech in the first half, when the Yellow Jackets ran off 13 consecutive points late in the period to take a 40-24 lead. Georgia Tech had a huge 25-13 rebounding advantage, and 14 of the Jackets’ 16 made field goals in the half came in the paint.</p>
<p>Lykes, Miami’s leading scorer, went scoreless until the final minute before intermission, and took just three shots in the half as Tech had a pair of defenders, the 6-foot Alvarado and 5-10 reserve guard Bubba Parham, who were quick enough to stay in front of the Hurricanes’ 5-7 point guard.</p>
<p>It didn’t help that Miami turned the ball over 11 times before halftime, as Alvarado picked up four of his seven steals for Georgia Tech.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes had to work so hard to overcome that 20-point deficit that they looked gassed over the game&#8217;s final four-plus minutes. Miami was often short on shots, and made just 2 of 17 3-pointers while shooting 36.7 percent overall.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech: The Yellow Jackets are in a five-way tie — locked with Notre Dame, North Carolina State, Clemson and Syracuse — for fifth place in the ACC. The top nine teams in the 15-team conference will have first-round byes in the conference tournament, and Tech has clinched a top nine spot at worst.</p>
<p>BIG IN THE MIDDLE</p>
<p>Banks was a force while playing his best game in several weeks. Not only were his 14 rebounds one short of his season and career highs, but his 13 points were his most in seven games. He hit double digits just once in that span, averaging seven points in the previous six. He also fouled out of four of those games. Saturday, he added two blocks and two steals.</p>
<p>“I thought James Banks was really big,” said Tech coach Josh Pastner. “But what turned it around was that we got extra possessions late based on offensive rebounds (Banks had seven of Tech&#8217;s 18).”</p>
<p>In addition to five free throws made, Banks had four dunks/layups and Tech made 16 of 21 shots (76%) at the rim to Miami&#8217;s 7 of 16 (44%).</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes will play host to Virginia on Wednesday night.</p>
<p>Georgia Tech: The Jackets will play their final home game Wednesday against Pittsburgh.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">598142</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former UM, Dolphins player Mark Walton arrested</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/former-um-dolphins-player-mark-walton-arrested/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cristina Alexander]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Dolphins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=596871</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Former University of Miami and Dolphins running back Mark Walton has been arrested. Opa-Locka Police responded to a domestic dispute call at 3261 NW 132nd...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former University of Miami and Dolphins running back Mark Walton has been arrested.</p>
<p>Opa-Locka Police responded to a domestic dispute call at 3261 NW 132nd Terrace, at around 3:30 a.m., Thurday.</p>
<p>According to police, Walton got into a verbal dispute with the mother of his child.</p>
<p>There was no physical contact between Walton and the woman, according to police, but he violated a restraining order she filed against him in Broward County.</p>
<p>Police arrested Walton and transported him to TGK.</p>
<p>In November, Walton was released from the Dolphins after he <a href="https://wsvn.com/sports/former-dolphins-rb-walton-posts-bond-after-making-court-appearance/">was arrested for allegedly striking his then pregnant girlfriend</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">596871</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/191120-mark-walton.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/191120-mark-walton.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2019/11/191120-mark-walton.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">191120 mark walton</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mooney, Gibbs lead Notre Dame to 87-71 win over Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/mooney-gibbs-lead-notre-dame-to-87-71-win-over-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=594495</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) &#8212; Prentiss Hubb reminded Notre Dame fans that John Mooney&#8217;s not the only Fighting Irish player who can uncork a double-double....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) &#8212; Prentiss Hubb reminded Notre Dame fans that John Mooney&#8217;s not the only Fighting Irish player who can uncork a double-double.</p>
<p>The sophomore point guard had 15 points 10 assists for his second career double-double as the hot-shooting Irish rolled to an 87-71 victory Sunday over Miami.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s all thanks to my teammates,&#8221; Hubb said. &#8220;They handled the shots, especially when Mooney and the other guys are running in transition. They just make it easier to get a double-double.&#8221;</p>
<p>Mooney got his, too &#8212; his nation-leading 22nd &#8212; with 19 points and 12 rebounds.</p>
<p>T.J. Gibbs scored 19 points as well and made 5-of-6 3-pointers as Notre Dame (17-10, 8-8 Atlantic Coast Conference) won for the sixth time in eight games.</p>
<p>Dane Goodwin chipped in 14 points off the bench.</p>
<p>DJ Vasiljevic, Isaiah Wong and Harlond Beverly each scored 12 points for the Hurricanes (14-13, 6-11), who saw their three-game win streak snapped.</p>
<p>The Irish converted 14 of 31 from 3-point range and finished with 21 assists on 32 field goals and committed just seven turnovers.</p>
<p>Those numbers were even gaudier during the first half as Notre Dame built a 48-29 lead by the break on 10-of-18 shooting outside the arc and 13 assists against no turnovers.</p>
<p>&#8220;Nobody plays like us,&#8221; Irish coach Mike Brey said, referring to his team&#8217;s nation-leading assist-to-turnover ratio of 1.72 entering the night. &#8220;Our assist-to-turnover has always been very good, (but) these numbers are off-the-chart kind of stuff. When you have 13 assists, no turnovers . and everybody can pass it. Our big guys are good with the ball.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Hurricanes&#8217; switching defense was somewhat effective early, but was no answer in the long haul.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s why they get so many assists,&#8221; Miami coach Jim Larranaga said of Notre Dame not settling for shots off the bounce.</p>
<p>&#8220;They&#8217;re a catch-and-shoot team,&#8221; Larranaga said. &#8220;Guys like Prentiss Hubb and T.J. Gibbs in particular not only make those 3s, but they make them from like NBA range, which stretches your defense out, which provides them the opportunity to post a Mooney or Juwan Durham inside. They&#8217;re completely isolated one-on-one, and those guys are good offensive players, too, so they score around the basket at a very high level.&#8221;</p>
<p>The Canes never got closer than 14 points in the second half, that being at 58-44 with 13:39 to go, before the Irish surged to a commanding 80-54 advantage at 6:24 left.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Miami: Barring an automatic NCAA Tournament berth by winning the ACC Tourney, the Hurricanes are scrambling for even an NIT bid. They don&#8217;t have to finish over .500 by rule, but achieving that optic would help as they head into their final three regular-season games &#8212; all against teams above them in the standings.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish continued to make a late push toward NCAA Tournament at-large consideration. If they can win their four remaining regular-season games, including No. 8 Florida State at home, they&#8217;ll head into the ACC Tourney with 21 victories. Working against them is an 0-5 mark so far against ranked teams and no wins against currently over-.500 ACC clubs.</p>
<p>BURNING AN EX-MATE</p>
<p>Hubb sent his former Gonzaga (District of Columbia) High School teammate, Chris Lykes, sprawling backwards to the ground with a vicious crossover move and step-back 3-pointer at just over three minutes left in the game.</p>
<p>Lykes stayed down for several minutes, with Larranaga saying after the game that his junior point guard suffered a turf toe injury to both feet and adding that &#8220;he&#8217;s going to be day-to-day.&#8221;</p>
<p>After the game, Hubb stayed humble over a play that had Irish fans oohing and aahing.</p>
<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t think it&#8217;s bragging rights,&#8221; Hubb said, &#8220;because he probably did it to me more times than I did it to him in high school. I really do hope he&#8217;s OK.&#8221;<br />
Lykes, Miami&#8217;s top scorer on the season at 15.5 points going in, was limited to eight on 4-of-11 shooting.</p>
<p>A year ago, Hubb had just two points on 1-of-6 shooting and two assists with six turnovers in his first collegiate matchup with his ex-teammate, while Lykes had 11 points in a 62-47 win.</p>
<p>&#8220;I know he wanted to play well,&#8221; Brey said of Hubb, &#8220;because Chris beat him up, treated him like a young guy last year, but he&#8217;s such a winner, and his decisions with the ball today, he was (like 2018 NFL MVP Pat) Mahomes.&#8221;</p>
<p>RAPID TURNABOUT</p>
<p>At just over 10 minutes to go, Beverly made a nifty strip-steal and took off for an uncontested dunk, but left it embarrassingly short.</p>
<p>Notre Dame snatached the rebound and snapped off a couple crisp passes in transition for a Mooney dunk in the face of a Hurricane defender.</p>
<p>It was the runaway play of the night, until Hubb&#8217;s killer crossover.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes are off until heading to Georgia Tech on Saturday.</p>
<p>Notre Dame: The Irish visit Boston College on Wednesday, looking to avenge a 73-72 home loss to the Eagles in December.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">594495</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Retired Hurricanes coach Morris teaches sports management to UM students</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/retired-hurricanes-coach-morris-teaches-sports-management-to-um-students/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=594491</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Longtime Miami Hurricanes baseball coach Jim Morris may have retired from the playing field, but he&#8217;s still imparting decades&#8217; worth of sports wisdom in the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longtime Miami Hurricanes baseball coach Jim Morris may have retired from the playing field, but he&#8217;s still imparting decades&#8217; worth of sports wisdom in the classroom.</p>
<p>7Sports caught up last week with Morris away from his familiar surroundings at the University of Miami in Coral Gables. These days he&#8217;s carrying backpack on his shoulder, but he still wears one of his championship rings.</p>
<p>&#8220;I promise you that your son will get a degree from the University of Miami if he does what we tell him to do,&#8221; he told students during a class.</p>
<p>Morris said he uses the same approach in the classroom that he once used on the diamond. As UM&#8217;s head baseball coach from 1994 to 2018, he won two College World Series titles. Both times, he was named the National Coach of the Year.</p>
<p>&#8220;I feel like I am giving back to the university. I tell the students from my class that I&#8217;m doing this for them,&#8221; he said. &#8220;I&#8217;m doing it to try to help them in their lives, deciding what to do, so my class is a little bit different. It exposes a lot of things to them.&#8221;</p>
<p>In the classroom, his students call him Professor Morris. The class he teaches is sports management.</p>
<p>&#8220;He teaches us how to conduct ourselves in a professional manner,&#8221; said student Hayley Tesser. &#8220;He&#8217;ll tell us to have a Plan B. He gives us really good life advice in general outside of the sports industry, but that can be applied to sports.&#8221;</p>
<p>All of these students, including athletes, said they want to be involved in some aspect of sports after college.</p>
<p>&#8220;He expects us to be professional. He expects us to be on time, and it&#8217;s really no different than in the real world,&#8221; said student Austin Pert, &#8220;because if you&#8217;re late to practice, if you&#8217;re late to anything, things aren&#8217;t going to go your way, so you learn that first hand.&#8221;</p>
<p>Morris, 70, admitted that, after racking up nearly 1,100 wins on the field for Miami, this environment poses a different challenge.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m a rookie again, so it&#8217;s something that is a learning process for me,&#8221; he said. &#8220;This first semester, and then the second semester is different. I learned a lot from one to two.&#8221;</p>
<p>Until his retirement two years ago, Morris had been involved in baseball as a coach since 1975.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m used to having a game plan in class. I figure a three-hour class that I&#8217;ve prepared, and then I normally talk about for about 10 hours,&#8221; he said. &#8220;If you want to be involved in athletics, my class aims to help them look at all the different areas and be able to expose them and talk to them about the good and the bad.&#8221;</p>
<p>When Morris is on campus and he&#8217;s not in the classroom, he can be found at Mark Light Field sitting right behind home plate to watch some of the players he once coached.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">594491</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/02/200223_jim_morris_sports_management.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />
<media:content medium='video' url='https://bcbolt446c5271-a.akamaihd.net/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/59f2b9b4-0762-4eaf-8d40-dba243d7939a/1539bcc9-5792-4071-afb8-44d3758faf70/main.mp4?akamai_token=exp=1615220065~acl=/media/v1/pmp4/static/clear/4368278029001/59f2b9b4-0762-4eaf-8d40-dba243d7939a/1539bcc9-5792-4071-afb8-44d3758faf70/main.mp4*~hmac=e5f147775b54533c9d38a4b1e0a9956ca9e2bc9cdef76e442dd9ae29e00e4688' type='video/mp4' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/02/200223_jim_morris_sports_management.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/02/200223_jim_morris_sports_management.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">200223_Jim_Morris_sports_management</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lykes, Wong lead Hurricanes to 71-54 win over Wake Forest</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/lykes-wong-lead-hurricanes-to-71-54-win-over-wake-forest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 01:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=590306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — It took 15 games but Miami finally has strung victories in its Atlantic Coast Conference schedule. Chris Lykes and Isaiah...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — It took 15 games but Miami finally has strung victories in its Atlantic Coast Conference schedule.</p>
<p>Chris Lykes and Isaiah Wong scored 13 points each to lead the Hurricanes to a 71-54 victory over Wake Forest Saturday afternoon.</p>
<p>Kameron McGusty and Dejan Vasiljevic finished with 11 points each and Rodney Miller grabbed 10 rebounds and had eight points for the Hurricanes, who last enjoyed a winning streak from Dec. 2 to Dec. 31, a stretch that featured four non-conference contests and an ACC game at Clemson.</p>
<p>McGusty and Lykes hit 3-pointers that keyed a 14-2 Miami run in the first half. Wong’s 3-point play with 4:45 remaining capped the surge and gave the Hurricanes (13-12, 5-10 Atlantic Coast Conference) a 28-16 lead.</p>
<p>Both teams struggled offensively; Miami at 40.3% and Wake Forest 38.9%. Miami also made just 13 of 21 free throws but out-rebounded Wake Forest 42-37 and committed only one turnover in the first half when it built the double-digit advantage.</p>
<p>“We’ve been able to score the ball pretty well most nights,” Miami coach Jim Larranaga said. “But tonight it was a very good defensive effort.”</p>
<p>Forward Sam Waardenburg’s return from a neck injury that forced him to miss the Hurricanes’ win over Boston College Wednesday night allowed Larranaga to use a nine-player rotation in the first half since Jan. 4. None of Miami’s players reached 30 minutes Saturday.</p>
<p>“That allows the player to play really hard and play really well,” Larranaga said of the expanded rotation. “When everybody is sharing that responsibility, it makes a huge difference. But it’s all about the preparation.”</p>
<p>The Demon Deacons (11-14, 4-11) rallied from a 17-point deficit in the second half and got to within 47-39 on Torry Johnson’s fast-break dunk with 9:11 remaining that ended a string of nine unanswered. Miami regained its double-digit advantage on McGusty’s 3-pointer.</p>
<p>Waardenburg’s layup with 1:20 remaining gave the Hurricanes their largest lead at 64-44.</p>
<p>“Miami came out and defensively took us out of what we wanted to do,” Wake Forest coach Danny Manning said. “We had some shots that we normally make that we missed and we didn’t do a good job of rebounding the baskeball.”</p>
<p>Brandon Childress scored 15 points for Wake Forest.</p>
<p>EAGER TO RETURN:</p>
<p>Waardenburg felt he had recovered sufficiently from the whip-lash type injury he sustained in practice Tuesday to play against Boston College. But Larranaga opted to sit his junior forward, allowing him additional time to heal and return for Wake Forest.</p>
<p>“We had Chris (Lykes), who had a groin injury and he played at Duke and kind of aggravated a bit, so I think coach was concerned about that,” said, Waardenburg, who scored nine points and had seven rebounds in 25 minutes Saturday. “Now, sitting out and getting treatment it’s much better.”</p>
<p>FEW VISITORS TO THE FREE THROW LINE:</p>
<p>The Demon Deacons lead the ACC in attempted and made free throws. But Childress, Johnson and Olivier Sarr were the only Wake Forest players who shot free throws against Miami.</p>
<p>“We need to do a better job of getting the ball below the free throw line, get more paint touches and have more guys get to the free throw line because that’s a source of where we need to get our points from,” Manning said.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE:</p>
<p>Wake Forest: the Demon Deacons won’t need to book flights for the remainder of the regular season. Their next three ACC games are at home before the Deacons finish the regular season at neighboring North Carolina and North Carolina State.</p>
<p>Miami: coach Jim Larranaga won his 658th career game, surpassing Ralph Miller for 37th on the all-time list. Larranaga is 188-109 in his nine seasons at Miami.</p>
<p>UP NEXT:</p>
<p>Wake Forest: the Deacons return home and face Georgia Tech Wednesday.</p>
<p>Miami: the Hurricanes begin a three-game road set at Virginia Tech Wednesday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">590306</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wong scores 21 as Miami rolls past Boston College 85-58</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/wong-scores-21-as-miami-rolls-past-boston-college-85-58/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=589051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Isaiah Wong is quickly shedding the inexperienced label. Miami’s freshman guard scored 21 points as the Hurricanes snapped a three-game...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Isaiah Wong is quickly shedding the inexperienced label.</p>
<p>Miami’s freshman guard scored 21 points as the Hurricanes snapped a three-game losing streak, defeating Boston College 85-58 on Wednesday. Following his career-high 23 point outing at Florida State Saturday, Wong became the first Hurricanes freshman to score 20 points or more in consecutive games since Marcus Barnes in 2001.</p>
<p>“My mentality is just play efficient and try to make the best plays possible for the team and try to get a win every possession,” Wong said.</p>
<p>The Hurricanes (12-12, 4-10 Atlantic Coast Conference) broke it open with a 24-2 run that began midway through the first half. Harlond Beverly scored seven points during the surge and Anthony Walker’s dunk with 3:55 remaining capped the spurt and gave Miami a 38-17 lead.</p>
<p>Chris Lykes finished with 16 points and Kameron McGusty scored 12 points for the Hurricanes, who had lost seven of their last eight. Rodney Miller was Miami’s fourth scorer in double figures with 11 points.</p>
<p>“The message after our last game was we have to rebound better, share the ball better, find the open man better,” Miami coach Jim Larranaga said. “It’s as good as 40 minutes that we’ve played all season long.”</p>
<p>Early in the season, Wong saw limited action. But injuries to guards Lykes and McGustry resulted in a substantial increase in minutes, such as his 30-minute outing against Boston College.</p>
<p>“This atmosphere in the ACC is crazy,” Wong said. “Getting used to it was hard to come into. In the games I kept getting (charging fouls) and it stressed me out sometimes. Luckily (my teammates) helped me through it and now on and through the season I am getting a lot better at making good decisions.”</p>
<p>Miami maintained a double-digit advantage following its first-half run as Boston College (12-13, 6-8) got no closer than 55-42 on Derryck Thornton’s 3-point play with 10:06 remaining in the second half.</p>
<p>Kamari Williams scored 14 points for Boston College.</p>
<p>“We just stopped competing for about four or five minutes against a team with that type of firepower,” Boston College coach Jim Christian said. “I’m very disappointed in our team but I want to give them credit. Sometimes we get too wrapped up in ourselves.”</p>
<p>The Eagles shot 1-of-11 from the field as Miami built its 21-point lead but closed the first half with unanswered points on Williams’ dunk and Nic Popovic’s two jumpers.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Boston College: A stretch of four of the next five games at Conte Forum will provide the Eagles an opportunity to improve on their home fortunes. Boston College is 7-7 at home, including 3-3 in the ACC.</p>
<p>Miami: Forward Sam Waardenburg’s undisclosed injury sustained in practice Tuesday sidelined him against Boston College and extended the Hurricanes’ string of games without their nine-player rotation. Miami last used its full complement of scholarship players in a 95-62 home loss to Duke on Jan. 4.</p>
<p>GOING SMALL</p>
<p>An injury to forward Sam Waardenburg in practice prompted Larranaga to start guards Wong, Lykes, McGusty and Dejan Vasiljevic against Boston College. Forward Keith Stone was the only interior player in the starting lineup. Despite a lack of post presence, the Hurricanes out-rebounded the Eagles 35-30 and matched them in points in the paint with 38.</p>
<p>“That group that started had never played a moment, a possession of basketball this year,” Larranaga said. “They normally go against each other in practice.”</p>
<p>OVERCOMING RUST</p>
<p>Lykes, who missed four consecutive games because of a groin injury before returning with a 21-minute outing at Florida State Saturday, played 29 minutes against Boston College.</p>
<p>“I feel pretty good, glad to be out there playing with my teammates,” Lykes said. “It was rough watching from the bench.”</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Boston College: The Eagles return home to face North Carolina State on Sunday.</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes conclude their two-game homestand against Wake Forest on Saturday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">589051</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2016/05/miami-hurricanes-logo.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">miami hurricanes logo</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walker, Williams lead Florida State&#8217;s 99-81 rout of Miami</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/walker-williams-lead-florida-states-99-81-rout-of-miami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rubén Rosario]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 01:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[College]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Florida State Seminoles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=586924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Florida State picked up win No. 20 on Sunday, finishing a season sweep of Miami. But the Seminoles also picked up...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) &#8212; Florida State picked up win No. 20 on Sunday, finishing a season sweep of Miami. But the Seminoles also picked up some needed rest for a short turnaround against No. 7 Duke.</p>
<p>M.J. Walker and Patrick Williams scored 14 points apiece as No. 8 Florida State beat Miami 99-81 to win its fifth straight against the rivals.<br />
Devin Vassell had 13 points and Wyatt Wilkes scored 11, knocking down three 3-pointers, for the Seminoles (20-3, 10-2 ACC). Florida State connected on 13 of 26 3-point attempts.</p>
<p>Florida State coach Leonard Hamilton made an effort to rest two starting guards, Trent Forrest and Vassell, with the top-10 showdown at Duke coming up Monday. Still, both were effective: Forrest had 10 points, six rebounds and six assists in just under 24 minutes, while Vassell shot 5 of 9 from the floor and had five rebounds on 24 minutes.</p>
<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s one of the things that if I could change anything in college basketball, I wouldn&#8217;t want to play three games a week and I would not ever want to play a game with a one-day turnaround,&#8221; Hamilton said. &#8220;I think that&#8217;s tremendously taxing on these young men, and we have three of them (Saturday-Monday games). One was North Carolina, Duke and the other was Louisville. By coincidence. Sometimes that&#8217;s part of the luck of the draw. &#8230; I do think it&#8217;s extremely tough on our guys.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coming off a Saturday-Monday turnaround in which the Seminoles won at Virginia Tech and then knocked off North Carolina at home, Hamilton opted to rest two of his stars against Miami. Forrest had played 30 or more minutes in each ACC game while Vassell had played 31 or more minutes in his last nine ACC games.</p>
<p>Florida State&#8217;s reserves more than picked up the slack. Williams, Wilkes, Dominik Olejniczak (eight points) and RayQuan Evans (eight points, four rebounds) led a Seminoles&#8217; bench that outscored Miami&#8217;s reserves 54-11.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s big,&#8221; Vassell said. &#8220;Our bodies are going through it when you have a few back-to-backs. People are hurting. It&#8217;s huge for people to come in and step up.&#8221;</p>
<p>Isaiah Wong had a career-high 23 points on 8 of 12 shooting for Miami (11-12, 3-10). Sam Waardenburg added 15 points, Harlond Beverly had 14 and Dejan Vasiljevic scored 12 on 5-of-13 shooting.</p>
<p>Wong became a starter in January and is averaging 13.3 points, but on Saturday he was a consistent scorer by driving the lane. The freshman also made both of his 3-point attempts.</p>
<p>&#8220;I thought Isaiah had a great first half,&#8221; Miami coach Jim Larranaga said. &#8220;He was really on the attack. He made some tough layups. He was able to get to the rim. He was able to get to the foul line as well.&#8221;</p>
<p>But Miami couldn&#8217;t keep the Seminoles from winning the lopsided rebounding battle. Anthony Polite had eight rebounds for Florida State, which outrebounded Miami 46-24.</p>
<p>Florida State won 83-79 in overtime at Miami on Jan. 18.</p>
<p>BIG PICTURE</p>
<p>Miami: The Hurricanes got a career day from Wong, and Chris Lykes returned after missing four games due to injury to score eight points. But the &#8216;Canes used just eight players and ran out of gas in the second half as they shot 10 of 33 (30.3%).</p>
<p>Florida State: Five players scored in double figures and 13 players scored, including walk-ons Travis Light and Harrison Prieto. The Seminoles also had a 22-rebound edge over an ACC opponent, by far the largest margin for Florida State this season.</p>
<p>STRING OF 20-WIN SEASONS</p>
<p>Florida State has won 20 games for a fifth straight season, which is a school record. The Seminoles have won 118 games since the 2015-16 season.</p>
<p>POLL IMPLICATIONS</p>
<p>Florida State has made an argument to move up in the polls on the strength of three straight wins: at Virginia Tech, vs. North Carolina and vs. Miami.</p>
<p>UP NEXT</p>
<p>Miami plays host to Boston College on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Florida State is at No. 7 Duke on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">586924</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2017/09/170918_fsu_generic.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">170918_fsu_generic</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ed Reed returns to the Miami Hurricanes as chief of staff</title>
		<link>https://wsvn.com/sports/ed-reed-returns-to-the-miami-hurricanes-as-chief-of-staff/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Franco]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 15:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Miami Hurricanes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wsvn.com/?p=583441</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Ed Reed is going back to his roots and rejoining the Miami Hurricanes. The Pro Football Hall of Famer has...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CORAL GABLES, Fla. (AP) — Ed Reed is going back to his roots and rejoining the Miami Hurricanes.</p>
<p>The Pro Football Hall of Famer has been hired as the new chief of staff for the Hurricanes’ football program, a deal that was announced Thursday and will be finalized when the school completes a standard background check.</p>
<p>Reed will be tasked with helping Miami coach Manny Diaz “in all aspects of the football program, including strategic planning, quality control, operations, player evaluation and player development,” the university said in a statement.</p>
<p>Reed’s duties will also include team building, student-athlete mentorship and as much recruiting as is allowed under NCAA rules.</p>
<p>“We are thrilled to welcome Ed back to Coral Gables,” Diaz said. “He is not only one of the most decorated players in Miami football history but also a devoted Cane who cares deeply about this program. All of our players, coaches and staff will be fortunate to tap into his experience, knowledge and passion on a regular basis.”</p>
<p>Reed was a five-time All-Pro safety, a member of the NFL 2000s All-Decade Team, the 2004 Defensive Player of the Year and made nine Pro Bowls. He had 64 career interceptions, led the league in that stat three times and scored 13 non-offense touchdowns in his career with the Baltimore Ravens.</p>
<p>&#8220;It would be hard to argue that he&#8217;s not the greatest safety in the history of football, right?&#8221; Ravens coach John Harbaugh said last year. &#8220;He&#8217;s one of the top 10 players maybe in the history of the game.&#8221;</p>
<p>At Miami, Reed was part of the Hurricanes’ most recent national title team in 2001. He set school records for career interceptions (21) and interception return yards (369), won a Big East championship in javelin in 1999 and graduated with a degree in liberal arts.</p>
<p>Reed is also a member of the College Football Hall of Fame and the University of Miami Hall of Fame.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">583441</post-id><media:content url='https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color' medium='image' />

		<media:thumbnail url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" />
		<media:content url="https://wsvn.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2020/01/miami-hurricanes-football-senior-day-11-9-19_1_moment.jpg?quality=60&#038;strip=color" medium="image">
			<media:title type="html">MIAMI HURRICANES FOOTBALL SENIOR DAY 11-9-19_1_Moment</media:title>
		</media:content>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
